“@JobHits: Business Development Manager - Banking Services job in London at Sage Personnel http://bit.ly/n2Iiov ”    
    
    
    #Desigual is conducting a presentation at #IE they need international #talent for their expansion plan #careers #empleo #job    
    
    
    #Desigual is conducting a presentation at #IE they need international #talent #careers #empleo #job http://yfrog.com/nvpixhj     
    
    
    Organising the session "#Networking with #head hunters" we have the #talent just vacancies needed!!#rrhh#IE#formacion    
    
    
    #IEfashion I Virtual #Career #Fair with #L'Orèal #Inditex #Mango #Desigual #Richemont #LVMH ,...for #IE alumni and students 23rd November    
    
    
    Job opportunity: RESPONSABLE MARKETING ON LINE at DIGITAL SUGGAR - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/4QSD9U     
    
    
    What's happening when today "NO" is the new "YES"?Let's balanced our personal & professional life!    
    
    
    @IEbusiness #Chinese dragon year at IE career oportunies at job bank http://yfrog.com/nw77emzj     
    
    
    I'm searching  job opportunitites for IE students in China. Please upload your cv on the careers website, vacancy...: http://lnkd.in/TMAZsP     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/fwvCKZ  Thank you Xinrong. You can send it to me gabriela.planas@ie.edu in English and Chinese but I recomendo you to...    
    
    
    President of Asia-Pacific #Diageo at #IE http://yfrog.com/nvhxseoj     
    
    
    #Kellogg's presentation at #IE Business School  http://yfrog.com/es69702321j     
    
    
    #Richemont at #IE Business School really smarth presentation http://yfrog.com/nvavfcoj     
    
    
    SC #Johnson's at #IE Representatives from finance,marketing and sales and the #HR Manager on campus    
    
    
    SC Johnson team http://yfrog.com/h0rqcoxj     
    
    
    #IECarrefour Todd Hooper conducting a presentation at #IE #retail is "hands on" http://yfrog.com/ob884buj     
    
    
    #BAT on #IE Campus Top emloyers since 2009 by CFR Institute http://yfrog.com/oek09bfdj     
    
    
    @diegovilarino thank you for your wonderful presentation and all the knowledge that you shared with us http://yfrog.com/odr4nwej     
    
    
    @juantinocofeber conducting a presentation at #IE Business School @redbullesp #RRHH #IEredbull http://yfrog.com/od1w4ixj     
    
    
    @ieWilliamDavila I'm following you.FYI: Burger King will lunch their management t. programme with #IE as the only European Business School    
    
    
    @WebBlancaSuarez @holacom @BlancaSuarezWeb @clubMariaLeon #SpiritAwards en Miami increibles #joyas de @Piaget me encantan! #moda    
    
    
    #masquecoches #telecinco #divinity http://yfrog.com/ob4n4wgj     
    
    
    @ExecEducationIE Gran Programa en Marzo Mobile Business http://execed.ie.edu/openprograms/ProgramasAbiertosDetalle.aspx?id=1593 … Manuel Alonso Coto #IE #mobile #marketing    
    
    
    Job opportunity: INTERNATIONAL SENIOR AUDITOR at Toys R Us - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/Av6Y-i     
    
    
    #Amazon Europe at #IE Business School.Really interesting #job opportunities at this fast growing enviroment! http://yfrog.com/oewmsouj     
    
    
    @FashionJobsUK #HR Manager Responsible for the people agenda within the Distribution Centre an... http://bit.ly/z9JKMN  #Jobs    
    
    
    Searching for vacancies in Miami for #IE Business School alumni #employ #empleo #jobs #retail #fmcg    
    
    
    My session today:#Careers in Retail: #cosmetics #fashion. New markets,new players.Cv Tips for #bba students at @IEuniversity,Segovia #jobs    
    
    
    #Google EMEA conducting a Company presentation at #IE Business School.A really challenge company #jobs http://yfrog.com/kg1mocnj     
    
    
    Ready to bring job opportunities from #China to #IE Students #Retail #jobs #empleo    
    
    
    Searching for interesting retail positions in China (Beijing)    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Buyer's Assistant at WHSmith - London, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/DzDhWb     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Store Manager, Barcelona  at Burberry - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/eNrXpP     
    
    
    Job opportunity: DIRECTOR DE MARKETING at Michael Page - Spain - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/2_Ctgs     
    
    
    Menudo Marathon. Enhorabuena @RunRocknRoll estuvo fenomenal . Congrats for the Madrid one!!!!    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Associate Creative Director at Open D Group - Singapore #jobs http://lnkd.in/TzX2UN     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Sales Manager - Madrid at BookGenie - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/W8we8H     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Sales Account Manager at TOSHIBA TEC EUROPE - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/vAVVCn     
    
    
    With Daniel Porot (http://www.porot.com ) a guru in "piloting your #career to land the right #job http://yfrog.com/nu7cfpj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director, Integrated Marketing, Consumer at Johnson & Johnson - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/ztdeA7     
    
    
    With the #HR manager of L'Oréal conducting a presentation about careers in #FMCG sector #jobs #empleo #IE http://yfrog.com/nxrbkswj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Purchasing Manager at zooplus AG - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/KpFp8J     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Group Financial Controller at International Luxury Retail Group - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/UMiYSE     
    
    
    Job opportunity: International HR Manager  at Carlton Senior Appointments Ltd - Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/hcWyzj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Retail Channel Account Manager Northern  at Ergotron - Munich Area, Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/NUxqsc     
    
    
    Shoe street art in Madrid (Serrano St) http://yfrog.com/es9qqrnj     
    
    
    ·jobs Assistant at Marketing (Chester, England): Online & Digital Marketing... http://bit.ly/KFjaWN  #looktohire    
    
    
    Job opportunity: DIRECTOR DE MARKETING CORPORATIVO at NEXUS EXECUTIVE SEARCH - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/Ezfw3Z     
    
    
    Job opportunity: CONTROLLER PRODUCTO ZARA at Zara - A Coruña Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/yW2XQq     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Manager HR Business Partner, New  at Amadeus - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/G3fhYq     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Brand Manager at Paramount Pictures - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/vgcK3K     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Strategy Manager at VF Corporation - Ticino, Switzerland #jobs http://lnkd.in/TNnREP     
    
    
    Vogue who's on next winner http://yfrog.com/kk8r3lxaj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Regional General Manager / Head of Retai at Quantica Retail - Leeds, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/C2hg_M     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Manager - External Reporting at Tiffany & Co. - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/dkNstM     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Retail Business Analyst at Tommy Hilfiger - Amsterdam Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/5usQtk     
    
    
    #mbfwm #EvaSotoConde #Cibeles http://yfrog.com/obbcffjuj     
    
    
    1.000 executives from more than 50 countries at #iealumniforum http://yfrog.com/g0wjkraj  @IEAlumni    
    
    
    #Makro @metrogroup conducting interviews on campus to our MBA and MIM #IE students http://yfrog.com/nufhmmxj     
    
    
    Mercedes Benz Fashion Week Madrid. Pasarela Cibeles 2012 http://pasarelacibeles.hola.com/madrid/primavera-verano-2013m/ …    
    
    
    #LOreal recruiting at #IE Business School  http://yfrog.com/mgkpjqtj     
    
    
    @nestlé leader in nutrition and health at #IE Business School opp available at http://www.nestle.es  Nesfit Programme   http://yfrog.com/h2xsovtj     
    
    
    “@GJobsmarketing: Brand Manager - Penguin Classics - London - PENGUIN http://mjobx.com/KFLgAQ ”    
    
    
    In NY...seaching for some innovation    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director of Marketing and Business Devel at Comunycarse - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/nu2cwH     
    
    
    @IEbusiness ranking BusinessWeek, 3º puesto, well done! http://numrl.com/98686  #IE    
    
    
    Job opportunity: International Financial Controller at Grupor Gransolar, S.L. - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/wD4XEK     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Marketing Manager - Ecommerce, Sp at Visa Europe - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/_6TaG6     
    
    
    Job opportunity: DISEÑADOR/A DE MODA MUJER at ADOLFO DOMINGUEZ,S.A. - Ourense Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/PN5E8K     
    
    
    Job opportunity: DISEÑADOR/A DE MODA MUJER at ADOLFO DOMINGUEZ,S.A. - Ourense Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/PN5E8K     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Brand Manager at Sophie Paris - Greater Jakarta Area, Indonesia #jobs http://lnkd.in/uky6fn     
    
    
    Job opportunity: CONSULTOR DE PROCESOS ESPECIALISTA EN RE at SteelMood - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/ZAZmHy     
    
    
    Job opportunity: NikeiD Online Merchandiser at Nike EMEA - Amsterdam Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/n9veVy     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Responsable de Marketing y RRPP at Disparala  - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/xjQdjZ     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Gestor de Grandes Cuentas (sector retail at Unibail Rodamco - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/jxftDJ     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Sales Manager-Social Media at ADESIS Netlife - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/nq5yaF     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director de Ventas Adjunto at U-tad - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/_Ugbnr     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Buying Manager at The Retail Talent Network - London, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/cAfmWA     
    
    
    Job opportunity: CORPORATE COMMUNICATIONS  MANAGER at Toys R Us - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/XHMWxd     
    
    
    Job opportunity: COMERCIAL DE PACKAGING PARA EL SECTOR LÁ at GRUPO ENTECO - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/8BJEYm     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Brand Manager Cardiovascular at Takeda Farmacéutica España - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/GmR6ib     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Junior Financial Controller at ITC Accessories - Almere Stad Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/gJ62yX     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Trading Manager - France at http://ASOS.com  - London, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/xiWmJS     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director Comercial y de Marketing (Gran  at Adecco Professional - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/yak6Hq     
    
    
    Job opportunity: LOGISTICS & SUPPLY CHAIN MANAGER at OPTAR. Consultoria de Búsqueda,  - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/wRvbWj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Area Manager at Primadonna Spagna,sl - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/wE2Dic     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Account Manager at COSENTINO, S.A. - Cologne Area, Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/WeiRmK     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Gestor de Grandes Cuentas (sector retail at Unibail Rodamco - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/-HAYEK     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Junior Fashion Buyer OYSHO at Inditex - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/EqQDbv     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Manager, Merchant Services, Spain at Amazon - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/-T8yU6     
    
    
    Job opportunity: STORE MANAGER / BRANCH MANAGER at 360 Executive Search - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/D4CgwG     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager Mens Originals_Blue (m/f) at adidas - Nürnberg Area, Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/Tjg43V     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Merchandise Planner - Victoria's Secret  at Victoria's Secret - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/EfyN_p     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager marketing online con Fra at ElTenedor.es - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/bpNEBV     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Loss Prevention Manager - Retail at Dollar Financial Group - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/8_55q3     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager marketing online con Fra at ElTenedor.es - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/bpNEBV     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Supply Chain Project Manager - Fashion at http://Amazon.co.uk  - Slough, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/wEuyQy     
    
    
    Job opportunity: PRODUCT & CATEGORY DEVELOPMENT DIRECTOR  at The Martin Veasey Partne - Kingston upon Thames, United Kingdom #jobs http://l…    
    
    
    Job opportunity: STRATEGIC INSIGHT MANAGER EMEA – FMCG/Re at The Martin Veasey Partne - Kingston upon Thames, United Kingdom #jobs http://l…    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Retail Manager Moda Mujer  at Randstad España - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/d_-dbS     
    
    
    Job opportunity: RETAIL PROCESS MANAGER at Swarovski - Zürich Area, Switzerland #jobs http://lnkd.in/JiDGQD     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Business Support Coordinator at Dobotex Ltd. - PUMA AG Group - Tilburg Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/xM-9Dn     
    
    
    Job opportunity: COORDINADOR/A DE PLANIFICACIÓN Y DISTRIB at Grupo Cortefiel - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/cTYC-j     
    
    
    Job opportunity: RESPONSABLE DE MARKETING ONLINE (CITY PL at GD Human Capital - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/fwdVGD     
    
    
    Marc Jacobs's bottle designs in celebration of Diet #Coke 30th Europe Anniversary @MarcJacobsIntl AMAZING pic.twitter.com/f23wboTwnH    
    
    
    Road race next Friday at Dublin-St.Patricks´Day http://numrl.com/stpatriks  I will be there    
    
    
    Job opportunity: comprador at Circa - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/B7apqD     
    
    
    Comprador bañadores (Merchant, Swim - Victoria's Secret) New York, NY podeis aplicar via linkedin en este link:... http://fb.me/QrXzGsc0     
    
    
    CIRCA is the leading international buyer of jewelry, #diamonds and watches with private offices throughout North... http://fb.me/1DVYzVJ2m     
    
    
    Head of Retouching to 40K http://www.fashionmonitor.com/Jobs/VL/Head-of-Retouching-to-40K … #jobs #empleo #fashion    
    
    
    ACCOUNT MANAGER- BEAUTY EUROPE #jobs #empleo for @Burberry a global brand with a distinctly British attitude. http://numrl.com/vacanteshr     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager at The Hip Tee - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/e3UuyS     
    
    
    We-want-to-seduce-and-LOrealize-buyers- The Times of India http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/We-want-to-seduce-and-LOrealize-buyers/articleshow/7289240.cms …    
    
    
    Why the Valentino buyout is the future of fashion http://gu.com/p/39292/tw  vía @guardian    
    
    
    Premio Nacional de # Marketing MarketingNews pic.twitter.com/jhH1DubXqr    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director de Fábrica at 360 Executive Search - Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/gYBjsV     
    
    
    I love London and with the 40´s principales more :-) #ALondresConDel40al1 @Tony__Aguilar @del40al1_Spain @FastFurious    
    
    
    Job opportunity: diseñador de moda textil at The Hip Tee - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/h_bdcj     
    
    
    @MarkFritz great conference on managing virtual teams No boundaries,just balance..thank you Mark!    
    
    
    Fashion Creative Director para Portugal). Posted  by SNTalent    
    
    
    Job opportunity: DEPUTY STORE MANAGER at Bulgari - Rome Area, Italy #jobs http://lnkd.in/4hgVBP     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Asia International Area Manager at Pepe Jeans - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/ZtH5wT     
    
    
    Muy bueno!good tips on your job search 2.0!http://khac.es/50701    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Russian Business Development Intern at Grupo LVMH - LOEWE - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/TQRtzC     
    
    
    Job opportunity: International Sales Director at Smartmood - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/XESQzA     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Community Manager at alternatiba - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/VEbSTh     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director/a de Almacén at Bricomart - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/zjeuMw     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LyC22Ze-lJ0 … Orientation Day #rrhh #formacion    
    
    
    @edans Estupendo como siempre con @Oracle @Accenture @everis en @IEbusiness "What happens in an internet minute?" pic.twitter.com/cOVnR36OzJ    
    
    
    @IEbusiness @IEAlumni @el_pais gracias! #IEluxury #IEfashion    
    
    
    @piaget experience Anne #roseday so nice! pic.twitter.com/pWOHWQWwyj    
    
    
    @piaget today with their #roseday event and  @LovelyPepa in the photocall. We love #luxury pic.twitter.com/31EvMpweXM    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Manager Estrategia Consumo y Retail  at Accenture - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/uminxd     
    
    
    Workshop for an international cv http://www.careerboutique.es/espa%C3%B1ol-1/cursos-y-talleres-1/ …    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Responsable de Dpto. de Diseño Camisetas at Inditex - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/VhDT2e     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Store Manager at Nike EMEA - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/4VeXdV     
    
    
    Luxury Store Manager.South Coast Plaza, CA. experience in luxury leather goods and staff development erica@shopthejobs.com    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Manager de Negocio con experienci at Accenture - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/V8TWgt     
    
    
    Job opportunity: BAGS AND SLG MERCHANDISER/BUYER at Grupo LVMH - LOEWE - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/zuFQnt     
    
    
    I was #mentor for 2 years with #EPWnMadrid really good experience! I encouraged all of you!    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager - Retail Merchandise & C at Starbucks - Amsterdam Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/ZzEkia     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Comprador at Amichi - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/WtBeHX     
    
    
    ¿Ready for #IEfashion?    
    
    
    #IEFashion Marc Jacobs...the beginning    
    
    
    #IEfashion internal promotion.Good opportunities entering on a store as a manager    
    
    
    #IEfashion opportunities for Portugal,Marocco,South Europe,Middle East    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Purchaser Marionnaud Spain  at MARIONNAUD - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/8-f_Tb     
    
    
    #IEfashion @louisvuitton evaluates potential of the candidate and possible career plans    
    
    
    #IEfashion Dubay booming    
    
    
    #iefashion very good questions @IEstudents    
    
    
    #iefashion the Cover letter needs to be inspiring    
    
    
    #iefashion Retail implies starting from the point of view of a store manager with the potential of what an MBA gives    
    
    
    @rickypedraza good question!needs to inspire in order to show a commitment with the company to the #HR dep and to the Manager:)    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Responsable Creativo de Imagen- Stradiva at Inditex - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/NkqhUX     
    
    
    Job opportunity: PM W´s Bags at Grupo LVMH - LOEWE - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/kv7hH3     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Parfums Givenchy MARKETING DIRECTOR at LVMH - Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/KqHVcw     
    
    
    Job opportunity: VP, Marketing at Moda Operandi - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/nmpFJE     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Press and Publicity Manager- Male at Diesel - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/j5AW_H     
    
    
    @rickypedraza thanks!!!    
    
    
    Sunday = Runday With my @ASICSeurope @adidasrunning and my @PolarFitness ;-) pic.twitter.com/juIjGl5gev    
    
    
    Store Manager #Madrid #empleo https://m.infojobs.net/offer/detail.xhtml?code=c893dc8e4a481bba5b6766335e77cd&dgv=2421576380571502349 …    
    
    
    #ego nos sorprende #yingyao "Fashion needs to be radical and experimental" #MBFWMadrid @MBFWMadrid @SamsungMobileES pic.twitter.com/WcX7tWAkpJ    
    
    
    Job openings: . Human Resources Officer via @UN_Careers http://fb.me/RpU7wbpR    
    
    
    Que bonito @ewanfood al atardecer #buenasideas @TheIvidBand @CondePrendes pic.twitter.com/LTpqocEQxQ    
    
    
    Negrosoro brillos y ,encajes...bright in the night http://yfrog.com/h279507660j http://yfrog.com/h43wpmpj    
    
    
    Negrosoro brillos y ,encajes...bright in the night #CMFW http://yfrog.com/h279507660j http://yfrog.com/h43wpmpj    
    
    
    #greygoose uhmmm cofee i need it,thanks    
    
    
    @gABiplanas_rrhh:Negros-oro+encaje.Bright in the night #CMFW http://yfrog.com/h279507660j http://yfrog.com/h43wpmpj” #cibeles #kinafernandez    
    
    
    @Marat_Ch #recruiting a Menswear Designer for Massimo Dutti Barcelona.Min 3 years exp in menswear design #jobs #fashion @massimodutti #moda    
    
    
    Proyecto de @AJEASTURIAS @FADE_COMUNICA #goforit #mentoring http://fb.me/1MJ3xiU0r     
    
    
    It's frozen outside but... Who cares?I've my @HaagenDazs_ES ready! @HaagenDazsLoves pic.twitter.com/rJbxULuNtT    
    
    
    Con @VogueSpain en #voguejoyas impresionante @tousjewelry @Piaget @JoyeriaSuarez y @ysacristan pic.twitter.com/zz5H8xr49u    
    
    
    @MartiniSpain Luck is an #attitude !! With my. #litlesister pic.twitter.com/uLUt7pXhMw    
    
    
    Shoes transform body language and attitude.They lift you physically & emotionally @LouboutinWorld @Louboutin_Blog pic.twitter.com/plxMJpKYAH    
    
    
    @MerlinUK interesting #vacancies on their website for UK! #jobs Head of Programme Funding    
    
    
    Interesante @ZipRecruiter: Luxottica #Retail is hiring Retail Sales Manager http://ziprecruiter.com/tj/0af81d95  #jobs    
    
    
    Que buena iniciativa @Humannova:"Pásate esta tarde a tomar algo y hacer #networking con Profesionales #RRHH.19:30h http://ht.ly/4eKti ”    
    
    
    #British #American #Tobacco presenting on #IE campus their trainee programme on Tuesday!#jobs    
    
    
    Take risks when looking for a #job danger is always more attractive    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director, Human Resources at VWR International - Rochester, New York Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/KB9DxN    
    
    
    Burberry London is looking for an HR Manager for Italy (London based)!    
    
    
    Preparando un speed networking con Head Hunters #retail #moda para los alumnos MBA,novedoso y rompedor-)    
    
    
    Diageo Is Said to Be in Talks to Buy Jose Cuervo Tequila Brand From Family  http://bloom.bg/m04Ri8  vía @BloombergNow    
    
    
    A Real Digital Marketing Plan for a Pop Band http://learningexperiences.blogs.ie.edu/2011/05/a-real-digital-marketing-plan-for-a-pop-band/ … @maacoto siempre estas innovando!,me encanta!    
    
    
    June 2011: The 10 Best (and Worst) Cities for Finding a Job
 http://www.careercast.com/career-news/june-2011-10-best-and-worst-cities-finding-job …    
    
    
    “@JobHits: Business Development Manager - Banking Services job in London at Sage Personnel http://bit.ly/n2Iiov ”    
    
    
    #Desigual is conducting a presentation at #IE they need international #talent for their expansion plan #careers #empleo #job    
    
    
    #Desigual is conducting a presentation at #IE they need international #talent #careers #empleo #job http://yfrog.com/nvpixhj     
    
    
    Organising the session "#Networking with #head hunters" we have the #talent just vacancies needed!!#rrhh#IE#formacion    
    
    
    #IEfashion I Virtual #Career #Fair with #L'Orèal #Inditex #Mango #Desigual #Richemont #LVMH ,...for #IE alumni and students 23rd November    
    
    
    Job opportunity: RESPONSABLE MARKETING ON LINE at DIGITAL SUGGAR - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/4QSD9U     
    
    
    What's happening when today "NO" is the new "YES"?Let's balanced our personal & professional life!    
    
    
    @IEbusiness #Chinese dragon year at IE career oportunies at job bank http://yfrog.com/nw77emzj     
    
    
    I'm searching  job opportunitites for IE students in China. Please upload your cv on the careers website, vacancy...: http://lnkd.in/TMAZsP     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/fwvCKZ  Thank you Xinrong. You can send it to me gabriela.planas@ie.edu in English and Chinese but I recomendo you to...    
    
    
    President of Asia-Pacific #Diageo at #IE http://yfrog.com/nvhxseoj     
    
    
    #Kellogg's presentation at #IE Business School  http://yfrog.com/es69702321j     
    
    
    #Richemont at #IE Business School really smarth presentation http://yfrog.com/nvavfcoj     
    
    
    SC #Johnson's at #IE Representatives from finance,marketing and sales and the #HR Manager on campus    
    
    
    SC Johnson team http://yfrog.com/h0rqcoxj     
    
    
    #IECarrefour Todd Hooper conducting a presentation at #IE #retail is "hands on" http://yfrog.com/ob884buj     
    
    
    #BAT on #IE Campus Top emloyers since 2009 by CFR Institute http://yfrog.com/oek09bfdj     
    
    
    @diegovilarino thank you for your wonderful presentation and all the knowledge that you shared with us http://yfrog.com/odr4nwej     
    
    
    @juantinocofeber conducting a presentation at #IE Business School @redbullesp #RRHH #IEredbull http://yfrog.com/od1w4ixj     
    
    
    @ieWilliamDavila I'm following you.FYI: Burger King will lunch their management t. programme with #IE as the only European Business School    
    
    
    @WebBlancaSuarez @holacom @BlancaSuarezWeb @clubMariaLeon #SpiritAwards en Miami increibles #joyas de @Piaget me encantan! #moda    
    
    
    #masquecoches #telecinco #divinity http://yfrog.com/ob4n4wgj     
    
    
    @ExecEducationIE Gran Programa en Marzo Mobile Business http://execed.ie.edu/openprograms/ProgramasAbiertosDetalle.aspx?id=1593 … Manuel Alonso Coto #IE #mobile #marketing    
    
    
    Job opportunity: INTERNATIONAL SENIOR AUDITOR at Toys R Us - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/Av6Y-i     
    
    
    #Amazon Europe at #IE Business School.Really interesting #job opportunities at this fast growing enviroment! http://yfrog.com/oewmsouj     
    
    
    @FashionJobsUK #HR Manager Responsible for the people agenda within the Distribution Centre an... http://bit.ly/z9JKMN  #Jobs    
    
    
    Searching for vacancies in Miami for #IE Business School alumni #employ #empleo #jobs #retail #fmcg    
    
    
    My session today:#Careers in Retail: #cosmetics #fashion. New markets,new players.Cv Tips for #bba students at @IEuniversity,Segovia #jobs    
    
    
    #Google EMEA conducting a Company presentation at #IE Business School.A really challenge company #jobs http://yfrog.com/kg1mocnj     
    
    
    Ready to bring job opportunities from #China to #IE Students #Retail #jobs #empleo    
    
    
    Searching for interesting retail positions in China (Beijing)    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Buyer's Assistant at WHSmith - London, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/DzDhWb     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Store Manager, Barcelona  at Burberry - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/eNrXpP     
    
    
    Job opportunity: DIRECTOR DE MARKETING at Michael Page - Spain - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/2_Ctgs     
    
    
    Menudo Marathon. Enhorabuena @RunRocknRoll estuvo fenomenal . Congrats for the Madrid one!!!!    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Associate Creative Director at Open D Group - Singapore #jobs http://lnkd.in/TzX2UN     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Sales Manager - Madrid at BookGenie - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/W8we8H     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Sales Account Manager at TOSHIBA TEC EUROPE - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/vAVVCn     
    
    
    With Daniel Porot (http://www.porot.com ) a guru in "piloting your #career to land the right #job http://yfrog.com/nu7cfpj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director, Integrated Marketing, Consumer at Johnson & Johnson - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/ztdeA7     
    
    
    With the #HR manager of L'Oréal conducting a presentation about careers in #FMCG sector #jobs #empleo #IE http://yfrog.com/nxrbkswj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Purchasing Manager at zooplus AG - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/KpFp8J     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Group Financial Controller at International Luxury Retail Group - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/UMiYSE     
    
    
    Job opportunity: International HR Manager  at Carlton Senior Appointments Ltd - Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/hcWyzj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Retail Channel Account Manager Northern  at Ergotron - Munich Area, Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/NUxqsc     
    
    
    Shoe street art in Madrid (Serrano St) http://yfrog.com/es9qqrnj     
    
    
    ·jobs Assistant at Marketing (Chester, England): Online & Digital Marketing... http://bit.ly/KFjaWN  #looktohire    
    
    
    Job opportunity: DIRECTOR DE MARKETING CORPORATIVO at NEXUS EXECUTIVE SEARCH - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/Ezfw3Z     
    
    
    Job opportunity: CONTROLLER PRODUCTO ZARA at Zara - A Coruña Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/yW2XQq     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Manager HR Business Partner, New  at Amadeus - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/G3fhYq     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Brand Manager at Paramount Pictures - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/vgcK3K     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Strategy Manager at VF Corporation - Ticino, Switzerland #jobs http://lnkd.in/TNnREP     
    
    
    Vogue who's on next winner http://yfrog.com/kk8r3lxaj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Regional General Manager / Head of Retai at Quantica Retail - Leeds, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/C2hg_M     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Manager - External Reporting at Tiffany & Co. - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/dkNstM     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Retail Business Analyst at Tommy Hilfiger - Amsterdam Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/5usQtk     
    
    
    #mbfwm #EvaSotoConde #Cibeles http://yfrog.com/obbcffjuj     
    
    
    1.000 executives from more than 50 countries at #iealumniforum http://yfrog.com/g0wjkraj  @IEAlumni    
    
    
    #Makro @metrogroup conducting interviews on campus to our MBA and MIM #IE students http://yfrog.com/nufhmmxj     
    
    
    Mercedes Benz Fashion Week Madrid. Pasarela Cibeles 2012 http://pasarelacibeles.hola.com/madrid/primavera-verano-2013m/ …    
    
    
    #LOreal recruiting at #IE Business School  http://yfrog.com/mgkpjqtj     
    
    
    @nestlé leader in nutrition and health at #IE Business School opp available at http://www.nestle.es  Nesfit Programme   http://yfrog.com/h2xsovtj     
    
    
    “@GJobsmarketing: Brand Manager - Penguin Classics - London - PENGUIN http://mjobx.com/KFLgAQ ”    
    
    
    In NY...seaching for some innovation    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director of Marketing and Business Devel at Comunycarse - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/nu2cwH     
    
    
    @IEbusiness ranking BusinessWeek, 3º puesto, well done! http://numrl.com/98686  #IE    
    
    
    Job opportunity: International Financial Controller at Grupor Gransolar, S.L. - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/wD4XEK     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Marketing Manager - Ecommerce, Sp at Visa Europe - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/_6TaG6     
    
    
    Job opportunity: DISEÑADOR/A DE MODA MUJER at ADOLFO DOMINGUEZ,S.A. - Ourense Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/PN5E8K     
    
    
    Job opportunity: DISEÑADOR/A DE MODA MUJER at ADOLFO DOMINGUEZ,S.A. - Ourense Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/PN5E8K     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Brand Manager at Sophie Paris - Greater Jakarta Area, Indonesia #jobs http://lnkd.in/uky6fn     
    
    
    Job opportunity: CONSULTOR DE PROCESOS ESPECIALISTA EN RE at SteelMood - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/ZAZmHy     
    
    
    Job opportunity: NikeiD Online Merchandiser at Nike EMEA - Amsterdam Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/n9veVy     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Responsable de Marketing y RRPP at Disparala  - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/xjQdjZ     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Gestor de Grandes Cuentas (sector retail at Unibail Rodamco - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/jxftDJ     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Sales Manager-Social Media at ADESIS Netlife - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/nq5yaF     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director de Ventas Adjunto at U-tad - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/_Ugbnr     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Buying Manager at The Retail Talent Network - London, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/cAfmWA     
    
    
    Job opportunity: CORPORATE COMMUNICATIONS  MANAGER at Toys R Us - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/XHMWxd     
    
    
    Job opportunity: COMERCIAL DE PACKAGING PARA EL SECTOR LÁ at GRUPO ENTECO - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/8BJEYm     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Brand Manager Cardiovascular at Takeda Farmacéutica España - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/GmR6ib     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Junior Financial Controller at ITC Accessories - Almere Stad Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/gJ62yX     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Trading Manager - France at http://ASOS.com  - London, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/xiWmJS     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director Comercial y de Marketing (Gran  at Adecco Professional - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/yak6Hq     
    
    
    Job opportunity: LOGISTICS & SUPPLY CHAIN MANAGER at OPTAR. Consultoria de Búsqueda,  - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/wRvbWj     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Area Manager at Primadonna Spagna,sl - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/wE2Dic     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Account Manager at COSENTINO, S.A. - Cologne Area, Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/WeiRmK     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Gestor de Grandes Cuentas (sector retail at Unibail Rodamco - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/-HAYEK     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Junior Fashion Buyer OYSHO at Inditex - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/EqQDbv     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Manager, Merchant Services, Spain at Amazon - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/-T8yU6     
    
    
    Job opportunity: STORE MANAGER / BRANCH MANAGER at 360 Executive Search - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/D4CgwG     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager Mens Originals_Blue (m/f) at adidas - Nürnberg Area, Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/Tjg43V     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Merchandise Planner - Victoria's Secret  at Victoria's Secret - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/EfyN_p     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager marketing online con Fra at ElTenedor.es - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/bpNEBV     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Loss Prevention Manager - Retail at Dollar Financial Group - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/8_55q3     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager marketing online con Fra at ElTenedor.es - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/bpNEBV     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Supply Chain Project Manager - Fashion at http://Amazon.co.uk  - Slough, United Kingdom #jobs http://lnkd.in/wEuyQy     
    
    
    Job opportunity: PRODUCT & CATEGORY DEVELOPMENT DIRECTOR  at The Martin Veasey Partne - Kingston upon Thames, United Kingdom #jobs http://l…    
    
    
    Job opportunity: STRATEGIC INSIGHT MANAGER EMEA – FMCG/Re at The Martin Veasey Partne - Kingston upon Thames, United Kingdom #jobs http://l…    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Retail Manager Moda Mujer  at Randstad España - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/d_-dbS     
    
    
    Job opportunity: RETAIL PROCESS MANAGER at Swarovski - Zürich Area, Switzerland #jobs http://lnkd.in/JiDGQD     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Business Support Coordinator at Dobotex Ltd. - PUMA AG Group - Tilburg Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/xM-9Dn     
    
    
    Job opportunity: COORDINADOR/A DE PLANIFICACIÓN Y DISTRIB at Grupo Cortefiel - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/cTYC-j     
    
    
    Job opportunity: RESPONSABLE DE MARKETING ONLINE (CITY PL at GD Human Capital - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/fwdVGD     
    
    
    Marc Jacobs's bottle designs in celebration of Diet #Coke 30th Europe Anniversary @MarcJacobsIntl AMAZING pic.twitter.com/f23wboTwnH    
    
    
    Road race next Friday at Dublin-St.Patricks´Day http://numrl.com/stpatriks  I will be there    
    
    
    Job opportunity: comprador at Circa - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/B7apqD     
    
    
    Comprador bañadores (Merchant, Swim - Victoria's Secret) New York, NY podeis aplicar via linkedin en este link:... http://fb.me/QrXzGsc0     
    
    
    CIRCA is the leading international buyer of jewelry, #diamonds and watches with private offices throughout North... http://fb.me/1DVYzVJ2m     
    
    
    Head of Retouching to 40K http://www.fashionmonitor.com/Jobs/VL/Head-of-Retouching-to-40K … #jobs #empleo #fashion    
    
    
    ACCOUNT MANAGER- BEAUTY EUROPE #jobs #empleo for @Burberry a global brand with a distinctly British attitude. http://numrl.com/vacanteshr     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager at The Hip Tee - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/e3UuyS     
    
    
    We-want-to-seduce-and-LOrealize-buyers- The Times of India http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/We-want-to-seduce-and-LOrealize-buyers/articleshow/7289240.cms …    
    
    
    Why the Valentino buyout is the future of fashion http://gu.com/p/39292/tw  vía @guardian    
    
    
    Premio Nacional de # Marketing MarketingNews pic.twitter.com/jhH1DubXqr    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director de Fábrica at 360 Executive Search - Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/gYBjsV     
    
    
    I love London and with the 40´s principales more :-) #ALondresConDel40al1 @Tony__Aguilar @del40al1_Spain @FastFurious    
    
    
    Job opportunity: diseñador de moda textil at The Hip Tee - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/h_bdcj     
    
    
    @MarkFritz great conference on managing virtual teams No boundaries,just balance..thank you Mark!    
    
    
    Fashion Creative Director para Portugal). Posted  by SNTalent    
    
    
    Job opportunity: DEPUTY STORE MANAGER at Bulgari - Rome Area, Italy #jobs http://lnkd.in/4hgVBP     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Asia International Area Manager at Pepe Jeans - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/ZtH5wT     
    
    
    Muy bueno!good tips on your job search 2.0!http://khac.es/50701    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Russian Business Development Intern at Grupo LVMH - LOEWE - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/TQRtzC     
    
    
    Job opportunity: International Sales Director at Smartmood - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/XESQzA     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Community Manager at alternatiba - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/VEbSTh     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director/a de Almacén at Bricomart - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/zjeuMw     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LyC22Ze-lJ0 … Orientation Day #rrhh #formacion    
    
    
    @edans Estupendo como siempre con @Oracle @Accenture @everis en @IEbusiness "What happens in an internet minute?" pic.twitter.com/cOVnR36OzJ    
    
    
    @IEbusiness @IEAlumni @el_pais gracias! #IEluxury #IEfashion    
    
    
    @piaget experience Anne #roseday so nice! pic.twitter.com/pWOHWQWwyj    
    
    
    @piaget today with their #roseday event and  @LovelyPepa in the photocall. We love #luxury pic.twitter.com/31EvMpweXM    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Manager Estrategia Consumo y Retail  at Accenture - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/uminxd     
    
    
    Workshop for an international cv http://www.careerboutique.es/espa%C3%B1ol-1/cursos-y-talleres-1/ …    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Responsable de Dpto. de Diseño Camisetas at Inditex - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/VhDT2e     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Store Manager at Nike EMEA - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/4VeXdV     
    
    
    Luxury Store Manager.South Coast Plaza, CA. experience in luxury leather goods and staff development erica@shopthejobs.com    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Manager de Negocio con experienci at Accenture - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/V8TWgt     
    
    
    Job opportunity: BAGS AND SLG MERCHANDISER/BUYER at Grupo LVMH - LOEWE - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/zuFQnt     
    
    
    I was #mentor for 2 years with #EPWnMadrid really good experience! I encouraged all of you!    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Product Manager - Retail Merchandise & C at Starbucks - Amsterdam Area, Netherlands #jobs http://lnkd.in/ZzEkia     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Comprador at Amichi - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/WtBeHX     
    
    
    ¿Ready for #IEfashion?    
    
    
    #IEFashion Marc Jacobs...the beginning    
    
    
    #IEfashion internal promotion.Good opportunities entering on a store as a manager    
    
    
    #IEfashion opportunities for Portugal,Marocco,South Europe,Middle East    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior Purchaser Marionnaud Spain  at MARIONNAUD - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/8-f_Tb     
    
    
    #IEfashion @louisvuitton evaluates potential of the candidate and possible career plans    
    
    
    #IEfashion Dubay booming    
    
    
    #iefashion very good questions @IEstudents    
    
    
    #iefashion the Cover letter needs to be inspiring    
    
    
    #iefashion Retail implies starting from the point of view of a store manager with the potential of what an MBA gives    
    
    
    @rickypedraza good question!needs to inspire in order to show a commitment with the company to the #HR dep and to the Manager:)    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Responsable Creativo de Imagen- Stradiva at Inditex - Barcelona Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/NkqhUX     
    
    
    Job opportunity: PM W´s Bags at Grupo LVMH - LOEWE - Madrid Area, Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/kv7hH3     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Parfums Givenchy MARKETING DIRECTOR at LVMH - Spain #jobs http://lnkd.in/KqHVcw     
    
    
    Job opportunity: VP, Marketing at Moda Operandi - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/nmpFJE     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Press and Publicity Manager- Male at Diesel - Greater New York City Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/j5AW_H     
    
    
    @rickypedraza thanks!!!    
    
    
    Sunday = Runday With my @ASICSeurope @adidasrunning and my @PolarFitness ;-) pic.twitter.com/juIjGl5gev    
    
    
    Store Manager #Madrid #empleo https://m.infojobs.net/offer/detail.xhtml?code=c893dc8e4a481bba5b6766335e77cd&dgv=2421576380571502349 …    
    
    
    #ego nos sorprende #yingyao "Fashion needs to be radical and experimental" #MBFWMadrid @MBFWMadrid @SamsungMobileES pic.twitter.com/WcX7tWAkpJ    
    
    
    Job openings: . Human Resources Officer via @UN_Careers http://fb.me/RpU7wbpR    
    
    
    Que bonito @ewanfood al atardecer #buenasideas @TheIvidBand @CondePrendes pic.twitter.com/LTpqocEQxQ    
    
    
    Negrosoro brillos y ,encajes...bright in the night http://yfrog.com/h279507660j http://yfrog.com/h43wpmpj    
    
    
    Negrosoro brillos y ,encajes...bright in the night #CMFW http://yfrog.com/h279507660j http://yfrog.com/h43wpmpj    
    
    
    #greygoose uhmmm cofee i need it,thanks    
    
    
    @gABiplanas_rrhh:Negros-oro+encaje.Bright in the night #CMFW http://yfrog.com/h279507660j http://yfrog.com/h43wpmpj” #cibeles #kinafernandez    
    
    
    @Marat_Ch #recruiting a Menswear Designer for Massimo Dutti Barcelona.Min 3 years exp in menswear design #jobs #fashion @massimodutti #moda    
    
    
    Proyecto de @AJEASTURIAS @FADE_COMUNICA #goforit #mentoring http://fb.me/1MJ3xiU0r     
    
    
    It's frozen outside but... Who cares?I've my @HaagenDazs_ES ready! @HaagenDazsLoves pic.twitter.com/rJbxULuNtT    
    
    
    Con @VogueSpain en #voguejoyas impresionante @tousjewelry @Piaget @JoyeriaSuarez y @ysacristan pic.twitter.com/zz5H8xr49u    
    
    
    @MartiniSpain Luck is an #attitude !! With my. #litlesister pic.twitter.com/uLUt7pXhMw    
    
    
    Shoes transform body language and attitude.They lift you physically & emotionally @LouboutinWorld @Louboutin_Blog pic.twitter.com/plxMJpKYAH    
    
    
    @MerlinUK interesting #vacancies on their website for UK! #jobs Head of Programme Funding    
    
    
    Interesante @ZipRecruiter: Luxottica #Retail is hiring Retail Sales Manager http://ziprecruiter.com/tj/0af81d95  #jobs    
    
    
    Que buena iniciativa @Humannova:"Pásate esta tarde a tomar algo y hacer #networking con Profesionales #RRHH.19:30h http://ht.ly/4eKti ”    
    
    
    #British #American #Tobacco presenting on #IE campus their trainee programme on Tuesday!#jobs    
    
    
    Take risks when looking for a #job danger is always more attractive    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Director, Human Resources at VWR International - Rochester, New York Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/KB9DxN    
    
    
    Burberry London is looking for an HR Manager for Italy (London based)!    
    
    
    Preparando un speed networking con Head Hunters #retail #moda para los alumnos MBA,novedoso y rompedor-)    
    
    
    Diageo Is Said to Be in Talks to Buy Jose Cuervo Tequila Brand From Family  http://bloom.bg/m04Ri8  vía @BloombergNow    
    
    
    A Real Digital Marketing Plan for a Pop Band http://learningexperiences.blogs.ie.edu/2011/05/a-real-digital-marketing-plan-for-a-pop-band/ … @maacoto siempre estas innovando!,me encanta!    
    
    
    June 2011: The 10 Best (and Worst) Cities for Finding a Job
 http://www.careercast.com/career-news/june-2011-10-best-and-worst-cities-finding-job …    
    
    
    