    
    
    
    Wooden rockets - You ask a carpenter to build a rocket and the rocket will be made of wood, because that’s... http://tumblr.com/xg54u08z5p     
    
    
    Functionality vs evolution - It looks like, from an evolutionary point of view, for living things it’s... http://tumblr.com/xg552ajjof     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxMY7w46     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Principled UX - “A compass will point you true north. But it won’t show you the swamps between you and... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxecEy9B     
    
    
        
    
    
    Travel light, but don't forget to bring your lungs - How often do we come back from holiday with clothes and... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxjuc_AB     
    
    
    Product owner, you have won the lottery - Some product owners behave as if they have won the lottery and,... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxj-T8b2     
    
    
    The personal is political: building a library of components - The radical feminist Carol Hanish explained in... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxl7OCWi     
    
    
    Vision vs Strategy - In my line of business I find that, very often, these two concepts are used as... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxmjNLYt     
    
    
    Written history - Not coincidentally, knowledge advanced in leaps after humans started writing things down. http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxnEPKZW     
    
    
    Post hoc ergo propter hoc - One of my favourite rational fallacies: Post hoc ergo propter hoc, after this,... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxnF7f_N     
    
    
    Some functionality is like gay marriage - We have been testing a new functionality on a group of users. This... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxrsyjH2     
    
    
    This application could end like Michael Jackson - Sometimes, working as a UX in a software project feels... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxsvadVP     
    
    
    The socratic method for UX - From Wikipedia, the socratic method: is a form of inquiry and discussion... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxtJQawZ     
    
    
    Build the bridge first, then build it again - Fig.1: Old London Bridge The area around the current London... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmxz3SWBm     
    
    
    The product is what gets built, not what is designed - It may sound like a truism, but it is very easy for... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmx-181Tt     
    
    
    Lean to discover, JFDI for everything else - Lean UX methodologies allow UXrs to quickly get rid of... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmx-UB-YF     
    
    
    @theyearofelan I was with you on the plane argument, until the "eat my dick" bit. No need for that. Stinks of misogyny.    
    
    
    More socratic thoughts for UX - Socrates’ attributed quote of "I know that I know nothing" is a reminder to... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmx10Ghemi     
    
    
    Isaac Newton was a bit thick - "Well, he didn’t come up with quantum mechanics, now did he? or with the... http://tmblr.co/ZPhDmx10WT1rJ     
    
    
    @zanzandel lovely meeting you Saturday. Hopefully I'll be using twitter a bit more now :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    The second law of thermodynamics (or why we should design for chaos) - As wikipedia puts it Which, I... http://tumblr.com/xg51p83rmt    
    
    
    Photo: Copper handrail - the more people use it, the more polished it is http://tumblr.com/xg51p83xvy    
    
    
        
    
    
    An Introverted UX: http://facecan.tumblr.com/post/3721119630/i-was-at-a-conference-recently-in-berlin#disqus_thread    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Good design alters our expectations of the objects around us, our object-world" - Tin Munkey http://tumblr.com/xg51qmnyqc    
    
    
    workflowed out    
    
    
        
    
    
    is my site/application a digital swiss_army_knife? - Difficult to maintain and with more features and... http://tumblr.com/xg522vwrux    
    
    
        
    
    
    John, the (UX) evangelist - I’m not sure how common this is but it seems that some corporations have “UX... http://tumblr.com/xg52adtyen    
    
    
    "you were asking me to design a logotype which would have taken me a few hours and fifteen years..." http://tumblr.com/xg52agajlr    
    
    
        
    
    
    Photo: Beautiful 1854 infographic on the world’s rivers and mountains http://tumblr.com/xg52h5gl63    
    
    
        
    
    
    Uncertainty principle and UX - From Wikipedia: › In [quantum mechanics], the Heisenberg uncertainty... http://tumblr.com/xg52lnhoh3    
    
    
    Blacks swans in UX - A colleague of mine explained to me the other day the Black swan theory. Wikipedia says... http://tumblr.com/xg537vjj00    
    
    
    Pastry with your coffee? about non-primary user journeys - Went to the coffee shop with a colleague of mine... http://tumblr.com/xg53gjvtne    
    
    
    Infinite monkey theorem...monkey wireframes - From wikipedia: This approach is quite common in UX, do lots... http://tumblr.com/xg53hu7dbf    
    
    
        
    
    
    #uxg1 very interesting UX talk on gamification, wondering what the overlap with nudge theory there is    
    
    
    #uxg1 if I could roll my eyes, I would have done...the same person keeps having something (irrelevant) to say about everything. Speaker rox    
    
    
        
    
    
    *balanced*    
    
    
    This application is for EVERYONE - Stakeholder says something like the following: › This application is for... http://tumblr.com/xg53twk5so    
    
    
    