Working on a new mid-size to small series that I'll launch with my Spring Art Shows. To see current works visit www.alicialeeke.com.    
    
    
    Tuscan Villa Signed & Numbered Limited Edition by Alicialeeke http://etsy.me/r0G6Vq  via @Etsy    
    
    
    Collector as Artist: The Barnes Foundation - http://nyti.ms/qqLaaq     
    
    
    Red, Red, Red...Fire Series is Back!    
    
    
    Ashamed to admit it took this long, but I had a "me" morning today, and saw "An Artist's Eye, A Journey through... http://fb.me/1eBHngQmE    
    
    
    #AT&T's admen apparently didn't check out #HTC Thunderbolt before making their #IPHONE commercial. Surf and Talk at the same time on Verizon    
    
    
    The Yahoo Article about Linked-in forgot to mention under: Turn on/off data sharing with 3rd party applications: be sure to uncheck the yes.    
    
    
    Art still a good investment. . . http://resource.wur.nl/en/wetenschap/detail/art_is_a_better_investment_than_shares/ …    
    
    
    Launching a new body of abstracts that will only be available for purchase at the Atlanta Arts Festival Sept 17-18, 2011 at investor prices    
    
    
    One of the selling points to purchase my #HTC Thunderbolt was that on Verizon, the majority of the Apps I use are free!    
    
    
    Gearing up for a busy show month! Working on a new body of landscapes!    
    
    
    http://online.wsj.com/video/news-hub-is-art-the-new-gold/15615C82-E8E0-4483-A431-6BF4B2FD9891.html you heard this from me first in 2009.    
    
    
    Avoid phishing scams, malware etc., by examining short url's with http://www.longurl.org/     
    
    
    Google to buy Motorola...wonder if they'll catch up to HTC?    
    
    
    Dyeing and prepping new hand-dyed scarves for Fall!    
    
    
    I'll be showcasing new work Thursday night! Come out with your wallets full and leave with great art! Remember,... http://fb.me/16U58VYFD     
    
    
    The first installation of the Digital Graffiti project is totonight during Mingle and Jingle on Main Street in... http://fb.me/ByHNIDuD    
    
    
    Best art supply Investment yet; the Collapsable Wagon from Costco in Charleston, SC. Under $100 and reduces load-in and out times by 50%!    
    
    
    Here is the link for the collapsable wagon at Costco in Charleston, SC It has reviews on here; ignore the negative one.
http://reviews.costco.com/2070/11306719/on-the-edge-folding-utility-cart-reviews/reviews.htm …    
    
    
    Columbia Museum of Art to Open: Masterpieces of the Hudson River School Painters November 19, 2011 in Columbia, SC: http://www.columbiamuseum.org/art/exhibitions?exID=84 …    
    
    
    Great news! Juried into the Piccolo Spoleto outdoor festival this year! http://bit.ly/bpRrpD    
    
    
    After the Art with a Heart fundraiser I viewed the South Carolina Arts Commission's Triennial Revisited... http://fb.me/10iqv3cZ3     
    
    
    I posted 9 photos on Facebook in the album "What's on the Brush March 2010" http://bit.ly/dxzNlK    
    
    
    Hi Facebook Friends, These new paintings are hot off the brush. Last year, I had a lot of friends help me name pics... http://bit.ly/cFSIWD    
    
    
    Deivering new work to the Columbia Museum of Art's Museum Shop today in Columbia, SC! Here is a preview of new... http://fb.me/JlvVRUjG     
    
    
    I posted 22 photos on Facebook in the album "August 23, 2011 New Silk Scarves" http://fb.me/18izSRgMR     
    
    
    Naming of paintings tonight! HIstory!  http://www.facebook.com/pages/Alicia-Leeke-American-Contemporary-Painter-Official-Site/54036227159    
    
    
    Help me make history by naming my new small works. Facebook Alicia Leeke Contemporary American Painter! Thanks for your help!    
    
    
    @FrankAdman need your west coast creativity tonight on my facebook fan page to name some original artworks!    
    
    
    Thanks to all my fabulous friends who came to the party! You guys are great! http://bit.ly/aPa7cm    
    
    
    Trenholm Artist Guild's member show is up for one more week. We've sold several  paintings & there is work still available at HofP Gallery.    
    
    
    Hello Atlanta friends! If you don't have plans for Labor Day, please come out and say hi during the Art on the... http://fb.me/xpJ0KGJU     
    
    
    If you are afraid to buy art as a gift for someone else...forget about it and buy it for yourself! -- Alicia Leeke    
    
    
    I WANT TO BE THE SOCK MONKEY!  http://vimeo.com/9238869    
    
    
    Show time in Atlanta - Saturday!    
    
    
    I posted 6 photos on Facebook in the album "What's on the Brush March 2010" http://bit.ly/dxzNlK    
    
    
    Hi Facebook friends. I just added four new paintings to this batch that I need naming. The building one is an older... http://bit.ly/9P1Wle    
    
    
    Sunday is the last day to see my work in Atlanta at the Arts on the Creek Show. I will be there early tomorrow... http://fb.me/16ZZwYYm0     
    
    
    Sorry for so many posts this week, but, if you are in Charleston, SC for the bridge run and are looking for... http://bit.ly/aotm0f    
    
    
    Please vote for me at: https://www.facebook.com/#!/media/set/?set=a.158815287527318.40747.142955885779925 …. To vote hit Like on Arts on the Creek, then Like Alicia Leeke. Thanks!    
    
    
    New Gallery representation announcement coming soon!    
    
    
    Great article in Charleston Regional Business Journal: http://www.charlestonbusiness.com/news/39525-art-galleries-set-for-long-term-growth?rss=0 …    
    
    
    Looking forward to the Atlanta Arts Festival! Stop by my my booth # 089...in the meantime, please visit my work at... http://fb.me/JgqVZMN9     
    
    
    Come to "Piccolo Spoleto" Friday, May 28 at 10:00 am until <br />Saturday, June 5 at 5:00 pm. Art Exhibit at Marion... http://bit.ly/9xxc86    
    
    
    Working like crazy for the Atlanta Arts Festival. I hope my Atlanta friends will come by and say hello! It's in Piedmont Park.    
    
    
    Today's good news you can use... just browse this site... http://www.suzeorman.com/ Check out the part on credit unions... good stuff.    
    
    
    BTW, don't know if I mentioned, but I was juried into Piccolo Spoleto USA. WOO HOO! We're gonna sell MORE art!    
    
    
    I'll be bringing a lot of new abstract paintings to the Atlanta Arts Festival this weekend. I'm in booth no.... http://fb.me/X2nMGa7n     
    
    
    I'll be bringing a lot of new abstract paintings to the Atlanta Arts Festival this weekend. I'm in booth no. 089... http://fb.me/ZWzAHnSI     
    
    
    Christmas came early today with my new Chevy Uplander!! So excited about my new outfitted ride custom outfitted for hauling art! WOO HOO!    
    
    
    http://www.atlantaartsfestival.com/schedule.php  http://fb.me/Mg7VSH1n     
    
    
    Atlanta arts Festival 10 to. 6 Sunday piedmont park booth 89.    
    
    
    A good night of #DancingWithTheStars for pre-season line up to compete w/ Two and A Half Men would have been #CharlieSheen; nobody asked me    
    
    
    Lots of great new abstracts painted!    
    
    
    Great show in Atlanta during the Atlanta Arts Festival...now time to gear up for the next show this weekend in Charlotte, North Carolina!    
    
    
    Fellow artists, musicians, videographers, photographers and trade show people...

I'm selling a shipping storage... http://fb.me/1l8ARQUlm     
    
    
    Getting ready for the Festival in the Park Art Show in Charlotte, NC. Hope to see you there if you're in the area this weekend.    
    
    
    About Face Member's Show and Exhibition will be held Tuesday, September 27, 2011 at the Columbia Museum of Art in... http://fb.me/11f2auTge     
    
    
    Getting ready to show at the Charlotte Festival in the Park this weekend in Charlotte, NC. http://www.festivalinthepark.org/artistswalk.htm     
    
    
    You can now connect with me on Google+ lookup Alicia Leeke.    
    
    
    You can now connect with me on Google+ by looking up Alicia Leeke.    
    
    
    I will be introducing new landscape paintings during the Charlotte Festival in the Park held this weekend in... http://fb.me/GZj1Qpgr     
    
    
    See you in Freedom Park; show opens at 4 pm today rain or shine!! I'll be showing new work!... http://fb.me/1fJ7knqa2     
    
    
    Not to be a shameless self promoter, but...Mothers Day is coming up as well as Father's Day and I have some work... http://bit.ly/aPcrc4    
    
    
    Wonder if this means paying for Youtube in the future? http://bl129w.blu129.mail.live.com/default.aspx?n=714768037&wa=wsignin1.0    
    
    
    Please join Walker Covin, Bill Davis and me at Worth Repeating Sunday, December 12th for the Holiday Artisan's... http://fb.me/J8vlj9cE    
    
    
    October, Acrylic on Canvas, framed is one of the large works I'll have on hand Sundy. http://fb.me/PZVtY8aW    
    
    
    Thinks doing business with big banks is the equivalent to putting money in the back yard without the jar, after running a lawnmower over it.    
    
    
    I'll be at Saluda Shoals Park October 2, this Sunday, painting on the overlook as part of the Unearth Celebration.... http://fb.me/JQtWRZag     
    
    
    I have all new works at this event...come if you can! 

http://www.sandhillsschool.org/artgala.html http://bit.ly/9gckyU    
    
    
    http://www.icrc.net/parks/saluda-shoals.aspx … 

I will be painting at Saluda Shoals Park during Unearth, an event... http://fb.me/sZQN191f     
    
    
    Love this sound! http://www.facebook.com/mellowcolumbia?v=wall#!/video/video.php?v=1169982571910    
    
    
    Adding a skylight to my show tent for Piccolo Spoleto Festival USA!    
    
    
    Our Chihuly! http://www.thestate.com/2010/04/11/1238844/a-work-of-art-a-work-of-heart.html#storylink=addthis#storylink=addthis via @addthis    
    
    
    Who is your favorite painter in history present or future...and if you could interview them what questions would... http://bit.ly/aYSPRA    
    
    
    @WineandFoodSC Can't wait for Lake Carolina's 9th Annual Wine & Food Festival on Saturday October 22: 1-5 pm in Columbia, South Carolina!    
    
    
    @WineandFoodSC Glad to have my art selected for the 9th #LakeCarolinaWineandFoodFestival Poster! This is my favorite event! Oct. 22: 1-5 pm!    
    
    
    @DiscoverSC @WineandFoodSC Mark your calendar for the 9th annual #WineandFoodFestival on Saturday, October 22: 1-5 pm! Tickets now available    
    
    
    The South Carolina State Fair has one of the Southeast's largest art shows. My piece, Jubilation, has been juried... http://fb.me/11cO3HY9v     
    
    
    Is pondering Customer Loyalty and decided if big banks & corporations can't be loyal to THEIR customers then why should WE be loyal to them?    
    
    
    "Jubilation," featured in the Professional Division at the South Carolina State Fair. It is eligible for a... http://fb.me/VER6J8On     
    
    
    Buy your tickets early (and often :) for the Lake Carolina Food & Wine Festival that's coming up October 22 at... http://fb.me/133q4lztl     
    
    
    Mark your calendar for December 4, 2011 for my Christmas Clearance Sale and Open House in my studio. Reception is on 12.8.2011 from 6-8pm    
    
    
    I feel like a kid in a candy shop for the first time in anticipation of the #LakeCarolinaFood&Wine Festival in #Columbia #South Carolina!    
    
    
    Getting new paintings ready for the Charleston Fine Arts Festival!    
    
    
    http://www.lcweekly.com/art/2335-artwalk-in-downtown-beaufort …

Pinkney Simons Gallery is celebrating its 10th... http://fb.me/1klbDjs1E     
    
    
    Great article on owner Michael Mitchell and his Gallery in Charleston, SC where I show my artwork! http://www.charlestonstyleanddesign.com/art-of-design/     
    
    
    Great article on owner Michael Mitchell in the current issue of Charleston Style & Design Magazine!... http://fb.me/1hGxpEL9T     
    
    
    @SqSupport sent a few emails...need an answer, thanks.    
    
    
    Interesting read about the future of credit card processing devices...http://venturebeat.com/2011/09/21/intuit-card-reader-die/?sf2231972=1    
    
    
        
    
    
    If you are in Hilton Head this weekend, stop by the Art Market at Historic Honey Horn. I'll be showing new works... http://bit.ly/cKICvQ    
    
    
    So looking forward to the  #LakeCarolinaFood&Wine Festival in #Columbia #South Carolina this Saturday! Don't forget..it is tomorrow!!    
    
    
    Craig Ferguson is a great relaxor at the end of a long day!    
    
    
    Ok, if you are on Hilton Head Island this weekend, come out to the Coastal Discovery Center's Historic Honey Horn Art Market! I'm booth 20    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Bruce Lee_Be Water My Friend http://youtu.be/USlnfTGlhXc    
    
    
    Looking forward to the Lake Carolina Food & Wine Festival this afternoon! Come out and purchase one of my wine... http://fb.me/1p7QnkkXr     
    
    
    Thanks to all the great people that came out and supported the Ronald McDonald house!    
    
    
    Less than a week before the Greater Charleston Fine Arts Festival!!    
    
    
    The Newark School of the Arts is hosting an opening reception for the Let it Snow exhibition Friday, December 10th... http://fb.me/Qps30ocX    
    
    
    Just had an ephiphany that I was one degree of separation from Kevin Bacon, Jessie Jackson and get down James Brown. That's going in my book    
    
    
    I will be showcasing new paintings during the Greater Charleston Fine Arts Festival in Mount Pleasant this... http://fb.me/1mJqL8Dj4     
    
    
    One more day until show time! Lots of new work from me will be on display!... http://fb.me/GZz0onL7     
    
    
    I hope to see some of my Chucktown friends and make some new friends at this great show right by the Yorktown!. My... http://fb.me/Q7yq4YCF     
    
    
    Be sure to spread the word about this show in Charleston!    
    
    
    Free Admission to Greater Charleston Fine Arts Festival http://j.mp/uxgkUc  via @AddToAny    
    
    
    http://www.postandcourier.com/news/2011/oct/23/festival-focuses-on-arts/ … http://fb.me/148S16G3o     
    
    
    One more day to see my work and that of other great artists. Open Sunday until 5 pm. http://fb.me/1hG0ZeG6N     
    
    
    FYI, here are the hours for the show tomorrow. One of the other articles didn't seem to have the hours and someone... http://fb.me/IFZeYom2     
    
    
    http://events.postandcourier.com/mt-pleasant-sc/events/show/219324004-greater-charleston-fine-art-festival … Greater Charleston Fine Arts Festival Oct 30, Patriot's Point, Charleston, SC.    
    
    
    http://charleston.thedigitel.com/arts-culture/patriots-point-playing-host-first-ever-greater-cha-34434-1017 … One Day left!    
    
    
    http://charleston.thedigitel.com/arts-culture/patriots-point-playing-host-first-ever-greater-cha-34434-1017 … http://fb.me/1eGs49qAc     
    
    
    A HUGE thank you to all my Charleston friends that came out to the first annual Greater Charleston Fine Art... http://fb.me/QkoLC5sc     
    
    
    I just returned from Charleston and now it's time to get ready for the next show. Please join me for this... http://fb.me/1qte47ckT     
    
    
    Autumn Day, 28 x 40 will be on display in Charlotte, NC. Copyright, 2011 all rights reserved. http://fb.me/LGmxwlhv     
    
    
    I just returned from Charleston and now it's time to get ready for the next show. Please join me for this... http://fb.me/112ParXkc     
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/#!/photo.php?fbid=212439875492708&set=a.193047404098622.43698.192367750833254&type=1&theater … http://fb.me/EqtlWKnr     
    
    
    Secret special for Facebook friends only: This weekend at Trinity Cathedral's Bazaar on Gervais and Sumter Street... http://fb.me/t5PnapoX     
    
    
    Three pieces were juried into the Columbia Museum of Art Contemporaries' Artist of the Year Auction, two of which... http://bit.ly/bRSuNs    
    
    
    Secret sale on my art at the Trinity Cathedral Bazaar in Columbia, SC Saturday. Booth located near the band in the breezeway. Hours are 10-3    
    
    
    Join me at the Charlotte Fine Arts Festival Nov. 5-6, Symphony Park at South Park Mall. I will be showing new paintings in booth number 61    
    
    
    New representation of my work announced soon in Columbia, SC.    
    
    
    Hanging system for wall hangings paintings foir sale by Alicialeeke http://etsy.me/ui9BQV  via @Etsy. Made to outfit a 10x10 carpeted display    
    
    
    http://localtalknews.com/newark/education/684-newark-school-of-the-arts-to-host-qlet-it-snowq-exhibition-on-dec-10 http://fb.me/M4XIQ3cL    
    
    
    Looking forward to seeing you in Charlotte at the Fine Arts Festival!

It's this weekend! Saturday 10-6 and Sunday... http://fb.me/EzsORDBC     
    
    
    Looking forward to seeing you in Charlotte at the Fine Arts Festival! It's this weekend! Saturday 10-6 and Sunday 10-5!
http://www.thecharlotteweekly.com/arts_entertainment/2011/11/local-artists-ready-to-shine-in-fine-art-fest/ …    
    
    
    Getting ready for a show in Savannah, GA this weekend.    
    
    
    Getting ready to show my art at the Civic Center in Savannah, GA on Oglethorpe just over the Talmadge Bridge this weekend!  Opens Sat.10 am!    
    
    
    Looking forward to a great art week in Columbia, South Carolina. First is Vista Lights this Thursday and I'll be... http://fb.me/1dgUZRSJF     
    
    
    Looking forward to a great art show in Wilmington, North Carolina at the Convention Center Thanksgiving Weekend.    
    
    
    Come see my art in #Wilmington, North Carolina http://www.wilmingtontickets.com/wilmington-nc/events/show/166108205-wilmington-art-craft-show … Thanksgiving weekend! Link is to event details.    
    
    
    @cornpicker49 Yes, I did. Thank you very much; had to have #Square cancel the account and reset it. Three hour was the correct response time    
    
    
    @SqSupport  Thanks. It took #Square #SqSupport three hours to respond, but I got all my answers and fixed. East Coast time vs. West Coast.    
    
    
    Oh and I like #Square a lot. Great notifications and print outs. Only downside is no live person, guess that's why they have lower rates.    
    
    
    @Norm_Valz Probably an oversite?    
    
    
    @soxinsc Thanks and congrats!!!    
    
    
    @DollyLynnPaul Thank you for the #FF shout out. Does Tudy have a Tweet account?    
    
    
    @twittersuggests Thanks for the referral! http://www.alicialeeke.com     
    
    
    @BethBaldauf Thanks for the Shout out on #FF. Sorry for the late response!    
    
    
    Less than a week away! Don't miss the Hudson River School Exhibit at the #Columbia Museum of Art, #Columbia, SC! http://www.columbiamuseum.org/exhibitions/hudsonriver/ …    
    
    
    http://www.facebook.com/?ref=home#!/event.php?eid=108372269206600&ref=mf http://bit.ly/apAk0L    
    
    
    This Thursday I'll be showcasing some of my abstract paintings at Nonnah's. This will be my going away party from... http://fb.me/Dk3sqZhI     
    
    
    Downside of working for yourself is when vacations roll around it's not paid. The upside of painting for a living is the permanent vacation.    
    
    
    Only two more days until Vista Lights in Columbia, South Carolina!    
    
    
    If you want to buy and investment piece of my work...Thursday is the night to come to Vista Lights and see me in... http://fb.me/1ft2wbLxc     
    
    
    This is one of the abstract paintings that will be in the sale entitled: Botanicals. 24 x 24 and under $200!... http://fb.me/18aq9y3Gj     
    
    
    Inner Circle I, 24 x 24 will be be featured during Vista Lights for a fantastic price at the Gallery at Nonnah's... http://fb.me/100Novuak     
    
    
    If any of you remember when I first started selling my paintings on Devine Street in 2006, you might remember the... http://fb.me/OEVMtqse     
    
    
    Vista Lights is Thursday & I'll be selling geometric abstract paintings at blockbuster prices for the holidays..930 Gervais St. 29202    
    
    
    Plains, 24 x 24 Gallery wrapped, acrylic on canvas will be available during my Thanksgiving sale at the Gallery... http://fb.me/1tZyGkOwm     
    
    
    OK friends, you've told me you want to collect my work...Thursday is your day at Nonnah's in the Vista, Columbia, SC 930 Gervais Street!    
    
    
    It will almost be like a silent auction where you are the winning bidder and the prices are that good! Nonnah's 6 pm!    
    
    
    Cannot WAIT to set up Thursday at Nonnah's!! Excitement is building for a great show!    
    
    
    Busy, Busy Art week this week with two Shows Wednesday then a second on Thursday in Columbia, South Carolina.    
    
    
    Happy Mothers Day to all the mommies and plus the daddies who are Mr. Mom!    
    
    
    Realm of Possibility, 24 x 24, gallery wrapped. Available in less than 24 hours!! http://fb.me/RDKEjMgD     
    
    
    I've been posting a lot of abstract work on my page for the show this evening and you can see the paintings here... http://fb.me/1kBaOKjyv     
    
    
    Realm of Possibility, 24 x 24, acrylic on canvas will be available at the Gallery at Nonnah's During Vista Lights... http://fb.me/16Wj9DnIf     
    
    
    MY THANKSGIVING SALE STARTS TONIGHT!!    
    
    
    Heart Shaped Box, 24 x 24, gallery wrapped on canvas. Available at Nonnah's in the Vista tonight 6-10 pm. Jaw... http://fb.me/RB26heKR     
    
    
    You said you wanted to collect my work and I'm making that possible in a few hours with my Thanksgiving Sale at... http://fb.me/101cibVzb     
    
    
    Yaw'll, I am humbled and amazed at the amont of support I received this evening at the Gallery at Nonnah's in the... http://fb.me/1t3zrKHMp     
    
    
    Yaw'll, I am humbled and amazed at the amount of support I received this evening at the Gallery at Nonnah's in the... http://fb.me/LmT2ytdw     
    
    
    OK, I'm still feeling festive for the holidays, SO, I will have more news for you later today and how you can... http://fb.me/LSm1K72r     
    
    
    Great art sales at Nonnah's last night...closest I've come to selling out in a long time...will update you later with more Thanksgiving news    
    
    
    I love you #Square, #SqSupport! You make my life easy and simple!    
    
    
    Today at the Columbia Museum of Art. 10-4 there will be a lot of great artists showing their wares for the... http://fb.me/GhTkkBj1     
    
    
    Just found out about Google Calendar. Going to use it and you are going to love it! http://www.google.com/intl/en/googlecalendar/about.html    
    
    
    In the spirit of the holidays, I am continuing my sale at the Gallery at Nonnah's in the Vista. Art is the number... http://fb.me/1nNstrid5     
    
    
    The Artmobile is making deliveries today!    
    
    
    Tonight from 4-6. Hope to see you there! Rebecca Howser and Jodi Jenkins are hosting a local art sale at Rebecca... http://bit.ly/bmIwB2    
    
    
    Be there Thursday!! Great deals on art to be had! http://www.cayevent.com/Contemporaries_Artist_of_the_Year/Welcome.html    
    
    
    Next stop, Piccolo Spoleto Festival, USA!!    
    
    
    Need Art? Spruce up your walls with great buys at the Columbia Museum of Art's Contemporaries Artist of the Year Art Auction tonight 7-10 pm    
    
    
    Safe travels this holiay season my friends; may you an your family have a blessed holiday season filled with art and music!    
    
    
    The Charity Show in Charleston is already starting to get great publicity. Please stop by 438 King Street and... http://bit.ly/9OM6X2    
    
    
    Hope you al have a safe and Happy Thanksgiving!    
    
    
    Today is the date for the Worth Repeating Show of works by Walker Covin, Bill Davis and Alicia Leeke. There will... http://fb.me/O5PT8Le6    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/maryannhaven#!/media/set/?set=a.10150422669759105.377297.157659659104&type=1 … http://fb.me/1dRIvXjVj     
    
    
    Wilmington Art & Craft Show, Wilmington, NC
Thanksgiving Weekend:

Hours:
Saturday, November 26 
10:00 am ~ 5:00... http://fb.me/1sKflVwVt     
    
    
    Having my own Cyber Monday for the holidays! Any print 30 percent off framed or unframed. Monday only!... http://fb.me/PoUny6qP     
    
    
    Prints, like this one, are available from me on Cyber Monday!! Enjoy 30 percent savings today only on any signed... http://fb.me/Vk5HdCMh     
    
    
    Great show today. Thanks to all the people that came out to support the arts and original gifts for the holidays!!    
    
    
    Nothing says you care more than selecting an original piece of art or handmade work of art for the holidays! Give... http://fb.me/1mHhC32St     
    
    
    Just a week and 1/2 away from Piccolo Spoleto USA in Marion Square Park! Lots of art for sale by SC Artists!!    
    
    
    Getting ready for Festivus!    
    
    
    Affordable Christmas gifts for the holiday season right here in Charleston, SC! Opening Reception Thursday,... http://fb.me/1sHqQBiNp     
    
    
    TONIGHT IN CHARLESTON, SC...Art Reception at Michael Mitchell Gallery tonight 6 pm at 438 King Street! Great... http://fb.me/F9o6mUHT     
    
    
    Flash forward to Columbia! It's Festivus for the rest of us in Five Points in Columbia, SC Saturday from 4-8 pm!!... http://fb.me/LKj3zoiZ     
    
    
    Here's the map!... http://fb.me/13w71nQ5o     
    
    
    New discovery on the Mona Lisa?

http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/26184891/vp/45541410#45541410 …    
    
    
    http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2069571/Call-artistic-licence-Upper-East-Side-gallery-duped-buyer-paying-1 …... http://fb.me/1o9HM7wzD     
    
    
    Please come see my new body of abstract landscapes at Posh in Madison Hall on Gervais Street in Columbia, SC this... http://fb.me/1rXLNPeMw     
    
    
    http://www.nytimes.com/2011/12/05/arts/design/leonardo-da-vinci-blockbuster-at-national-gallery-in-london.html?_r=1 …... http://fb.me/xZT8Edj4     
    
    
    Don't forget I have wine totes for sale for the holidays and make great hostess gifts!! They are just $15 each... http://fb.me/12HYTz2tN     
    
    
    Please come out Thursday evening to take a look and do some holiday shopping. I will be showcasing my newest... http://fb.me/t5D3kJdn     
    
    
    What artists travel by: Check this video out -- bob marley http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nlk9Sj4Ns2k&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    Getting ready to paint new work! Stay tuned!    
    
    
    My artwork at Posh! Interiors on Gervais Street in Columbia, SC!! I have about nine pieces here. Mine are all the... http://fb.me/1kqEvtU1T     
    
    
    Here is a video clip from several of the artists that participated in the Charlotte Arts Festival. You can see... http://fb.me/NnwsMFdc     
    
    
    I am continuing my sale at the Gallery at Nonnah's in the Vista located at 930 Gervais Street in Columbia, SC. I... http://fb.me/1hOmLeOAj     
    
    
    Piccolo Spoleto USA starts Friday! Memorial Weekend. Please stop by as I will be unveiling new abstract paintings.... http://bit.ly/dk6AvE    
    
    
    This is the last shopping Saturday before Christmas and if you want to get a great deal on art this month, please... http://fb.me/XccWuRos     
    
    
    This is the last shopping Saturday before Christmas, so if you want to give original paintings, I'm running a... http://fb.me/10tUovODd     
    
    
    Desert Sunrise, part of the Holiday Sale at Nonnah's and one of the few miniature landscapes in the show and the... http://fb.me/TVD9M4ye     
    
    
    I still have mousepads, wine totes, greeting cards and a few scarves that can be purchased in time for the... http://fb.me/1rVtTKyJU     
    
    
    Corsica, painted prior to 2008 is a 24 x 24 gallery wrapped piece. http://fb.me/1zlt0pIL6     
    
    
    My sale will end Jan. 2, 2012. Extending for the holidays!    
    
    
    Wishing you all a happy, safe, healthy and most prosperous New Year! See you in 2012!    
    
    
    Apocalypse not now: 2012 doomsday predictions debunked by NASA: http://on.msnbc.com/sxSLqB  via @msnbc    
    
    
    Nice display of Degas drawings & pastels at the Phillips Museum in Washington DC. To me it shows how his mind worked to develop compositions    
    
    
    Announcing my online print sale! Signed and numbered, limited-edition prints of my work will be on sale starting... http://fb.me/I03GcjTW     
    
    
    The print sale continues.    
    
    
    Vintner's Harvest. Available framed or unframed. Approximately 18 x 24 framed. http://fb.me/IlIOksm7     
    
    
    Enchantee a Paris. One of the woks available in my print sale, now through Feb. 15, 2012.... http://fb.me/ZgIpwTKE     
    
    
    Is selling a lot of work in Charleston. Better see me in Marion Square Park if you want to buy some art as it's... http://bit.ly/9CajEN    
    
    
    http://www.alicialeeke.com/imageviewer.php?cat=cityscapes1&img=02 …

A Game of Boulle, 18 x 24, signed and numbered,... http://fb.me/XdvIJjrg     
    
    
    http://www.alicialeeke.com/imageviewer.php?cat=cityscapes1&img=03 …

Jardin du Luxembourg, 18 x 24 framed and... http://fb.me/1fdO9P0iO     
    
    
    http://www.alicialeeke.com/imageviewer.php?cat=cityscapes1&img=04 …

Summerville Flowertown Festival Run. Signed... http://fb.me/1ARQrsnSb     
    
    
    http://www.alicialeeke.com/imageviewer.php?cat=cityscapes1&img=05 …

Attendre Vous en Paris? 18 x 24 framed or... http://fb.me/1DEr4krPc     
    
    
    These guys need to be signed now!! Great new music release! http://soundcloud.com/popdeezmusic/hitnrun … by PopDeez!! New release as of yesteday folks!!    
    
    
    Check out this hot musician Popdeez with his new release of Hit and Run. It is fantastic!! http://soundcloud.com/popdeezmusic/hitnrun … #deeziac    
    
    
    http://www.alicialeeke.com/imageviewer.php?cat=cityscapes1&img=09 …

Print Sale through Valentines's Day. Email me... http://fb.me/1FZaoAbGo     
    
    
    My wine totes are now also available at Morganelli's in Forest Acres, South Carolina on Forest Drive. Hurry and... http://fb.me/NwenVaDV    
    
    
    http://www.alicialeeke.com/imageviewer.php?cat=cityscapes1&img=10 …

Bride at Pont Neuf, 18 x 24, signed and... http://fb.me/10385BLnY     
    
    
    http://www.alicialeeke.com/imageviewer.php?cat=cityscapes1&img=10 …
 
Bridge at Pont Neuf, 18 x 24, signed and... http://fb.me/yo8t6iAM     
    
    
    The Holy City, signed and numbered, limited edition print.... http://fb.me/11eKfImav     
    
    
    Today is the last day art and artists will be at Piccolo Spoleto's 2010 Art Festival in Marion Square Park. If you... http://bit.ly/cI3Vl4    
    
    
    http://t.co/yiLH9z0g

Stockholm. Artist Proof Print available. http://fb.me/1bZJuXfAx     
    
    
    Five O'clock Shadows, Artists proof available.

http://www.alicialeeke.com/imageviewer.php?cat=landscapes2&img=02 … http://fb.me/1Dc5Vslzy     
    
    
    Music to paint to!!   

The Cure - Just Like Heaven: http://youtu.be/RS_ux2H473I  via @youtube    
    
    
    Twitter peeps, I'm selling a lot of art show fixtures, garmet racks & other things. Hit me up if you have an interest @alicialeeke for pics.    
    
    
    A little inspiration: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_7I7iasuIdw&feature=pyv … http://fb.me/14LROXYMA     
    
    
    Working on new landscape paintings!    
    
    
    Only 14 more days left in my print sale. You can check out my website at http://www.alicialeeke.com  and see the images... http://fb.me/16wWKSYRn     
    
    
    Please join me at Wine Down 1520 Main Street, Suite 1 B in Columbia, South Carolina where I will be showing... http://fb.me/1lqViG2Xk     
    
    
    Wow, had great ROI on my Charleston exhibits and art showings. Getting ready to work on new paintings which I hope... http://fb.me/B9Uw627c    
    
    
    Tonight is the night to see some of my masterworks at Wine Down, a new venue located at 1520 Main Street, Suite 1... http://fb.me/1tw9h5NAy     
    
    
    See you at Wine Down for the First Thursday Art Walk between 6 and 6:30 -- until!    
    
    
    Time for a morning Paint-a-Thon!    
    
    
    If you have a painting you like of a bird, don't let anyone try & tell you to make the bird a peacock. It may end up looking like a buzzard.    
    
    
    Great inspirational day at the High Museum. Do not let this show pass you by. Get tickets ahead!    
    
    
    If you have tried to reach me regarding artwork, my phone port is not charging. Please leave a message or email... http://fb.me/1jKkjIsjJ     
    
    
    Looking forward to documenting the America Speaks event this Saturday with paint brushes in Columbia, SC.    
    
    
    Sometimes, it IS about winning.    
    
    
    I posted 8 photos on Facebook in the album "" http://fb.me/WXlbH8x9     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1e5cfevlY     
    
    
    I am running a special on my signed and numbered, limited-edition prints through Valentine's Day. Framed or... http://fb.me/1vBNGnefs     
    
    
    Please let me know if you are interested in updates on my next show via facebook or email:... http://fb.me/1LcvOwoec     
    
    
    Don't miss the FIRST MAJOR ART WORLD EVENT OF THE YEAR! It's the 13th annual POSTCARDS FROM THE EDGE benefit for... http://fb.me/GMoi1CxA    
    
    
    Happy Valentine's Day to all my collectors, friends, family and fellow artists!    
    
    
    I have been selected at the artist to paint the America Speaks event this Saturday at the Convention and Visitor's... http://fb.me/tHhveW1Q    
    
    
    I am having an invitation-only art showing this Thursday, February 23 for existing and potential art collectors... http://fb.me/1gHs5WM9p     
    
    
    WiS-TV just covered the America Speaks event in Columbia, SC tonight and my painting was on TV tonight. The... http://fb.me/BE6uUBwc    
    
    
    This is where my fear of flying began: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lwEclI_ffOA&feature=related … http://fb.me/15FBhdsAz     
    
    
    Come out tonight. About 90 artists have repurposed the City of Columbia's old parking meters and turned them into... http://fb.me/DJQo9yjT    
    
    
    What a great art showing tonight with new friends and existing customers. I am honored!!    
    
    
    http://www.nytimes.com/2012/02/24/arts/design/rembrandt-and-degas-at-the-metropolitan-museum-of-art.html?_r=1&ref=d …... http://fb.me/KHBDNuLY     
    
    
    http://www.ted.com/talks/anthony_atala_growing_organs_engineering_tissue.html http://on.ted.com/8QPY    
    
    
    http://mashable.com/2010/06/29/verizon-iphone-january/ Thanks @Mashable. That is why I never switched from Verizon.    
    
    
    Tweeter family, you might not want to use Foursquare to let everyone know where you will be and when you won't be home for security reasons.    
    
    
    Worth Repeating has a special sale on my prints this month. While supplies last. Please check out the large... http://fb.me/1qnZKii1Z     
    
    
    Fellow artisans and musicians, I am selling this cargo container which is great for long-term convention center... http://fb.me/1Eh52TMda     
    
    
    Interesting inverview with Josh Baer a few weeks back where he points out that artists like Richter and Warhol... http://fb.me/1HCRZVZab     
    
    
    Earlier I mentioned art was an investment. Here's proof! Citi Private Bank Art Advisry & Finance tracks art like stock http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OwhgDHoqx-w&context=C3b310fcADOEgsToPDskLIcRa6_TTTE-xthNDIaPo_ …    
    
    
    A peek into the 2012 Art Market: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OFKCwUvhDSE&feature=related    
    
    
    Great short film with a painter and canvas. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QQ00JSOYTaM … http://fb.me/1avqKd116     
    
    
    Please join me at my studio during Open Studios where art patrons and collectors can visit the studios of local... http://fb.me/1JLfHJ8HF     
    
    
    I will also be showing new work that same week during Artista Vista at the Gallery at Nonnah's 930 Gervais Street.... http://fb.me/PTC4lAK3     
    
    
    April 9, 2012.

I'm going to mark that down! It is a defining momement in my art career at this point where I... http://fb.me/1G87o6oYn     
    
    
    Just dropped off new works at Michael Mitchell Gallery at 438 King Street in Charleston, SC earlier this week... http://fb.me/CXiKgvBf    
    
    
    http://gallery80808.blogspot.com/2012/03/about-face-two-in-row.html …

Look forward to seeing fellow friends and... http://fb.me/RtYfWU3g     
    
    
    Only a few days left of my print sale at Worth Repeating for deals on framed and unframed prints!    
    
    
    Working on a huge abstract commission project this week!! So psyched!    
    
    
    The second show by the Columbia Museum of Art's affiliate group, About Face, will open this Saturday evening. http://fb.me/1Nz154XaJ     
    
    
    My 19 commissions large format abstract paintings are coming along nicely! Can't wait to photograph this body of work!    
    
    
    Twenty days and counting! Here is the map for the Open Studios Tour 2012.... http://fb.me/TSji7Sx5     
    
    
    Looking forward to being in Piccolo Spoleto again this year! The outdoor art show will run from Friday, May 25 to... http://fb.me/F2uhKQBp     
    
    
    Looking forward to being a juried artist into Piccolo Spoleto again this year! The outdoor art show will run from... http://fb.me/1JYaA7h7p     
    
    
    Phew! Finishing up the final details on my 19-piece abstract art commission for Michael Mitchell Gallery with... http://fb.me/KzVrldjG     
    
    
    @MarthaSteward While your in St. Pete do not miss the Chihuly show at the Morean Art Center...http://moreanartscenter.org/    
    
    
    The best art installation art exhibit of glass I have ever seen: http://moreanartscenter.org/    
    
    
    Is pleased that her new body of abstracts have positively received.    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/DTsRlHnn    
    
    
    http://www.freakingnews.com/Edgar-Degas-Pictures---1088.asp    
    
    
    Don't miss the opening reception this Friday, for the opening reception of the Trenholm Artists Guild annual... http://fb.me/WWRnVcE2     
    
    
    Today I am finishing up a triptych of the San Francisco Bay Bridge. It is an abstract, palette knife and... http://fb.me/1durWz4DY     
    
    
    Here is the guide for the 2012 Columbia Open Studios event April 21-22. Please be sure to visit my Columbia studio... http://fb.me/Z15wgly3     
    
    
    Oooh! Painting to Everlong by the Foo Fighters and Brass Monkey by the Beastie Boys! Diggin' Lithium on XM 34!... http://fb.me/1fqWhlrP5     
    
    
    NASA says Wind at Sea is Strangely Van Goghish.... http://fb.me/1y5VjCytN     
    
    
    Love is blind, but the neighbor's ain't!    
    
    
    WOW! Columbia Open Studios is in 8 days!    
    
    
    Focus on the journey, not the destination.    
    
    
    If you slow down, you will get there faster.    
    
    
    What an awesome art weekend with the TAG show at HoFP and the CAY event at the Columbia Museum of Art! Plus, lots... http://fb.me/1yzQjoXvC     
    
    
    Great painting track for late night! :) Nirvana Reggae!

Nirvana-Smells Like Teen Spirit(Reggae Version): http://youtu.be/-71W6omjHN4  via @youtube    
    
    
    Today is going to be another great art day! Getting ready for Open Studios next weekend in Columbia, South Carolina!    
    
    
    Getting ready for two shows in Columbia in early August. Join during the FOM Series on Main Street at the Columbia... http://fb.me/vMaVKUCp    
    
    
    I will be showing a new batch of abstract landscape paintings during Open Studios. These are hot off the brush... http://fb.me/1l8AFFUH0     
    
    
    Here are the directions to my Open Studio event this weekend:

http://www.701cca.org/2012/03/alicia-leeke-2/ … http://fb.me/vvNw9tbx     
    
    
    Here is a sneak peek of some of the smaller works I'll have at Open Studios this Saturday and Sunday. Remember,... http://fb.me/1Z4iULq80     
    
    
    Vote for Mark Plessinger from Frame of Mind in NRF's #ThisisRetail video contest! http://rpx.me/db6f     
    
    
    Getting ready for Columbia Open Studios 2012! Here is another of my mini works that will be on view.

Moss Tree,... http://fb.me/1BpAPANSm     
    
    
    This is one of my all time favorite abstract landscapes and it is one of the larger paintings I'll be showing... http://fb.me/1wkFFNOAm     
    
    
    Vote for Mark Plessinger from Frame of Mind in NRF's #ThisisRetail video contest! http://rpx.me/db6f     
    
    
    Working on a new batch of abstract paintings today.    
    
    
    For artists visiting my studio this weekend, I have about 6 copies left of Alyson Stanfield's book "I'd Rather Be... http://fb.me/1mxyggNFp     
    
    
    Don't forget, Open Studio's is this weekend!

Spring Colors, 10 x 10, acrylic on paper. http://fb.me/XmI3LTQw     
    
    
    If only everyone knew the behind the scenes of an Open Studio event. Ho Hum :) life is great!    
    
    
    Open Studios Saturday from 10 am to 6 pm! Come on by!    
    
    
    Vote for Mark Plessinger from Frame of Mind in NRF's #ThisisRetail video contest! http://rpx.me/db6f     
    
    
    OK! I have OVER 27 new pieces of art, both abstract (geometric) and abstract landscapes for your viewing and... http://fb.me/1rNbCxw8m     
    
    
    Here is one of the special little abstracts in my show. It has companion pieces and this piece has not been... http://fb.me/XXV0fLpp     
    
    
    Vote for Mark Plessinger from Frame of Mind in NRF's #ThisisRetail video contest! http://rpx.me/db6f     
    
    
    A good friend of mine asked me earlier yesterday what is an Open Studio. Good question. It's where an artist... http://fb.me/1VU5Dc13O     
    
    
    Open Studio today for me from 10 am - 6 pm! Come early as some of the new abstract work went fast yesterday! Refreshments served!    
    
    
    Vote for Mark Plessinger from Frame of Mind in NRF's #ThisisRetail video contest! http://rpx.me/db6f     
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/#!/events/281552578523344/ …

Today is the final day of the studio crawl and your only... http://fb.me/AeTAPIUw     
    
    
    Thanks to everyone that came out to my Open Studio event this weekend. I know there was a lot going on this... http://fb.me/1XsaAU1jl     
    
    
    Dear friends, you may have seen this story on WIS-TV, but some friends of mine are gathering together for a... http://fb.me/1sNDIR4DK     
    
    
    Getting ready for Vista Lights tomorrow night at the Gallery at Nonnah's!!    
    
    
    Getting ready for Artista Vista tomorrow night at the Gallery at Nonnah's!    
    
    
    Here's a little history on Artista Vista! http://www.artistavista.com/about.aspx  http://fb.me/JTVOAnyD     
    
    
    Secrets of the Most Productive People I Know http://www.inc.com/margaret-heffernan/most-productive-people-i-know-secrets.html … via @Inc    
    
    
    Make every second count: MSN Video: Every Second Counts - Short Films Trailer http://www.bing.com/videos/watch/video/every-second-counts-short-films-trailer/20fl5yii …    
    
    
    Artista Vista is tonight!! Viva la Vista!! I'll be at 930 Gervais Street in the Gallery at Nonnah's!!    
    
    
    Of course, money can't buy you love, but it can buy art you love! -- Alicia Leeke    
    
    
    The White Stripes - 'Seven Nation Army': http://youtu.be/0J2QdDbelmY  via @youtube Good art party music!    
    
    
    The Horrors - 'Who Can Say': http://youtu.be/yNjcSgU0Nrg  via @youtube    
    
    
    Just Like Heaven Lyrics: http://youtu.be/B0N9yFcz4ho  via @youtube    
    
    
    If you have any experience using the new Droid or a verizon air card for internet. Tweet me @alicialeeke. Would like to know your experience    
    
    
    Art for Charity Kick Off is this coming Friday! http://fb.me/1hDODDn26     
    
    
    The White Stripes - 'Seven Nation Army': http://youtu.be/0J2QdDbelmY  via @youtube    
    
    
    Hello friends, if you received a direct tweet from me, do not open it. My account was hacked and I rarely, ever send emails much less spam.    
    
    
    Getting ready for the Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Exhibit 2012.... http://fb.me/23FQw8lkE     
    
    
    Debating to move to the Droid. Checked the Storm and returned it. Check this video out -- Droid X Review http://youtu.be/aMW-5rfqXtw    
    
    
    The 52 Window's event is tonight and I have a window in the show for purchase to help a great cause. Show starts... http://fb.me/10SNvKwC7     
    
    
    Hope, 30 x 30, acrylic on reclaimed window pane for the MIRCI 52 Windows Gala. Available for puchase. Starting... http://fb.me/10BZyWrHj     
    
    
    The event is tonight!!

https://www.facebook.com/MIRCISC  http://fb.me/1DVCTcZXe     
    
    
    Starts in less than 3 hours! Get your tickets!!

http://columbiametro.com/Columbia-Metro/May-2012/52-Windows-of-Hope/ … http://fb.me/ZfvSp9mR     
    
    
    Less than a week for showtime at the Museum and I will have several new works available. Hope you can make it out... http://fb.me/CF92HgJp    
    
    
    Next Stop Michael Mitchell Gallery, 438 King Street, Charleston, SC. I will be painting Friday night from 6-8 pm!... http://fb.me/1pINPWEhM     
    
    
    http://www.charlestonmag.com/charleston_magazine/photogallery/art_for_charity_kick_off_party … http://fb.me/16fsAPFLv     
    
    
    Twitter Hacked again. I don't send direct tweets from Twitter, so ignore and do not open any direct twitter messages!    
    
    
    Paint-a-thon in progress!    
    
    
    I love working on a painting to a point of it almost being completed and walking away for the day. My favorite... http://fb.me/1SzEDMdAT     
    
    
    I have adorned a silk necktie for the Family Ties" event on May 20th to benefit Family Service Center in... http://fb.me/1CV3rr0XC     
    
    
    Here is the info for the Family Service Center May 20 event! http://fb.me/1mAP3KFQp     
    
    
    Co-hosted the Blues show on WUSC FM in SC with Clair DeLune. If you missed it, here is the play list: http://bluesmoonradio.blogspot.com/    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1oogMg0rg     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1T7sA54NQ     
    
    
    Lots of new stuff on the brush!! Getting ready for Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Show in Marion Square 2012!    
    
    
    I am space number 39 to the right of the Calhoun Monument and behind the performance stage!! http://fb.me/1kJegVucQ     
    
    
    Philiosophies, acrylic on paper, by South Carolina Artist Alicia Leeke. This painting can be viewed next week at... http://fb.me/1RS2ZFgDZ     
    
    
    Hope you can come out to my art show at the Columbia Museum of Art at the Corner of Main and Taylor Streets... http://fb.me/DNzusV1u    
    
    
    'Mini Monet': Boy of 8 sells paintings for $235,803 http://bit.ly/dxJLFg    
    
    
    I am excited to have my art juried into the Digital Graffiti Spontaneous ArtRageous Project and have it projected... http://fb.me/JXflfAFh    
    
    
    While I was painting just after lunch today working on a new triptych titled "La Bamba," I became very aware of... http://fb.me/1dKBC8xRI     
    
    
    Rose Colored Glasses, acrylic on paper will be on view during the Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Exhibit in Marion... http://fb.me/1CsD76kXz     
    
    
    Thank you to my friends and patrons that came out to the Columbia Museum of Art Show Thursday. There was a... http://fb.me/D5JrW5nq    
    
    
    Thank you WLTX Channel 19 for the coverage! http://www.wltx.com/news/local/story.aspx?storyid=93140&catid=2    
    
    
    Don't forget that my work is also on display during Spoleto at Michael Mitchell Gallery, 438 King Street in... http://fb.me/1TG0VXw76     
    
    
    Wishing you all a Happy, Prosperous and artsy New Year!    
    
    
    Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Festival!!!! WOO HOO. Showing all new work!    
    
    
    So far, the rain has held out during the day for the Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Exhibit, so come on down and browse a lot of great art!    
    
    
    I will by painting at Michael Mitchell Gallery tonight during the Susan Komen Art for Charity fundraiser tonight... http://fb.me/HPHMkRdC     
    
    
    Setting dates for new fall art shows!    
    
    
    Last week for the Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor.Art Show!    
    
    
    Professional artists are working rain or shine during the Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Show in Marion Square Park! Nuff said!    
    
    
    It's beautiful weather in Marion Square for the Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Festival. I will be painting in the park again today!    
    
    
    Misty Lake, acrylic on paper. http://fb.me/1ATvcsqN7     
    
    
    Tall Grasses, acrylic on paper. http://fb.me/20rqQvwDm     
    
    
    Today is the last day we'll be in the park for the Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Festival in Marion Square.... http://fb.me/15Jww5nmf     
    
    
    What a great show at Piccolo Spoleto 2012! Looking forward to next year!

River Sunrise, acrylic on paper. http://fb.me/17PnWhTi9     
    
    
    Hey, if you've tried to text me or call me I've been without a phone the last several days and I didn't get your... http://fb.me/1IgtBbkut     
    
    
    Using Facebook more and more for all business with success.    
    
    
    @cbsatl thanks for the follow. Feel free to call or email if you ever need a source.    
    
    
    Support Ronald McDonald House by buying art Aug. 26 from 5:30 - 8:30 pm @ 701 Whaley St Columbia, SC Tickets $15 ea/ $25 couple 803-254-0118    
    
    
    Coolio! Miracle Film Turns Any Surface into a Touchscreen http://mashable.com/2010/08/17/displax-skin/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Hope all the dads have been having a great day!    
    
    
    I just heard the greatest line!!

You can either wait...or create!

I love it!    
    
    
    I have been doing some personal development as the summer solstice is generally a tad bit slower part of the year... http://fb.me/J6fVxrU1     
    
    
    Beach Thistles, acrylic on paper. http://fb.me/2dSerRZsy     
    
    
    http://fb.me/15BosZLt5     
    
    
    Painting a commission to this great song! http://fb.me/tl4E9Vxq     
    
    
    My guided tour of the Picasso to Warhol Exhibit at the High Museum of Art in Atlanta, GA. http://fb.me/OTmIIaht     
    
    
    Be like Nike! http://fb.me/1EfWForgg     
    
    
    The other day I posted pics from the Picasso to Warhol show I attended in Atlanta, Georgia earlier this year. In... http://fb.me/1TkHjuA5F     
    
    
    At Boone Hall, acrylic on paper by Alicia Leeke. http://fb.me/1uqHNTstB     
    
    
    Happy Independence Day! Remember to keep your pets inside! Have a safe time out there!    
    
    
    Christmas in July Print Sale! 
Details at: https://www.facebook.com/#!/events/240394149413800/ …    
    
    
    Getting ready to sign a new Gallery contract soon!    
    
    
    Available at Michael Mitchell, 438 King Street, Charleston, SC. http://fb.me/1MYYx5chc     
    
    
    A Sense of Place: McKissick Museum's 2012 Art Exhibition | McKissick Museum http://fb.me/1aEppJ1c4     
    
    
    Indigo Palm, 24 x 20 is one of the prints included in my Christmas in July Print Sale. It is double matted and is... http://fb.me/1bB9oRpDv     
    
    
    Bistro Street Scene, 24 x 20 also included in my Christmas in July Print Sale. It is double matted and is a... http://fb.me/234O8KQqb     
    
    
    Love, 24 x 20 is one of the prints included in my Christmas in July Print Sale. It is double matted and is a... http://fb.me/1xYYf6JIf     
    
    
    Summerville Flowertown Festival Run, 24 x 20, signed and numbered, limited-edition print. In the Christmas in... http://fb.me/29gpRsTmL     
    
    
    The Holy City, 24 x 20, signed and numbered, limited-edition print. Available framed or unframed in the Christmas... http://fb.me/1hvTC8Pzt     
    
    
    Plimsouls "A Million Miles Away" 45rpm: http://youtu.be/klX77CEzh1I  via @youtube    
    
    
    Psychedelic furs- Heaven: http://youtu.be/I_O90A0G8lA  via @youtube    
    
    
    I will be accepting painting commissions now through August 31. After that, it's show season and I will only be... http://fb.me/2hQGvphib     
    
    
    Deja Vu, 24 x 20. Artist's Proof Print in my Christmas in July Sale Event. http://fb.me/1UTbsI2ak     
    
    
    Adluh Flour 24 x 20. I'm adding this piece to the Christmas in July Sale. http://fb.me/1aQ9JHN0v     
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/events/260539337393196/ … http://fb.me/1c4AnMAe7     
    
    
    Daybreak, Artists Proof Print. Part of my Christmas in July print sale! Currently unframed, but framing options... http://fb.me/1WjXGLzLi     
    
    
    Meracages, 20 x 18, signed and numbered, limited-edition print. http://fb.me/1NudCx4dv     
    
    
    Getting ready for additional gallery representation!    
    
    
    Prima Ballerina, 20 x 20 is a signed and numbered, limited-edition print available in my Christmas in July print... http://fb.me/1A9leqymE     
    
    
    This is my first collaborative work. and is in the 2nd Annual Silent Auction Fundraiser with S&S Art Gallery. It... http://fb.me/1uK8g2PdR     
    
    
    Also available tomorrow from 2-6 at the S&S Art Supply Auction tomorrow benefitting a good cause! http://fb.me/1ed3YNBUC     
    
    
    Don't forget to go by S&S Art Supply and support this great event and pick up some artwork too!... http://fb.me/DkQyuC7E     
    
    
    Ibearan Wilderness 18 x 20, unframed. Signed and numbered, limited-edition print available in my Christmas in... http://fb.me/1utuWoNPC     
    
    
    High Cotton, 18 x 24, signed and numbered limited-edition print also available in my Chrstmas in July Sale! http://fb.me/16mr0OAgq     
    
    
    If you're in Charleston tonight, please come to the preview party for "Artists Helping Artists" event at the... http://fb.me/FT9Y76dD    
    
    
    Marshlands II, 18 x 24 signed and numbered, limited-edition print part of the Christmas in July sale. http://fb.me/sF48ApTN     
    
    
    These homes have curve appeal...http://on-msn.com/NVmito via @MSNRealEstate    
    
    
    Ibearian Wilderness, 18 x 24, signed and numbered, limited-edition print part of my Christmas in July Print Sale. http://fb.me/2aKR1ZyTq     
    
    
    Never tire of this song!  Gotye - Somebody That I Used To Know (feat. Kimbra) - official video: http://youtu.be/8UVNT4wvIGY  via @youtube    
    
    
    Love Kimbra too!  "Settle Down": http://youtu.be/yHV04eSGzAA  via @youtube    
    
    
    Simply the best interview of a great actor: Inside The Actors Studio - Johnny Depp: http://youtu.be/XgvgO5f0nSw  via @youtube    
    
    
    Two more men with HIV now virus-free. Is this a cure?: http://bit.ly/Oqp6m8  via @msnbc    
    
    
    Amelia Island Marsh, 5 x 5 available framed or unframed. Signed and numbered, limited-edition print that's part... http://fb.me/1Ha3u8qPY     
    
    
    Selling a few supplies from my studio: GBC Ultra Clear 100 pieces laminating film by Alicialeeke http://etsy.me/N8T5Lh  via @Etsy    
    
    
    Selling off some studio supplies on Etsy. Avery Note Cards 8315 60 cards/envelopes 2 cards by Alicialeeke http://etsy.me/OuF1zV  via @Etsy    
    
    
    Opening one week from today! http://fb.me/2bP2yHqeQ     
    
    
    Selling off a few studio supplis including this pack of GBC Heat Seal Menu Size Laminating FIlm: Alicialeeke http://etsy.me/OrE8bn  via @Etsy    
    
    
    Cherry Grove, 5 x 5 unframed and 11 x 11 framed. This is one of my all time favorite pieces. It is my memory of... http://fb.me/1O55DTyZB     
    
    
    Most dangerous beaches: http://local.msn.com/travel/slideshow.aspx?cp-documentid=252817657#scptmt …    
    
    
    Red Light District 18 x 24, signed and numbered, limited edition print. This is the last day of my Christmas in... http://fb.me/1Yus37GXa     
    
    
    Don't forget to come to the Open Reception today at Best Matress on Devine Street in Columbia. The event runs... http://fb.me/1fOdHKLlu     
    
    
    Great article on MSN Money: 10 ideas that each made $100 million http://on-msn.com/yFB1p4  via @MSN_Money    
    
    
    I am producing a totally new body of work and am so psyched! It's the hottest thing since the invention of fire for me! Launches in 4thQ!    
    
    
    I am ever so thankful to be an artist in the 21st Century. I would not have done well in earlier times! Art... http://fb.me/28Pk1oe4u     
    
    
    Today I spent most of the day learning to can in a class offered by the Clemson Extension Service on pressure... http://fb.me/24U07NkEl     
    
    
    Controversy in the Olympics: http://msn.foxsports.com/olympics/gallery/Controversies-at-2012-London-Olympics-Lolo-Jones-Hope-Solo-073012#tab=photo-title=Cheap+shot%2521&photo=31252619 …    
    
    
    I'm selling two drafting tables in Columbia, SC. First come-first served $100 each. http://fb.me/1A2uRFs2l     
    
    
    In New York City Tonight:  Postcards from the Edge Preview Party, from 6-8 PM

Benefit Sale is this Weekend!  Jan... http://fb.me/I40adepn    
    
    
    In New York City Tonight: Postcards from the Edge Preview Party, from 6-8 PM

Tonight! Sneak Peek: The only... http://fb.me/RljPOy0g    
    
    
    Journey into the Soul, acrylic on paper. Available for purchase. http://fb.me/1wtKtqMtf     
    
    
    This week is going to be an awesome week of creativity!    
    
    
    Autumn, 36 x 24, acrylic on canvas. http://fb.me/uTXtKAOO     
    
    
    Autumn, 36 x 24, acrylic on canvas.    
    
    
    Study: Japan nuclear disaster caused mutated butterflies http://worldnews.nbcnews.com/_news/2012/08/14/13274288-study-japan-nuclear-disaster-caused-mutated-butterflies#.UCqKCms1vfc.twitter … via @NBCNewsWorld    
    
    
    http://todayentertainment.today.com/_news/2012/08/01/13073319-missing-4-million-lichtenstein-painting-turns-up-in- …... http://fb.me/25AV5kHdA     
    
    
    Well, according to this site, Jack Black and I share the same birth day. http://people.famouswhy.com/jack_black/ ... http://fb.me/2m7e4RA7e     
    
    
    Hope to see you this Saturday night: https://www.facebook.com/alicia.leeke?ref=tn_tnmn#!/events/340433726046429/ … http://fb.me/1SGOQSRiQ     
    
    
    This painting will be in the Art Show tomorrow evening. We hope you can make it by. HHuntArt, 2615 River Drive,... http://fb.me/VeTXz0NJ     
    
    
    This 4 x 6 painting that was accepted into the Postcards from the Edge show is called Solitary Passion and was... http://fb.me/ssGwv1Mr    
    
    
    What a surpirsingly good turn out to the art show last night for a holiday weekend. Thanks to everyone that came out!    
    
    
    http://www.nytimes.com/2012/09/03/arts/design/growth-in-online-art-market-brings-more-fraud.html?_r=1&pagewanted=2 …... http://fb.me/1vazgOYi2     
    
    
    Getting ready to launch a new fall line! Can't wait!    
    
    
    This is an absolutely amazing documentary about a New York City fashion photographer. It's free to watch on HULU.... http://fb.me/1zk3VfldL     
    
    
    Check this video out -- The Joy of a Salesman http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cVLAvix-dX0 … via @youtube    
    
    
    5 mind-bending facts about dreams  http://www.mnn.com/health/fitness-well-being/stories/5-mind-bending-facts-about-dreams …    
    
    
    The real truth about cats; they become doglike when it is snowing & icy. After that, forget you, it's all about them again.    
    
    
    Art is a great investment!... http://fb.me/sBD2tloh     
    
    
    I recently finished some new landscape paintings but I've also created some new items for the holidays which you... http://fb.me/2qy550KeC     
    
    
    See you all Sunday! I will be painting on the trail along the banks of the Saluda for Unearth. http://fb.me/1iErHbQM0     
    
    
    Remember, I keep telling you about the value of investing in artwork.... http://fb.me/JYDgf26X     
    
    
    I love it when stolen paintings are found!... http://fb.me/1v9PMxW48     
    
    
    Thrilled with the new artwork I created for the Lake Carolina's 2013 Wine Festival on October 13!    
    
    
    You can buy tickets for the Lake Carolina Wine Festival here: Purchase tickets here http://www.lakecarolinawineandfood.com/     
    
    
    This is this year's poster for the 2013 Lake Carolina Wine Festival. The original will be for sale during the... http://fb.me/13Dk6VNEq     
    
    
    Don't forget to get your tickets to the Lake Carolina Food and Wine Festvial here: http://www.lakecarolinawineandfood.com/     
    
    
    I am selling this art shipping container 4 x 4 x 8 feet on casters. Fits standard freight elevators. $495.00... http://fb.me/2fR30qnqe     
    
    
    This is a great show. Check it out if you haven't been by there! http://fb.me/2m0tRzpxF     
    
    
    I'm not so sure cloning a woolly mammoth is such as good idea. http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/49304338/ns/technology_and_science-science/ …    
    
    
    Today was a great art day! Be sure to check out the art (and make the trip upstairs) to see all the great... http://fb.me/2sHFLU4UF     
    
    
    "God works wonders in mysterious ways" I used to always hear when I was growing up as a child; and "beware of the... http://fb.me/1hGAwjuqV     
    
    
    What a great evening dinner with friends! They confirmed my suspicions and dreams on this new body of work!!... http://fb.me/21Cjk9RYN     
    
    
    Great article and good for team building:... http://fb.me/AnauyaDI     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1NCmaKRZy     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1hvekS16W     
    
    
    There is nothing more satisfying than knowing you did a good job on a painting. That is how I feel about the 2012... http://fb.me/2gBx4OKzj     
    
    
    I keep telling you all to buy art as an investment. Don't take it from me. Read this article about Eric Clapton... http://fb.me/1PHRnKQUf     
    
    
    Hot new retail trend is partnering artists w/dying malls. If they'd kept retail rents reasonable, they wouldn't have vacancies now.    
    
    
    And, consumers are buying American-made products and products manufactured stateside. Green was 2008's trend folks.    
    
    
    Off to bed for a fresh face for more autograph signings in the morning!    
    
    
    Oh, one last thought, The Retail report says Entrepreneurs to Turn Economy around. After all, there are hot new product launches going on!    
    
    
    I love the Met and this is good news!... http://fb.me/26yKiasvo     
    
    
    I love the Met and this is good news!... http://fb.me/2oHh3Ij1g     
    
    
    I love the Met and this is good news!... http://fb.me/1JuGxtL7Z     
    
    
    I love the Met and this is good news!... http://fb.me/YxwnNTUp     
    
    
    I love the Met and this is good news!... http://fb.me/TqJJsXI6     
    
    
    I love the Met and this is good news!... http://fb.me/2iNOXBKvl     
    
    
    Investors are diversifying their portfolios with art, photography, motorcycles, stamps to name a few:... http://fb.me/2fXO4vqTC     
    
    
    Happy Halloween!    
    
    
    Getting a new body of work ready for exhibition later this month. Can't wait!    
    
    
    A Facebook friends is awaiting a heart transplant. Please consider bidding on a signed and numbered,... http://fb.me/z9frsbTT    
    
    
    Last Call a signed and numbered limited-editon print, framed. Opening bid $150 for the framed piece. If you can... http://fb.me/IfP12TO1    
    
    
    Please join me in a cause for a friend in need of a heart transplant. Pledges starting at $25 will receive a small Last Call print.    
    
    
    It will be interesting to see how this pans out with Macy's. http://lifeinc.today.com/_news/2012/11/14/15161859-macys-urged-to-dump-trump-from-ads-or-else …    
    
    
    Anyone know who has best prices on the Blackberry Storm or new Iphone G32 & if the Storm has a app for credit card processing?    
    
    
    Just back from the AMC show in Atlanta; retailers are restocking product. Good sign for the economy.    
    
    
    Anyone have experience with credit card apps/processing on the Iphone? Please DM me.    
    
    
    Can anyone tell me about their experience pos or neg with authorize.com? DM alicialeeke thanks!    
    
    
    Blackberry Tour vs. IPhone. Which is better?    
    
    
    @mashable Thanks for the 411 on Google Voice    
    
    
    This just in from @mashable Google just sent out a wave of Google Voice invites. Neat video on how Google Voice works: http://bit.ly/c2tai    
    
    
    Check this video out -- BlackBerry Storm vs iPhone 3G, Part 2 - Messaging & Keyboard http://bit.ly/15oHj6    
    
    
    Comparison of the Iphone vs. Blackberry. http://bit.ly/X9OvN    
    
    
    Be sure to go to Columbia Museum of Art for scarves, The Gallery at Nonnah's, Tombo Grille in Columbia, Michael... http://fb.me/1I9YNfkeF     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1oElf17h6     
    
    
    Research on the 3Gs Iphone: this seems to be the only issue http://bit.ly/2kwpj    
    
    
    If you can hold out on a new Blackberry: http://bit.ly/AamTo    
    
    
    Anyone have experience with credit card processing on the Blackberry Storm?    
    
    
    PC World review on Smartphones: http://bit.ly/bj958    
    
    
    Consider these facts when buying a smart phone. Chart by PC World on 3G providers: http://bit.ly/HAwhm    
    
    
    Remember to buy original art today for Small Business Saturday! That means when you see art at Big Box Stores and... http://fb.me/CuxXtfdG     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1Mjm3JoHR     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1ps7ELxXR     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/wLhhjIyI     
    
    
    This is a mini of mine. Only 5 x 5 gallery wrapped...a perfect stocking stuffer at $65!! http://fb.me/1Hy1yRq9X     
    
    
    The only other little mini stocking stuffer for the holidays. GO GAMECOCKS! http://fb.me/ADkyI9Zr     
    
    
    This is pretty cool cinemaphotography: http://www.youtube.com/watch_popup?v=KcuDdPo0WZk … http://fb.me/1OCFSDZIu     
    
    
    This gets me in the Christmas spirit. Can't wait to see all the homes!! http://www.midlandsbiz.com/articles/12652/  http://fb.me/1nlSvicp9     
    
    
    The Iphone 3Gs, Should you get it? http://bit.ly/AvC8C
 Great article.    
    
    
    @abstanfield I use Godaddy for hosting and they have great customer service. Hope that helps.    
    
    
    WOW! I just received back the final piece I created for a commission for a super-secret Christmas present for one... http://fb.me/1HEi3ln4X     
    
    
    Anyone have any experience with credit card processing on the Blackberry Storm?    
    
    
    Bloggers beware: Article from Cnet and webware http://bit.ly/JRwxh    
    
    
    @KyNamDoan Great article, Thanks for sharing: Study Finds Correlation Between Social Media and Financial Success http://bit.ly/n8W9w    
    
    
    Looking for inexpensive and secure based credit card solutions for phone and laptop. DM me if you currently use any plus your experience.    
    
    
    @Laurie_Henry I am interested in knowing more. Haven't purchased a device yet.    
    
    
    @moorjames Do you have a comparison chart for credit card processing?    
    
    
    @byronwells Thanks for posting that simplified answer on Affiliate Marketing.    
    
    
    Check this video out -- What is Affiliate Marketing? http://bit.ly/1FYxuy    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Affiliate Marketing in a Nutshell http://bit.ly/SkSSi
 From an advertising standpoint.    
    
    
    Who doesn't like an art bargain. What a great find at a thrift store!... http://fb.me/wEcCelgd     
    
    
    Along the Intercoastal Waterway, signed Artists Proof. http://fb.me/1vKs9dj1V     
    
    
    HP Customer Service, please hold, Let me transfer you...hold more 11 minutes. only for them to ask me the same questions 2 times x 2 people.    
    
    
    I recommend companies gladly that have exceptional customer service, like Go Daddy...TQM with follow up surveys.    
    
    
    This is the last monotype I have in stock of Mount Pleasant. It was painted on glass and the print was... http://fb.me/2fbE6Xuvt     
    
    
    Using Twitter more for business purposes. I'm becoming a techno, info junkie.    
    
    
    Now taking orders for my wine totes. They make great hostess gifts for the holidays! They hold a 12 pack or two... http://fb.me/CLuy2QPh     
    
    
    BTW, HP Customer Support...after 30 minutes... says go to hp.com. They must have gotten their customer service training from Time Warner.    
    
    
    @brandingexpert I heard he? Just resigned within the week.    
    
    
    Along the Potomac. Matted and framed, signed and numbered, limited-edition print. http://fb.me/D5feU6Ns     
    
    
    Getting together a new body of work inspired by "Winter"    
    
    
    What artists eat for lunch: Brugger's Bagel: Cheddar/Jalapino bagel toasted, spinach egg omlette, ham, lettuce, tomato, onion. No condiments    
    
    
    As an artist myself, I want to meet the artist who created: The Crevasse-Making of 3D Street Art http://bit.ly/uMEam    
    
    
    Winter, 40 x 30. http://fb.me/v0kkyIC2     
    
    
    http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2211849/Have-Mona-Lisa-Archaeologists-reveal-TWO-new-female-skeleto …... http://fb.me/25djaqBSA     
    
    
    I can tell you most anything you want to know about smart phones vs. reg. cell phones and how to process credit cards now. Out of kindness.    
    
    
    Thankful I am not writing a column on smart phones. Twitter is 1 line. Read my posts when making a smart phone decision. Posts are accurate.    
    
    
    Keep in mind, in life, you get what you pay for. Some things are definately worth it and some, well just aren't.    
    
    
    @anunquietmind Boy was that statement well said: Holding a grudge is letting someone live rent-free in your head.    
    
    
    Feeling less technologically challenged today; & Wow! Just when you think you're getting Twitter, you find out more interesting stuff.    
    
    
    Living on West Coast time on the East Coast today.    
    
    
    http://www.forbes.com/sites/kathryntully/2012/12/09/the-steady-rise-of-fine-art-photography/ … http://fb.me/2ioj01c7P     
    
    
    http://www.forbes.com/sites/kathryntully/2012/12/09/the-steady-rise-of-fine-art-photography/ … http://fb.me/2hq66osfI     
    
    
    Making a list and checking it twice.    
    
    
    http://www.facebook.com/home.php#!/video/video.php?v=1696297439874&oid=178385275507167&comments http://fb.me/SDhGLuin    
    
    
    Just disassembled my first "large" painting for shipping to a customer in Europe! I now have collectors in... http://fb.me/1TraBOvJI     
    
    
    Just disassembled my first "large" painting for shipping to a customer in Europe! I now have collectors in... http://fb.me/Wx91xmdu     
    
    
    Just disassembled my first "large" painting for shipping to a customer in Europe! I now have collectors in... http://fb.me/1W7SWNG5O     
    
    
    Need a stocking stuffer idea for Christmas? I have boxed sets of greeting cards containing 8 cards per box with... http://fb.me/2BBvOucIx     
    
    
    It's a shame you can't advertise on Craigslist anymore without every reply being spam.    
    
    
    What do you think about your followers protecting their tweets? Do you return the follow if they follow you first?    
    
    
    I just had the most incredible, positive customer service with Delta! They are awesome! Fly Delta!    
    
    
    Like Indian food, but don't have time to dine out? Try this new product Ethnic Gourmet Chicken Tikka Masala. Taste is awesome from a box!    
    
    
    @Laurie_Henry Let me get through the trial process on the Storm prior to cc.Also, many people have storms don't know about that capability.    
    
    
    If you need a last minute gift idea, I have gift certificates available in amounts from $20 and up! Inbox me and I'll hook you up!    
    
    
    If you need a last minute gift idea, I have gift certificates available in amounts starting at $20! Inbox me and I'll hook you up!    
    
    
    Merry Christmas everyone!    
    
    
    Anyone know any sources for used ata road cases?    
    
    
    Here's the 411 on my phone selection. Doing a trial on the Blackberry Storm vs the Iphone. Reason: Verizon vs. signal strength.    
    
    
    Anyone know any sources for used ATA road cases?    
    
    
    Despite having sinus issues the past four weeks, this has been an extremely creative month. I have three new... http://fb.me/2gpD5UqzT     
    
    
    Thanks to the people who came out to Brian's event. Last Call sold, but smaller prints are still available.    
    
    
    Checking my grid and making adjustments to scale and correcting the drawing for accuracy on this weeks commission. http://fb.me/2q2Qh9OHy     
    
    
    I just went to the Member Opening of Impressionism from Monet to Matisse last night and am passing on my personal... http://fb.me/295shr8ru     
    
    
    I just went to the Member Opening of Impressionism from Monet to Matisse last night and am passing on my personal... http://fb.me/TE0SdpA7     
    
    
    Please join me at Worth Repeating in West Columbia for their Holiday Open House where I will be signing wine... http://fb.me/KJBWHV0c    
    
    
    Vote to give this idea $250K: Train a new generation of artisans    
    
    
    http://www.refresheverything.com/search/?q=acba Vote to give this idea $250 K. Train a new generation of artisans.    
    
    
    Took the past few days from painting to clean the studio and declutter for my Spring Shows. That was work, but it... http://fb.me/1tFgZc1P4     
    
    
    Here is the link to the items I'm selling:... http://fb.me/E9M7zHlm     
    
    
    Who's checking your credit; you might be surprised...http://on-msn.com/eSbV2X    
    
    
    We love fans; please consider liking: http://www.facebook.com/pages/Alicia-Leeke-American-Contemporary-Painter-Official-Site/54036227159    
    
    
    Arts Commission will not go quietly The Post and Courier, Charleston SC - News /  Entertainment http://www.postandcourier.com/news/2011/jan/21/arts-commission-will-not-go-quietly/ … via @postandcourier    
    
    
    Mark your calendars now to see where I create my art during the 2013 Open Studio's tour Sat. March 22 10-6 and... http://fb.me/1kFWgMjVe     
    
    
    Artists, gallery friends and retailers, I'm selling this greeting card stand. Great deal at $125. http://fb.me/Es1a4WgT     
    
    
    WOO HOO! I just got my ArtFields 2013 acceptance! Looking forward to participating since I have family and friends... http://fb.me/ALk8pJdC     
    
    
    http://money.msn.com/auto-insurance/10-things-your-auto-insurer-will-not-say.aspx?page=2 Great article!    
    
    
    Trying to increase awareness on my Facebook business page for people who are interested in my work please "like" http://tinyurl.com/62a7u8h    
    
    
    Just received notification that I was juried into the 2011 Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Juried Show!! YAY!! Official... http://fb.me/NAclKQMr    
    
    
    Art market boom next 10 years? Count me in!

http://video.cnbc.com/gallery/?video=3000146797 … http://fb.me/24z2RMqDJ     
    
    
    2 seconds ago.

Spent last night painting and changing the wall color for Open Studios which is about a... http://fb.me/1lKyUydK5     
    
    
    I'm having a fun experimenting this week working on three collage works of art on glass. It's nice to be able to... http://fb.me/1VVxssGMV     
    
    
    Join me today from 10-4 at the S.C. State Museum for Art Day. I will be doing a demo of a landscape. This isbmy primed background pictured.    
    
    
    Priming the canvas. http://fb.me/1ZQfdUVNT     
    
    
    Art Day Demo! http://fb.me/ElmMQMeb     
    
    
    Startin to prime a second canvas for afternoon painting. http://fb.me/1r2VzMzGl     
    
    
    Painting in the base coat. http://fb.me/1n9Dbk125     
    
    
    The 24 x 36 is starting to take shape in form and color. http://fb.me/10oSDpNCw     
    
    
    A little more painting progress on the larger work. Taking a break for it to dry a bit. http://fb.me/2mUvqMRWB     
    
    
    The Fine Art Ramblers are getting ready to take the stage at the S.C.  State Museum. http://fb.me/YDSo3ab8     
    
    
    Back to work on the 24 x 24 @ the S.C. State Museum. http://fb.me/C6tkf4w7     
    
    
    Time to step back and see what the other artists are working on while this rests. http://fb.me/1Z4BsA0QB     
    
    
    Stepping back from the smaller painting to see where to go next with it. http://fb.me/2k9WCrWcf     
    
    
    Trying to increase awareness on my Facebook business page for people who are interested in my work please "like" http://tinyurl.com/62a7u8h    
    
    
    http://on.ted.com/8s4W An unusual lab putting art to work!    
    
    
    Amazing Artist, engineer, performance art from TED!  http://on.ted.com/8s4k    
    
    
    Debating whether to paint the other half of the studio prior to the Open Studio gallery opening March 23rd. It's... http://fb.me/1AqgXLtd9     
    
    
    Debating whether to paint the other half of the studio prior to the Open Studio gallery opening March 23rd. It's... http://fb.me/1J2XvCtBZ     
    
    
    So, painting the other half of the studio is in progress! http://fb.me/EeXRey6o     
    
    
    So, priming my studio walls like a blank canvas prior to Open Studios March 23rd! http://fb.me/2CBjsXM0R     
    
    
    Studio painted and everything put back into place. Whew!    
    
    
    Finished painting the studio and all is back in place for now.    
    
    
    Even the art dog is tired. http://fb.me/1NWAba4yW     
    
    
    Even the art dog is tired. http://fb.me/2aFiMbB1x     
    
    
    The studio walls have been repainted. Now to get the art hung. This year I have two galleries again, one with the... http://fb.me/12DV8PuXT     
    
    
    Do you need display stands for your garden art? Selling display stands in my Etsy Store Alicialeeke http://etsy.me/XQVH9w  via @Etsy    
    
    
    Here is the info on Open Studios 2013 and a first sneak peek at some of my new work:... http://fb.me/1AoW375Kx     
    
    
    Here is the info on Open Studios 2013 and a first sneak peek at some of my new work:... http://fb.me/FS0Gdzsj     
    
    
    http://carolinaartsnews.wordpress.com/tag/columbia-open-studios/ … http://fb.me/xoasPUlx     
    
    
    http://carolinaartsnews.wordpress.com/tag/columbia-open-studios/ … http://fb.me/unKbx9KX     
    
    
    Is pleased to announce representation by M. Gallery in Lexington, South Carolina. They are located here: http://tinyurl.com/63exbb3    
    
    
    Great episode! The Dog Whisperer - S06E01 - How to Raise the Perfect Dog: http://youtu.be/vxtETfCAdN4  via @youtube    
    
    
    This is a busy month with commissions, Open Studios, restocking and new ventures. Getting ready to post some pics... http://fb.me/2fWrIKyrk     
    
    
    Great article in the Herald.  http://www.miamiherald.com/2013/03/08/3275287/realor-notlegal-drama-over-art.html … http://fb.me/2FlqZbbRp     
    
    
    Great article in the Herald.  http://www.miamiherald.com/2013/03/08/3275287/realor-notlegal-drama-over-art.html … http://fb.me/1N5JUldEE     
    
    
    Well, the photo shoot went well for the new collage works. I had to hire a professional commercial Photographer to... http://fb.me/GTKJMDYi     
    
    
    Here is the first collage I worked on to figure out how to work with new products. It is my first collage since... http://fb.me/A8Zt1WzX     
    
    
    Wishing everyone the luck of the Irish. May you find your pot of gold!    
    
    
    Five days until Open Studios. I'll be showcasing new art!    
    
    
    My studio will be open RAIN OR SHINE during Open Studios this weekend. I have 2 gallerys open. Also, three collage... http://fb.me/HDmnpzth     
    
    
    All the framing is done for Open Studios and is now hung. Looking forward to seing everyone on the tour tomorrow and Sunday.    
    
    
    Blue and Grey, 20 x 20, acrylic on canvas! It's on the Open Studios tour! http://fb.me/2owKF2iU5     
    
    
    You can add a little spice to your weekend by coming by my studio for the 701 Open Studios Tour this weekend. I... http://fb.me/1jSwyeEvA     
    
    
    9.14 am All the Open Studio signs assembled and placed on the streets in the rain. I have enough dirt in my car... http://fb.me/2vHQaiz0W     
    
    
    Get out of the rain and enjoy a fire at my studio today during Open Studios 2013. http://fb.me/1Zqmx5Q7B     
    
    
    This is a blank canvas I primed. Come by my studio to see the progress over the weekend for this new landscape. http://fb.me/2vokJjXhS     
    
    
    The Open Studios tour is over for today, but we will be here in the morning!    
    
    
    The Open Studios tour is over for today, but we will be here in the morning! The Official Tour Starts at Noon!    
    
    
    Open Studios starts in 20 minutes!    
    
    
    Progress on that blank canvas I posted last week. http://fb.me/1XE77Jelp     
    
    
    Fifteen minutes more for the tour and Miss Lucy Liu the art dog gets released. http://fb.me/EwmdHMiZ     
    
    
    Come let's celebrate five years of art on Main Street at Frame of Mind with me and four fellow artists the first... http://fb.me/DZJrHXFZ     
    
    
    Come let's celebrate five years of art on Main Street at Frame of Mind with me and four fellow artists the first... http://fb.me/N8C2b9p3     
    
    
    Come let's celebrate five years of art on Main Street at Frame of Mind with me and four fellow artists the first... http://fb.me/1AvvZzZvI     
    
    
    Great article on travel saving:... http://fb.me/NbWxZ10x     
    
    
    Great article on travel saving:... http://fb.me/11J96cOwd     
    
    
    My studio during Open Studios 2013! http://fb.me/16G5ZXnZ1     
    
    
    August is off to a great start with steady art sales! A great sign for the economy.    
    
    
    I strongly recommend Private Selection Brand Petite Chocolate Ganache Cakes. Warning: Don't eat the whole box in 1 sitting!    
    
    
    If you missed the new body of work that I launched during Open Studios last week you can get another chance to see... http://fb.me/R5d6izRI     
    
    
    If you missed the new body of work that I launched during Open Studios last week you can get another chance to... http://fb.me/2m333baER     
    
    
    If you missed the new body of work that I launched during Open Studios last week you can get another chance to... http://fb.me/2copbIZRx     
    
    
    Just updated my website with new info. Not a full update yet. Check it out at www.alicialeeke.com. Will get new work posted soon.    
    
    
    @anunquietmind Thanks for the follow Friday! I have been out of town and would have followed up sooner!    
    
    
    Back to the Blackberry vs. Iphone. I settled (possibly temporarily) for the Blackberry for signal/battery. Addicted to notifications.    
    
    
    I'm researching why they call the Blackberry the Crackberry. BB has longer life with apps open vs Iphone. Signal not as good as Razor.    
    
    
    A truly good sales rep at Best Buy or BB vs. Iphone videos will show you the value of the 2 devices. Solely depends on YOUR INDIVIDUAL needs    
    
    
    Did I mention I switched to AT&T Universe...works much better than TWC without constant rebooting and poor customer service of the latter.    
    
    
    This looks like a cool tool http://www.ipagerank.org/index.php    
    
    
    If you missed the new body of work that I launched during Open Studios last week you can get another chance to... http://fb.me/1zJSaDePF     
    
    
    If you like Frank Adman on Twitter, you'll love him on Youtube http://bit.ly/9FC9r    
    
    
    Have you tried the new and improved @mrtweet?  Get great people recommendations with one click. http://mrtweet.com?v=20    
    
    
    Recommended @mashable to @MrTweet 'Always on time and accurate.' http://bit.ly/Q2UMD    
    
    
    I can't wait to see the movie:... http://fb.me/2yj1F0dAD     
    
    
    I don't pay the TA! AA BB CC!

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WTFnmsCnr6g … http://fb.me/1EJ8Srmlm     
    
    
    So excited to be accepted into the Columbia Museum of Art's Contemporary Artist of the Year event!    
    
    
    I totally 100% endorse the gomohu leaf antenna:  #http://www.gomohu.com/    
    
    
    Get rid of cable and save $ go #gomohu here 
http://www.gomohu.com/     
    
    
    I'll let you know about the #magicjack plus next. From this geeky artist :)    
    
    
    And I like this guy too #@Ericthomasbtc! Good motivational speaker. I'm not paying the TA!    
    
    
    I just got news this morning that two of my works, "Fashion for Fashion's Sake" and "Looking Over Your Shoulder"... http://fb.me/BzoTNc54     
    
    
    So today, I figured out why we have teachers. It's for the rest of us that never read the directions. Visual and... http://fb.me/FoHH8mbU     
    
    
    Don't forget tomorrow night is the First Thursday Art Walk on Main Street in Columbia, SC. I will be celebrating... http://fb.me/2kRFvVHY0     
    
    
    http://www.thestate.com/2013/04/04/2706411/one-thursday.html … http://fb.me/2zI3BaP2C     
    
    
    What a great First Thursday Five Year Anniversary show last night. If you didn't want to slush out in the rain,... http://fb.me/27Zt1dkDc     
    
    
    I entered the Art Fields competition in Lake City SC not only because I have friends there, but also because... http://fb.me/17iGIQRBi     
    
    
    This Friday is the Trenholm Artists Guild annual member show at HoFP Gallery on Devine Street in Columbia, SC.... http://fb.me/PEyDDPR7     
    
    
    Saturday is the Elmwood Park Tour of Homes and several artists will be selling art from the porches of the homes... http://fb.me/2j889tph4     
    
    
    http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=1230013948#!/event.php?eid=143455909035696    
    
    
    The 62nd Annual Trinity Bazaar is tomorrow, Saturday, November 13, 2010, from 10:00 a.m. to 3:00 p.m. The... http://fb.me/KN6djaOE    
    
    
    Twilight, Signed and numbered, limited edition framed print, size 24 x 18. Available for purchase.... http://fb.me/2fpQMrSqs     
    
    
    http://fb.me/K1mg23Dg     
    
    
    Elmwood Park tour of homes today 10-5, Columbia, SC. http://fb.me/2F6Cuhcxu     
    
    
    Here is the map. I am showing at 2400 Park St. http://fb.me/Aof9hQ52     
    
    
    This is my painting in the TAG show at HofP Gallery, 24 x 24, acrylic on canvas. http://fb.me/ERMz3wrY     
    
    
    New work shown at the Elmwood Park Tour of Homes today. http://fb.me/15QlPSxjw     
    
    
    All set up! Here til 5. http://fb.me/1ikHXF41W     
    
    
    Getting ready for Color the Arts Friday night. Get your tickets early! http://colorthearts.info/colorthearts/  http://fb.me/1LvYp67do     
    
    
    Here's where to begin if you're going to Artfields in Lake City, SC. Please visit Wards Comfort Shoes on Main... http://fb.me/14tsceHIe     
    
    
    Here is the piece juried onto Artfields. http://fb.me/2GAR5R5hA     
    
    
    Collectors of my work, pay close attention: My mistake is your gain! I would normally sell Gervias Street Ladies... http://fb.me/1fDivtXxn     
    
    
    Worth Repeating is moving to a new location and they are having a huge sale. I am jumping on the band wagon and am... http://fb.me/RS8wQ7Nm     
    
    
    I have two pieces juried into the Contemporaries' Artist of the Year Soriee this Friday. This is a fun,... http://fb.me/2fxpzBYw7     
    
    
    Celebrate our 22nd Year! Thursday April 25th-Saturday April 27th in the Heart of the Vista! I'll be showing my... http://fb.me/Hek69xjC     
    
    
    Only two more days to view the Frame of Mind Show celebrating five years with artists Roger Hutchison, Bonnie... http://fb.me/TeobiaJv     
    
    
    Please join me at the Gallery at Nonnah's tomorrow night for desert and cocktails at the Gallery at Nonnah's with... http://fb.me/2nyLrQ9Rr     
    
    
    Here is the list of gallery's on the tour tonight. I'll see you for cocktails and dessert at the Gallery At... http://fb.me/2hijA637h     
    
    
    If you missed Vista Lights tonight, many of the artists have works available for viewing on their websites.    
    
    
    TONIGHT: I have two pieces in the show. Can you find them?

http://www.columbiamuseum.org/events/calendar?event=70146 … http://fb.me/2eL1sLcL7     
    
    
    I'm in the network. Are you?

http://www.dailyfinance.com/2013/04/23/free-museum-admissions-NARM/ … http://fb.me/2pn6FcXBh     
    
    
    Great variety of art at Artfields. No tight pickets for that show and a huge turnout and win for economic... http://fb.me/1WYLrUg8p     
    
    
    Undervalued female artists (buy my art direct; or buy it later at Sothebys or Christys.... http://fb.me/1jd40JtZQ     
    
    
    My space at the Piccolo Spoleto Outdoor Art Festival in Marion Square is #36. I am to the right of the tallest... http://fb.me/yPUql1Qi     
    
    
    Lawd have mercy there's not much difference between running for president and politics in art.    
    
    
    You might want to rethink cutting arts funding. City leaders saw the vision, artists helped build it and the... http://fb.me/2i2ZLeXDY     
    
    
    articles/Judge says Sid Vicious street art breaks copyright http://fb.me/TiwcbZBL     
    
    
    http://www.scnow.com/newsandpost/news/article_2e689b08-b275-11e2-be10-001a4bcf6878.html … http://fb.me/1H9fEXS57     
    
    
    Working on a Winter body of work. So far, 18 paintings finished and another 17 or so in the works. I will be... http://fb.me/S9DvbXIL    
    
    
    Gambling, money laundering, art heists...this art business gets more and more interesting. Now one of my favorite... http://fb.me/2fq9yth6x     
    
    
    Working "Inspired by Winter" artwork. So far 19 new works completed. Of course, all are not about snow, some are "Wishful Spring Thinking!"    
    
    
    http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2011/02/03/verizon-iphone-the-reviews-are-in/ Iphone Reviews    
    
    
        
    
    
    Coming up for air after four 12-hour days. I've been working on 8 commissions of my favorite city, Paris, for a... http://fb.me/R7qa7ule     
    
    
    Just getting started on my next commission. Floral still life.  Highly collectible of my work..-bet Ive done less than 10 en toto.    
    
    
    See my last comment about this pic. http://fb.me/zUAUMtit     
    
    
    Late night wind down from painting: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XycBLF6kWuY … http://fb.me/1IaGTlCrg     
    
    
    Ok now I'm confused. The last video said monkey goes to heaven; I thought Goats Go to Heaven! Love Cake! This is... http://fb.me/26UjsN9zo     
    
    
    OK, this late night wind down thing is not going so well when I keep finding more of my favorite songs!!  Love... http://fb.me/1J7SYUtSU     
    
    
    One of my new works was chosen for inclusion in the Columbia Museum of Art's 100 x 100 exhibition. You have to go... http://fb.me/17v6nIfQT     
    
    
    #UPS I would never cheat on you but I was forced to do in RMA via another company...  bad idea. Service is not the... http://fb.me/AdHW4P60     
    
    
    Got some more good news in the mail today! Sharing later...too tired to post!    
    
    
    I am now accepting requests for commissions for Pet Portraits. Contact me via my website at... http://fb.me/zNK41cnS     
    
    
    This is another example of the pet portrait work I'e been doing. 

Contact me via my website at... http://fb.me/2Wgkor1jz     
    
    
    Another example of a black and white pet portrait. You can contact me via Facebook email for more information to... http://fb.me/UZPjXINq     
    
    
    I just finished framing 53 pieces of art not including the backing in two days. Time for a small break! That is A LOT of work!!!    
    
    
    This is a fun, colorful portrait of my pup Lucy Liu, aka Lucy Poo! http://fb.me/LQfGAfp6     
    
    
    This is a fun portrait of my own pup, Lucy Liu! Love my doggie! I can do this for you too! http://fb.me/1yxsB4oAX     
    
    
    Put this on your list of things to do this Memorial Weekend and the days that follow to buy some great art! In... http://fb.me/Tv6Rs2OL     
    
    
    BB&T Bank charges non-account holders $5 to cash checks. What message are they sending about their own customers & to incent new ones?    
    
    
    If a bank charges you to cash a check, will your business stop taking checks from that bank or just pass that charge onto their customers?    
    
    
    You're invited to attend ArtFields Extended in Columbia, SC! Here is the link for the opening reception. http://fb.me/VAtHPsSg     
    
    
    Back to the Blackberry Storm. After using for less than a month, I think I'll return and wait for Storm II. Rumors say new one has WIFI    
    
    
    New work on view at Piccolo Spoleto. Booth no. 39. http://fb.me/1fj7aSOQD     
    
    
    Selling art at Piccolo Spoleto 2013 in Marion Square Park, Charleston South Carolina. Space no. 36 under the... http://fb.me/2FCOPos8V     
    
    
    Here is a map with my location at the Piccolo Spoleto outdoor Art Exhibition and sale in Marion Square Park 2013.... http://fb.me/AUE7pBsy     
    
    
    http://mobile.nytimes.com/2013/05/28/arts/design/jackson-pollocks-one-number-31-1950-restored-by-moma.html …    
    
    
    I am directly to the right of the Calhoun monument pictured here in Marion Square Park in Charleston South... http://fb.me/xEuXiLMy     
    
    
    New work showing today...Mysterious Evening Dunes in Marion Square booth 36. http://fb.me/2jk845EDl     
    
    
    Tropical Paradise 36 x 60 at Piccolo Spoleto in Marion Square. http://fb.me/OPkXmZ8l     
    
    
    My booth will be open today rain or shine in Charleston South Carolina at the Piccolo Spoleto outdoor art show in... http://fb.me/2GdbAioxz     
    
    
    Just like the postman, we are showing art in Marion Square. Rain or shine. Since there was a 30% chance of rain... http://fb.me/2jNBbEOQd     
    
    
    Just like the postman, we are showing art in Marion Square. Rain or shine. Since there was a 30% chance of rain... http://fb.me/ECSj3bGA     
    
    
    Open for business in Marion Square. Pleasant temperature in the park...great art buying weather! http://fb.me/1MKqDKZN8     
    
    
    I went to this exhibition Monday, a show not to be missed at the Halsey Museum of Contemporary Art in Charleston,... http://fb.me/UTxjbvye     
    
    
    http://halsey.cofc.edu/exhibitions/rebound/ …    
    
    
    It is a beautiful day Come buy some art. We will be here today and part of Sunday! In Marion Square at Piccolo... http://fb.me/2m5kow0wd     
    
    
    New work on display. Snowy Fence post. http://fb.me/1B5lCYo9F     
    
    
    I am liking the online customer service chats that various companies are offering these days. Makes doing business on EST easier after hours    
    
    
    Fine Art and Fine wine! Buy early and often and you might be able to get a loan.... http://fb.me/2NHL9uw43     
    
    
    Art Hedge Funds: http://blogs.barrons.com/penta/2013/06/07/the-hedge-funds-of-the-art-world/?mod=google_news_blog …    
    
    
    Selling this storage / shipping container. Has four entry way doors. Great for hauling and storing music gear,... http://fb.me/MgWJ4c6E     
    
    
    Paint-a-thon in progress!!    
    
    
    Merger Monday sends stocks climbing http://shar.es/32fHR     
    
    
    I love all the colors at the beach and the bridge as a backdrop. http://fb.me/XT3wSVXr     
    
    
    Government gets something right: 
http://www.cnn.com/2013/06/24/us/picasso-painting/ … http://fb.me/32gC9ZmuG     
    
    
    Going once, going twice....Christmas in July ends in 2 hours 15 minutes :)    
    
    
    The Columbia Museum of Art is having its Holiday Artisan's fair this Sunday. Hope to see you there where I will be... http://fb.me/GG8t39nK    
    
    
    I have new large works at Tombo Grille in Columbia and a reception for me and two other artists that evening. Please come out. Columbia, SC.    
    
    
    Columbia Museum of Art Artisan Fair is Sunday from noon - 3 pm at the Corner of Main and Hampton Street in Columbia, SC.    
    
    
    Interesting read. http://www.artnews.com/2013/08/05/sandy-creates-paradigm-shift-for-insurers/ … http://fb.me/1R5J4t6KF     
    
    
    And the saga continues...stay tuned Bat fans:... http://fb.me/JFNHZiI5     
    
    
    I guess this sums up private vs. government control in the arts:... http://fb.me/KqzzuNG9     
    
    
    High profile stars don't have easy transition into art career: http://hyperallergic.com/75344/celebrities-failing-at-art/ …    
    
    
    Are you an introvert? http://elibishop.com/2011/07/27/10-myths-about-introverts/ …    
    
    
    I find comfort in knowing I'm not here to solve the world's problems. I am here to make the world a more beautiful... http://fb.me/X5VOjE5k     
    
    
    I wil be hosting a naming party tonight...get reaty!    
    
    
    Naming party on my Facebook page tonight thru Wednesday. Just uploaded about 38 works!    
    
    
    Happy Artsy Valentin's Day! Paint the town Red!    
    
    
    Is making some sound business decisions!    
    
    
    Be my Valentine, please like http://www.facebook.com/?ref=home#!/pages/Alicia-Leeke-American-Contemporary-Painter-Official-Site/54036227159    
    
    
    All Valentines "Facebook fans" will receive 15 percent off any art purchase too!"; >    
    
    
    Happy Artsy Valentine's Day!    
    
    
    Hmmm. Maybe I'll hold onto my home studio...or sell...... http://fb.me/2XiI3vhN8     
    
    
    http://fb.me/22NM9RRbF     
    
    
    I love this song! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EJN-rzytlYI&list=PLqrGkzo4esV3Q8cixiPjZgOUmV_QxIvMZ … http://fb.me/2AMVckCl4     
    
    
    And this song equally!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ghb6eDopW8I&list=PLqrGkzo4esV3Q8cixiPjZgOUmV_QxIvMZ … http://fb.me/2CvE3SC6j     
    
    
    But, this is my favorite! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DHEOF_rcND8&list=PLqrGkzo4esV3Q8cixiPjZgOUmV_QxIvMZ … http://fb.me/1LcN3O36i     
    
    
    See you there! http://www.facebook.com/alicia.leeke#!/event.php?eid=150370971687743 http://fb.me/vsx9vLS0    
    
    
    Hgh import taxes on art in Brazil.... http://fb.me/2nbkzAzsA     
    
    
    The saga continues in Detroit, but on a positive note, if you collect good art and get in a bind, you just may be... http://fb.me/1mTrjISLT     
    
    
    Facebook Changes Terms of Service — Photographers Be Wary! http://fb.me/14kl3yM72     
    
    
    Top selling living women artists:... http://fb.me/2K5pfK0yW     
    
    
    I love selling art. In fact, I'm like selling equally to painting. It is rewarding for someone to purchase one of... http://fb.me/1Jk1sMtfA     
    
    
    Looking forward to a great day painting new landscapes!    
    
    
        
    
    
    It's official, You can now upload your Twitter from Your Facebook.    
    
    
    Haven't been on in a while because I've been working on a show in Columbia South Carolina for Tombo Grille, one of my favorite eats. Its up!    
    
    
    Two commissions down, five to go!    
    
    
    Come out to Michael Mitchell Gallery Friday afternoon to see painting demos by Alicia Leeke. Additional painting... http://fb.me/SfPfJHH8    
    
    
    I'll be doing landscape demos Friday afternoon at Michael Mitchell Gallery at 438 King Street.  Be sure to stop by.    
    
    
    This is my painting that won a purchase patron award at the SC State Fair! http://fb.me/2sDtGzSEi     
    
    
    This is my painting that won a purchase patron award at the SC State Fair! http://fb.me/LhPk5VSE     
    
    
    This is my painting that won a purchase patron award at the SC State Fair! http://fb.me/6w8pwnvTt     
    
    
    I hope to be getting back to commissions and painting shortly. Another big project has taken three months of my... http://fb.me/2v5GmibXh     
    
    
        
    
    
    Getting ready for the Artisan's Show and Sale at the Columbia Museum of Art this Saturday. I will have a new... http://fb.me/11tAAjQda     
    
    
    Did you make the switch from your cable or phone provider to AT&T for rewards? Be sure to follow up on your rewards because they won't.    
    
    
    I have had to follow up for the third time for my rewards and on the 3rd time, wasn't even in the system and it takes 4-6 weeks; so check it    
    
    
    Columbia's best kept secret...in Forest Acres, South Carolina! http://fb.me/6mS7GGhKN     
    
    
    Don't forget, the event is THIS Saturday!! http://fb.me/LfmqKyaw     
    
    
    If you went to the Southeastern Wildlife Expo and missed the touch tank at Michael Mitchell Gallery in Charleston,... http://fb.me/PRwI5s3K    
    
    
    Here is the official Piccolo Spoleto Facebook Page and artists and a preview of work including me! http://tinyurl.com/6bwku5s    
    
    
    The holidays are almost here. Give original art from artisans showing at the Columbia Museum of Art in Columbia,... http://fb.me/1MtcbyBBh     
    
    
    This just described me and many of my painting friends! I find I've already had the conversation and moved on to... http://fb.me/3o7WU2mJA     
    
    
    I bet Bacon would have changed his mind.... http://fb.me/2LgiY5Eye     
    
    
    I hope everyone is taking a few minutes to look up at the moon and the colors of fall this week. I've picked a... http://fb.me/1bmiTT4GO     
    
    
    Don't forget, Vista Lights is tomorrow night. I'll be in the Gallery at Nonnahs located at 930 Gervais Street in... http://fb.me/6wn6eKR1e     
    
    
    Tomorrow Night! See you at 6! http://fb.me/2zoJKGOE9     
    
    
    Thankful for all my friends and art patrons that came out tonight to Nonnahs during Vista Lights!    
    
    
    With new bank rules, guess who pays?  http://on-msn.com/gzjSOM    
    
    
    Article about my current art show in Charleston, SC: http://bit.ly/rGSxn via @addthis    
    
    
    Piccolo Spoleto's Outdoor Art Show is right around the corner!... http://fb.me/HMhI3yF8    
    
    
    A frame makes a painting! This article is so timely for me since I just sold a painting last week that had the... http://fb.me/1ZQUpkkiy     
    
    
    I just got my photos back from a project I've been working on for four months!! They look great! Thank you John... http://fb.me/24MxlYPGC     
    
    
    For those of you that I owe commissions, please know I'm working diligently on them. It's been a tough year since... http://fb.me/2UfiH6gUG     
    
    
    There have been a lot of articles about what makes art collectable and the madness in the art market. Well here... http://fb.me/1Wkanog49     
    
    
    There have been a lot of articles about what makes art collectable from very credible sources and Sotheby's and... http://fb.me/2FgDa4G01     
    
    
    For the holidays, my art page would like some new friends in the spirit of the holidays! I'm also feeling a tad... http://fb.me/2FHaXzopt     
    
    
    If you have been following the Detroit art scene, you will like this documentary. It's rather long.... http://fb.me/XTsYbtEN     
    
    
    As a reminder, with all the Facebook changes, if you want to keep current on my fine art page on Facebook, please... http://fb.me/VoQPoT7V     
    
    
    As a reminder, with all the Facebook changes, if you want to keep current on my fine art page on Facebook, please... http://fb.me/2xHRm4IUZ     
    
    
    As a reminder, with all the Facebook changes, if you want to keep current on my fine art page on Facebook, please... http://fb.me/2EzUh24js     
    
    
    Interesting read. 

Inhttp://www.vanityfair.com/culture/2013/11/vermeer-secret-tool-mirrors-lenses_slideshow_item5_6 http://fb.me/2epSTCXTL     
    
    
    Things you need to know:  http://bit.ly/RZirc via @addthis clip about Biomimicry.    
    
    
    Happy New Year! Thanks for all my art patrons and friends that make my career as an artist possible! Look forward... http://fb.me/6jkji3GoQ     
    
    
    Today is a great day. Going on day 3 for making new art. Glad to be able to start the New Year this way. It's... http://fb.me/6Cq0gxejG     
    
    
    New work: "South Carolina Philharmonic." http://fb.me/6Ca0htofd     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/RAuRyBLV     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6kxKtZtPV     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2ArGCYNoj     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2zaQ2vroV     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/SX4Nqrb8     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2Xn6NqjQe     
    
    
    I am now accepting new commissions for pet portraits just in time for Valentine's Day! Affordable ever-lasting memories of your fur babies!    
    
    
    Great article on jobs of the future: http://tinyurl.com/4pb5uds.    
    
    
    The Trenholm Artists Guild Annual Exhibit & Sale Opening Reception is Friday 3-4-11 from 6:30 - 8:30 pm in Columbia, SC at HoFP Gallery.    
    
    
    Nothing like discovering the Magic 8 Ball app on Facebook.    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=131786716891520 http://fb.me/TipC6eU3    
    
    
    Columbia Home & Garden | Our magazine showcases homes, gardens, people, life... - http://bit.ly/f8HbhF via @columbiaHG    
    
    
    Thank you Columbia Home and Garden Magazine for your wonderful article on my artwork!    
    
    
    Volkswagen Bulli news - Geneva 2011: Volkswagen Bulli concept - 2011 - BBC Top Gear http://www.topgear.com/uk/car-news/vw-bulli-concept-2011-03-01 … via @BBC_Topgear    
    
    
    VW microbus: Will VW bring back '60s icon? http://www.csmonitor.com/Business/Latest-News-Wires/2011/0303/VW-microbus-Will-VW-bring-back-60s-icon?cmpid=addthis_twitter&sms_ss=twitter&at_xt=4d72abe0861495b5,0 … via @AddThis    
    
    
    The Dogbrella - Hammacher Schlemmer http://www.hammacher.com/Product/79317?source=AddThis … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Snowstorm, 24 x 24, framed, $575. Available at HoFP Gallery during the TAG Annual Members Exhibit and Sale until... http://fb.me/UDhwCvlo    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Front 242 - Headhunter http://bit.ly/8S61f    
    
    
    Made In America: Smithsonian Promises to Sell More American-Made Souvenirs in its Gift Shops - ABC News http://abcnews.go.com/Business/made-america-smithsonian-promises-sell-american-made-souvenirs/story?id=13087867 …    
    
    
    So excited to be the featured artist in the March issue of Columbia Home and Garden Magazine!! Great article. The... http://fb.me/x9nGoXmO    
    
    
    Is excited to be the featured artist in the March issue of Columbia Home and Garden Magazine. Please pick up your cop…http://columbiahg.com/    
    
    
    Several people have asked to get copies of the March issue of Columbia Home and Garden Magazine. Get your copy... http://fb.me/XP76GYSw    
    
    
    @TeddyShabba I love that quote! So true! The secret of success is constancy of purpose.”––Benjamin Disraeli    
    
    
        
    
    
    Vending the rules: 25 weird, wild vending machines - Money - TODAYshow.com http://today.msnbc.msn.com/id/41876929/ns/today-money/ … via @todayshow    
    
    
    Check this video out -- EMF: Unbelieveable http://bit.ly/Km1qM    
    
    
    Vista Lights is in Columbia, SC this Thursday night from 5-10 in Columbia. Please stop by the Gallery at Nonnah's... http://fb.me/OmZNAg8S    
    
    
    Is thinking the AT&T Rewards for customers switching from cable to FastAccess® DSL is a scam. Called 4 x; went online & says disqualified    
    
    
    For those that signed up for the AT&T Rewards program, it does have an expiration date, so be sure to keep following up. Mine is not expired    
    
    
    I am interested to know if other folks have signed up for the AT&T Reward probram w/ Uverse and had problems redeeming cash back offer.    
    
    
    Getting ready for show season!    
    
    
    Pepsi goes green with first 100 percent plant-based plastic bottle | syracuse.com http://www.syracuse.com/news/index.ssf/2011/03/pepsi_goes_green_with_first_10.html …    
    
    
    An artists palette is like a strand of DNA; a definable signature that controls the structure & function of an entire painting: Alicia Leeke    
    
    
    As I was conceptualizing a new body of work this evening for for the upcoming Piccolo Spoleto Show in late May and... http://fb.me/Y3Tx0NU6    
    
    
    Happy St. Patty's Day from South Carolina!    
    
    
    Darla Moore's Full-Court Press http://www.inc.com/articles/2000/01/16336.html?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=socialmedia&utm_campaign=button … via @IncMagazine    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Bob Marley- Three Little Birds (With Lyrics!) http://bit.ly/XBEjC    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/OosX2 Check out Google Voice.    
    
    
    Only two days left to see the TAG Show at HoFP Gallery in Columbia, SC.    
    
    
    Looking forward to great sales in Atlanta this week!    
    
    
    Great News! My work has been accepted into the South Carolina Arts Gala Art Auction and Sale!    
    
    
    Atlanta is hopping with buyers. It has been a long time since I've seen buyers like this! Great sign for the economy!    
    
    
    Artists, before signing on with a new gallery, contact that city's Better Business Bureau. You might be grateful & save yourself surprises.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Is thrilled to be hosting Alyson B. Stanfield, internationally renowned author of I'd Rather Be in the Studio at... http://fb.me/tcQLrXeQ    
    
    
    Is thrilled to host author Alyson Stanfield (I'd Rather Be in the Studio) at my art studio for a book party May 14, 2-4 pm in Columbia, SC!    
    
    
    Vista Lights is tonight from 5-10 pm! Be sure to swing by Nonnah's at 930 Gervais Street in Columbia, SC!    
    
    
    Off to the races this weekend? Consider taking this versatile, insulated wine tote and have a stylish Carolina Cup... http://fb.me/Yz0vpbU4    
    
    
    I'm attending Cultural Visions Art Show - VIP Performance Evening -- http://bit.ly/38uPtF    
    
    
        
    
    
    It's official. My studio will be open for 2011 Columbia Open Studios! Details forthcoming.    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/alicia.leeke/posts/203370626351311?ref=notif&notif_t=like http://fb.me/VGr9msnj    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/ColumbiaContemporaries http://fb.me/TtLqx99J    
    
    
    Watching a msnbc.com video: Cutting the arts? -  http://on.msnbc.com/eAeNhP Kevin Spacey is a great arts advocate. Thanks Kevin!    
    
    
    Is gearing up for two big art shows: Chicago and New York One of A Kind! Be there!    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/pages/Coastal-Discovery-Museum/113196365416965?ref=ts&sk=wall#!/photo.php?fbid=14103966596... http://fb.me/U1imFUIB    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/home.php#!/event.php?eid=212337758779696 http://fb.me/JgD7VQUm    
    
    
    Working on new abstract paintings for Piccolo Spoleto Festival USA in Charleston, SC!    
    
    
    A new batch of abstract paintings is in the works for Piccolo Spoleto 2011!!!    
    
    
    Please show a little love to my Facebook fan page by clicking like! 

https://www.facebook.com/Alicia.Leeke.Official.Fan.Page?sk=info    
    
    
    Anyone know of fine art shippers or insured and bonded drivers from the Southeast to Chicago and New York?    
    
    
    http://www.colorthearts.info/ http://fb.me/XFkRNq9q    
    
    
    Packing tape, check; boxes, check;. Shrink wrap, check! Let's get this party started!    
    
    
    Waiting for the Ice Road Truckers to pick up art for the Chicago and New York One of A Kind Shows...hope to see you there!!    
    
    
    Greg and Raymond picked a parcel of palletized paintings. Just finished at 10:40! 800 and some odd miles to Chicagoland! See them go, go, go    
    
    
    I am so blessed to have my work selected for the SC Arts Commission Gala! Hope to see you there!... http://fb.me/WCXSsJ9f    
    
    
    Why yes, I do think art, yachts and diamonds pair nicely with Champagne!    
    
    
    Here are the details on the Gala!... http://fb.me/OZEpDfWL    
    
    
    I love this guy. I'm now reviewing the Storm II versus Droid and he's done a great comparison...http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=foWJvkbFQW0    
    
    
    Happy Easter everyone!    
    
    
    http://www.islandpacket.com/2011/04/24/1629685/artful-appreciation-from-across.html

Come out and look at my new... http://fb.me/EDjTd0YT    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/home.php#!/notes/sc-arts-alliance/emergency-governor-calls-for-elimination-of-state-arts-funding/169904029730312    
    
    
    Just a reminder that Artista Vista is tonight in Columbia, SC. See you at the Gallery at Nonnah's in the Vista at 930 Gervais Street!    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/alicia.leeke#!/event.php?eid=206113779403558 http://fb.me/UwktUxeS    
    
    
    If you missed Vista Lights, you can still go by Nonnah's and check out my new body of work. They are located at... http://fb.me/y4twrcC4    
    
    
    Color the Arts is tonight! Get your tickets and then buy some art and jewelry! http://fb.me/TVRioJo7    
    
    
    The Cultural Council of Richland and Lexington County presents: Color the Arts art show and sale tonight. Here is... http://fb.me/WKD6GH4w    
    
    
    Alicia Leeke Blog: Color the Arts Event Showcases Local Talent This E... http://alicialeeke.blogspot.com/2011/04/color-arts-event-showcases-local-talent.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Alicia Leeke Blog: Art Market at Historic Honey Horn to be Held This ... http://alicialeeke.blogspot.com/2011/04/art-market-at-historic-honey-horn-to-be.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The Cultural Council of Richland and Lexington Counties presents its 7th annual Color the Arts fundraiser tonight... http://fb.me/UfBQ0wWC    
    
    
    Today is the last day of the Art Market. Come out if you're on Hilton Head Island!    
    
    
    For those of you interested in coming to the Arts Commission Gala, it is this week!... http://fb.me/EvMOYp1a    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/#!/ColumbiaContemporaries http://fb.me/MRim1W9U    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/#!/photo.php?fbid=10150249452771959&set=a.10150249442526959.378830.13402831958&type=1&theater http://fb.me/KLvpYAZ4    
    
    
    You are invited to the 3rd Annual Trenholm Artists Guild Holiday Market featuring the artwork of over 60 local... http://fb.me/OAnS4BY2    
    
    
    Chicago One of a Kind Show: Great press coverage & 2 of my paintings were chosen for Designer Julia Buckingham Edleman's Artful Living Room.    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/#!/event.php?eid=208975922463709 http://fb.me/U2Q16rHS    
    
    
    Thrilled to be hosting author Alyson Stanfield at my studio in Columbia, SC tomorrow from 2-4 pm. Please come on... http://fb.me/12zzS6Xzf    
    
    
    Merry Christmas all!    
    
    
    @FrankAdman Merry Merriment!    
    
    
    Today is Columbia Open Studios and I'll be previewing new paintings before they go on to Piccolo Spoleto Festival... http://fb.me/NK9LcuFZ    
    
    
    Going to the Shore, 8 x 10 on panel is just one of the many paintings being showcased this weekend at my studio. http://fb.me/vyDQgB0z    
    
    
    Composition No. 2 by Alicia Leeke, 18 x 24. http://fb.me/zFNal81I    
    
    
    Already getting ready for the first art show of 2010 in Atlanta next week!    
    
    
    Use your Columbia Open Studios map and follow the yellow, red and black signs to find artists studios. When you... http://fb.me/11yfuvs2L    
    
    
        
    
    
    Open Studios: Like a scavenger hunt for local art - Weekend - TheState.com http://www.thestate.com/2011/05/19/1825501/open-studios-like-a-scavenger.html?storylink=addthis#storylink=addthis … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Open Studios: Like a scavenger hunt for local art - Weekend - TheState.com http://lnkd.in/Mh4J3C    
    
    
    Tropical Paradise, 36 x 60, acryic on canvas. Located at Tombo Grille in Columbia, SC. Pop by and take a look. http://fb.me/FTgahYQi    
    
    
    No rest for the weary, gearing up for Piccolo Spoleto in Marion Square Park!    
    
    
    Countdown to Spoleto Festival USA...3 days!!    
    
    
    Can't remember if I shared this article on my work at the One of A Kind Show or not...http://bit.ly/8yPEJA    
    
    
    come see me in Marion square park charleston sc for picccolo Spoleto and look at new works...    
    
    
    Just wanted to let you know I added almost three pages of new landscape paintings and new abstract pages to... http://bit.ly/5JnVxX    
    
    
    New abstract landscapes unveiled during Spoleto today.    
    
    
    Art Sales Remaining Strong!    
    
    
    Just got back from eight straight weeks of work from the Chicago and New York One of a Kind Shows to a wholesale show in Atlanta. Art sells!    
    
    
    Recovering from Spoleto and gearing up for a show at OBX! If you're in the area come by!    
    
    
    If you are in Columbia, SC in January, I am the featured artist of the month at House Brand Furniture. You can see... http://bit.ly/8llhhy    
    
    
    Tonight! http://fb.me/13kNVeAcX    
    
    
    Headed to the Outerbanks for a show! Long drive, but looking forward to meeting new customers and seeing art... http://fb.me/HOuN0rpg    
    
    
    Updated my website with new landscape paintings www.alicialeeke.com; many are 24 x 36 or larger.    
    
    
    Just hit my 1000th FB friend. Please fan my FB Fan page so it can keep up.... http://bit.ly/d863CK    
    
    
    Best business tool / investment on the go: Thuderbolt 4 G! Everything you need to do business on the road!    
    
    
    WCIV-TV | ABC News 4 - Arts community concerned over Haley veto: http://bit.ly/iKvfEJ  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Great show in OBX! Now for a break to create more work for my Fall Shows!    
    
    
    Many of you know I got rid of my Blackberry & went back to my Razor; Now I have the Thunderbolt 4G on Verizon. It has some great free apps!    
    
    
    http://www.southcarolinaradionetwork.com/2011/06/25/celebrity-artists-make-case-against-arts-commission-veto-audio/ …  Celebrity artists argue against Arts Commission veto    
    
    
    More on the Thunderbolt apps. Artists, carpenters or anyone needing a level. Check out the Bubble App! A virtual bubble level by Ben Zibble.    
    
    
    Collectors should mix art and charity more often. Picasso lovers win hearts at Christie's sale - chicagotribune.com http://www.chicagotribune.com/entertainment/sns-rt-us-picasso-christiestre75k6oi-20110622,0,6350083.story …    
    
    
    Buy art not stocks! Picasso lovers win hearts at Christie's sale - chicagotribune.com http://www.chicagotribune.com/entertainment/sns-rt-us-picasso-christiestre75k6oi-20110622,0,6350083.story …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Video games declared art; and now have First Amendment protection. http://www.nytimes.com/2011/06/29/arts/video-games/what-supreme-court-ruling-on-video-games-means.html?_r=1&ref=arts …    
    
    
    This is a good sign for the art market...http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2011/06/28/christies-contemporary-art-sale-signals-continued-strength-in-market/?ref=design …    
    
    
    Facebook Is Quietly Testing First Major Redesign in Over a Year - The Atlantic: http://bit.ly/lEulvm  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Don't forget to register your phone numbers on the Do Not Call Registry. https://www.donotcall.gov/default.aspx     
    
    
    Working on new paintings and planning to have a naming party on Facebook in the near future. Hope you can help me... http://bit.ly/bHp4v4    
    
    
    Independence Day Sale July 4, 2011!

In honor of the men and women serving our country to protect our Freedom, I'm... http://fb.me/E7EhsPWf    
    
    
    2 million Americans primary occupation = artist; they are 2x more likely to have a college degree & 3.5x more to be self-employed - NEA    
    
    
    http://www.nea.gov/research/artistsinworkforce_execsum.pdf … Stats on artists in the workforce...via NEA    
    
    
    Yeah! I just received notification of being juried into the Atlanta Arts Festival in September!    
    
    
    Thunderbolt compass app rules! Military, campers, hikers & artists will love this directional finder. Helps me find shade for outdoor shows!    
    
    
    If you like me here, you might love my artwork at www.alicialeeke.com. Follow me on Facebook at https://www.facebook.com/#!/Alicia.Leeke.Official.Fan.Page …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Art sales are strong despite the current economy. Many investors are adding art as an investment option addition for financial portfolios.    
    
    
    Happy Valentine's Day! http://bit.ly/c0DeMZ    
    
    
    Another good feature of the HTC: Tenants said rental property was clean; took pics of dirty oven and fridge and sent via text. Saved time!    
    
    
    Is finding a lot of new uses for my HTC Driod that I didn't know I even needed!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Paint-a-Thon in my studio started Saturday and is going on until the end of July!    
    
    
    Will be announcing new gallery representation!    
    
    
    The Story behind the Nonnah's painting on my Blog: http://alicialeeke.blogspot.com/2010/02/story-behind-nonnahs-painting-ive-been.html    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanks for the #Friday new followers! I was on the road yesterday so no tweets. Brevity. I'll make up for it with a tweet re: my HTC next.    
    
    
    My HTC obsoletes cumbersome devises for me like: calculators, GPS, cameras, tip cards, desktop/laptops for some, clocks & flashlights, XM.    
    
    
    How a U.S. Downgrade May Affect Consumers - http://www.nytimes.com/2011/07/27/your-money/how-a-us-debt-downgrade-may-affect-consumers.html?pagewanted=all …?src=tp    
    
    
    McDonald’s Happy Meal to Get Healthier - http://www.nytimes.com/2011/07/27/business/mcdonalds-happy-meal-to-get-healthier.html?src=tp …    
    
    
    Hey McDonalds...I'm an adult that likes/eats Happy Meals the way they are. Ditch the toys, keep the caramel for the apples! Reduce portions.    
    
    
    Beaufort gallery adds Leeke's landscapes | islandpacket.com: http://bit.ly/pv8kY6  via @AddThis    
    
    
        
    
    
    @proglobber Thanks for the tip on custom backgrounds. Finally updated mine with my art! http://www.twitip.com/custom-twitter-backgrounds/ …    
    
    
    Does anyone know how to make the side bar transparent in Twitter with IE9?    
    
    
    @stevesipress Congrats!!...@WarrenWhitlock said you have a new gig!    
    
    
    Just completed adding finishing touches to the Wine Festival poster!    
    
    
    http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-14340470 … Maybe we should hire these folks to run US Gov't since they seem to do a good job with cash flow? Just a thought...    
    
    
    Pleased to announce my representation at I. Pinckney Simons Gallery in Beaufort, SC, 711 Bay Street: See work here at: http://www.ipinckneysimonsgallery.com/paintings/leeke/artist.html …    
    
    
    More about my work at Pinckney Simons Gallery. Follow my art blog at: http://alicialeeke.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    Republicans and Democrats Agree on Arts in South Carolina - http://nyti.ms/ni4vnP     
    
    
    http://www.nytimes.com/2011/08/02/arts/republicans-and-democrats-agree-on-arts-in-south-carolina.html?_r=3 http://fb.me/RIA1Yxfq    
    
    
    GREAT new abstract paints in the works!! Getting ready for shows in Atlanta!!    
    
    
    GREAT new abstract paintings in the works!! Getting ready for shows in Atlanta!!    
    
    
    This kid is hot! Someone needs to sign "Ben G" (Hiott) to a major #record label while they still have the opportunity! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ve3MWz14qRs&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    @BenG803 Great new video! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ve3MWz14qRs …    
    
    
    Good read for #entrepreneurs: How the Best Get Better by @strategiccoach Dan Sullivan.    
    
    
    Just opened my new Etsy Store where you can purchase signed & numbered, limited-edition prints of my fine art paintings.    
    
    
    Nonnah's Signed & Numbered Limited-edition Giclee by Alicialeeke http://etsy.me/qoWugE  via @Etsy.    
    
    
    Tuscan Villa Signed & Numbered Limited-Edition Giclee by Alicialeeke http://etsy.me/r0G6Vq  via @Etsy    
    
    
    