I Never get the Good One’s! How many Paper to Review? http://pielot.org/2013/07/14/i-never-get-the-good-ones-how-many-paper-to-review/ …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Nothing about the collections/methodologies developed at CLEF and INEX?    
    
    
    Prepare for the New Permanent Temp - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/schrage/2013/07/prepare-for-the-new-permanent.html …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Piwowarski et al. Sound and Complete Relevance Assessment for XML Retrieval, ACM TOIS, 27(1), Article 1, 37 pages, 2008.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Ogilvie & Lalmas. Investigating the Exhaustivity Dimension in Content-Oriented XML Element Retrieval Evaluation, CIKM 2006.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Trotman & Lalmas. Why Structural Hints in Queries do not Help XML Retrieval, ACM SIGIR August 2006 (Poster).    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Have sent you a selection which is about what we did, what worked and what didn't (sent only those co-authored by me).    
    
    
    Google Maps wipes out Scottish island of Jura http://bbc.in/12DqlGF     
    
    
    Agree "A dinosaur hangs up his claws: why I am leaving the EPSRC College of Peers" the ending kind of says it all! http://iansommerville.com/techstuff/a-dinosaur-hangs-up-his-claws-why-i-am-leaving-the-epsrc-college-of-peers/ …    
    
    
    "Big Science vs. Little Science: How Scientific Impact Scales with Funding" It seems it does not!!! http://www.plosone.org/article/info:doi/10.1371/journal.pone.0065263 …    
    
    
    Yes right!!! Senior Pakistani Taliban leader 'shocked' by Malala attack http://bbc.in/1dEW23W     
    
    
    Counting crowds http://bbc.in/15IVs4i     
    
    
    Stevie Wonder’s Florida Boycott: His Zimmerman verdict protest is savvy and important. http://www.slate.com/articles/arts/culturebox/2013/07/stevie_wonder_s_florida_boycott_his_zimmerman_verdict_protest_is_savvy_and.html …    
    
    
    Arghh! Wished that workshop submissions were all a max of 4 pages ... not full 10 pages ... arghh arghh.    
    
    
    Yes! - Fifa loses free-to-air World Cup TV battle in the UK http://bbc.in/12JyiKs     
    
    
    :-) What Your Toilet Paper Style Says About You [COMIC]  http://on.mash.to/13AMhO0  via @mashable    
    
    
    France's knicker industry: In a twist and losing jobs http://bbc.in/13jAjcI     
    
    
    Bots help geeks nab best tables http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23462687 …    
    
    
    Twitter action urged after threats http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23477130 …    
    
    
    :-((( Italy minister suffers banana insult http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-23480489 …    
    
    
    Have all a great #sigir2013 ... will try to follow tweets from lovely Antibes.    
    
    
    Very very very sad news - Ilya Segalovich, Yandex co-founder, dies after cancer http://bbc.in/16qew5i     
    
    
    I struggle to understand such evil ... why? - Caroline Criado-Perez Twitter abuse case leads to arrest http://bbc.in/1e4j9Fb     
    
    
    Am I the only researcher reviewing papers while on holiday?    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai Oh I have another 2 conf papers to review and they are not for you ... but OK for the drink :-)    
    
    
    Thomas Roelleke M&C book on "Information Retrieval Models: Foundations and Relationships" out in time for #sigir2013 http://www.morganclaypool.com/doi/abs/10.2200/S00494ED1V01Y201304ICR027 …    
    
    
    #cikm2013 UEO workshop paper "Networked User engagement" online at http://www.dcs.gla.ac.uk/~mounia/Papers/cikm2013_ueo.pdf … w/ @_nettele_ Baeza-Yates & @elad1    
    
    
    Twitter abuse: Why cyberbullies are targeting women http://bbc.in/11pK7o1     
    
    
    +1 RT @sharathrao: @dtunkelang your excellent tweets summarizing sessions/papers must be filed under community service!  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Haha :-) Passengers on delayed easyJet flight are given 86 years for replacement http://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/passengers-on-delayed-easyjet-flight-are-given-86-years-to-browse-dutyfree-shops-8737340.html …    
    
    
    #FancyAcademics looking forwards to photos #sigir2013 rather curious I have to admit :-)    
    
    
    +1 RT @djoerd: @tetsuyasakai I vote for Tokyo!    
    
    
    Open-plan offices http://bbc.in/1cbSWrz     
    
    
    Zhou etal  slides #sigir2013 #mube Evaluating Heterogeneous Information Access (Position Paper)  #aggregatedsearch at http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/mube-slides …    
    
    
    @dtunkelang Quantum cognition: and does it work?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang I could not have come up with a better answer ... I did try to work on QT for IR ... but decided slowly it was beyond me :-)    
    
    
    @julian_urbano Happened at INEX many years ago - I kept saying "If I can't get it 150% we can't use it - we had heated debate about metrics.    
    
    
    @YahooLabs work on user engagement - Ricardo Baeza-Yates keynote at #sigir2013 industry track "An engaging click" http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/an-engaging-click …    
    
    
    Living room TV 'making a comeback' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23521277 …    
    
    
    ++++1 RT @yelenamm Some of these have plagued me for a long time http://grammarist.com/easily-confused-words/ …    
    
    
    @SIGIR2013? MT @marcosluis2186: @mounialalmas @YahooLabs amazing keynote about User Engagement from Baeza-Yates. Do you have the video?    
    
    
    We should tell some this :-) Selfish traits not favoured by evolution, study shows http://bbc.in/17okTWf     
    
    
    Which country gets the most tourists? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23433149 …    
    
    
    Should you take an email sabbatical? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23547802 …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs UPF and Glasgow paper "User Engagement in Online News: Under the Scope of Sentiment, Interest, Affect & Gaze" accepted at JASIST    
    
    
    :-) 10 things Italy does better than anywhere http://edition.cnn.com/2013/08/05/travel/10-things-italy-does-better/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    A Disturbing Note in a Recent SI File: "and for this compound, just make up an elemental analysis…"  http://blog.chembark.com/2013/08/06/a-disturbing-note-in-a-recent-si-file/ …    
    
    
    #cikm2013 paper "Social Media News Communities: Gatekeeping, Coverage, and Statement Bias" + appendix now online at http://tinyurl.com/ma532wu     
    
    
    JASIST paper "User Engagement in Online News: Under the Scope of Sentiment, Interest, Affect, and Gaze" now online at http://tinyurl.com/lxp9dy3     
    
    
    #cikm2013 paper "Penguins in Sweaters, or Serendipitous Entity Search on User-generated Content" now available at http://tinyurl.com/lg86e7w     
    
    
    #cikm2013 paper "On the Reliability and Intuitiveness of Aggregated Search Metrics" available now online at http://tinyurl.com/lahcoqq     
    
    
    Here are the fifteen professions that drink the most coffee. Guess who's number one? <<<< "scientists"  http://io9.com/5948206/here-are-the-fifteen-professions-that-drink-the-most-coffee-guess-whos-number-one …    
    
    
    #cikm2013 paper "Online Multitasking and User Engagement" now at http://tinyurl.com/karfox8  more @YahooLabs results on user engagement research    
    
    
    The Machine Zone: This Is Where You Go When You Just Can't Stop Looking at Pictures on Facebook - Atlantic Mobile http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/07/the-machine-zone-this-is-where-you-go-when-you-just-cant-stop-looking-at-pictures-on-facebook/278185/ …    
    
    
    Blogging's First Peer Review - Neuroskeptic | http://DiscoverMagazine.com  http://bit.ly/18lLVzG   via @DiscoverMag    
    
    
    "Measuring Inter-Site Engagement" accepted at IEEE #BigData2013 w/ @elad1 Baeza-Yates @gdupret @_nettele_ & @donmez_pinar    
    
    
    UK wages decline among worst in Europe http://bbc.in/14k6gBx     
    
    
    One in five children bullied online (UK study), says NSPCC survey http://bbc.in/14z58xV     
    
    
    Dibaba ... amazing runner ... elegance, style and power ... http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tirunesh_Dibaba …    
    
    
    Norway PM works as secret cab driver http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-23655675 …    
    
    
    Still no internet in 17% of UK homes http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23620856 …    
    
    
    The Management Myth  http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2006/06/the-management-myth/4883/ …    
    
    
    Usain Bolt crossing the finish line as lightning flashes in the sky could be the best sports photo of 2013 http://on.mash.to/1cHYA5d     
    
    
    What's it like being called Messiah? http://bbc.in/19eDQhy     
    
    
    Search Solutions 2013: lineup announced! http://lnkd.in/Nd3R8G     
    
    
    MSF closes operations in Somalia <<< :-(  feel very very very sorry for "normal" civilians. http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-africa-23697275 …    
    
    
    Toddler verbally abused via baby cam <<< beyond understanding how evil some can be!!! Speechless! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23693460 …    
    
    
    Venezuela gets tough on hair thieves http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-latin-america-23707452 …    
    
    
    Very very very sad news @HCIR_GeneG I will miss your smartness, kindness and sense of humour. Be in peace.    
    
    
    Me too RT @ian_soboroff: Still reeling from the news about @HCIR_GeneG    
    
    
    Twitter trolls attack Gibraltar chief http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-23724064 …    
    
    
    Does it make statistical sense to sack a football manager? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23724517 …    
    
    
    Hello @acmcikm When will the programme be posted ... information would help me planning my trip and how to register. Thanks.    
    
    
    Writing a negative result paper ... not easy ... but easier that writing it as 'see how promising things could perhaps be in the future' :-)    
    
    
    I hardly get any of these ... is it me or they are just not that great? - Chocolate joke is Fringe 'funniest' http://bbc.in/1bO6bfm     
    
    
    Application letter :-) http://image-store.slidesharecdn.com/c678ae84-03cd-11e3-8542-22000a91e9a7-large.jpg …    
    
    
    Have registered for CIKM 2013 - Early registration ends today https://www.regonline.com/cikm2013  #cikm2013    
    
    
    So who remember them all? :-) "25 Things That Were Totally Normal In 1999" http://www.buzzfeed.com/ariellecalderon/things-that-were-totally-normal-in-1999 …    
    
    
    Some truth in this indeed ...  "Why I’m quitting the academy" | Opinion http://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/comment/opinion/why-im-quitting-the-academy/2006622.article …    
    
    
    Humm! A fascinating map of the world’s most and least racially tolerant countries http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2013/05/15/a-fascinating-map-of-the-worlds-most-and-least-racially-tolerant-countries/ …    
    
    
    Why Do So Many Incompetent Men Become Leaders? - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/08/why_do_so_many_incompetent_men.html …    
    
    
    @elad1 I totally agree.    
    
    
    #Batfleck is trending (for me) ... Twitter humour :-)    
    
    
    The Little Mermaid marks centenary http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-23821626 …    
    
    
    City intern death prompts review http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-23820378 …    
    
    
    Excellent read - A Point of View: Democracy and Islamic law http://bbc.in/16E2jfe     
    
    
    Save your work – give software engineers a career track  http://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/news/save-your-work-give-software-engineers-a-career-track/2006431.article …    
    
    
    Seems a good list - Finding Data on the Internet http://www.inside-r.org/howto/finding-data-internet …    
    
    
    :-) RT @GreatestQuotes "The scariest moment is always just before you start." - Stephen King    
    
    
    Liberia students all fail university admission exam http://bbc.in/19UMLIz     
    
    
    At Radboud Uni Nijmegen Information Foraging summer school to give a four-hour lecture on "user engagement" 
http://www.ru.nl/is/ifl/education/eu-intensive-0/call-participation/ …    
    
    
    Research finds 'US effect' exaggerates results in human behaviour studies http://gu.com/p/3t99n/tw     
    
    
    Under current incentive structure in academia, scientists who put the collective good ahead of own personal career are severely punished.    
    
    
    It has always been a great feeling when students enjoy or at least appreciate your lecture/teaching ... I experienced today - so rewarding.    
    
    
    @denzil_correa on a submitted paper or while lecturing?    
    
    
    @denzil_correa I often know when I do good/bad (it can be for many reasons) - I learned to toughen up and I see what I can improve (if)    
    
    
    @denzil_correa when you love the topic it usually works but students don't appreciate then you feel it->I take a deep breath and just do it    
    
    
    @denzil_correa and then I have a serious drink later :-) but for me it is about how I feel the lecture is received & less about the reviews    
    
    
    Reading the news ... the state of the "Middle-East" :-(    
    
    
    The Middle East, explained in one (sort of terrifying) chart http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2013/08/26/the-middle-east-explained-in-one-sort-of-terrifying-chart/ …    
    
    
    'Twerking' makes Oxford dictionary http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-23861702 …    
    
    
    Skype confirms 3D tech research http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23866593 …    
    
    
    Self-Promotion Is Not Crucial (Unless You Want To Get Ahead!)  http://onforb.es/10mFBl9  via @forbes    
    
    
    We submitted a very very very nice negative results paper at #wsdm2014 ... hope the reviewers appreciate it :-)    
    
    
    Brilliant! E-mail error ends up on road sign "I am not in the office at the moment. Send any work to be translated"  http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/7702913.stm …    
    
    
    Ouch! Celtic draw Barca, AC Milan and Ajax http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/23869438 …    
    
    
    Why is Sydney University on strike? Because students are not our 'clients' | Nick Riemer http://gu.com/p/3tbq3/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Saudi Arabia cabinet approves domestic abuse ban http://bbc.in/1dQytYA     
    
    
    Why It's Insane to Pay $132 Million for a Soccer Player  http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130901194138-228008844-why-it-s-insane-to-pay-132-million-for-a-soccer-player-and-why-it-isn-t …    
    
    
    +1 RT @GreatestQuotes "You must have long term goals to keep you from being frustrated by short term failures." - Charles C. Noble    
    
    
    Can't help smiling! 'Walkie-Talkie' skyscraper melts Jaguar car parts http://bbc.in/1cyGyQc     
    
    
    Hilarious :-) Back to work: 10 worst things about post-holiday blues http://bbc.in/15wMF1z     
    
    
    BT switches off dial-up net service http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23877364 …    
    
    
    Hidden mothers in Victorian portraits http://wp.me/p1G5t6-ec  via @MofRIT    
    
    
    Hilarious :-) Parents celebrate the end of six weeks of hellish full-time childcare. http://www.thedailymash.co.uk/news/society/parents-celebrate-end-of-nightmare-2013090379096 …    
    
    
    Re-reading a stats book with great examples of association not being causation, eg the rise of the Samaritans and decrease in suicide.    
    
    
    Brilliant :-) Noam Chomsky to become new X-Factor judge - http://www.newsbiscuit.com/2013/08/30/noam-chomsky-to-become-new-x-factor-judge/ …    
    
    
    Love it :-) :-) True Fact: The Lack of Pirates Is Causing Global Warming  http://onforb.es/GMs6W7     
    
    
    @elunca Statistics by Freedman, Pisani & Purves. Great examples in Chapter 2.    
    
    
    Jonathon Fletcher: forgotten father of the search engine http://bbc.in/1dEn9An     
    
    
    :-) "One day YouTube Twitter and Facebook will join together and be called YouTweetFace!" #fb    
    
    
    Does pressing the pedestrian crossing button actually do anything? http://bbc.in/15XabJf     
    
    
    Not so surprising but can we predict any of this? "To Go from Big Data to Big Insight, Start with a Visual" http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/08/visualizing_how_online_word-of.html …    
    
    
    Interesting how some research gets lots of PR & when you look into it you think either "why" or "humm". I came across 2 such cases recently.    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo Twitter indeed and prediction.    
    
    
    Girl, 2, walked out of nursery http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-merseyside-23973542 …    
    
    
    Loch swimming lesson for island kids http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-glasgow-west-23972383 …    
    
    
    Oh NO! - Currys interview 'humiliation' as graduate 'made to dance' http://bbc.in/17aRfXf     
    
    
    Will China ever be a wine superpower? http://bbc.in/15HHHiy     
    
    
    Love it when a paper slowly starts to shape up ... fun working with @_nettele_ and colleagues.    
    
    
    Surprised to hear it is 1st time in 118 years that a woman conducts Last Night of BBC Proms  http://gu.com/p/3thvg/tw     
    
    
    Why embracing change is the key to happiness http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23986212 …    
    
    
    :-) RT @GreatestQuotes: "No one would talk much in society, if he knew how often he misunderstands others." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe    
    
    
    ++++1 RT @Neuro_Skeptic: "If you torture the data enough, it will confess to anything." Do we need an International Court of P-Value Rights?    
    
    
    Marin Alsop: 'It's a girl!' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24008355 …    
    
    
    The enduring legacy of Freud - Anna Freud http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-23965388 …    
    
    
    -1 RT @BBCSport: Wrestling is reinstated as an Olympic sport from 2020 after being preferred to squash and baseball/softball in an IOC vote    
    
    
    Excellent ... do read ... Recipes for PhD on  #computerscience #informationretrieval http://www.slideshare.net/shokouhi1/recipes-for-phd … @invertedindex    
    
    
    An Aspiring Scientist’s Frustration with Modern-Day Academia: A Resignation http://crypto.junod.info/2013/09/09/an-aspiring-scientists-frustration-with-modern-day-academia-a-resignation/ …    
    
    
    :-) "Academia: The Violent Land of Giant Egos" http://crypto.junod.info/2013/09/09/an-aspiring-scientists-frustration-with-modern-day-academia-a-resignation/ …    
    
    
    "Glaswegians Cockney" ouch ... EastEnders turning Glaswegians Cockney says TV study http://bbc.in/14A4l2m     
    
    
    Looking for query recommender alg for Twitter - we don't want to improve it, just want good query recommendations. Suggestions welcome. Thx.    
    
    
    World's happiest nations are mostly in Scandinavia :-) http://www.cnn.com/2013/09/09/business/earth-institute-world-happiness-rankings/index.html …?    
    
    
    +1 RT @GreatestQuotes: "When you judge another, you do not define them, you define yourself. - Wayne Dyer”    
    
    
    "cool girls" doing science: "I am preparing new adorable slides" I love it :-)    
    
    
    :-) :-) Inaccurate Models [cartoons] http://online-behavior.com/cartoons/inaccurate-models … via @onbehavior    
    
    
    :-) :-) :-) First World Problems on Twitter http://9gag.com/gag/aAYdxzL     
    
    
    Panda diplomacy sparks Belgium row http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-24049879 …    
    
    
    Pushed to the limit as a banking intern http://bbc.in/1g20VFi     
    
    
    :-) Boston (in Lincolnshire) bike rack fixed by group on night out http://bbc.in/17PWYma     
    
    
    "to find a temporary nanny for two meerkat babies that the family had rescued" --  The high-earning butlers of Dubai http://bbc.in/17XCXIs     
    
    
    Lessons Learned From a Freshman-Composition MOOC http://shar.es/ijg5k  via @chronicle    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai looks great.    
    
    
    Wished that conference organisers always provide accommodation that does not blow one travel budget ... #cikm2013 hotel is geez!!!    
    
    
    Yes :-) RT @GreatestQuotes "Silence is more musical than any song." - Christina Rossetti    
    
    
    US woman celebrates name victory http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-24097775 …    
    
    
    ;-) The UK's oddest days out http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24080506 …    
    
    
    Another beautifully negative results paper submitted #chi2014 ... hope reviewers enjoy the beauty of them :-)    
    
    
    Hey "you" ... please don't endorse me for MapReduce ... it just shows you have no clue about my work and skills :-) #LinkedIn    
    
    
    Civet coffee: why it's time to cut the crap http://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/wordofmouth/2013/sep/13/civet-coffee-cut-the-crap …    
    
    
    About to attend my 1st ever scrum ... and this has nothing to do with rugby :-)    
    
    
    Writing a paper with German co-authors ... they must be detective ... they love to "detect" and "reveal" :-)    
    
    
    Sarcasm at its best ... 30 Tips To Being A Better Racist On Twitter http://www.clutchmagonline.com/2013/09/30-tips-better-racist-twitter/ …    
    
    
    I like this say "the cream always rises" :-)    
    
    
    Backlash against running firms like progressive schools   http://econ.st/161wuxy     
    
    
    :-) Merkel about Germany: I think of well-sealed windows. No other country can make such well-sealed and nice windows http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2013/09/2013920114517911768.html …    
    
    
    Khartoon: A satirical take on power by Khalid Albaih http://bbc.in/17NwqkX     
    
    
    I love this one RT @GreatestQuotes: "The difference between stupidity and genius is that genius has its limits." - Albert Einstein    
    
    
    What Lies Between R and D http://www.machinedlearnings.com/2013/09/what-lies-between-r-and-d.html …    
    
    
    Evaluate, evaluate, evaluate (thesis, paper, grant, etc)  http://deevybee.blogspot.co.uk/2013/09/evaluate-evaluate-evaluate.html …    
    
    
    The average woman faces in different countries ... Interesting ... Why no north-African one.  http://myscienceacademy.org/2013/09/22/the-average-women-faces-in-different-countries/ …    
    
    
    As of today, I am a principal research scientist at @YahooLabs and will be based in London. Topic: User engagement :-)    
    
    
    Hilarious ... totally :-) 21 Really Annoying Facebook Friends We All Have http://www.generalforum.com/general-discussion/21-really-annoying-facebook-friends-we-all-have-106532.html …    
    
    
    Cookisto: A new Greek way of getting dinner http://bbc.in/1dC1YfH     
    
    
    @DrSimoneStumpf Happy to do so. Give me a month until I am all settled. Thanks.    
    
    
    Ouch!! Waterproof iPhone Advert: 'Owners Fooled' http://news.sky.com/story/1145439/waterproof-iphone-advert-owners-fooled …    
    
    
    "Things are somehow different in Canada…" beatifullly hilarious :-) http://themetapicture.com/things-are-somehow-different-in-canada/ …    
    
    
    Reader's Digest Dropped Wallets In 19 Cities To Find Out Which One Was The Most Honest http://www.businessinsider.com/helsinki-is-the-worlds-most-honest-city-2013-9 …    
    
    
    “The User Engagement  Death Spiral” by @shashashasha https://medium.com/p/df099b5795f7     
    
    
    Not sure about the term "dark social" though .... Is there more to hidden traffic than 'dark social'? http://www.journalism.co.uk/a554142     
    
    
    It seems that many still confuse "interestingness" and "relevance" ... oh well.    
    
    
    @elunca Some of the papers I am reading on mouse/eye movement ... they use both words I would say not consistently.    
    
    
    @elunca in fact they use the two words as synonyms.    
    
    
    Your Casual Acquaintances on Twitter Are Better Than Your Close Friends on Facebook http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/09/your-friends-have-informational-deficit-which-is-why-we-need-weak-ties/ …    
    
    
    Good read on "creativity & productivity" and "home vs office"  http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/05/fa_thompson/ …    
    
    
    :-) :-) :-) Dinning Out these days http://www.stanleycolors.com/2013/06/dinner-out/ …    
    
    
    Gates calls Ctrl+Alt+Del a mistake http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-24283185 …    
    
    
    +1 RT @GreatestQuotes "One resolution I have made, and try always to keep, is this: To rise above the little things." - John Burroughs    
    
    
    Thanks MT @safetymd: Good talk - Measuring User Engagement by @mounialalmas #eyetracking #focusattention http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/measuring-userengagement …    
    
    
    @safetymd it is being written up.    
    
    
    Top Tweets by Physicists http://wp.me/P38JEA-li     
    
    
    :-) RT @RAGECOLLECTION True friendship is when you walk into their house and your wifi connects automatically.    
    
    
    14 Weird, Open-Ended Job Interview Questions  http://www.businessinsider.com/weird-interview-questions-from-apple-google-amazon-2013-9 …    
    
    
    Many great friends/colleagues at #ictir2013 which I am missing ... have a great conference ... hope to see some tweets about work presented.    
    
    
    :-) Willa's World: 15 Signs You Work At Google http://www.willa.me/2013/09/15-signs-you-work-at-google.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Yup RT @iFromm "Many times the best theory is the simplest one" concludes Baeza-Yates #ictir2013 #keynote    
    
    
    Sweden ranked first for treatment of elderly in UN report http://bbc.in/18JKZ8n     
    
    
    :-) Why Finland loves saunas http://bbc.in/18HMKCN     
    
    
    :-) :-) :-) RT @iFromm Thomas Roelleke demonstrating a Golf analogy to abstraction/models in IR #ictir2013 #panel    
    
    
    @Zolley Nah he is playing golf ... way cheaper ... and I don't get scared when the wind is too strong :-)    
    
    
    How engaged are Wikipedia users? A small study by @JanetteLehmann et al http://wp.me/p3teg2-9c     
    
    
    Indeed :-) RT @RAGECOLLECTION: It's not a good morning without coffee.    
    
    
    France approves 'anti-Amazon' bill http://bbc.in/19jQIpn     
    
    
    :-) Luxury car worth £1.2m clamped outside Harrods http://bbc.in/iJ9DHG     
    
    
    38 tips on writing an academic CV http://blogs.nature.com/naturejobs/2011/09/27/38-tips-on-writing-an-academic-cv …    
    
    
    Purest of the Purists: Grigori Perelman Nautilus http://nautil.us/blog/purest-of-the-purists-the-puzzling-case-of-grigori-perelman …    
    
    
    Sinéad O'Connor's open letter to Miley Cyrus http://gu.com/p/3j963/tw     
    
    
    Georgia Woman Revealed as Voice of Siri http://bit.ly/1hpURqS     
    
    
    Maybe news is just more efficient http://buzzmachine.com/2013/10/06/maybe-news-is-just-more-efficient/ … via @jeffjarvis    
    
    
    The quicker your visit to [a site], ...  then, the better its service <<< yes "dwell time" is not THE metric of engagement.    
    
    
    Humm ... no information about actual measurement! What Part of a Web Page Gets the Highest Viewership? http://www.adweek.com/news/technology/what-part-web-page-gets-highest-viewership-152443 … via @lmoses    
    
    
    If you're a feminist you'll be called a man-hater. You don't need rebranding  http://gu.com/p/3jbm8/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Online, users multitask http://wp.me/p3teg2-aL  @YahooLabs work on user engagement with @JanetteLehmann @gdupret & Baeza-Yates    
    
    
    Cute :-) 22 Animals Who’ve Been Hiding Out In The London Underground Map http://www.buzzfeed.com/robinedds/22-animals-whove-been-hiding-out-in-the-london-underground-m …    
    
    
    Turning the Mirror on Oneself http://occamstypewriter.org/athenedonald/2013/10/08/turning-the-mirror-on-oneself/ … via @athenedonald    
    
    
    Whose science is it anyway? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24477064 …    
    
    
    Made me laugh :-) The new Oxford Dictionary of Humorous Quotations http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/iv-drip/quiz-the-new-oxford-dictionary-of-humorous-quotations-do-you-know-who-said-what-8886548.html …    
    
    
    Awesome "everything you wanted to know about a number but were afraid to ask" http://www.numbergossip.com/     
    
    
    Tried it on several - bad everywhere: Sexism in Autocomplete; rather sad! (not the engine, the people!) http://on.mash.to/1cD3gqI  via @mashable    
    
    
    How the social status of teachers stack up http://econ.st/1gQGChi     
    
    
    11 Unsung Science Heroines  http://www.buzzfeed.com/kellyoakes/11-unsung-science-heroines-you-really-should-have-heard-of …    
    
    
    The F Problem With The P-Value Sciences http://bit.ly/17ClKDx     
    
    
    Bounce rate, infinite clicks and dwell time are my new bedtime words :-)    
    
    
    @denisparra Came up with this word to mean a click from which users never return back to whatever they were doing before the click.    
    
    
    UK Wikipedia in fake entries probe http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-24613608 …    
    
    
    Math For Babies http://on.natgeo.com/17H1Zui     
    
    
    An A-Z of modern office jargon http://www.theguardian.com/money/2013/oct/22/a-z-modern-office-jargon …    
    
    
    "daily active users" >>>  Can Facebook Rewrite the Industry Standard For User Engagement? http://on.mash.to/18KbevL     
    
    
    I like "Define the Action(s) of the Engagement" -- Thinking Strategically About User Engagement Now | Idiom http://www.idiom.co/3-ways-to-start-thinking-strategically-about-user-engagement-now …    
    
    
    BBC News - 100 Women: Who is taking part? http://bbc.in/18AmkFd     
    
    
    Is it just me but papers submitted to database conferences (at least those I am reviewing) are not really about databases?    
    
    
    "Papers submitted to Interaction Records must have been rejected by other publication channels at least three times" http://www.interaction-records.org/index.php/ir     
    
    
    'Spider outbreak' at school! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-gloucestershire-24644816 …    
    
    
    Yes! Coffee v smoothies: Which is better for you? << the former it seems  http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24621394 …    
    
    
    Londoners 'take the most university places' http://bbc.in/1dkofS6     
    
    
    :-) @Queen_UK President Obama just called. Answered in German as a joke and he hung up.    
    
    
    Sad (and shocked) that this is actually needed! Conference anti-harassment policy http://adainitiative.org/what-we-do/conference-policies/ …    
    
    
    :-( :-( :-( @yvolkovich @mounialalmas have you seen this list http://geekfeminism.wikia.com/wiki/Timeline_of_incidents … …?    
    
    
    Women better at multitasking, scientists confirm ... And finding keys :-) hahaha http://fw.to/c8Jmlub     
    
    
    #cikm2013 here I come. Looking forward to meet friends and colleagues and many others.    
    
    
    Love it ... I understand my son better :-)  The joy of slang http://bbc.in/19FQJ4D     
    
    
    :-) None of Your IT Coworkers Understand Your Job [COMIC]  http://on.mash.to/1a2V30H  via @mashable    
    
    
    Wikipedia pilots articles via SMS http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-24662267 …    
    
    
    US immigration asked me "How is Yahoo doing?" ... was about to reply "How is the US doing?" ... but then decided to just say "good"    
    
    
    There’s one key difference between kids who excel at math and those who don’t http://qz.com/139453     
    
    
    A PhD with your coffee? Barista serving your drink might be better educated than you are http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/features/a-phd-with-your-coffee-barista-serving-your-drink-might-be-better-educated-than-you-are-8895053.html …    
    
    
    Many good points here ... Slaves of the Internet, Unite! http://nyti.ms/H9hPau     
    
    
    You made the right choice RT @elunca Large crowd at Dagstuhl. Seems like there was a preference over Burlingame #dagEIR #cikm2013    
    
    
    arrrghhh! RT @elunca @mounialalmas There is fine wine selection :) Just saying.    
    
    
    But I don't like the Dagstuhl pillows :-) RT @elunca @mounialalmas There is fine wine selection :) Just saying.    
    
    
    Looking forward to #esair ... some good science to listen at #cikm2013 in lovely and inspiring Burlingame!    
    
    
    No Woman, No Drive viral video http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24709179 …    
    
    
    Avios mix-up sees woman fly to Grenada, not Granada http://bbc.in/1dhZYJT     
    
    
    Total friendship is when you meet once/twice a year but it feels you met just last week ... total joy.    
    
    
    Penguins in Sweaters, or Serendipitous Entity Search #cikm2013 slides http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/penguins-in-sweaters-or-serendipitous-entity-search-on-usergenerated-content … with @ibordino @yelenamm from @YahooLabs    
    
    
    Online Multitasking and User Engagement #cikm2013 slides  http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/online-multitasking-and-user-engagement … @JanetteLehmann @gdupret & Baeza-Yates -- UPF & @YahooLabs    
    
    
    On the Reliability and Intuitiveness of Aggregated Search Metrics #cikm2013 http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/on-the-reliability-and-intuitiveness-of-aggregated-search-metrics … with Zhou @tetsuyasakai Cummins @joemonj    
    
    
    Social Media News Communities: Gatekeeping, Coverage, and Statement Bias slides #cikm2013 http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/social-media-news-communities-gatekeeping-coverage-and-statement-bias … Saez-Trumper & @ChaToX    
    
    
    Online, users multitask http://wp.me/p3teg2-aL  a blog post about our #cikm2013 paper    
    
    
    Fun at #cikm2013 poster session with @ibordino, @JanetteLehmann & @yelenamm pic.twitter.com/plpw6uBj2S    
    
    
    Diego to present #cikm2013 "Social Media News Communities: Gatekeeping, Coverage, and Statement Bias" ... Slides at http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/social-media-news-communities-gatekeeping-coverage-and-statement-bias …    
    
    
    The penguins are saying thank you #cikm2013    
    
    
    "Networked User Engagement" #cikm2013 #ueo workshop slides at http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/ueo-networks … work with @JanetteLehmann (PhD), Baeza-Yates & @elad1    
    
    
    At #cikm2013 user engagement optimization workshop http://www.ueo-workshop.com  organised by @hongliangjie  et al.    
    
    
    #ueo #cikm2013 take-away message "multiple-response, multi-context modelling to optimise multiple objectives" from Deepak Agarwal keynote.    
    
    
    A tweet being about a topic or some chatter #ueo #cikm2013 from Aleksander Kołcz keynote.    
    
    
    Running  A/A tests ... simple and highly effective ... #ueo #cikm2013 from Ronny Kohavi Keynote.    
    
    
    :-) HIPPO = Highest Paid-Person in Org, or Highest-Paid Person's Opinion #ueo #cikm2013    
    
    
    Thank you RT @Yoellem @mounialalmas so proud of you for your best paper at CIKM 2013!!! You are a rock star! Totally deserved!    
    
    
    Definitions of 34 Twitter Terms http://blog.hubspot.com/marketing/34-twitter-terms-defined-list … via @hubspot    
    
    
    ACM Multimedia 2013 – Best Papers and the Revision Process: "Author's Advocate" blog@CACM  http://cacm.acm.org/blogs/blog-cacm/169387-acm-multimedia-2013-best-papers-and-the-revision-process/fulltext …    
    
    
    We didn't make the title up ... we experienced total serendipity "Penguins in Sweaters" :-) http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Penguin_sweater … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Letters of recommendation for Albert Einstein http://www.lettersofnote.com/2013/11/one-of-most-original-thinkers-i-have.html …    
    
    
    Are children given too many toys? http://bbc.in/1fim93i     
    
    
    High-heel Golfer!!!!! --  Do women need to improve their networking skills? http://bbc.in/190Polx     
    
    
    :-) 30 Very British Problems http://www.buzzfeed.com/lukelewis/very-british-problems …    
    
    
    Camus & Algeria - 7 November 2013 marks Camus’s centenary http://www.nybooks.com/articles/archives/2013/nov/07/camus-and-algeria-moral-question/ … (via @hintikka)    
    
    
    Where in the world are people most depressed? http://gu.com/p/3k8y5/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Lang Lang: Piano teacher said try something else http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24865797 …    
    
    
    Dave Prowse: 'Why I accepted the Star Wars role of Darth Vader' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24876609 …    
    
    
    "scientometrics": The science of science http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/in-their-element-the-science-of-science-2053374.html …    
    
    
    Accurate ... US Expat Describes The Best And Worst Things About England http://www.businessinsider.com/us-expats-in-england-2013-10 …    
    
    
    Politically Adrift, Algeria Clings to Its Old Ways http://nyti.ms/17e3pNd     
    
    
    @tafanor @GillesHub I have just general interests on this topic.    
    
    
    @seawan Yes I am back.    
    
    
    @seawan Yes indeed ... our work also intersect. Let us arrange a meeting.    
    
    
    Dear #london #tube we are not having adverse weather conditions. It is just spitting and the floor is slippery ... Really! Nothing more!    
    
    
    :-) Plan dropped to end cone tradition on Glasgow's Wellington statue http://bbc.in/16WR7vq     
    
    
    Brilliant :-) :-) :-) 25 Frustrating Things About Being An Extrovert http://www.buzzfeed.com/jessicamisener/frustrating-things-about-being-an-extrovert …    
    
    
    John Lewis's Christmas ad: 10 interpretations http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24901114 …    
    
    
    A Victorian model's tragic story http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24803177 …    
    
    
    Botox your CV and online profile http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-24809935 …    
    
    
    Programming as a Profession http://symbo1ics.com/blog/?p=2218     
    
    
    England: Photographs from a bygone era http://bbc.in/HIf2Wa     
    
    
    Oh dear my #linkedin profile makes recruiters think that I am a data scientist :-)    
    
    
    +1 RT @GreatestQuotes: "I'd rather be a failure at something I love than a success at something I hate." - George F. Burns    
    
    
    Russian Subways Now Accept Squats for Payment http://mashable.com/2013/11/12/russian-subway-squats …    
    
    
    Wine-tasting: it's junk science http://gu.com/p/3gjjg/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Recreating childhood photos DOES NOT WORK :-) :-) http://imgmoo.com/index.php/896/recreating-childhood-photos/ …    
    
    
    Oh  #chi2014 you didn't understand that our paper was reporting negative results ... Very interesting ones in fact. Oh well.    
    
    
    @elunca It was rather good negative results ... every time I present this work (talk/seminar) ... people get really interested :-)    
    
    
    Advanced Mathematics With Legos In A Washing Machine http://po.st/tLJvR6  via @popsci    
    
    
    Women's magazines ignore technology and demean women http://www.theguardian.com/women-in-leadership/2013/nov/15/womens-magazines-ignoring-tech …    
    
    
    Barcelona & London ... yeah :-) World's best 18 cities for higher education | Times Higher Education http://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/news/worlds-best-18-cities-for-higher-education/ …    
    
    
    @yvolkovich never buy them ... only times I read them is when in  waiting room (doctor, hairdresser, etc) ... I recognize hardly anybody :-)    
    
    
    anybody remember ref of paper/poster on using webpage "features" to predict its "aesthetics" ... maybe published at WWW etc ... thanks.    
    
    
    @shoha99 Thanks but I have this one.    
    
    
    San Francisco rallies for sick 'Batkid' Miles Scott http://bbc.in/1ja55fK     
    
    
    Argh please GIVE us a break & let us be the way we wish ... The Top 5 Mistakes Women Make in Academic Settings http://theprofessorisin.com/2013/11/10/the-top-5-mistakes-women-make-in-academic-settings/ …    
    
    
    :-) 30 hilarious street posters you certainly haven’t seen around | Just something (creative) http://justsomething.co/30-hilarious-street-posters-you-certainly-havent-seen-around/ … via @justsomethingco    
    
    
    Weak statistical standards implicated in scientific irreproducibility http://www.nature.com/news/weak-statistical-standards-implicated-in-scientific-irreproducibility-1.14131 …    
    
    
    'You're Not A Princess' Ad Campaign Pushes Female Empowerment http://mashable.com/2013/11/16/you-are-not-a-princess-ad/#:eyJzIjoidCIsImkiOiJfbnJ5bzVldzcyencxemt0MXExMjlxXyJ9 … via @mashable    
    
    
    One should not confuse "user experience", "usability" and "user engagement" :-)    
    
    
    If you want to understand/study "user engagement" do it with respect to a decent user experience and a decent interface/GUI!    
    
    
    ... and it is perfectly fine to keep some level of modesty in your "bio" ... or at least some neutrality :-)    
    
    
    :-) RT @krisztianbalog There seems to be an inverse correlation between review length and academic seniority.    
    
    
    'Selfie' named by Oxford Dictionaries as word of 2013 http://bbc.in/1gZAdSy     
    
    
    Cyclist tweet rant driver guilty http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-norfolk-25000788 …    
    
    
    Many children 'slower runners than their parents were' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-24998497 …    
    
    
    Broadband: Readers' bad and good experiences http://bbc.in/1eh1lcl     
    
    
    Don't Confuse Engagement with User Experience - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/2012/12/dont-confuse-engagement-with-u/ …    
    
    
    Thanks for a great welcome @ddholliday @cityuni_hcid    
    
    
    @DrSimoneStumpf thanks so much for the invitation. It was great fun.    
    
    
    Thank you so much @BioStew    
    
    
    oh dear .... The Ashes 2013-14: England ridiculed for sending 82-page list of goji berry and quinoa catering demands http://fw.to/YQYJsvF     
    
    
    +100 :-) RT @GreatestQuotes "Common sense is not so common." - Voltaire    
    
    
    The football match that started a revolution http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-25033749 …    
    
    
    Does university management matter? http://www.theguardian.com/higher-education-network/blog/2013/nov/12/university-management-teaching-research-impact …    
    
    
    Bounce Rate (another def - not discussed here - is time spent on site below threshold) http://mashable.com/2013/11/22/bounce-rate-metrics …    
    
    
    BIS blew its budget, and now the entire higher education sector will have to pay  http://gu.com/p/3ktz9/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Cal lecturer's email to students goes viral: "Why I am not canceling class tomorrow" http://alumni.berkeley.edu/california-magazine/just-in/2013-11-21/cal-lecturers-email-students-goes-viral-why-i-am-not …    
    
    
    anybody have pdf of "Predicting user attention in complex web pages" ... please DM me.    
    
    
    Do More Women on the Board Mean Better Results? http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/currency/2013/11/do-companies-with-female-board-members-perform-better.html …  via @NewYorker    
    
    
    Will be talking about "An engaging click" at Search Solutions 2013 http://irsg.bcs.org/SearchSolutions/2013/sse2013.php …    
    
    
    @kelvinnewman I would say the events tend to be IR/search focused ... but anybody with basic IR/search should follow with no problem.    
    
    
    @annviera I did already.    
    
    
    +1 "easy is a plus, not a minus" http://mybiasedcoin.blogspot.co.uk/2013/11/easy-now.html …    
    
    
    Opposition to mobile chat on planes http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-25058358 …    
    
    
    Interested in research in user engagement? I am looking for interns. Please DM. Thanks.    
    
    
    An Engaging Click ... or how can user engagement measurement inform web search evaluation #SearchSolutions2013 http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/an-engaging-click-28635338 …    
    
    
    Stunning Photographs Inspired by Edward Hopper Paintings http://www.slate.com/blogs/behold/2013/11/25/richard_tuschman_edward_hopper_recreations_are_inspired_by_the_painter_s.html … via @slate    
    
    
    Question at #searchsolutions2013 "do you like your search results to be personalised?" Answers kind of split half. Curious about others?    
    
    
    International problem solving techniques :-) https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-CVLwi6lJjuY/UpTVa_YhexI/AAAAAAAAFhM/NvisFJf7Ynw/w551-h874-no/1470057_10201625328649688_1725790405_n.jpg … pic.twitter.com/1M8H4cHYBN    
    
    
    IQ: How important is a high IQ? http://bbc.in/1fP9ms6     
    
    
    The quest to turn computers into creative artists http://bbc.in/1hlMfWs     
    
    
    Rather surprised by number of websites not optimised for mobile experience ... even for reading ...    
    
    
    I like this definition RT @GreatestQuotes "Success is liking yourself, liking what you do, and liking how you do it." - Maya Angelou    
    
    
    Engagement is synonymous with retention, which is the most critical element in a sustainable, scalable growth dynamic http://500.co/2013/11/19/when-and-how-to-define-your-user-engagement-cycle/ …    
    
    
    UE=positive emotional connection with users leading in user experience that exceeds simple matter of supply & demand http://socialfresh.com/community-engagement/ …    
    
    
    + London @YahooLabs This week's featured job post is for our Barcelona 2014 internship opportunities. Go on, apply! http://comunicacio.barcelonamedia.org/yahoo/     
    
    
    Know any detailed report/review about how frequently users click on online ads (any format)? Looking for general insights and trends. Thx.    
    
    
    RIP Mandela    
    
    
    The sporting legacy of Nelson Mandela http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/25262862     
    
    
    :-) 25 readers' designs for a new union jack http://bbc.in/1blCbsQ     
    
    
    1/2 Higgs said he became "an embarrassment to the department when they did research assessment exercises".    
    
    
    2/2 Message would go in department: "Please give a list of your recent publications." Higgs said: "I would send back a statement: 'None.'    
    
    
    women strategy: not to try to be like men but to be themselves &need to be better at telling what they are doing&why http://huff.to/1dUFHxQ     
    
    
    Nelson Mandela Tweet Leads to Backlash Against Hollywood Journalist http://mashable.com/2013/12/06/nikki-finke-obit-hashtag/ …    
    
    
    @BBCNews Archbishop Desmond Tutu now addressing the stadium, asking the crowd to be quiet - he "wants to hear a pin drop".    
    
    
    @Yoellem superb great news.    
    
    
    French cafe causes a stir by rewarding 'polite' clients http://bbc.in/1h2uedn     
    
    
    :-) RT @imdaGrumpyCat: I should just change my voicemail greeting to: "Please hang up and text me, thanks."    
    
    
    Bots 'take up 61% of web traffic' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-25346235 …    
    
    
    Brilliant :-) 38 Test Answers That Are 100% Wrong But Totally Genius At The Same Time http://distractify.com/fun/fails/test-answers-that-are-totally-wrong-but-still-genius/ … via @Distractify    
    
    
    #BBCtrending: #NotYourAsianSidekick goes global http://bbc.in/1cM2ngq     
    
    
    Facebook tops 2013 Google searches http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-25402626 …    
    
    
    The Top 10 Things People Didn't Understand in 2013 http://mashable.com/2013/12/17/things-to-understand-2013/#:eyJzIjoidCIsImkiOiJfbnJ5bzVldzcyencxemt0MXExMjlxXyJ9 … via @mashable    
    
    
    Standing ovation for Hacene Lalmas at the Algerian Ballon d'Or ceremony (in French) http://www.liberte-algerie.com/sports/slimani-succede-a-feghouli-lalmas-la-surprise-de-la-soiree-ballon-d-or-el-heddaf-le-buteur-212291 …    
    
    
    Tourist walks off Australia pier while checking Facebook http://bbc.in/1bP43oq     
    
    
    Toys R Us's Stockholm superstore goes gender neutral http://gu.com/p/3ydah/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Flying coach can be a bruising experience these days http://nyti.ms/1d2nVpq     
    
    
    BBC News - Did this family survive 2013 on British-made goods? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-25490772 …    
    
    
    :-) 10 People Who Only Show Up During the Holidays http://mashable.com/2013/11/28/holiday-stereotypes/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Happy holiday pic.twitter.com/TiWRU1vzTb (courtesy) @UberFacts    
    
    
    The sport of fists and the game of kings: boxing and chess! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-25491642 …    
    
    
    A bit of social media humour :-) pic.twitter.com/ykxTQqVSnW    
    
    
    Reduce Bounce Rate: 20 Things to Consider http://sewat.ch/XiguOK  via @sewatch    
    
    
    @EONhelp Our boiler broke down again & are told nobody can come until Friday. Who can I reach to help us (we have an e.on heating care) Thx.    
    
    
    A great person left us. RIP Gary Marsden. You will be missed dearly.    
    
    
    Composite retrieval of heterogeneous web search accepted at #www2014 with Bota, Zhou & @joemonj.    
    
    
    4 Trends Paid Search Marketers Must Address In 2014: Audience, Relevance, Social & Mobile http://searchengineland.com/4-trends-marketers-must-address-in-2014-audience-relevance-social-mobile-179844 … via @sengineland    
    
    
    Page Load Time - The Silent Sales Killer http://shar.es/9ouXe     
    
    
    'Time Spent' on site and what this means http://mashable.com/2013/12/13/time-spent-metrics/ …    
    
    
    20 of 2013's most overused words http://bbc.in/18WX4Mb     
    
    
    Bibliometrics: Global gender disparities in science http://www.nature.com/news/bibliometrics-global-gender-disparities-in-science-1.14321 …    
    
    
    Twitter and traditional bibliometrics are separate but complementary aspects of research impact. http://blogs.lse.ac.uk/impactofsocialsciences/2014/01/02/twitter-citations-research-impact-darling/ …    
    
    
    News Use Across Social Media Platforms http://pewrsr.ch/174IiQt     
    
    
    User experience debt. http://nform.com/blog/2013/05/user-experience-debt …    
    
    
    :-) 12 New Year's resolutions that should be abandoned http://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2014/jan/03/12-new-years-resolutions-should-be-abandoned …    
    
    
    "Hell" explained by a student in an exam :-) http://themetapicture.com/hell-explained-by-an-engineer-cant-say-i-didnt-expect-that/ …    
    
    
    Some university bosses 'had 8% rise' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/education-25577066 …    
    
    
    Last night on TV I saw an ad about online casino for ladies ... Pink Casino ... Why do "they" think that women require pink? Argh!    
    
    
    I Never get the Good One’s! How many Paper to Review? http://pielot.org/2013/07/14/i-never-get-the-good-ones-how-many-paper-to-review/ …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Nothing about the collections/methodologies developed at CLEF and INEX?    
    
    
    Prepare for the New Permanent Temp - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/schrage/2013/07/prepare-for-the-new-permanent.html …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Piwowarski et al. Sound and Complete Relevance Assessment for XML Retrieval, ACM TOIS, 27(1), Article 1, 37 pages, 2008.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Ogilvie & Lalmas. Investigating the Exhaustivity Dimension in Content-Oriented XML Element Retrieval Evaluation, CIKM 2006.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Trotman & Lalmas. Why Structural Hints in Queries do not Help XML Retrieval, ACM SIGIR August 2006 (Poster).    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Have sent you a selection which is about what we did, what worked and what didn't (sent only those co-authored by me).    
    
    
    Google Maps wipes out Scottish island of Jura http://bbc.in/12DqlGF     
    
    
    Agree "A dinosaur hangs up his claws: why I am leaving the EPSRC College of Peers" the ending kind of says it all! http://iansommerville.com/techstuff/a-dinosaur-hangs-up-his-claws-why-i-am-leaving-the-epsrc-college-of-peers/ …    
    
    
    "Big Science vs. Little Science: How Scientific Impact Scales with Funding" It seems it does not!!! http://www.plosone.org/article/info:doi/10.1371/journal.pone.0065263 …    
    
    
    Yes right!!! Senior Pakistani Taliban leader 'shocked' by Malala attack http://bbc.in/1dEW23W     
    
    
    Counting crowds http://bbc.in/15IVs4i     
    
    
    Stevie Wonder’s Florida Boycott: His Zimmerman verdict protest is savvy and important. http://www.slate.com/articles/arts/culturebox/2013/07/stevie_wonder_s_florida_boycott_his_zimmerman_verdict_protest_is_savvy_and.html …    
    
    
    Arghh! Wished that workshop submissions were all a max of 4 pages ... not full 10 pages ... arghh arghh.    
    
    
    Yes! - Fifa loses free-to-air World Cup TV battle in the UK http://bbc.in/12JyiKs     
    
    
    :-) What Your Toilet Paper Style Says About You [COMIC]  http://on.mash.to/13AMhO0  via @mashable    
    
    
    France's knicker industry: In a twist and losing jobs http://bbc.in/13jAjcI     
    
    
    Bots help geeks nab best tables http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23462687 …    
    
    
    Twitter action urged after threats http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23477130 …    
    
    
    :-((( Italy minister suffers banana insult http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-23480489 …    
    
    
    Have all a great #sigir2013 ... will try to follow tweets from lovely Antibes.    
    
    
    Very very very sad news - Ilya Segalovich, Yandex co-founder, dies after cancer http://bbc.in/16qew5i     
    
    
    I struggle to understand such evil ... why? - Caroline Criado-Perez Twitter abuse case leads to arrest http://bbc.in/1e4j9Fb     
    
    
    Am I the only researcher reviewing papers while on holiday?    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai Oh I have another 2 conf papers to review and they are not for you ... but OK for the drink :-)    
    
    
    Thomas Roelleke M&C book on "Information Retrieval Models: Foundations and Relationships" out in time for #sigir2013 http://www.morganclaypool.com/doi/abs/10.2200/S00494ED1V01Y201304ICR027 …    
    
    
    #cikm2013 UEO workshop paper "Networked User engagement" online at http://www.dcs.gla.ac.uk/~mounia/Papers/cikm2013_ueo.pdf … w/ @_nettele_ Baeza-Yates & @elad1    
    
    
    Twitter abuse: Why cyberbullies are targeting women http://bbc.in/11pK7o1     
    
    
    +1 RT @sharathrao: @dtunkelang your excellent tweets summarizing sessions/papers must be filed under community service!  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Haha :-) Passengers on delayed easyJet flight are given 86 years for replacement http://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/passengers-on-delayed-easyjet-flight-are-given-86-years-to-browse-dutyfree-shops-8737340.html …    
    
    
    #FancyAcademics looking forwards to photos #sigir2013 rather curious I have to admit :-)    
    
    
    +1 RT @djoerd: @tetsuyasakai I vote for Tokyo!    
    
    
    Open-plan offices http://bbc.in/1cbSWrz     
    
    
    Zhou etal  slides #sigir2013 #mube Evaluating Heterogeneous Information Access (Position Paper)  #aggregatedsearch at http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/mube-slides …    
    
    
    @dtunkelang Quantum cognition: and does it work?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang I could not have come up with a better answer ... I did try to work on QT for IR ... but decided slowly it was beyond me :-)    
    
    
    @julian_urbano Happened at INEX many years ago - I kept saying "If I can't get it 150% we can't use it - we had heated debate about metrics.    
    
    
    @YahooLabs work on user engagement - Ricardo Baeza-Yates keynote at #sigir2013 industry track "An engaging click" http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/an-engaging-click …    
    
    
    Living room TV 'making a comeback' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23521277 …    
    
    
    ++++1 RT @yelenamm Some of these have plagued me for a long time http://grammarist.com/easily-confused-words/ …    
    
    
    @SIGIR2013? MT @marcosluis2186: @mounialalmas @YahooLabs amazing keynote about User Engagement from Baeza-Yates. Do you have the video?    
    
    
    We should tell some this :-) Selfish traits not favoured by evolution, study shows http://bbc.in/17okTWf     
    
    
    Which country gets the most tourists? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23433149 …    
    
    
    Should you take an email sabbatical? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23547802 …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs UPF and Glasgow paper "User Engagement in Online News: Under the Scope of Sentiment, Interest, Affect & Gaze" accepted at JASIST    
    
    
    :-) 10 things Italy does better than anywhere http://edition.cnn.com/2013/08/05/travel/10-things-italy-does-better/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    A Disturbing Note in a Recent SI File: "and for this compound, just make up an elemental analysis…"  http://blog.chembark.com/2013/08/06/a-disturbing-note-in-a-recent-si-file/ …    
    
    
    #cikm2013 paper "Social Media News Communities: Gatekeeping, Coverage, and Statement Bias" + appendix now online at http://tinyurl.com/ma532wu     
    
    
    JASIST paper "User Engagement in Online News: Under the Scope of Sentiment, Interest, Affect, and Gaze" now online at http://tinyurl.com/lxp9dy3     
    
    
    #cikm2013 paper "Penguins in Sweaters, or Serendipitous Entity Search on User-generated Content" now available at http://tinyurl.com/lg86e7w     
    
    
    #cikm2013 paper "On the Reliability and Intuitiveness of Aggregated Search Metrics" available now online at http://tinyurl.com/lahcoqq     
    
    
    Here are the fifteen professions that drink the most coffee. Guess who's number one? <<<< "scientists"  http://io9.com/5948206/here-are-the-fifteen-professions-that-drink-the-most-coffee-guess-whos-number-one …    
    
    
    #cikm2013 paper "Online Multitasking and User Engagement" now at http://tinyurl.com/karfox8  more @YahooLabs results on user engagement research    
    
    
    The Machine Zone: This Is Where You Go When You Just Can't Stop Looking at Pictures on Facebook - Atlantic Mobile http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/07/the-machine-zone-this-is-where-you-go-when-you-just-cant-stop-looking-at-pictures-on-facebook/278185/ …    
    
    
    Blogging's First Peer Review - Neuroskeptic | http://DiscoverMagazine.com  http://bit.ly/18lLVzG   via @DiscoverMag    
    
    
    "Measuring Inter-Site Engagement" accepted at IEEE #BigData2013 w/ @elad1 Baeza-Yates @gdupret @_nettele_ & @donmez_pinar    
    
    
    UK wages decline among worst in Europe http://bbc.in/14k6gBx     
    
    
    One in five children bullied online (UK study), says NSPCC survey http://bbc.in/14z58xV     
    
    
    Dibaba ... amazing runner ... elegance, style and power ... http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tirunesh_Dibaba …    
    
    
    Norway PM works as secret cab driver http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-23655675 …    
    
    
    Still no internet in 17% of UK homes http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23620856 …    
    
    
    The Management Myth  http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2006/06/the-management-myth/4883/ …    
    
    
    Usain Bolt crossing the finish line as lightning flashes in the sky could be the best sports photo of 2013 http://on.mash.to/1cHYA5d     
    
    
    What's it like being called Messiah? http://bbc.in/19eDQhy     
    
    
    Search Solutions 2013: lineup announced! http://lnkd.in/Nd3R8G     
    
    
    MSF closes operations in Somalia <<< :-(  feel very very very sorry for "normal" civilians. http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-africa-23697275 …    
    
    
    Toddler verbally abused via baby cam <<< beyond understanding how evil some can be!!! Speechless! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23693460 …    
    
    
    Venezuela gets tough on hair thieves http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-latin-america-23707452 …    
    
    
    Very very very sad news @HCIR_GeneG I will miss your smartness, kindness and sense of humour. Be in peace.    
    
    
    Me too RT @ian_soboroff: Still reeling from the news about @HCIR_GeneG    
    
    
    Twitter trolls attack Gibraltar chief http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-23724064 …    
    
    
    Does it make statistical sense to sack a football manager? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23724517 …    
    
    
    Hello @acmcikm When will the programme be posted ... information would help me planning my trip and how to register. Thanks.    
    
    
    Writing a negative result paper ... not easy ... but easier that writing it as 'see how promising things could perhaps be in the future' :-)    
    
    
    I hardly get any of these ... is it me or they are just not that great? - Chocolate joke is Fringe 'funniest' http://bbc.in/1bO6bfm     
    
    
    Application letter :-) http://image-store.slidesharecdn.com/c678ae84-03cd-11e3-8542-22000a91e9a7-large.jpg …    
    
    
    Have registered for CIKM 2013 - Early registration ends today https://www.regonline.com/cikm2013  #cikm2013    
    
    
    So who remember them all? :-) "25 Things That Were Totally Normal In 1999" http://www.buzzfeed.com/ariellecalderon/things-that-were-totally-normal-in-1999 …    
    
    
    Some truth in this indeed ...  "Why I’m quitting the academy" | Opinion http://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/comment/opinion/why-im-quitting-the-academy/2006622.article …    
    
    
    Humm! A fascinating map of the world’s most and least racially tolerant countries http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2013/05/15/a-fascinating-map-of-the-worlds-most-and-least-racially-tolerant-countries/ …    
    
    
    Why Do So Many Incompetent Men Become Leaders? - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/08/why_do_so_many_incompetent_men.html …    
    
    
    @elad1 I totally agree.    
    
    
    #Batfleck is trending (for me) ... Twitter humour :-)    
    
    
    The Little Mermaid marks centenary http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-23821626 …    
    
    
    City intern death prompts review http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-23820378 …    
    
    
    Excellent read - A Point of View: Democracy and Islamic law http://bbc.in/16E2jfe     
    
    
    Save your work – give software engineers a career track  http://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/news/save-your-work-give-software-engineers-a-career-track/2006431.article …    
    
    
    Seems a good list - Finding Data on the Internet http://www.inside-r.org/howto/finding-data-internet …    
    
    
    :-) RT @GreatestQuotes "The scariest moment is always just before you start." - Stephen King    
    
    
    Liberia students all fail university admission exam http://bbc.in/19UMLIz     
    
    
    At Radboud Uni Nijmegen Information Foraging summer school to give a four-hour lecture on "user engagement" 
http://www.ru.nl/is/ifl/education/eu-intensive-0/call-participation/ …    
    
    
    Research finds 'US effect' exaggerates results in human behaviour studies http://gu.com/p/3t99n/tw     
    
    
    Under current incentive structure in academia, scientists who put the collective good ahead of own personal career are severely punished.    
    
    
    It has always been a great feeling when students enjoy or at least appreciate your lecture/teaching ... I experienced today - so rewarding.    
    
    
    @denzil_correa on a submitted paper or while lecturing?    
    
    
    @denzil_correa I often know when I do good/bad (it can be for many reasons) - I learned to toughen up and I see what I can improve (if)    
    
    
    @denzil_correa when you love the topic it usually works but students don't appreciate then you feel it->I take a deep breath and just do it    
    
    
    @denzil_correa and then I have a serious drink later :-) but for me it is about how I feel the lecture is received & less about the reviews    
    
    
    Reading the news ... the state of the "Middle-East" :-(    
    
    
    The Middle East, explained in one (sort of terrifying) chart http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2013/08/26/the-middle-east-explained-in-one-sort-of-terrifying-chart/ …    
    
    
    'Twerking' makes Oxford dictionary http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-23861702 …    
    
    
    Skype confirms 3D tech research http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23866593 …    
    
    
    Self-Promotion Is Not Crucial (Unless You Want To Get Ahead!)  http://onforb.es/10mFBl9  via @forbes    
    
    
    We submitted a very very very nice negative results paper at #wsdm2014 ... hope the reviewers appreciate it :-)    
    
    
    Brilliant! E-mail error ends up on road sign "I am not in the office at the moment. Send any work to be translated"  http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/7702913.stm …    
    
    
    Ouch! Celtic draw Barca, AC Milan and Ajax http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/23869438 …    
    
    
    Why is Sydney University on strike? Because students are not our 'clients' | Nick Riemer http://gu.com/p/3tbq3/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Saudi Arabia cabinet approves domestic abuse ban http://bbc.in/1dQytYA     
    
    
    Why It's Insane to Pay $132 Million for a Soccer Player  http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130901194138-228008844-why-it-s-insane-to-pay-132-million-for-a-soccer-player-and-why-it-isn-t …    
    
    
    +1 RT @GreatestQuotes "You must have long term goals to keep you from being frustrated by short term failures." - Charles C. Noble    
    
    
    Can't help smiling! 'Walkie-Talkie' skyscraper melts Jaguar car parts http://bbc.in/1cyGyQc     
    
    
    Hilarious :-) Back to work: 10 worst things about post-holiday blues http://bbc.in/15wMF1z     
    
    
    BT switches off dial-up net service http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23877364 …    
    
    
    Hidden mothers in Victorian portraits http://wp.me/p1G5t6-ec  via @MofRIT    
    
    
    Hilarious :-) Parents celebrate the end of six weeks of hellish full-time childcare. http://www.thedailymash.co.uk/news/society/parents-celebrate-end-of-nightmare-2013090379096 …    
    
    
    Re-reading a stats book with great examples of association not being causation, eg the rise of the Samaritans and decrease in suicide.    
    
    
    Brilliant :-) Noam Chomsky to become new X-Factor judge - http://www.newsbiscuit.com/2013/08/30/noam-chomsky-to-become-new-x-factor-judge/ …    
    
    
    Love it :-) :-) True Fact: The Lack of Pirates Is Causing Global Warming  http://onforb.es/GMs6W7     
    
    
    @elunca Statistics by Freedman, Pisani & Purves. Great examples in Chapter 2.    
    
    
    Jonathon Fletcher: forgotten father of the search engine http://bbc.in/1dEn9An     
    
    
    :-) "One day YouTube Twitter and Facebook will join together and be called YouTweetFace!" #fb    
    
    
    Does pressing the pedestrian crossing button actually do anything? http://bbc.in/15XabJf     
    
    
    Not so surprising but can we predict any of this? "To Go from Big Data to Big Insight, Start with a Visual" http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/08/visualizing_how_online_word-of.html …    
    
    
    Interesting how some research gets lots of PR & when you look into it you think either "why" or "humm". I came across 2 such cases recently.    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo Twitter indeed and prediction.    
    
    
    Girl, 2, walked out of nursery http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-merseyside-23973542 …    
    
    
    Loch swimming lesson for island kids http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-glasgow-west-23972383 …    
    
    
    Oh NO! - Currys interview 'humiliation' as graduate 'made to dance' http://bbc.in/17aRfXf     
    
    
    Will China ever be a wine superpower? http://bbc.in/15HHHiy     
    
    
    Love it when a paper slowly starts to shape up ... fun working with @_nettele_ and colleagues.    
    
    
    Surprised to hear it is 1st time in 118 years that a woman conducts Last Night of BBC Proms  http://gu.com/p/3thvg/tw     
    
    
    Why embracing change is the key to happiness http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23986212 …    
    
    
    :-) RT @GreatestQuotes: "No one would talk much in society, if he knew how often he misunderstands others." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe    
    
    
    ++++1 RT @Neuro_Skeptic: "If you torture the data enough, it will confess to anything." Do we need an International Court of P-Value Rights?    
    
    
    Marin Alsop: 'It's a girl!' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24008355 …    
    
    
    The enduring legacy of Freud - Anna Freud http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-23965388 …    
    
    
    -1 RT @BBCSport: Wrestling is reinstated as an Olympic sport from 2020 after being preferred to squash and baseball/softball in an IOC vote    
    
    
    Excellent ... do read ... Recipes for PhD on  #computerscience #informationretrieval http://www.slideshare.net/shokouhi1/recipes-for-phd … @invertedindex    
    
    
    An Aspiring Scientist’s Frustration with Modern-Day Academia: A Resignation http://crypto.junod.info/2013/09/09/an-aspiring-scientists-frustration-with-modern-day-academia-a-resignation/ …    
    
    
    :-) "Academia: The Violent Land of Giant Egos" http://crypto.junod.info/2013/09/09/an-aspiring-scientists-frustration-with-modern-day-academia-a-resignation/ …    
    
    
    "Glaswegians Cockney" ouch ... EastEnders turning Glaswegians Cockney says TV study http://bbc.in/14A4l2m     
    
    
    Looking for query recommender alg for Twitter - we don't want to improve it, just want good query recommendations. Suggestions welcome. Thx.    
    
    
    World's happiest nations are mostly in Scandinavia :-) http://www.cnn.com/2013/09/09/business/earth-institute-world-happiness-rankings/index.html …?    
    
    
    +1 RT @GreatestQuotes: "When you judge another, you do not define them, you define yourself. - Wayne Dyer”    
    
    
    "cool girls" doing science: "I am preparing new adorable slides" I love it :-)    
    
    
    :-) :-) Inaccurate Models [cartoons] http://online-behavior.com/cartoons/inaccurate-models … via @onbehavior    
    
    
    :-) :-) :-) First World Problems on Twitter http://9gag.com/gag/aAYdxzL     
    
    
    Panda diplomacy sparks Belgium row http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-24049879 …    
    
    
    Pushed to the limit as a banking intern http://bbc.in/1g20VFi     
    
    
    :-) Boston (in Lincolnshire) bike rack fixed by group on night out http://bbc.in/17PWYma     
    
    
    "to find a temporary nanny for two meerkat babies that the family had rescued" --  The high-earning butlers of Dubai http://bbc.in/17XCXIs     
    
    
    Lessons Learned From a Freshman-Composition MOOC http://shar.es/ijg5k  via @chronicle    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai looks great.    
    
    
    Wished that conference organisers always provide accommodation that does not blow one travel budget ... #cikm2013 hotel is geez!!!    
    
    
    Yes :-) RT @GreatestQuotes "Silence is more musical than any song." - Christina Rossetti    
    
    
    US woman celebrates name victory http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-24097775 …    
    
    
    ;-) The UK's oddest days out http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24080506 …    
    
    
    Another beautifully negative results paper submitted #chi2014 ... hope reviewers enjoy the beauty of them :-)    
    
    
    Hey "you" ... please don't endorse me for MapReduce ... it just shows you have no clue about my work and skills :-) #LinkedIn    
    
    
    Civet coffee: why it's time to cut the crap http://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/wordofmouth/2013/sep/13/civet-coffee-cut-the-crap …    
    
    
    About to attend my 1st ever scrum ... and this has nothing to do with rugby :-)    
    
    
    Writing a paper with German co-authors ... they must be detective ... they love to "detect" and "reveal" :-)    
    
    
    Sarcasm at its best ... 30 Tips To Being A Better Racist On Twitter http://www.clutchmagonline.com/2013/09/30-tips-better-racist-twitter/ …    
    
    
    I like this say "the cream always rises" :-)    
    
    
    Backlash against running firms like progressive schools   http://econ.st/161wuxy     
    
    
    :-) Merkel about Germany: I think of well-sealed windows. No other country can make such well-sealed and nice windows http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2013/09/2013920114517911768.html …    
    
    
    Khartoon: A satirical take on power by Khalid Albaih http://bbc.in/17NwqkX     
    
    
    I love this one RT @GreatestQuotes: "The difference between stupidity and genius is that genius has its limits." - Albert Einstein    
    
    
    What Lies Between R and D http://www.machinedlearnings.com/2013/09/what-lies-between-r-and-d.html …    
    
    
    Evaluate, evaluate, evaluate (thesis, paper, grant, etc)  http://deevybee.blogspot.co.uk/2013/09/evaluate-evaluate-evaluate.html …    
    
    
    The average woman faces in different countries ... Interesting ... Why no north-African one.  http://myscienceacademy.org/2013/09/22/the-average-women-faces-in-different-countries/ …    
    
    
    As of today, I am a principal research scientist at @YahooLabs and will be based in London. Topic: User engagement :-)    
    
    
    Hilarious ... totally :-) 21 Really Annoying Facebook Friends We All Have http://www.generalforum.com/general-discussion/21-really-annoying-facebook-friends-we-all-have-106532.html …    
    
    
    Cookisto: A new Greek way of getting dinner http://bbc.in/1dC1YfH     
    
    
    @DrSimoneStumpf Happy to do so. Give me a month until I am all settled. Thanks.    
    
    
    Ouch!! Waterproof iPhone Advert: 'Owners Fooled' http://news.sky.com/story/1145439/waterproof-iphone-advert-owners-fooled …    
    
    
    "Things are somehow different in Canada…" beatifullly hilarious :-) http://themetapicture.com/things-are-somehow-different-in-canada/ …    
    
    
    Reader's Digest Dropped Wallets In 19 Cities To Find Out Which One Was The Most Honest http://www.businessinsider.com/helsinki-is-the-worlds-most-honest-city-2013-9 …    
    
    
    “The User Engagement  Death Spiral” by @shashashasha https://medium.com/p/df099b5795f7     
    
    
    Not sure about the term "dark social" though .... Is there more to hidden traffic than 'dark social'? http://www.journalism.co.uk/a554142     
    
    
    It seems that many still confuse "interestingness" and "relevance" ... oh well.    
    
    
    @elunca Some of the papers I am reading on mouse/eye movement ... they use both words I would say not consistently.    
    
    
    @elunca in fact they use the two words as synonyms.    
    
    
    Your Casual Acquaintances on Twitter Are Better Than Your Close Friends on Facebook http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/09/your-friends-have-informational-deficit-which-is-why-we-need-weak-ties/ …    
    
    
    Good read on "creativity & productivity" and "home vs office"  http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/05/fa_thompson/ …    
    
    
    :-) :-) :-) Dinning Out these days http://www.stanleycolors.com/2013/06/dinner-out/ …    
    
    
    Gates calls Ctrl+Alt+Del a mistake http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-24283185 …    
    
    
    +1 RT @GreatestQuotes "One resolution I have made, and try always to keep, is this: To rise above the little things." - John Burroughs    
    
    
    Thanks MT @safetymd: Good talk - Measuring User Engagement by @mounialalmas #eyetracking #focusattention http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/measuring-userengagement …    
    
    
    @safetymd it is being written up.    
    
    
    Top Tweets by Physicists http://wp.me/P38JEA-li     
    
    
    :-) RT @RAGECOLLECTION True friendship is when you walk into their house and your wifi connects automatically.    
    
    
    14 Weird, Open-Ended Job Interview Questions  http://www.businessinsider.com/weird-interview-questions-from-apple-google-amazon-2013-9 …    
    
    
    Many great friends/colleagues at #ictir2013 which I am missing ... have a great conference ... hope to see some tweets about work presented.    
    
    
    :-) Willa's World: 15 Signs You Work At Google http://www.willa.me/2013/09/15-signs-you-work-at-google.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Yup RT @iFromm "Many times the best theory is the simplest one" concludes Baeza-Yates #ictir2013 #keynote    
    
    
    Sweden ranked first for treatment of elderly in UN report http://bbc.in/18JKZ8n     
    
    
    :-) Why Finland loves saunas http://bbc.in/18HMKCN     
    
    
    :-) :-) :-) RT @iFromm Thomas Roelleke demonstrating a Golf analogy to abstraction/models in IR #ictir2013 #panel    
    
    
    @Zolley Nah he is playing golf ... way cheaper ... and I don't get scared when the wind is too strong :-)    
    
    
    How engaged are Wikipedia users? A small study by @JanetteLehmann et al http://wp.me/p3teg2-9c     
    
    
    Indeed :-) RT @RAGECOLLECTION: It's not a good morning without coffee.    
    
    
    France approves 'anti-Amazon' bill http://bbc.in/19jQIpn     
    
    
    :-) Luxury car worth £1.2m clamped outside Harrods http://bbc.in/iJ9DHG     
    
    
    38 tips on writing an academic CV http://blogs.nature.com/naturejobs/2011/09/27/38-tips-on-writing-an-academic-cv …    
    
    
    Purest of the Purists: Grigori Perelman Nautilus http://nautil.us/blog/purest-of-the-purists-the-puzzling-case-of-grigori-perelman …    
    
    
    Sinéad O'Connor's open letter to Miley Cyrus http://gu.com/p/3j963/tw     
    
    
    Georgia Woman Revealed as Voice of Siri http://bit.ly/1hpURqS     
    
    
    Maybe news is just more efficient http://buzzmachine.com/2013/10/06/maybe-news-is-just-more-efficient/ … via @jeffjarvis    
    
    
    The quicker your visit to [a site], ...  then, the better its service <<< yes "dwell time" is not THE metric of engagement.    
    
    
    Humm ... no information about actual measurement! What Part of a Web Page Gets the Highest Viewership? http://www.adweek.com/news/technology/what-part-web-page-gets-highest-viewership-152443 … via @lmoses    
    
    
    If you're a feminist you'll be called a man-hater. You don't need rebranding  http://gu.com/p/3jbm8/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Online, users multitask http://wp.me/p3teg2-aL  @YahooLabs work on user engagement with @JanetteLehmann @gdupret & Baeza-Yates    
    
    
    Cute :-) 22 Animals Who’ve Been Hiding Out In The London Underground Map http://www.buzzfeed.com/robinedds/22-animals-whove-been-hiding-out-in-the-london-underground-m …    
    
    
    Turning the Mirror on Oneself http://occamstypewriter.org/athenedonald/2013/10/08/turning-the-mirror-on-oneself/ … via @athenedonald    
    
    
    Whose science is it anyway? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24477064 …    
    
    
    Made me laugh :-) The new Oxford Dictionary of Humorous Quotations http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/iv-drip/quiz-the-new-oxford-dictionary-of-humorous-quotations-do-you-know-who-said-what-8886548.html …    
    
    
    Awesome "everything you wanted to know about a number but were afraid to ask" http://www.numbergossip.com/     
    
    
    Tried it on several - bad everywhere: Sexism in Autocomplete; rather sad! (not the engine, the people!) http://on.mash.to/1cD3gqI  via @mashable    
    
    
    How the social status of teachers stack up http://econ.st/1gQGChi     
    
    
    11 Unsung Science Heroines  http://www.buzzfeed.com/kellyoakes/11-unsung-science-heroines-you-really-should-have-heard-of …    
    
    
    The F Problem With The P-Value Sciences http://bit.ly/17ClKDx     
    
    
    Bounce rate, infinite clicks and dwell time are my new bedtime words :-)    
    
    
    @denisparra Came up with this word to mean a click from which users never return back to whatever they were doing before the click.    
    
    
    UK Wikipedia in fake entries probe http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-24613608 …    
    
    
    Math For Babies http://on.natgeo.com/17H1Zui     
    
    
    An A-Z of modern office jargon http://www.theguardian.com/money/2013/oct/22/a-z-modern-office-jargon …    
    
    
    "daily active users" >>>  Can Facebook Rewrite the Industry Standard For User Engagement? http://on.mash.to/18KbevL     
    
    
    I like "Define the Action(s) of the Engagement" -- Thinking Strategically About User Engagement Now | Idiom http://www.idiom.co/3-ways-to-start-thinking-strategically-about-user-engagement-now …    
    
    
    BBC News - 100 Women: Who is taking part? http://bbc.in/18AmkFd     
    
    
    Is it just me but papers submitted to database conferences (at least those I am reviewing) are not really about databases?    
    
    
    "Papers submitted to Interaction Records must have been rejected by other publication channels at least three times" http://www.interaction-records.org/index.php/ir     
    
    
    'Spider outbreak' at school! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-gloucestershire-24644816 …    
    
    
    Yes! Coffee v smoothies: Which is better for you? << the former it seems  http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24621394 …    
    
    
    Londoners 'take the most university places' http://bbc.in/1dkofS6     
    
    
    :-) @Queen_UK President Obama just called. Answered in German as a joke and he hung up.    
    
    
    Sad (and shocked) that this is actually needed! Conference anti-harassment policy http://adainitiative.org/what-we-do/conference-policies/ …    
    
    
    :-( :-( :-( @yvolkovich @mounialalmas have you seen this list http://geekfeminism.wikia.com/wiki/Timeline_of_incidents … …?    
    
    
    Women better at multitasking, scientists confirm ... And finding keys :-) hahaha http://fw.to/c8Jmlub     
    
    
    #cikm2013 here I come. Looking forward to meet friends and colleagues and many others.    
    
    
    Love it ... I understand my son better :-)  The joy of slang http://bbc.in/19FQJ4D     
    
    
    :-) None of Your IT Coworkers Understand Your Job [COMIC]  http://on.mash.to/1a2V30H  via @mashable    
    
    
    Wikipedia pilots articles via SMS http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-24662267 …    
    
    
    US immigration asked me "How is Yahoo doing?" ... was about to reply "How is the US doing?" ... but then decided to just say "good"    
    
    
    There’s one key difference between kids who excel at math and those who don’t http://qz.com/139453     
    
    
    A PhD with your coffee? Barista serving your drink might be better educated than you are http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/features/a-phd-with-your-coffee-barista-serving-your-drink-might-be-better-educated-than-you-are-8895053.html …    
    
    
    Many good points here ... Slaves of the Internet, Unite! http://nyti.ms/H9hPau     
    
    
    You made the right choice RT @elunca Large crowd at Dagstuhl. Seems like there was a preference over Burlingame #dagEIR #cikm2013    
    
    
    arrrghhh! RT @elunca @mounialalmas There is fine wine selection :) Just saying.    
    
    
    But I don't like the Dagstuhl pillows :-) RT @elunca @mounialalmas There is fine wine selection :) Just saying.    
    
    
    Looking forward to #esair ... some good science to listen at #cikm2013 in lovely and inspiring Burlingame!    
    
    
    No Woman, No Drive viral video http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24709179 …    
    
    
    Avios mix-up sees woman fly to Grenada, not Granada http://bbc.in/1dhZYJT     
    
    
    Total friendship is when you meet once/twice a year but it feels you met just last week ... total joy.    
    
    
    Penguins in Sweaters, or Serendipitous Entity Search #cikm2013 slides http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/penguins-in-sweaters-or-serendipitous-entity-search-on-usergenerated-content … with @ibordino @yelenamm from @YahooLabs    
    
    
    Online Multitasking and User Engagement #cikm2013 slides  http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/online-multitasking-and-user-engagement … @JanetteLehmann @gdupret & Baeza-Yates -- UPF & @YahooLabs    
    
    
    On the Reliability and Intuitiveness of Aggregated Search Metrics #cikm2013 http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/on-the-reliability-and-intuitiveness-of-aggregated-search-metrics … with Zhou @tetsuyasakai Cummins @joemonj    
    
    
    Social Media News Communities: Gatekeeping, Coverage, and Statement Bias slides #cikm2013 http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/social-media-news-communities-gatekeeping-coverage-and-statement-bias … Saez-Trumper & @ChaToX    
    
    
    Online, users multitask http://wp.me/p3teg2-aL  a blog post about our #cikm2013 paper    
    
    
    Fun at #cikm2013 poster session with @ibordino, @JanetteLehmann & @yelenamm pic.twitter.com/plpw6uBj2S    
    
    
    Diego to present #cikm2013 "Social Media News Communities: Gatekeeping, Coverage, and Statement Bias" ... Slides at http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/social-media-news-communities-gatekeeping-coverage-and-statement-bias …    
    
    
    The penguins are saying thank you #cikm2013    
    
    
    "Networked User Engagement" #cikm2013 #ueo workshop slides at http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/ueo-networks … work with @JanetteLehmann (PhD), Baeza-Yates & @elad1    
    
    
    At #cikm2013 user engagement optimization workshop http://www.ueo-workshop.com  organised by @hongliangjie  et al.    
    
    
    #ueo #cikm2013 take-away message "multiple-response, multi-context modelling to optimise multiple objectives" from Deepak Agarwal keynote.    
    
    
    A tweet being about a topic or some chatter #ueo #cikm2013 from Aleksander Kołcz keynote.    
    
    
    Running  A/A tests ... simple and highly effective ... #ueo #cikm2013 from Ronny Kohavi Keynote.    
    
    
    :-) HIPPO = Highest Paid-Person in Org, or Highest-Paid Person's Opinion #ueo #cikm2013    
    
    
    Thank you RT @Yoellem @mounialalmas so proud of you for your best paper at CIKM 2013!!! You are a rock star! Totally deserved!    
    
    
    Definitions of 34 Twitter Terms http://blog.hubspot.com/marketing/34-twitter-terms-defined-list … via @hubspot    
    
    
    ACM Multimedia 2013 – Best Papers and the Revision Process: "Author's Advocate" blog@CACM  http://cacm.acm.org/blogs/blog-cacm/169387-acm-multimedia-2013-best-papers-and-the-revision-process/fulltext …    
    
    
    We didn't make the title up ... we experienced total serendipity "Penguins in Sweaters" :-) http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Penguin_sweater … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Letters of recommendation for Albert Einstein http://www.lettersofnote.com/2013/11/one-of-most-original-thinkers-i-have.html …    
    
    
    Are children given too many toys? http://bbc.in/1fim93i     
    
    
    High-heel Golfer!!!!! --  Do women need to improve their networking skills? http://bbc.in/190Polx     
    
    
    :-) 30 Very British Problems http://www.buzzfeed.com/lukelewis/very-british-problems …    
    
    
    Camus & Algeria - 7 November 2013 marks Camus’s centenary http://www.nybooks.com/articles/archives/2013/nov/07/camus-and-algeria-moral-question/ … (via @hintikka)    
    
    
    Where in the world are people most depressed? http://gu.com/p/3k8y5/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Lang Lang: Piano teacher said try something else http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24865797 …    
    
    
    Dave Prowse: 'Why I accepted the Star Wars role of Darth Vader' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24876609 …    
    
    
    "scientometrics": The science of science http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/in-their-element-the-science-of-science-2053374.html …    
    
    
    Accurate ... US Expat Describes The Best And Worst Things About England http://www.businessinsider.com/us-expats-in-england-2013-10 …    
    
    
    Politically Adrift, Algeria Clings to Its Old Ways http://nyti.ms/17e3pNd     
    
    
    @tafanor @GillesHub I have just general interests on this topic.    
    
    
    @seawan Yes I am back.    
    
    
    @seawan Yes indeed ... our work also intersect. Let us arrange a meeting.    
    
    
    Dear #london #tube we are not having adverse weather conditions. It is just spitting and the floor is slippery ... Really! Nothing more!    
    
    
    :-) Plan dropped to end cone tradition on Glasgow's Wellington statue http://bbc.in/16WR7vq     
    
    
    Brilliant :-) :-) :-) 25 Frustrating Things About Being An Extrovert http://www.buzzfeed.com/jessicamisener/frustrating-things-about-being-an-extrovert …    
    
    
    John Lewis's Christmas ad: 10 interpretations http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24901114 …    
    
    
    A Victorian model's tragic story http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24803177 …    
    
    
    Botox your CV and online profile http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-24809935 …    
    
    
    Programming as a Profession http://symbo1ics.com/blog/?p=2218     
    
    
    England: Photographs from a bygone era http://bbc.in/HIf2Wa     
    
    
    Oh dear my #linkedin profile makes recruiters think that I am a data scientist :-)    
    
    
    +1 RT @GreatestQuotes: "I'd rather be a failure at something I love than a success at something I hate." - George F. Burns    
    
    
    Russian Subways Now Accept Squats for Payment http://mashable.com/2013/11/12/russian-subway-squats …    
    
    
    Wine-tasting: it's junk science http://gu.com/p/3gjjg/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Recreating childhood photos DOES NOT WORK :-) :-) http://imgmoo.com/index.php/896/recreating-childhood-photos/ …    
    
    
    Oh  #chi2014 you didn't understand that our paper was reporting negative results ... Very interesting ones in fact. Oh well.    
    
    
    @elunca It was rather good negative results ... every time I present this work (talk/seminar) ... people get really interested :-)    
    
    
    Advanced Mathematics With Legos In A Washing Machine http://po.st/tLJvR6  via @popsci    
    
    
    Women's magazines ignore technology and demean women http://www.theguardian.com/women-in-leadership/2013/nov/15/womens-magazines-ignoring-tech …    
    
    
    Barcelona & London ... yeah :-) World's best 18 cities for higher education | Times Higher Education http://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/news/worlds-best-18-cities-for-higher-education/ …    
    
    
    @yvolkovich never buy them ... only times I read them is when in  waiting room (doctor, hairdresser, etc) ... I recognize hardly anybody :-)    
    
    
    anybody remember ref of paper/poster on using webpage "features" to predict its "aesthetics" ... maybe published at WWW etc ... thanks.    
    
    
    @shoha99 Thanks but I have this one.    
    
    
    San Francisco rallies for sick 'Batkid' Miles Scott http://bbc.in/1ja55fK     
    
    
    Argh please GIVE us a break & let us be the way we wish ... The Top 5 Mistakes Women Make in Academic Settings http://theprofessorisin.com/2013/11/10/the-top-5-mistakes-women-make-in-academic-settings/ …    
    
    
    :-) 30 hilarious street posters you certainly haven’t seen around | Just something (creative) http://justsomething.co/30-hilarious-street-posters-you-certainly-havent-seen-around/ … via @justsomethingco    
    
    
    Weak statistical standards implicated in scientific irreproducibility http://www.nature.com/news/weak-statistical-standards-implicated-in-scientific-irreproducibility-1.14131 …    
    
    
    'You're Not A Princess' Ad Campaign Pushes Female Empowerment http://mashable.com/2013/11/16/you-are-not-a-princess-ad/#:eyJzIjoidCIsImkiOiJfbnJ5bzVldzcyencxemt0MXExMjlxXyJ9 … via @mashable    
    
    
    One should not confuse "user experience", "usability" and "user engagement" :-)    
    
    
    If you want to understand/study "user engagement" do it with respect to a decent user experience and a decent interface/GUI!    
    
    
    ... and it is perfectly fine to keep some level of modesty in your "bio" ... or at least some neutrality :-)    
    
    
    :-) RT @krisztianbalog There seems to be an inverse correlation between review length and academic seniority.    
    
    
    'Selfie' named by Oxford Dictionaries as word of 2013 http://bbc.in/1gZAdSy     
    
    
    Cyclist tweet rant driver guilty http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-norfolk-25000788 …    
    
    
    Many children 'slower runners than their parents were' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-24998497 …    
    
    
    Broadband: Readers' bad and good experiences http://bbc.in/1eh1lcl     
    
    
    Don't Confuse Engagement with User Experience - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/2012/12/dont-confuse-engagement-with-u/ …    
    
    
    Thanks for a great welcome @ddholliday @cityuni_hcid    
    
    
    @DrSimoneStumpf thanks so much for the invitation. It was great fun.    
    
    
    Thank you so much @BioStew    
    
    
    oh dear .... The Ashes 2013-14: England ridiculed for sending 82-page list of goji berry and quinoa catering demands http://fw.to/YQYJsvF     
    
    
    +100 :-) RT @GreatestQuotes "Common sense is not so common." - Voltaire    
    
    
    The football match that started a revolution http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-25033749 …    
    
    
    Does university management matter? http://www.theguardian.com/higher-education-network/blog/2013/nov/12/university-management-teaching-research-impact …    
    
    
    Bounce Rate (another def - not discussed here - is time spent on site below threshold) http://mashable.com/2013/11/22/bounce-rate-metrics …    
    
    
    BIS blew its budget, and now the entire higher education sector will have to pay  http://gu.com/p/3ktz9/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Cal lecturer's email to students goes viral: "Why I am not canceling class tomorrow" http://alumni.berkeley.edu/california-magazine/just-in/2013-11-21/cal-lecturers-email-students-goes-viral-why-i-am-not …    
    
    
    anybody have pdf of "Predicting user attention in complex web pages" ... please DM me.    
    
    
    Do More Women on the Board Mean Better Results? http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/currency/2013/11/do-companies-with-female-board-members-perform-better.html …  via @NewYorker    
    
    
    Will be talking about "An engaging click" at Search Solutions 2013 http://irsg.bcs.org/SearchSolutions/2013/sse2013.php …    
    
    
    @kelvinnewman I would say the events tend to be IR/search focused ... but anybody with basic IR/search should follow with no problem.    
    
    
    @annviera I did already.    
    
    
    +1 "easy is a plus, not a minus" http://mybiasedcoin.blogspot.co.uk/2013/11/easy-now.html …    
    
    
    Opposition to mobile chat on planes http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-25058358 …    
    
    
    Interested in research in user engagement? I am looking for interns. Please DM. Thanks.    
    
    
    An Engaging Click ... or how can user engagement measurement inform web search evaluation #SearchSolutions2013 http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/an-engaging-click-28635338 …    
    
    
    Stunning Photographs Inspired by Edward Hopper Paintings http://www.slate.com/blogs/behold/2013/11/25/richard_tuschman_edward_hopper_recreations_are_inspired_by_the_painter_s.html … via @slate    
    
    
    Question at #searchsolutions2013 "do you like your search results to be personalised?" Answers kind of split half. Curious about others?    
    
    
    International problem solving techniques :-) https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-CVLwi6lJjuY/UpTVa_YhexI/AAAAAAAAFhM/NvisFJf7Ynw/w551-h874-no/1470057_10201625328649688_1725790405_n.jpg … pic.twitter.com/1M8H4cHYBN    
    
    
    IQ: How important is a high IQ? http://bbc.in/1fP9ms6     
    
    
    The quest to turn computers into creative artists http://bbc.in/1hlMfWs     
    
    
    Rather surprised by number of websites not optimised for mobile experience ... even for reading ...    
    
    
    I like this definition RT @GreatestQuotes "Success is liking yourself, liking what you do, and liking how you do it." - Maya Angelou    
    
    
    Engagement is synonymous with retention, which is the most critical element in a sustainable, scalable growth dynamic http://500.co/2013/11/19/when-and-how-to-define-your-user-engagement-cycle/ …    
    
    
    UE=positive emotional connection with users leading in user experience that exceeds simple matter of supply & demand http://socialfresh.com/community-engagement/ …    
    
    
    + London @YahooLabs This week's featured job post is for our Barcelona 2014 internship opportunities. Go on, apply! http://comunicacio.barcelonamedia.org/yahoo/     
    
    
    Know any detailed report/review about how frequently users click on online ads (any format)? Looking for general insights and trends. Thx.    
    
    
    RIP Mandela    
    
    
    The sporting legacy of Nelson Mandela http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/25262862     
    
    
    :-) 25 readers' designs for a new union jack http://bbc.in/1blCbsQ     
    
    
    1/2 Higgs said he became "an embarrassment to the department when they did research assessment exercises".    
    
    
    2/2 Message would go in department: "Please give a list of your recent publications." Higgs said: "I would send back a statement: 'None.'    
    
    
    women strategy: not to try to be like men but to be themselves &need to be better at telling what they are doing&why http://huff.to/1dUFHxQ     
    
    
    Nelson Mandela Tweet Leads to Backlash Against Hollywood Journalist http://mashable.com/2013/12/06/nikki-finke-obit-hashtag/ …    
    
    
    @BBCNews Archbishop Desmond Tutu now addressing the stadium, asking the crowd to be quiet - he "wants to hear a pin drop".    
    
    
    @Yoellem superb great news.    
    
    
    French cafe causes a stir by rewarding 'polite' clients http://bbc.in/1h2uedn     
    
    
    :-) RT @imdaGrumpyCat: I should just change my voicemail greeting to: "Please hang up and text me, thanks."    
    
    
    Bots 'take up 61% of web traffic' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-25346235 …    
    
    
    Brilliant :-) 38 Test Answers That Are 100% Wrong But Totally Genius At The Same Time http://distractify.com/fun/fails/test-answers-that-are-totally-wrong-but-still-genius/ … via @Distractify    
    
    
    #BBCtrending: #NotYourAsianSidekick goes global http://bbc.in/1cM2ngq     
    
    
    Facebook tops 2013 Google searches http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-25402626 …    
    
    
    The Top 10 Things People Didn't Understand in 2013 http://mashable.com/2013/12/17/things-to-understand-2013/#:eyJzIjoidCIsImkiOiJfbnJ5bzVldzcyencxemt0MXExMjlxXyJ9 … via @mashable    
    
    
    Standing ovation for Hacene Lalmas at the Algerian Ballon d'Or ceremony (in French) http://www.liberte-algerie.com/sports/slimani-succede-a-feghouli-lalmas-la-surprise-de-la-soiree-ballon-d-or-el-heddaf-le-buteur-212291 …    
    
    
    Tourist walks off Australia pier while checking Facebook http://bbc.in/1bP43oq     
    
    
    Toys R Us's Stockholm superstore goes gender neutral http://gu.com/p/3ydah/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Flying coach can be a bruising experience these days http://nyti.ms/1d2nVpq     
    
    
    BBC News - Did this family survive 2013 on British-made goods? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-25490772 …    
    
    
    :-) 10 People Who Only Show Up During the Holidays http://mashable.com/2013/11/28/holiday-stereotypes/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Happy holiday pic.twitter.com/TiWRU1vzTb (courtesy) @UberFacts    
    
    
    The sport of fists and the game of kings: boxing and chess! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-25491642 …    
    
    
    A bit of social media humour :-) pic.twitter.com/ykxTQqVSnW    
    
    
    Reduce Bounce Rate: 20 Things to Consider http://sewat.ch/XiguOK  via @sewatch    
    
    
    @EONhelp Our boiler broke down again & are told nobody can come until Friday. Who can I reach to help us (we have an e.on heating care) Thx.    
    
    
    A great person left us. RIP Gary Marsden. You will be missed dearly.    
    
    
    Composite retrieval of heterogeneous web search accepted at #www2014 with Bota, Zhou & @joemonj.    
    
    
    4 Trends Paid Search Marketers Must Address In 2014: Audience, Relevance, Social & Mobile http://searchengineland.com/4-trends-marketers-must-address-in-2014-audience-relevance-social-mobile-179844 … via @sengineland    
    
    
    Page Load Time - The Silent Sales Killer http://shar.es/9ouXe     
    
    
    'Time Spent' on site and what this means http://mashable.com/2013/12/13/time-spent-metrics/ …    
    
    
    20 of 2013's most overused words http://bbc.in/18WX4Mb     
    
    
    Bibliometrics: Global gender disparities in science http://www.nature.com/news/bibliometrics-global-gender-disparities-in-science-1.14321 …    
    
    
    Twitter and traditional bibliometrics are separate but complementary aspects of research impact. http://blogs.lse.ac.uk/impactofsocialsciences/2014/01/02/twitter-citations-research-impact-darling/ …    
    
    
    News Use Across Social Media Platforms http://pewrsr.ch/174IiQt     
    
    
    User experience debt. http://nform.com/blog/2013/05/user-experience-debt …    
    
    
    :-) 12 New Year's resolutions that should be abandoned http://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2014/jan/03/12-new-years-resolutions-should-be-abandoned …    
    
    
    "Hell" explained by a student in an exam :-) http://themetapicture.com/hell-explained-by-an-engineer-cant-say-i-didnt-expect-that/ …    
    
    
    Some university bosses 'had 8% rise' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/education-25577066 …    
    
    
    Last night on TV I saw an ad about online casino for ladies ... Pink Casino ... Why do "they" think that women require pink? Argh!    
    
    
    