Honorary Guest @JustFabOnline http://www.justfab.com/index.cfm?action=home.product_public_lp&pid=558385&ha=12FA5BFAE282330E43DB1940CD9F7848&layout=main …    
    
    
    More footwear goodness from @JustFabOnline #JustFabStyle http://instagram.com/p/fGY5HwyKez/     
    
    
    Look what TargetStyle shared on Instagram! LOVE! #RedHighHeels http://fb.me/1z3rXwrFW     
    
    
    @DUNCANMILESMD @JustFabOnline Great to support breast cancer research w/ #PINK  purchases!    
    
    
    My skin is really happy with this #Neutrogena Rapid Tone Repair Night Moisturizer! If you are looking… http://instagram.com/p/fIZjgaSKcn/     
    
    
    Found a great olive trench at @tjmaxx It was so chic! #Maxxinista #glamstyle http://instagram.com/p/fJYoCXSKXQ/     
    
    
    These are the top 3 favorite pins on my Pinterst Hair Inspiration board. Which one has your vote?? #hair

For... http://fb.me/2LgnwYpka     
    
    
    Style Squad: Effortless Halloween Costume Ideas: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SZtCSix9I4g&feature=share&list=SPijk13kqreIehFTCovlzjbfPCQQboQlD9 … via @Glam_com    
    
    
    Look what's new! Achieve Gorgeous Long Lashes by 2014 - When asked, what my one essential beauty product is, I alw... http://ow.ly/2AvEoo     
    
    
    Has it always been your dream to have long, lush lashes?  Yes? Then here is a deal you can't pass up! Dr. Duncan... http://fb.me/2T4YyYII5     
    
    
    Small business owners: @AliBrown's "Marketing Mastery Workshop" will help you start making the money you really want. http://ow.ly/pAcGc     
    
    
    The Ultimate Model-Approved Fall Fashion Wish List http://www.modelinia.com/blog/the-ultimate-model-approved-fall-fashion-wish-list/54924#.UlMNIns2FWp.twitter … via @modelinia    
    
    
    Don't Miss This: @AliBrown's "Marketing Mastery Workshop." Start making the money you really want, register for FREE. http://ow.ly/pAcT6     
    
    
    Biz Coach, @AliBrown shares her "Marketing Mastery Workshop" for FREE! Register now! Fun begins tmrw! http://ow.ly/pAcT6     
    
    
    The 6 (Simple) Style Secrets of Successful Women (Including How to Get Dressed Quickly and Look Fab!) http://ow.ly/pAOj6     
    
    
    Biz Coach, @AliBrown shares her "Marketing Mastery Workshop" for FREE! Register now! http://ow.ly/pAcT6     
    
    
    FREE Report: The 6 (Simple) Style Secrets of Successful Women (Including How to Get Dressed Quickly and Look Fab!) http://ow.ly/pAOj6     
    
    
    FREE FABulous tips for dressing your best every day! http://ow.ly/pAOio     
    
    
    Small business owners, join this free web event now! http://fb.me/1gH3LUpzZ     
    
    
    8 Successful Women Who Were Once Fired http://huff.to/1f5eEL5  via @HuffPostWomen    
    
    
    Sharing a tiny patch of sun. So sweet! http://instagram.com/p/fN1qNfSKb8/     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1JihYYrt9     
    
    
    Achieve Gorgeous Long Lashes by 2014 (+ an awesome deal you won't want to miss!) - http://amominredhighheels.com/achieve-gorgeous-long-lashes-2014/ …    
    
    
    Don't miss this special deal! http://lnkd.in/bv4MbX4     
    
    
    Look what's new! You'll Dye For These Fall Hair Colors - It's time to give your hair a seasonal update with a bra... http://ow.ly/2AyOn6     
    
    
    You'll Dye For These Fall Hair Colors - http://amominredhighheels.com/2013-fall-hair-colors/ …    
    
    
    It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas! Loving these Limited Edition Chapstick Holiday Tins. Look… http://instagram.com/p/fQT0gLSKeM/     
    
    
    You'll Dye For These Fall Hair Colors - Which color is your fave? http://amominredhighheels.com/2013-fall-hair-colors/ …    
    
    
    LIKE if you agree! http://fb.me/1s1zowhFK     
    
    
    Think fall, ladies!  These are the Hottest Hair Colors for Fall 2013!  Which is your favorite? Pin it or print it... http://fb.me/25uJefDns     
    
    
    Halloween style for your little #Maxxinista at @tjmaxx #glamstyle http://instagram.com/p/fRbSEVSKXa/     
    
    
    Rockin' the Red Booties @polyvore http://polyv.re/19BkSo5     
    
    
    Pro-Style in Red Booties @polyvore http://polyv.re/GMAGZb     
    
    
    Did you know you can pick up quality makeup brushes at @tjmaxx? They have everything a #Maxxinista… http://instagram.com/p/fRrHb7yKVr/     
    
    
    Love this heel and dress combo! http://amominredhighheels.com/enter-win-red-carpet-experience-neiman-marcus/ …    
    
    
    The purchase of this watch helps support the Breast Cancer Research Foundation.Love this watch! http://www.pinterest.com/pin/150166968798805914/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! 2 Ways to Rock the Red Bootie - Don't you love when you get a pair of shoes that you just love an... http://ow.ly/2ABuur     
    
    
    Latest trends + classics at @LordandTaylor's NEW store (Mizner Park, Boca Raton, FL)! Store opens TODAY! http://ow.ly/pF92m  #LTBoca #sp    
    
    
    Celebrate #NationalHandbagDay w/ a new one from @tjmaxx #glamstyle #Maxxinista Many colors and styles… http://instagram.com/p/fS8xkaSKaY/     
    
    
    2 Ways to Rock the Red Bootie "Harrison" from @JustFabOnline #JustFabStyle http://amominredhighheels.com/2-ways-rock-red-bootie/ …    
    
    
    This bootie is the perfect shade of red for fall and the perfect shape for casual or professional outfits.  Find out…http://lnkd.in/bYNE8sv     
    
    
    Two ways to rock these seriously awesome #RED booties!  
http://amominredhighheels.com/2-ways-rock-red-bootie/ …... http://fb.me/MJ261Iof     
    
    
    Thank goodness! You can still listen in on @AliBrown's Marketing Mastery Workshop" SUCH good info! Register for free: http://ow.ly/pJLc9     
    
    
    Triple braid bun updo http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798817618/ …    
    
    
    classic mini and white top compliment red heels nicely http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798817624/ …    
    
    
    You don't have to be born beautiful to be wildly attractive. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798817630/ …    
    
    
    Christian Louboutin Lady Peep-Toe Patent Platform Pump, Red - Neiman Marcus http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798817633/ …    
    
    
    Compete with yourself to improve your life! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798817639/ …    
    
    
    Ana Khouri Rough Emerald Michelle Cuff at http://Barneys.com  http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798817642/ …    
    
    
    The most pinned hairstyle on my Pinterest Hair Inspiration board with 1138 repins! Do you love this brunette ombre... http://fb.me/ZzcWAfxz     
    
    
    The "it" boot for fall is an ankle boot. @tjmaxx offers styles that work with pants, dresses and… http://instagram.com/p/fZGWJySKRm/     
    
    
    2 Ways to Rock the Red Bootie (these heels are HOT!) - http://amominredhighheels.com/2-ways-rock-red-bootie/ …    
    
    
    You'll Dye For These Fall Hair Colors - http://amominredhighheels.com/2013-fall-hair-colors/ …    
    
    
    Achieve Gorgeous Long Lashes by 2014 - http://amominredhighheels.com/achieve-gorgeous-long-lashes-2014/ …    
    
    
    Exercise finder: Click on the area of your body you want to tone and it gives you a list of exercise http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823536/ …    
    
    
    5 tips to make your blowout last http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823538/ …    
    
    
    Schutz Besma Embellished Open Toe Booties http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823547/ …    
    
    
    Schutz Brenae Studded T Strap Pumps http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823548/ …    
    
    
    Theory Eldah Paramount Wool Dress http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823549/ …    
    
    
    Rebecca Taylor Short Sleeve Scroll Embellished Dress http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823550/ …    
    
    
    Free People Modern Dress http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823552/ …    
    
    
    Gunmetal-tone trim creates an armored look on leather BCBGMAXAZRIA pumps http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823554/ …    
    
    
    Alejandro Ingelmo puts a sexy twist on the T-strap silhouette. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823555/ …    
    
    
    Rachel Roy Osana Ankle Strap Sandals http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823559/ …    
    
    
    FREE Encore presentation of a @AliBrown 6-HOUR LIVE online workshop just for small business owners http://ow.ly/pJM9a     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2D4bB04db     
    
    
    Pink Pony Soft http://RickyRalphLauren.com  http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798823591/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! 5 Tips to Make Your Blowout Last - Regular professional blowouts are becoming quite the norm late... http://ow.ly/2AGzy7     
    
    
    Mega tears when this beautiful boot was sold out in my size at @tjmaxx Some #Maxxinista totally… http://instagram.com/p/fc62BwyKbb/     
    
    
    Looking for a new fall hair color? These are the hottest hue trends of the season: http://amominredhighheels.com/2013-fall-hair-colors/ …    
    
    
    Amazing hair doesn't just happen. It takes good products, a great stylist and daily maintenance!  Use these tips... http://fb.me/1zPj8OX94     
    
    
    Gucci 2013 http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798831338/ …    
    
    
    Smooth http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798831341/ …    
    
    
    5 Tips to Make Your Blowout Last via @bestyledblowdry http://ow.ly/pNK3A     
    
    
    There is a chill in the air! @tjmaxx has great coats! These are so perfect for #travel - lightweight… http://instagram.com/p/fdNmMMSKbZ/     
    
    
    @DeniseDT Your bedhead hair question answered here:  http://ow.ly/pO52n  xo    
    
    
    JustFab and MARY KAY teamed up to bring you a gorgeous gift with purchase!

 Laurie Shumate, Mary Kay Independent... http://fb.me/2FGHkQCBF     
    
    
    Casual Chic Look @polyvore http://polyv.re/165jg5l     
    
    
    Glamorous! Vionnet Paneled Sleeveless Tunic http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798833153/ …    
    
    
    Colorblock Street Style http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798833417/ …    
    
    
    Yummy pumpkin scented body spray and lotion! @tjmaxx has a great selection of seasonal scents!… http://instagram.com/p/fd54TbyKUv/     
    
    
    I'm loving the darker shades of red too! Gorgeous! http://fb.me/3czAAHG03     
    
    
    Look what's new! Kim Kardashian GoesEven Blonder?! - Kim Kardashian is officially blonder than Bake Lively, Kate H... http://ow.ly/2AJv8t     
    
    
    #words #wisdom #quotes #inspirational http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798836658/ …    
    
    
    Fall 2013 Runway Report: Cozy Corner http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798836659/ …    
    
    
    Mfw Ss/14 http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798836661/ …    
    
    
    Milan Fashionweek Day 2 by The Blonde Salad http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798836662/ …    
    
    
    Simple. clean. effortless http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798836663/ …    
    
    
    Celine - 2013 Spring-Summer http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798836665/ …    
    
    
    Fall Trend: Mixing Patterns (with a little help from TJ Maxx) #Maxxinista #GlamStyle... http://fb.me/171HiZWMl     
    
    
    New blog post: Mixing patterns today! @tjmaxx helps! #Maxxinista #glamstyle http://instagram.com/p/fetVwGSKRl/     
    
    
    Look what's new! Fall Trend: Mixing Patterns - Who doesn't love to mix it up a bit when it comes to life? New tale... http://ow.ly/2AJWvu     
    
    
    Fall Trend: Mixing Patterns (with a little help from @TJMaxx ) #Maxxinista #GlamStyle http://ow.ly/pP6sv     
    
    
    We can! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798838661/ …    
    
    
    New mom, Kim Kardashian, changed up her look again! This time she is blonder than Kate Hudson! What do you think?... http://fb.me/3c8AbcEKu     
    
    
    From the #DERMAdoctor #blog: How to Conceal Under Eye Circles and Bags #makeup #skincare http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798838885/ …    
    
    
    rings http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798838892/ …    
    
    
    St. John ~ http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798838899/ …    
    
    
    golden blonde hair color: Falling under the ‘bronde’ category, this in-between shade flatters nearly http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798838906/ …    
    
    
    Believe in your beauty! http://fb.me/2YU7jW0rS     
    
    
    Dessert. A yummy choice. Have you tried it? http://instagram.com/p/fgxAXtyKZ3/     
    
    
    Check it out! Garnier Fructis – Miraculous Oil Review http://www.theplasticdiaries.com/popular/garnier-fructis-miraculous-oil-review …    
    
    
    Buckles galore! #Boots from @tjmaxx #Maxxinista #glamstyle http://instagram.com/p/fiFueoSKVH/     
    
    
    Look what's new! Fashion Forecast For The Week Ahead: Effortless Fall Looks http://ow.ly/2AMuoL     
    
    
    I love when my friends text me style questions or pictures of clothes they are trying on! Virtual style support... http://fb.me/2ZcQrmgEw     
    
    
    My new favorite lip colors! These #Neutrogena jumbo pencils are the BEST way to add lip color!… http://instagram.com/p/fiQdzxyKSa/     
    
    
    Awesome! Just did a whole video-with great energy- and forgot to turn my mic on! LOL http://fb.me/15s4UQwoB     
    
    
    From professional to casual to weekend wear, here are some outfits to inspire you! http://fb.me/2s1z4o8MQ     
    
    
    From professional to casual to weekend wear, here are some outfits to inspire you! http://lnkd.in/bCw8M63     
    
    
    Kim Karashian bleach-blonde, October 2013 http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798845883/ …    
    
    
    Weekend Comfort http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798845889/ …    
    
    
    Work It for Fall http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798845891/ …    
    
    
    Casual Chic Layering http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798845893/ …    
    
    
    Irresistible for the rest of your life... http://www.pinterest.com/pin/322922235752769198/ … via @pinterest & @DuncanMilesMD    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to our sweet 9 year old! You inspire us daily! http://instagram.com/p/fkqga8yKVh/     
    
    
    Birthday lunch! http://instagram.com/p/flIMxxyKQu/     
    
    
    Celebrating the birthday girl! #9 #birthday http://instagram.com/p/flIdtNyKRA/     
    
    
    At the salon getting my daughter's ears pierced for her 9th birthday. She has been waiting 3 years to do this :)    
    
    
    Thankful that at age 9 still wants to play with dolls :) http://instagram.com/p/flW2LyyKXR/     
    
    
    Total ladylike! FREIDA PINTO http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798854461/ …    
    
    
    skinny jeans, white tee and blazer! so clean, simple and perfect with red heels! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798854475/ …    
    
    
    Party time before the final rehearsal for Alice in Wonderland begins. #HappyBirthday #9yearsold… http://instagram.com/p/fl6iCGyKQr/     
    
    
    Karolina Kurkova wears the perfect day-to night transition skirt http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798854562/ …    
    
    
    Will you be wearing fuzzy boots or a more sleek casual boot this weekend? #FallStyle #BootWeather http://amominredhighheels.com/fashion-forecast-week-effortless-fall/ …    
    
    
    Dress + Boots = Winning Day Look http://amominredhighheels.com/dress-boots-winning-day/ …    
    
    
    A popular post every fall... Dress + Boots = Winning Day Look  #TBT post http://fb.me/KagXd3Tf     
    
    
    Don't waste your money or time...make it last!  5 Tips to Make Your Blowout Last http://amominredhighheels.com/5-tips-blowout/     
    
    
    Giorgio Armani http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798855023/ …    
    
    
    Brushology! Are you using the right one? http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798855030/ …    
    
    
    Great jacket! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798855051/ …    
    
    
    cream and black http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798855069/ …    
    
    
    FYI @shopbop's Friends and Family Sale ends in 3 hours! I just purchased 2 items at 25% off! Use code INTHEFAMILY25 https://www.shopbop.com/     
    
    
    beautiful hair http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798855327/ …    
    
    
    Miracle spray you can make at home with a few simple ingredients you already have! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798855335/ …    
    
    
    Adorable! Would you wear this? #TGIFab http://fb.me/2isJMgOs0     
    
    
    Gwen Stefani is pregnant!!! Can't wait to see her maternity style! #CelebrateMoms    
    
    
    @DramaFollower "Skinny Jeans" means they have a snug fit through the legs & end in a small leg opening. Size20: http://ow.ly/pXduO     
    
    
    Love this!  "I am not interested in looking younger. I want to look healthy & radiant. I want to look like me." http://ow.ly/pXeBt     
    
    
    Kim Kardashian Goes...Even Blonder?! @JordanaLorraine shares why she likes it! http://amominredhighheels.com/kim-kardashian-goeseven-blonder/ …    
    
    
    So you like the look of wearing a dress with boots? Get inspired here: http://amominredhighheels.com/dress-boots-winning-day/ …    
    
    
    Gorgeous colorblock heels http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798858373/ …    
    
    
    parisian-style http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798858376/ …    
    
    
    "When you're under stress, your brain sends messages to the adrenal gland, which releases hormones t http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798858380/ …    
    
    
    The awesomeness of boots available now at @tjmaxx #Maxxinista #glamstyle http://instagram.com/p/fnlMtgSKQ2/     
    
    
    "@bestyledblowdry: #FF to these fabulous ladies @JenniSixx @Mree43 @soalaina @jyuki @amominred @femcityboston @MckennaBleu" Thank you!    
    
    
    Check out what I saved from http://www.shopsueyboutique.com  (CAROLE SATCHEL - Red - Shop Suey Boutique) to @polyvore http://polyv.re/16VBJzW     
    
    
    Designer inspired at a fraction of the price :) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798859438/ …    
    
    
    @DramaFollower :)    
    
    
    Time for an extra layer... @tjmaxx has plenty of lightweight jackets and blazers for all style… http://instagram.com/p/fqPD_eyKRo/     
    
    
    I have 5 bottles of Tone Ocean Therapy™ Body Wash to give away! It's great stuff...leaving your skin soft and... http://fb.me/2pzAwoHxY     
    
    
    Look what's new! Expect More From Your Body Wash - Of course body wash matters! It cleans your skin but have... http://ow.ly/2ASCHg     
    
    
    This Tone body wash has the smell of summer and leaves sk8n feeling so soft. I am givong 5 bottles… http://instagram.com/p/fssuX2yKZK/     
    
    
    Ahhhh fall...how I love you! @tjmaxx has great beauty products to gift or keep with the fall theme!… http://instagram.com/p/fsw91BSKTK/     
    
    
    Sunday evening is the perfect time to plan the week ahead! http://fb.me/2HL4nSlrf     
    
    
    Nick is selling $5 car wash tickets for Boy Scouts Troop #33. Car wash is this Saturday, Oct 26. If… http://instagram.com/p/fvEkNXyKQ5/     
    
    
    Just bought my daughter the cutest fuzzy boots in gold sequins from @LoveFabKids http://www.fabkids.com/invite/13729950/ …    
    
    
    Sexy ankle wraps give these red high heels an edgy flair! Who else is loving this pair from Urban Outfitters??... http://fb.me/21PfCwVOZ     
    
    
    I love the look of camo and stripes! Pieces avail at @tjmaxx #MixItUp #Maxxinista #glamstyle http://instagram.com/p/fvUICXSKWq/     
    
    
    @NylonLover69 That is amazing! Thank you!!    
    
    
    Marie Claire Photo Shoot – Behind The Scenes | Negin Mirsalehi by Negin Mirsalehi http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798879063/ …    
    
    
    turquoise http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798879067/ …    
    
    
    @MarcellaMakeup Agreed! Loving the knuckle rings! Adds a whole new layer to the fingers :)    
    
    
    Love that statement necklace! Josephine Skriver for Dannijo SS 2013 http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798879567/ …    
    
    
    I almost want to go darker just to have this gorgeous contrast! @Brazilian Blowout by Jordana Lorrai http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798879579/ …    
    
    
    Sandy Blonde http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798879592/ …    
    
    
    Fall hair trends - honey pecan blonde http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798879601/ …    
    
    
    5 Emergency (MacGyver) Make-Up Tips that everyone should know... http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798879636/ …    
    
    
    Fall is all about layering! Not only is it a great season to layer clothes but your jewelry too! I… http://instagram.com/p/fv2qNqyKaK/     
    
    
    LIKE if you agree! http://fb.me/2LdKha3rE     
    
    
    How Exercise Reduces Your Breast Cancer Risk http://www.pinterest.com/pin/322922235752803250/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    So beautiful! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798882869/ …    
    
    
    Superwomen do it in high heels. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798882873/ …    
    
    
    Mango Military Fashion Shoot. #fashion #style #streetstyle #trends http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798882877/ …    
    
    
    elegance in black + white. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798882878/ …    
    
    
    In Pursuit of the perfect red heel... http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798882900/ …    
    
    
    Red #heels are ALWAYS a good choice. Team Parsons #StudioSessions http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798882902/ …    
    
    
    Red heels for a pop  of color. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798882906/ …    
    
    
    Tone Ocean Therapy™ Body Wash with Deep Sea Extracts and Pearl Essence works to keep skin soft and s http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798882931/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! The Diamond Shield Turns Cell Phone Screen Into Mirror (every woman's dream come true) http://ow.ly/2AWgZ3     
    
    
    Shaping Tights are the secret to great curves! Feel slimmer, firmer and more flattering in your clot http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798885399/ …    
    
    
    Seriously cool cell phone protector that transforms your phone screen into a mirror. #Awesomeness http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798885414/ …    
    
    
    Seriously cool cell phone protector that transforms your phone screen into a mirror. Available for Iphone 4, 4s,... http://fb.me/wT1Ujvvg     
    
    
    5 Bottles of Tone® Ocean Therapy™ Body Wash with Deep Sea Extracts and Pearl Essence up for grabs! #Giveaway http://amominredhighheels.com/body-wash/     
    
    
    "Get Width It"  New Wide Calf boots available at @JustFab http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798885494/ …    
    
    
    Alberta Ferretti | Spring 2014 | Milan Fashion Week. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798885499/ …    
    
    
    So, @JordanaLorraine, Kim K is back to bronde again? http://ow.ly/q4THE     
    
    
    This yellow pepper is as big as a small pumpkin! #Goodforyoufood http://instagram.com/p/fykjjcyKRd/     
    
    
    This jacket from @tjmaxx has it going on! Studs, zippers, mixed media...all the hottest trends!… http://instagram.com/p/f0MWw3yKYr/     
    
    
    Completely in love with this handbag from Shop Suey Boutique! There are many new great styles on the site today!... http://fb.me/2UTmakwJa     
    
    
    Have you taken time for yourself yet today??

It was a power struggle but I did it! I got up this morning, when... http://fb.me/1W7ETOATg     
    
    
    Get Your Life Together, Finally http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798891854/ …    
    
    
    That habit of bed making is correlated with greater well-being and higher productivity http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798891860/ …    
    
    
    Put your priorities on your to-do list and commit to it.  Drop those things that are not important t http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798891870/ …    
    
    
    Semi-precious Aventurine set in a frame of textured reeds combines natural and modern influences http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798891974/ …    
    
    
    Sculpted metal stick earring in shiny gold plating http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798892026/ …    
    
    
    @jordanalorraine I like it better. I hope w/ all that color she is using Brazilian Blowout Split End Repair Treatment http://ow.ly/q6IeA     
    
    
    Important info so you can finally get the hair color you really want! xo http://fb.me/2AGlxGJE5     
    
    
    Great shoulder zipper detail on this designer brand sweater found at @tjmaxx #Maxxinista #glamstyle http://instagram.com/p/f2qb34yKfH/     
    
    
    Sarah wants a hair color makeover. Platinum is too damaging, brunette is too serious.  Find out what http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798898512/ …    
    
    
    "When the waves are taking you under
Hold on just a little longer
He knows that this is gonna make you... http://fb.me/6vdJPaYyK     
    
    
    Good morning! http://instagram.com/p/f24lBDSKVr/     
    
    
    5 Top Tips From Hollywood Makeup Artists - http://amominredhighheels.com/5-top-tips-hollywood-makeup-artists/ …    
    
    
    Model Makeover--Blonde Addiction @JordanaLorraine gives hair color advice to a model looking for a new color - http://amominredhighheels.com/model-makeoverblonde-addiction/ …    
    
    
    Final Day! Enter to Win a Free bottle of TONE body wash! http://amominredhighheels.com/body-wash/     
    
    
    Today's post: How to Layer Your Outfit (and love it!) #Maxxinista #GlamStyle... http://fb.me/15y9ZTkWh     
    
    
    New on the blog: Layering for fall (w/ help from @tjmaxx) #Maxxinista #glamstyle http://instagram.com/p/f4cCkAyKeo/     
    
    
    Look what's new! 5 Steps To A Perfectly Layered Look - It’s Fall! Let the layering begin! My favorite season f... http://ow.ly/2B2f81     
    
    
    I do love this blazer w/ faux leather trim. It makes a great layering piece for fall! @tjmaxx… http://instagram.com/p/f5HQsDyKYZ/     
    
    
    Today on the blog: Be sure to check out why my designer sweater from @tjmaxx is so cool (a great… http://instagram.com/p/f5Ta3SSKbG/     
    
    
    Layering with Twisted! Cameo necklace, Key necklace and the 3 bracelet. http://pinterest.com/pin/49680402113380721/ …    
    
    
    What Roald said. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798905131/ …    
    
    
    Street style. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798905132/ …    
    
    
    5 Steps To A Perfectly Layered Look http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798905175/ …    
    
    
    Fall 2013 Burgundy http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798905209/ …    
    
    
    Adult acne is bad. Acne and wrinkles is even worse!  If you have problem skin, check out this video...it gives... http://fb.me/6rAHqm3rD     
    
    
    For optimal self-esteem, you should be getting 12 hugs a day! Make sure you take a hug whenever you can and hand... http://fb.me/1BupZuPWH     
    
    
    Halloween Beauty: Sexy Pirate Makeup http://amominredhighheels.com/halloween-beauty-sexy-pirate-makeup/ …    
    
    
    Sexy Pirate Makeup http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798918664/ …    
    
    
    Fairy Fierce makeup how-to http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798918683/ …    
    
    
    Get the Look For Halloween: Fairy Fierce! - http://amominredhighheels.com/fairy-fierce/     
    
    
    Halloween How-To: Zombie Makeup (warning, mega gross zombie photo!)  - http://amominredhighheels.com/halloween-howto-zombie-makeup/ …    
    
    
    Need a costume idea?  How about this? http://fb.me/6Id2DaCpx     
    
    
    #TargetStyle: Pre-Show Episode 1 (+playlist): http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N_EvYpfmqZw&feature=share&list=SPijk13kqreIeb2ekoxL9zG_sUsWAvKtVP … via @youtube @Glam_com    
    
    
    Feel Slimmer in 13 Seconds Flat - http://amominredhighheels.com/feel-slimmer-13-seconds-flat/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Office Casual Done Right - What does “business casual” attire mean? Does it mea... http://ow.ly/2B6fk6     
    
    
    What does “business casual” attire mean? Does it mean it’s okay to rock your faded jeans and flip-flops to work?... http://fb.me/33HZVDRHS     
    
    
    Have you made a fall hair color change yet? I'm DYING over these hair hues! Gorgeous! http://amominredhighheels.com/2013-fall-hair-colors/ …    
    
    
    All the pretty colors... http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798922833/ …    
    
    
    How To Create a Dazzling Smile With Cosmetic Dentistry http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798922912/ …    
    
    
    Did you do what needs to be done yet today? If not, do it now! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798922940/ …    
    
    
    Geoges Hobeika http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798922956/ …    
    
    
    The Breakfast Club Inspiration! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798923306/ …    
    
    
    Don't you dare, for one more second, surround yourself with people who are not aware of the greatnes http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798923329/ …    
    
    
    DIANE VON FURSTENBERG Mini Sutra cross-body bag http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798923369/ …    
    
    
    How-To: Office Casual Done Right http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798923767/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Get Your Lips Mistletoe-Ready - Dry weather has officially arrived. Your lips will suffer if you... http://ow.ly/2B6WEE     
    
    
    NEW ChapStick flavors and Limited Edition tins (avail 11/1). Gingerbread or Candy Cane anyone? http://amominredhighheels.com/lips-mistletoeready/ …    
    
    
    Don't get caught with dry, chapped lips! NEW ChapStick holiday flavors and tins can help! (Plus, they make really... http://fb.me/3cI3yUGV2     
    
    
    Max Studio Printed Silk Organza Dress is the perfect print for autumn! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798925670/ …    
    
    
    Flared Dress is charming and sexy! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798925672/ …    
    
    
    A-Line Party Dress with gorgeous detail!  Paired with pumps or boots, this dress will work well in a http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798925675/ …    
    
    
    Elegant wide leg pants http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798925702/ …    
    
    
    Pinstriped Voile Dress has girlish charm and luxurious silk/cotton fabric http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798925714/ …    
    
    
    5 Amazing Things to Do With Avocados Besides Eat Them http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798926002/ …    
    
    
    SATIN RED HIGH-HEELS http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798926010/ …    
    
    
    A healthy hair makeover! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798926050/ …    
    
    
    8 amazing Halloween Makeup YouTube Tutorials http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798926059/ …    
    
    
    Learn Your Body Type and How To Dress It Well http://lnkd.in/b4G9W-e     
    
    
    @JimCarpe_Diem Thanks for the share! Never too early to prepare for mistletoe season ;)    
    
    
    @NickiZevola Right??? :)    
    
    
    @NickiZevola Definitely the way to go...heels over flip flops, skirts over denim... You are a stylish group, no doubt!    
    
    
    Your body type determines what clothing styles look best on you.  Every type is beautiful and every type can... http://fb.me/1AAE2WICf     
    
    
    Congrats to expectant mom Olivia Wilde! #CelebrateMoms http://ow.ly/qgPTm  via @BabbleEditors    
    
    
    A good thing to remember... http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798930422/ …    
    
    
    FENDI http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798930427/ …    
    
    
    Artistically Posh Video Outfits @polyvore http://polyv.re/16117Ts     
    
    
    Your body type determines what clothing styles look best on you.  Every type is beautiful and every  http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798930529/ …    
    
    
    Hourglass body shape http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798930531/ …    
    
    
    Inverted Triangle body shape http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798930533/ …    
    
    
    Rectangle body shape http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798930534/ …    
    
    
    Triangle body shape http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798930536/ …    
    
    
    Learn the secret to great style every time you get dressed! http://icont.ac/21BVx     
    
    
    Nicky Hilton's closet http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798932839/ …    
    
    
    dreamy closet! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798932849/ …    
    
    
    I need jewelry drawers for all my @Twisted Silver http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798932858/ …    
    
    
    The ultimate: Closet/Office combo! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798932865/ …    
    
    
    Fall Outfit Idea http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798932898/ …    
    
    
    Up-do. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798932918/ …    
    
    
    Jewelry Organizer via Michelle Money http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798932926/ …    
    
    
    Diy Jewelry Organizer - This Is Fabulous http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798932928/ …    
    
    
    http://fb.me/22ROHIfB1     
    
    
    dramatic eyes with a natural glow, try Jouer Liquid Shimmer Eyeliner in Panther to create this smoot http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798933089/ …    
    
    
    Should You Take Supplements for Hair? http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798933090/ …    
    
    
    Learn Your Body Type and How To Dress It Well  http://amominredhighheels.com/body-type/     
    
    
    Closet / dressing room by Habachy Designs http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798934739/ …    
    
    
    Jimmy Choo http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798934741/ …    
    
    
    The Truth: Can I Have a Keratin Treatment While Pregnant? @JordanaLorraine gives it to you straight... http://amominredhighheels.com/keratin-treatment-pregnant/ …    
    
    
    The Truth: Can I Have a Keratin Treatment While Pregnant? http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798938682/ …    
    
    
    Red/Black Colorblock bootie with metallic stiletto heel #FABulous http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798938703/ …    
    
    
    Learn Your Body Type and How To Dress It Well http://amominredhighheels.com/body-type/     
    
    
    HOT OR NOT? Red/Black Colorblock bootie with metallic stiletto heel
http://ow.ly/qkjoE  http://fb.me/IBdQN1yq     
    
    
    Feel FABulous, look amazing and turn heads in your LBD this holiday season!  Learn how here: http://ow.ly/qkkmj     
    
    
    37 million Bees found dead in Canada, after large planting of GMO corn seed treated w/ Neonicotinoid pesticides http://shar.es/I4Spn     
    
    
    An awesome nail color for fall... #L'Oreal "The Muse's Attitude" http://instagram.com/p/gGlipsSKXC/     
    
    
    How to Manage Unruly Hair Texture - http://amominredhighheels.com/managing-unruly-hair-texture/ …    
    
    
    Nick's Halloween costume and the inspiration for it :) #awesomeness http://instagram.com/p/gHJB-lyKdV/     
    
    
    Reverse French. Love the metallic! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798942829/ …    
    
    
    Dark Red Faux Nubuck Single Sole Heels http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798942830/ …    
    
    
    AnnaLynne McCord Went Brunette http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798942834/ …    
    
    
    Birkins, one in every colour... http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798942837/ …    
    
    
    Amanda Thaarsti http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798942840/ …    
    
    
    Miranda Kerr chic http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798942842/ …    
    
    
    dark blonde hair http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798942849/ …    
    
    
    Fall Style http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798942865/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Cure For The  Common Tangles - It's scarf season! I love scarf season! I love how versatile scar... http://ow.ly/2BcGfA     
    
    
    WAIT!  Who is that??! WOW! Very chic!  Makeover Alert! Pamela Anderson Got a Pixie Haircut http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798943106/ …    
    
    
    Wow! Pamela Anderson made a HUGE change! What do you think of her new pixie cut? http://fb.me/YPXAdCOu     
    
    
    Last minute costume idea: Halloween How-To: Zombie Makeup  - http://amominredhighheels.com/halloween-howto-zombie-makeup/ …    
    
    
    Throw together a costume! Halloween Beauty: Sexy Pirate Makeup - http://amominredhighheels.com/halloween-beauty-sexy-pirate-makeup/ …    
    
    
    Did you see Pamela Anderson's MAJOR makeover?? http://fb.me/YPXAdCOu     
    
    
    8 amazing Halloween Makeup YouTube Tutorials http://www.pinterest.com/pin/150166968798926059/ …    
    
    
    Have fun today! http://fb.me/2u3JAwPXr     
    
    
    Halloween Nails - http://amominredhighheels.com/halloween-nails/ …    
    
    
    Fairy Fierce makeup how-to http://www.pinterest.com/pin/150166968798918683/ …    
    
    
    FREE LEOPARD PRINT SCARF - With Purchase Offer ends Nov 1 at midnight PST http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798945732/ …    
    
    
    7 Ways Pumpkin Boosts Your Beauty: It's great for your hair! #hairmask #diy #natural #greenbeauty http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798945737/ …    
    
    
    Cure for the common tangles... http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798946166/ …    
    
    
    This is going on under the boots today. #Halloween http://instagram.com/p/gJUKA0yKRa/     
    
    
    Don't you just LOVE to wear scarves? Don't you just HATE the mess they make of your hair at that nape of you... http://fb.me/1anlMc3wP     
    
    
    Ask a Stylist: How Do I Become a Stylist? http://laurenmessiah.com/2013/10/ask-stylist-become-stylist/ …    
    
    
    Heavy metal happiness! @twistedrocks Monocle Necklace, Grace Necklace, Kitter Bracelet http://instagram.com/p/gJY7Z_yKan/     
    
    
    You do realize, of course, that from here on out, it is all about the holidays...are you ready?    
    
    
    Wow!  Do you know who this is without reading the headline? http://fb.me/6xKCSTX6y     
    
    
    Christian Louboutin http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798952289/ …    
    
    
    Head into the Holidays with Confidence. Get Little Black Dress Ready & SAVE $50 (sale ends tonight!) http://ow.ly/qpGsX     
    
    
    Are you in LBD shape? If not, this workout will help you get there ($50 off today only)! http://icont.ac/228Ux     
    
    
    Yes, you Can rock that LBD! Get Little Black Dress Ready & SAVE $50 (sale ends tonight!) http://ow.ly/qpGsX     
    
    
    Remind yourself that you CHOOSE to say NO to the Halloween candy because you want good energy, clear skin and a... http://fb.me/2TB7MLL7Y     
    
    
    Yep... http://fb.me/OcVOw6qF     
    
    
    3-Step Quick Beauty Looks- Strong Brows @polyvore http://polyv.re/1hGD95g     
    
    
    Do you know your body type and how to dress it? Learn how here: http://amominredhighheels.com/body-type/     
    
    
    Cure For The  Common Tangles (caused by scarves and high collars) - http://amominredhighheels.com/cure-common-tangles/ …    
    
    
    Learn Your Body Type and How To Best Dress It http://amominredhighheels.com/body-type/     
    
    
    Auburn? Chocolate? Honey? Which fall hair hue is right for you? You'll Dye For These  http://amominredhighheels.com/2013-fall-hair-colors/ …    
    
    
    If you have a DIAMOND body shape, wear tops with wide ‘V’ necklines and hemlines that finish above or below the... http://fb.me/32Lm5KmdA     
    
    
    To Jorge Cortell From a High-Heeled Entrepreneur: 'You're Right' http://huff.to/1aZ9nG0  via @HuffPostWomen    
    
    
    Love the texture and colors going on in this outfit. #SoCalFall http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798978614/ …    
    
    
    Sparkle and shine heels http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798978845/ …    
    
    
    Deliciously red #ArdenRed http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798978865/ …    
    
    
    10 Skinny Cocktails http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798978882/ …    
    
    
    The Top 8 New Nail Polish Shades for Fall http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798978886/ …    
    
    
    Jennifer Aniston's New Haircut 2013 http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798978912/ …    
    
    
    The Most Comprehensive Guide To Formaldehyde-Free Brazilian Blowout and Keratin Treatment Alternatives - http://amominredhighheels.com/comprehensive-guide-formaldehydefree-brazilian-blowout-keratin-treatment-alternatives/ …    
    
    
    Are you a Diamond, Rectangle, Triangle, Inverted Triangle or an Hourglass? Learn your body type and how to dress it http://amominredhighheels.com/body-type/     
    
    
    5 Top Tips From Hollywood Makeup Artists - http://amominredhighheels.com/5-top-tips-hollywood-makeup-artists/ …    
    
    
    How to Get Wavy Hair Like Sienna Miller - http://amominredhighheels.com/wavy-hair-sienna-miller/ … http://amominredhighheels.com/wavy-hair-sienna-miller/ …    
    
    
    Jennifer Aniston's New Dramatic Haircut...Everyone is talking about it. Read what @JordanaLorraine thinks of it! http://amominredhighheels.com/jennifer-anistons-dramatic-haircut-2013/ …    
    
    
    How confident are you with your look? Take the Beauty Confidence Quiz to find out! http://ow.ly/qyjQL     
    
    
    Another expecting celebrity mom...Anne Hathaway! Congrats!  #CelebrateMoms http://ow.ly/qylma     
    
    
    5 Body-Changing Tips From Tracy Anderson http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798983725/ …    
    
    
    Click the story for pics and how-to! http://fb.me/31wCAskKP     
    
    
    Cold Weather Style: LOVE this gray/sequin beanie from @ShopSueyBoutiqu http://www.shopsueyboutique.com/lizzy-beanie-gray/#.UnqLdbxmlIM.twitter …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Jennifer Aniston's New Dramatic Haircut 2013 (and what to ask for if you want it!) http://ow.ly/2BlHES     
    
    
    @LarryLGibson Hi! Enjoy your swim #Strong #swift    
    
    
    @Apothederm Thank you for sharing! xo    
    
    
    Jennifer Lawrence gets a pixie cut. CUTE! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798984675/ …    
    
    
    ANOTHER major celebrity makeover.  Jennifer Lawrence gets a pixie!  CUTE, right??!  via Daily Makeover... http://fb.me/MncHYc3b     
    
    
    Details on Jennifer Aniston’s New Dramatic Haircut 2013 (and what to ask for if you want it!) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798984719/ …    
    
    
    Gifts for those hard to buy for kids... http://amominredhighheels.com/time-personal-2/ … #GiftsByBSK    
    
    
    Some seriously CUTE gifts for those hard to shop for kids in your life. Don't miss this selection of gift ideas!... http://fb.me/12ahIDcEC     
    
    
    Christmas Tree wall sticker. Great when a crawling baby is in the house, for classroom or dorm room! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798987624/ …    
    
    
    It’s Time to Get Personal : gifts you'll love to give and they will love to receive http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798987625/ …    
    
    
    DIY FRAMED INITIAL ART-  great personalized gift http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798987627/ …    
    
    
    RED High Heel Fused Glass Christmas Ornament / by Purpleslug http://etsy.me/1hOMh7Z  via @Etsy    
    
    
    Black and white closet glamour http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798987725/ …    
    
    
    TAYLOR GOLD Over-Ear headphones. So beautiful! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798987730/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! It's Time to Get Personal - Gift buying time is here! This year, don't procrastinate! Get start... http://ow.ly/2BmyVu     
    
    
    Sleek and Sexy have never looked so good. Foiled lace surrounds a retro inspired silhouette that jus http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798987959/ …    
    
    
    A wardrobe essential. This classic wrap dress is both fun and flirty. This dress has a fashionable s http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798987961/ …    
    
    
    Cropped Layers, mixed textures and amazing shoes! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798989456/ …    
    
    
    Loving the striped ruffles! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798989539/ …    
    
    
    Sparkly plaid dress and star tights?? Adorable! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798989545/ …    
    
    
    Christian Louboutin, fall 2013. Really, there is nothing better than a good leopard/red combo! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798989762/ …    
    
    
    What are your shoes saying about you today? http://fb.me/2DlWF82Yx     
    
    
    Don't be Delicate. Be Vast and Brilliant! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798989904/ …    
    
    
    Ways to Make Lashes Look Longer http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798989931/ …    
    
    
    Use your story to empower others like Lara McKeever does. @Mary Kay http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798990405/ …    
    
    
    *GIVEAWAY!* 30 Beatnik Bracelets from @Twisted Silver http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798990456/ …    
    
    
    @LarryLGibson drive thru pick-up is nice, huh?    
    
    
    @LarryLGibson yes there are those... or the one's who park in line and leave their car...    
    
    
    Happy Friday! http://fb.me/2zpIZiCf4     
    
    
    I Heart Handbags @polyvore http://polyv.re/HNaLjT  pic.twitter.com/LtTkYneb96    
    
    
    I Heart Handbags @polyvore http://polyv.re/HNaLjT  pic.twitter.com/YWTAvFTegO    
    
    
    Luxe closet!! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798995561/ …    
    
    
    Happy Friday Handbag Lovers! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798995567/ …    
    
    
    Colorstud Padlock Tote in Olive http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798995568/ …    
    
    
    Red heels looks so great with denim! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798995577/ …    
    
    
    via @Windtraveler09 "Why Are We Doing This?" >>> Love why they are living life on the sea. #CelebrateMoms http://www.windtraveler.net/2011/04/why-are-we-doing-this.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Gwen Stefani Balances Her Bump On Red High Heeled Boots During A Zuma School Drop Off! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798995591/ …    
    
    
    Gorgeous burgundy bootie http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968798995609/ …    
    
    
    @LarryLGibson I knew you'd agree :)    
    
    
    Want success? Dress well! Six secrets of successful women: http://ow.ly/qDsVe     
    
    
    The Big Chill: A fall look we love inspired by @ShannaSaidSo http://wp.me/p6nJR-1VR  via @ShopSueyBoutiqu    
    
    
    @LarryLGibson sounds like a great book. Leaving it with me this weekend?    
    
    
    A true statement :) http://lnkd.in/bXdjucZ     
    
    
    Gift giving idea: SUPER cute personalized tees for kids #GiftsByBSK http://amominredhighheels.com/time-personal-2/ …    
    
    
    23 Five-Minute Hairstyles For Busy Mornings http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799000027/ …    
    
    
    The one where I get a Brazilian... a great testimonial for @Brazilian Blowout by Jordana Lorraine an http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799000045/ …    
    
    
    This dose of reality may be too much for me. I want to believe in the fairytale.  What say you?... http://fb.me/2tIP4nBdE     
    
    
    glossy bronde http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799000127/ …    
    
    
    A Day at the Salon in LA http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799000130/ …    
    
    
    Don't miss out on what I'm sharing and discussing - follow me on Bunch to keep in the loop! http://joinbunch.com/profile/93319/     
    
    
    Ali's Blog | “The Day I Learned to Start Saying ‘No’” by Ali Brown http://www.alibrown.com/blog/2013/10/24/%e2%80%9cthe-day-i-learned-to-start-saying-%e2%80%98no%e2%80%99%e2%80%9d-by-ali-brown/ …    
    
    
    Floral on Black @polyvore http://polyv.re/197p8pw  pic.twitter.com/Pszf9VixZL    
    
    
    Look what's new! Get The Look: Jenna Dewan-Tatum's Soft, Sexy Curls http://ow.ly/2BoEq5     
    
    
    @LarryLGibson whoo hoo! Loud and dangerous, as promised :)    
    
    
    Celebrities Who Fixed Bad Skin Adult Acne http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799004542/ …    
    
    
    dailylook // navy + black http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799004552/ …    
    
    
    Get The Look: Jenna Dewan-Tatum’s Soft, Sexy Curls http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799004558/ …    
    
    
    A Fall Favorite: 6 Ways to Wear Knee-High Boots - http://amominredhighheels.com/6-ways-wear-kneehigh-boots/ …    
    
    
    Black with a pop of red http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799004580/ …    
    
    
    6 Ways to Wear Knee-High Boots http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799004586/ …    
    
    
    Hair Inspiration | Hair Length Chart  #paul #mitchell #pmtslombard #hair #chart #length #cut #style http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799004604/ …    
    
    
    Have a little fun with color! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799007247/ …    
    
    
    Have you changed up your hair color for fall? If you are still looking for the perfect hue, check out Hair... http://fb.me/Uv178XBr     
    
    
    #Truth http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799007464/ …    
    
    
    How to Find Narrow-Calf Boots That Fit - http://amominredhighheels.com/narrow-calf-boots/ …    
    
    
    Get younger looking skin w/ @Meaningfulbty products! Shop via http://MyPoints.com  & receive reward points! http://ow.ly/qFgJ5  #sp    
    
    
    New Lace Up Boots at @JustFabOnline Loving the Sasson boot! #FabForAll. http://www.justfab.com/invite/amominred/ …    
    
    
    Flats on sale at @Shop6PM These DV by Dolce Vita Gully flats are super cute!  http://www.6pm.com/product/8283681/color/469566 …    
    
    
    Did you know Kohl's is rolling out GORGEOUS new beauty department with name brand beauty products? Here are three... http://fb.me/2PNV6BzHz     
    
    
    3-Step Quick Beauty Looks To Get You Out The Door And Looking Great - http://amominredhighheels.com/3step-quick-beauty/ … #KohlsBeauty    
    
    
    Quick Beauty Looks: Golden Fall #kohlsBeauty http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799016269/ …    
    
    
    LORAC Couture Shine in Trend Setter gives one sexy shine! #KohlsBeauty http://instagram.com/p/glbsiPSKaj/     
    
    
    The 3 beauty products you'll need for a Metallic eye and plump lips. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799016874/ …    
    
    
    Today on the blog... #KohlsBeauty is rolling out new beauty departments and they are fabulous! http://instagram.com/p/glrafeSKUy/     
    
    
    Knocked out 10 videos today! Thanks to my hubby for usimg his day off to be my video guy!! xo http://instagram.com/p/gmMQ-syKW6/     
    
    
    @LarryLGibson thanks for being my video guy on your day off! you are the best! xo    
    
    
    light blonde http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799020010/ …    
    
    
    Courtney Cox has had Ultherapy to help build collagen. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799020014/ …    
    
    
    Black satin ribbon heels- perfect for holiday parties http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799020019/ …    
    
    
    How to get perfectly arched brows | http://SheKnows.com  http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799021458/ …    
    
    
    Workplace beauty: The perfect beauty kit for your desk http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799021471/ …    
    
    
    Lipstick love http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799021519/ …    
    
    
    A classic dress with edgy accessories makes for the perfect Edgy Elegance look! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799021534/ …    
    
    
    How to create the longer, fuller ponytail. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799021546/ …    
    
    
    So feminine! Dying for that skirt! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799021557/ …    
    
    
    How to find your perfect nude . . . lipstick, that is! Great guide. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799021565/ …    
    
    
    Looking for a nude lipstick that won't wash you out?  This pin is so good (and too big to post here).  Go to... http://fb.me/Uig7FJQy     
    
    
    @BonBonRoseGirls Thanks! #KohlsBeauty has so much to offer in makeup now! #LOVE    
    
    
    Get in on the shopping rewards! http://amominredhighheels.com/smart-shoppers-maximize-shopping-dollar-mypointscom/ … #rewardsprogram @MyPoints    
    
    
    9 DIY Looks For YOUR Eye Color http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799023515/ …    
    
    
    Super cute blue evening bag! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799023736/ …    
    
    
    how-to wear a nude lip http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799023782/ …    
    
    
    @LarryLGibson still feeling that camping trip?    
    
    
    @LarryLGibson True, I'd rather travel than have things.    
    
    
    I can earn 8 points per dollar spent at @DSWSHOELovers via @MyPoints! I love bonuses for shopping! http://ow.ly/qKyPk  #rewardsprogram    
    
    
    Yes, please! The Mother Lode by Urban Decay #wishlist http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799024178/ …    
    
    
    Great combo: Lace and red heels http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799024188/ …    
    
    
    A great twist on a feminine skirt! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799024210/ …    
    
    
    Smart Shoppers Maximize Their Shopping Dollar with @MyPoints #rewardsprogram http://amominredhighheels.com/smart-shoppers-maximize-shopping-dollar-mypointscom/ …    
    
    
    3-Step Quick Beauty Looks To Get You Out The Door And Looking Great - http://amominredhighheels.com/3step-quick-beauty/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Smart Shoppers Maximize Their Shopping Dollar with http://MyPoints.com  http://ow.ly/2BpdLP     
    
    
    LORAC Breakthrough Performance Lipstick SPF 15 #kohlsbeauty http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799028676/ …    
    
    
    Beauty Event Invite @polyvore #KohlsBeauty http://polyv.re/1a3zUlc     
    
    
    Smart Shoppers Maximize Their Shopping Dollar with http://MyPoints.com  - http://amominredhighheels.com/smart-shoppers-maximize-shopping-dollar-mypointscom/ …    
    
    
    Beauty Event Invite #kohlsbeauty http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799028720/ …    
    
    
    Meet me in Vegas this weekend?  To celebrate the new beauty department Kohl's and all it’s fabulousness, 49... http://fb.me/1bzrZDJwa     
    
    
    Meet me in Vegas this weekend? To celebrate the new beauty department Kohl's and all it’s fabulousness, 49 select... http://fb.me/2QyjgEago     
    
    
    Beauty Trade-in Event on November 16th from 9am-1pm at #KohlsBeauty.  http://amominredhighheels.com/beauty-event-invitation/ …    
    
    
    5 Emergency (MacGyver) Make-Up Tips that everyone should know... http://www.pinterest.com/pin/322922235752799702/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Equal parts sheer tint and moisture, these color-balm hybrids go on smoothly and are a must for dry, flaky lips. http://www.pinterest.com/pin/322922235752722531/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Beauty Event Invitation!  Will You Be There? http://ow.ly/2Bqdwp     
    
    
    Beauty Trade-in Event at @Kohls_Official this Saturday! Find a store near you http://ow.ly/qMz0k  #KohlsBeauty    
    
    
    @DeannaGarretson @Kohls_Official @LORAC_Cosmetics @thebalm They are not hosting the Trade-in Event but they do have the new FAB beauty dept.    
    
    
    @DeannaGarretson  Chk out the exclusive @LORAC_Cosmetics Sweet Temptations Shadow Pallettes. They look like gourmet choc bars! #kohlsbeauty    
    
    
    Enzo Angiolini Fayson Pumps- not your usual pump shape! Love it! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799030192/ …    
    
    
    Beauty Trade-in Event Trade in 2 old beauty products & receive a $10 Kohl’s gift card (first 100 only) http://ow.ly/qMz0k  #KohlsBeauty    
    
    
    Put your money where your shoe closet is! #DSW #quote #shoelover http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799030770/ …    
    
    
    Minky Leather Leopard Clutch http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799030772/ …    
    
    
    Healthy Skin Tips: 10 Surprising Things You Didn't Know http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799030827/ …    
    
    
    Kohl’s Beauty Trade-in Event Participating Stores: http://ow.ly/qMzP7  #kohlsbeauty    
    
    
    Beauty Trend: Strong Eyebrow for Fall http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280060441/ …    
    
    
    3-step Beauty: Red Lips http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280060443/ …    
    
    
    Quick Beauty Look: Golden Fall http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280060444/ …    
    
    
    Don't you love shopping rewards? Me too! Something for them, Something for me = win/win! @MyPoints #rewardsprogram http://ow.ly/qNrZQ     
    
    
    CABLE KNIT TIGHTS Can I really say anything more about them!?! I love wearing dresses in the Fall no http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799034598/ …    
    
    
    Boot Cuffs Boot Toppers- Must-have winter accessory! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799034877/ …    
    
    
    Kushyfoot is an essential layering piece for cold weather! Enter now to win the entire Kushyfoot Fall 2013 Tights... http://fb.me/2wFUo8cg5     
    
    
    @Kohls_Official Beauty Trade in Event happens on Saturday. See what stores are participating: http://ow.ly/qMzP7  #kohlsbeauty    
    
    
    Busy Mom Beauties http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280063212/ …    
    
    
    3-Step makeup looks from our favorite bloggers via @SheKnows http://www.sheknows.com/beauty-and-style/articles/1022851/3-step-makeup-looks-from-our-favorite-bloggers …    
    
    
    An Outfit Is Not Complete Without The Right Leg Wear (+ enter to win the @Kushyfoot Fall Collection) - http://amominredhighheels.com/outfit-complete-leg-wear-enter-win/ …    
    
    
    I joined Bunch to follow topics I love and discuss them with like-minded people. Sign up to see my discussions http://joinbunch.com/HrN     
    
    
    Look what's new! An Outfit Is Not Complete Without The Right Leg Wear (+ enter to win) http://ow.ly/2Bs5Tj     
    
    
    Coe & Company is doing a jewelry giveaway on Facebook. Loving the bangles! http://fb.me/2uftMQ60u     
    
    
    This Paparazzi clutch is so fun!! Party time! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799037323/ …    
    
    
    Hot Hollywood Accessory: See-Thru 2-in-1 Evening Bag http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799037492/ …    
    
    
    a great casual look! #quiltedJacket http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799037645/ …    
    
    
    Don't miss Kohl's Beauty Trade-in Event happening on Saturday! I'll be hosting at the North Summerlin, Las Vegas... http://fb.me/1KAFr9eaS     
    
    
    Travel Pouch Duo- great for keeping dirty laundry separate in your suitcase when you travel! #vbwish http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799037741/ …    
    
    
    Puppy wants this! #vbwishlist http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799037759/ …    
    
    
    A beautiful day for a cross country race! #GoBears http://instagram.com/p/gtm-sxSKRP/     
    
    
    Enter to win a collection of @Kushyfoot tights/trouser socks. So perfect with boots for fall/winter! http://amominredhighheels.com/outfit-complete-leg-wear-enter-win/ … #giveaway    
    
    
    Morning beauty routines in THREE steps! Learn how!  http://amominredhighheels.com/3step-quick-beauty/ …    
    
    
    Are you coming to the @Kohls_official Beauty Trade-in event? Details here:  http://amominredhighheels.com/beauty-event-invitation/ …    
    
    
    Holiday Travel is upon us! Add color to your travel gear w/ @VeraBradley #vbwishlist - http://amominredhighheels.com/color-confident/ …    
    
    
    Holiday Travel is upon us! Add color to your travel gear w/ @VeraBradley #vbwishlist -... http://fb.me/6mPU0XHYq     
    
    
    Holiday Travel is upon us! Add color to your travel gear w/ @VeraBradley #vbwishlist -... http://fb.me/16mOaFGPX     
    
    
    Chic travel bags from @VeraBradley on the blog today. #vbwishlist http://instagram.com/p/gvjRbmyKWk/     
    
    
    Packing for my trip to Vegas. I'll be hosting the @Kohls Beauty Trade-in Event tmrw at North Summerlin store. http://ow.ly/qRBRQ     
    
    
    Rock Your Roots With Ombre Hair Color (a great way to do low maintenance hair)  - http://amominredhighheels.com/ombre/     
    
    
    Look what's new! Be Color Confident #vbwishlist - I love wearing black. I am not one of those people that tell you... http://ow.ly/2BuG8M     
    
    
    Beauty Event happening at @Kohls tmrw from 9-1 at select stores. Bring in 2 old products, get $10 Kohl's cash http://ow.ly/qRCEu     
    
    
    Heading to Vegas for the #KohlsBeauty Trade-in Event tomorrow! Hope to see some of you there! #NorthSummerlin... http://fb.me/6wpAqRltp     
    
    
    Sharing a #red velvet cupcake with a Vegas bride and groom. Yep, met them in the hall and was invited… http://instagram.com/p/gwx3z3yKba/     
    
    
    Time to get some beauty sleep before the #KohlsBeauty event tomorrow. Night!    
    
    
    Good morning! Time to get ready for #kohlsbeauty event! Will you be there?    
    
    
    Some morning under eye help. #pixi http://instagram.com/p/gyCacIyKTV/     
    
    
    So many new Prestiges Brands now available in the #KohlsBeauty department.  Trade-in Event happens… http://instagram.com/p/gyFwd4yKZN/     
    
    
    The beauty trade-in has begun! #KohlsBeauty Trade 2 old products in for a $10 gift card. http://instagram.com/p/gyH6tDSKda/     
    
    
    Marisa is here with @theBalm_Cosmetics #KohlsBeauty #beauty #makeup http://fb.me/2O7BWyZBI     
    
    
    Cargo Limited-Edition "Let's Meet in Paris" Holiday Collection is available at #KohlsBeauty ♥♥ http://fb.me/117b3Y3Fn     
    
    
    "For an instant eye lift add a little darker color to your brow arch." Elizabeth from @lorac_cosmetics… http://instagram.com/p/gyLXL0yKTO/     
    
    
    Tod recommends Adam Levine men's fragrance for your sporty guy. It smells really good! #KohlsBeauty http://instagram.com/p/gyO9W5yKaG/     
    
    
    Beautiful natural look acheived with @Cargo_Cosmetics New Mendocina Blush, Dubai Lip Color and Las… http://instagram.com/p/gySmf1yKQd/     
    
    
    @Lorac_cosmetics must-have carry along is this Touch-Up To Go Convealer/foundatiom pen in CF6...the… http://instagram.com/p/gyT4dKSKTV/     
    
    
    @LORAC_Cosmetics 3D Liquid Lustre Eye Shimmer is a "grown up glitter". Use alone or over shadow… http://instagram.com/p/gyV-97yKW1/     
    
    
    Busy women, this is your must-have beauty product: @lorac_cosmetics Touch-Up To Go… http://instagram.com/p/gyWp08SKX6/     
    
    
    Busy women, this is your must-have beauty product! LORAC Touch-Up To Go concealer/foundation. #KohlsMusic    
    
    
    Under eye coverage by @CargoCosmetics HD Concealer and Jet Lag #KohlsBeauty http://fb.me/NvZYo752     
    
    
    @purminerals Correcting Primers prep and correct skin tone. Loving this sampler set! #KohlsBeauty http://instagram.com/p/gyecG5SKWs/     
    
    
    @cargocosmetics Ima Goodkiss theBalm Girls Lipstick, @Cooococoa my coconut plump your pucker gloss. A… http://instagram.com/p/gyf0WQyKZc/     
    
    
    theBalm_Cosmetics perfect neutral lip combo: Cocoa my Coconut gloss and Ima Goodkisser lip color. Oh… http://instagram.com/p/gyf-_TyKZ4/     
    
    
    The 100th (and last) customer who brought in old cosmetic products and receive d a $10 #KohlsBeauty… http://instagram.com/p/gyigNuSKeW/     
    
    
    Oh my, some of these beauty products needed to be traded in! #KohlsBeauty Glad these women were able… http://instagram.com/p/gykXoByKRV/     
    
    
    David is showing @lorac_cosmetics and @purminerals the Kohl's app that reminds you to use your Kohl's… http://instagram.com/p/gyk1_ISKSE/     
    
    
    @purminerals consulting a customer #KohlsBeauty http://instagram.com/p/gymQpLSKUj/     
    
    
    Thank you #KohlsBeauty for an excellent event! I had a great time! Good bye Las Vegas! http://fb.me/31m83XgpU     
    
    
    Time for one of these before my flight. #cheers #travel http://instagram.com/p/gys4NySKQS/     
    
    
    I have a long list of beauty wants from the new Kohl's Beauty Department. A full list will be shared on the blog... http://fb.me/36ABksTwd     
    
    
    @LarryLGibson sooooo good.    
    
    
    @LarryLGibson much needed. The burrito and chips are good too :)    
    
    
    Look who came to the #KohlsBeauty Trade-in event earlier today... http://instagram.com/p/gywxAByKXr/     
    
    
    @lorac_cosmetics Pro Powder Cheek Stain lasts 12 hours! #KohlsBeauty http://instagram.com/p/gyzSVwyKb1/     
    
    
    Love music? You'll love this @thebalm Rockstar pallete, Balm Jovi! (Look closely at the names! ) ♥♥♥… http://instagram.com/p/gy00QMyKeO/     
    
    
    Head count...everyone in the Midwest accounted for? Praying for your safety! #tornado hugs!!    
    
    
    Be Color Confident with @VeraBradely travel gear #vbwishlist - http://amominredhighheels.com/color-confident/ …    
    
    
    Today's TOP content:Guide to Formaldehyde-Free Brazilian Blowout & Keratin Treatment Alternatives by @jordanalorraine http://amominredhighheels.com/comprehensive-guide-formaldehydefree-brazilian-blowout-keratin-treatment-alternatives/ …    
    
    
    On the Top 5 Tips From Hollywood Makeup Artists - "Skip the sparkle and glitter and go for subtle sheen" http://amominredhighheels.com/5-top-tips-hollywood-makeup-artists/ …    
    
    
    Do all your holiday shopping via @mypoints and earn FREE stuff like cash, gift cards and more! http://amominredhighheels.com/smart-shoppers-maximize-shopping-dollar-mypointscom/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! BFF: Best Foot Forward - ANN INC.* just released its first mobile app called BFF. BFF is your 24/... http://ow.ly/2BxTzj     
    
    
    3-Step Quick Beauty Looks To Get You Out The Door And Looking Great http://lnkd.in/bXcg9eW     
    
    
    Having fun with fashion! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799065086/ …    
    
    
    BFF: Best Foot Forward, the app.  BFF is your 24/7 friend in the fashion business. It helps you put  http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799065096/ …    
    
    
    The pixie cut works really well for a variety of hair types and strengthens and brings out any woman http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799065101/ …    
    
    
    "Women Who Wear Black Lead Colorful Lives." - Neiman Marcus quote http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799065120/ …    
    
    
    After traveling, I always use a great mask to deep clean my skin (and have a little me time).  Proactiv+ Purifying... http://fb.me/N5jH3m6n     
    
    
    I love a deep cleaning mask after a travel weekend! @Proactiv + Purifying Mask works great and smells good! #MomsLoveProactivPlus #sp    
    
    
    Holiday Glitz and Glam: all the beauty products you'll need to create your holiday look are available at Kohl's... http://fb.me/1dSJ58A3g     
    
    
    Love your look this holiday season! Shop @Kohls for beauty, fashion and footwear! #KohlsBeauty http://ow.ly/qV2P3     
    
    
    Shop Kohl's Beauty Department for your holiday look! #KohlsBeauty http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280090364/ …    
    
    
    10 Ways to Get the Best Hair of Your Life http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799065356/ …    
    
    
    Red Lips, Bold Brows and Metallic Shine, oh my! 3 Looks, 3 products each.  http://amominredhighheels.com/3step-quick-beauty/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Holiday Glitz and Glam - Are you ready to dazzle? It's the holiday season and there is nothing mo... http://ow.ly/2By4cg     
    
    
    Holiday Glitz and Glam: All the #beauty products you need are at @Kohls #KohlsBeauty - http://amominredhighheels.com/holiday-beauty/     
    
    
    @oldergirlbeauty Such a great quote! I love wearing black and don't agree with the campaigns against wearing black! ;)    
    
    
    How fun would it be to add this little sparkler to your holiday wardrobe? Perfectly on trend, vintag http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799067261/ …    
    
    
    Nude is so sophisticated http://www.pinterest.com/pin/272608583667894595/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Love this layered look! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799067467/ …    
    
    
    uber-chic leather booties by Michael Michael Kors #red http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799067469/ …    
    
    
    5 Things You Didn't Know About Retinol But Should! | Shine-Beauty - Yahoo Shine http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799067495/ …    
    
    
    Have you seen the new BFF app from ANN, INC? Fashion industry news, inspiration, trends and more! #SoGood http://amominredhighheels.com/bff-foot/     
    
    
    Enter to win: $50 worth of Kushyfoot tights and trouser socks. They are a great way to start your ou http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799068302/ …    
    
    
    layers of rings http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799068304/ …    
    
    
    Loving this large clutch in olive green from @JustFab http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799068365/ …    
    
    
    Could Going #Gluten-Free Clear Your Skin? http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799072154/ …    
    
    
    Do You Need #Gluten-Free Glamour? http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799072158/ …    
    
    
    "Repin" this picture if you LOVE makeup, too! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799072302/ …    
    
    
    Lipstick Love http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799072305/ …    
    
    
    Three tried-and-true tactics to help you lose weight over the holidays! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799072309/ …    
    
    
    Makeup Artist Mélanie Meyer’s Signature Look in 6 Steps http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799072315/ …    
    
    
    Thick and creamy is the way to be when you are a facial mask. #ProactivPlus Purifying Mask passes the… http://instagram.com/p/g566gqSKfA/     
    
    
    Did you check out the BFF app yet from ANN, INC? So good! #Fashion #career #Trendspotter http://amominredhighheels.com/bff-foot/     
    
    
    Which look is your go to: Red lips, metallic shadow or strong brow/natural face? http://amominredhighheels.com/3step-quick-beauty/ …    
    
    
    Holiday Party Hair Made Easy (step-by-step tutorials) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799074486/ …    
    
    
    Don't miss the chance to learn the Style Secrets of Successful Women! (Do you do these things?? If not, you should!) http://ow.ly/qYML4     
    
    
    I pretty much live in these #Neutrogena MoistureSmooth Color Sticks! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799074503/ …    
    
    
    Have you tried the Neutrogena MoistureSmooth Color Sticks yet? I love, love, love!  Check them out, you won't be... http://fb.me/3nc58mcR8     
    
    
    @LarryLGibson hi ♡♥♡♥    
    
    
    essie nail polish available at #KohlsBeauty (I mean, Kohls has everything!!) http://instagram.com/p/g6sDMuyKTD/     
    
    
    If you haven’t already heard, People Magazine has just dubbed Adam Levine the “Sexiest Man Alive!" Adam is a... http://fb.me/32PIC3ErO     
    
    
    Holiday Glitz and Glam - your must-have beauty products! #KohlsBeauty http://amominredhighheels.com/holiday-beauty/     
    
    
    Holiday Glitz and Glam http://lnkd.in/bx_uTms     
    
    
    I had a fantastic time at the Kohl's Beauty Trade-in Event on Saturday.  Here's the recap:
#KohlsBeauty... http://fb.me/2RQ87WYGw     
    
    
    #KohlsBeauty - my wishlist http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280102155/ …    
    
    
    Beauty Event Recap: #KohlsBeauty Trade-in event brings women of all ages that want to up-level their beauty! http://ow.ly/r03LU     
    
    
    Look what's new! #KohlsBeauty Trade-In Event Recap - Talk about beauty upgrades! Many women, of all ages as you'll... http://ow.ly/2BBMs6     
    
    
    After all these years of beauty blogging and trying different makeup, urbandecay Underground is still… http://instagram.com/p/g8aFCESKUZ/     
    
    
    Glam up the holidays with stunning holiday beauty looks from SheKnows Beauty Experts http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280104573/ …    
    
    
    During the holidays, we come together with family and friends to celebrate everything that's good in http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799082897/ …    
    
    
    Glam up the holidays with stunning holiday beauty looks via @SheKnows http://www.sheknows.com/beauty-and-style/articles/1023433/glam-up-the-holidays-with-stunning-holiday-beauty-looks …    
    
    
    From Polished Ladylike to Edgy Elegance with the touch of leather. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799082914/ …    
    
    
    AHHH!!!! Hot pink booties!!! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799082921/ …    
    
    
    Joy is a soy chai latte your husband so thoughtful brings you! Thanks LarryLGibson ♥☆♡★ http://instagram.com/p/g8xeDpSKTK/     
    
    
    See my microphone necklace? It's an exclusive Adam Levine necklace honoring his fragrance line at… http://instagram.com/p/g8-W_WyKXA/     
    
    
    Check out my exclusive microphone necklace in honor of Adam Levine's fragrance collection at #KohlsBeauty Thanks... http://fb.me/TfraW3MU     
    
    
    Lace Cocktail Dress for the holidays http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799087020/ …    
    
    
    Great gifts for them, great rewards for you! Shop via @MyPoints this holiday season! http://ow.ly/r2mcw  #rewardsprogram    
    
    
    Women of Style: Lauren Bush Lauren http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799089460/ …    
    
    
    Women of Style: Jessica Alba http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799089464/ …    
    
    
    Holiday Sale Special in @AliBrown's Success Store: Save 40% but only until Friday, Nov. 22nd! http://ow.ly/r3yDW     
    
    
    40% off until Friday: “21 Cash Flow Strategies: Quick Ideas to Increase Your Cash Flow Now!” http://ow.ly/r3zt7     
    
    
    “57 Income Streams: For More Money, Now and Later” now 40% off! http://ow.ly/r3yHK     
    
    
    "The 6 (Simple) Style Secrets of Successful Women (Including How to Get Dressed Quickly and Look Fab!)" http://ow.ly/r3Gj8     
    
    
    “IncomePublishing Strategies: Create New Revenue Streams & Expert Status from Knowledge You Already Have” 40% off! http://ow.ly/r3yU7     
    
    
    “List Building System: Strategies, Tools, and Secrets to Grow Your Own Profitable List of Prospects Who Buy!” 40% off http://ow.ly/r3z6h     
    
    
    40% off: Ezine Marketing Power: How to Use Email Publishing to Grow Your Revenues FAST http://ow.ly/r3zeK     
    
    
    Want to get inspired to get in shape and lose some weight? Check out these great stories on Fit Yummy Mummy! Vote... http://fb.me/12afsLEuG     
    
    
    “Networking Secrets: Simple Strategies for New Friends, Success, and Profits” http://ow.ly/r3zt7     
    
    
    40% off Success Tool “Solid Steps to Success Kit” http://ow.ly/r3zIc     
    
    
    40% off @AliBrown's product: “Divine Success: The 7 Phases to Realizing Your Dreams” http://ow.ly/r3A29     
    
    
    40% off: “Product Launch System: Proven Formula for Greatest Impact and Maximum Profit” (a program by @AliBrown)http://ow.ly/r3zeK     
    
    
    "Millionaire Time & Productivity Secrets: Get the Important Things Done…in Less Time!" Get it for 40% off today! http://ow.ly/r3zeK     
    
    
    Pour la Victoire Chantel Scalloped Mesh Pump, Red - Neiman Marcus Last Call http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799095870/ …    
    
    
    Pretty much obsessed with the "Red Haute Hues" collection at Neiman Marcus Last Call! Click over to see it for... http://fb.me/6zzSXh7fR     
    
    
    Rachel Roy Spider Mesh Dress http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799095894/ …    
    
    
    So in love with the asymmetric design! Chetta B Faux-Leather Asymmetric Faux-Wrap Dress, Ivory/Black http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799095960/ …    
    
    
    cluster pendant necklace http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799095982/ …    
    
    
    Erin Fetherston Sequined Ponte Combo Sheath Cocktail Dress - Neiman Marcus Last Call http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799095988/ …    
    
    
    Polished Ladylike: Party Style @polyvore http://polyv.re/Ik3NTG     
    
    
    Polished Ladylike party style http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799096034/ …    
    
    
    “It’s Time to Get Help! How to Find and Work with an Assistant or a Team to Support You and Your Business.” http://ow.ly/r3zeK     
    
    
    “24-7 Web Sales: Get More Leads and Clients Online at Little to No Cost” Get this popular @AliBrown product- 40% off http://ow.ly/r3zeK     
    
    
    "The Feminine Edge: Brilliant women. Breakthrough strategies. Redefining Success" product is 40% off in @AliBrown's Success store...    
    
    
    "@LarryLGibson: @ChipotleTweets Excellent service at Casa Grande, AZ location for my daughter with celiac. Thank you!" Yes, thank you!    
    
    
    Looking for a shaving product for both you and your man? Try Proactiv + Soothing Shaving Gel. I used up my... http://fb.me/2BoYtbQXu     
    
    
    @Proactiv + Soothing Shaving Gel will keep your man's face (& your legs) soft and touchable. #MomLoveProactivPlus    
    
    
    @SheKnows shares beauty: http://www.sheknows.com/beauty-and-style/articles/1024149/beauty-bloggers-trade-old-for-new-at-kohls-makeup-trade-in-event … #KohlsBeauty    
    
    
    The beauty department at Kohl's had a makeover! http://SheKnows.com  Experts share:... http://fb.me/Ot45UMH1     
    
    
    News from Beauty Departments at Kohl's #KohlsBeauty http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280139371/ …    
    
    
    Seriously, don't shop online unless it is via @myPoints It would be like throwing $$ away doing it any other way http://amominredhighheels.com/smart-shoppers-maximize-shopping-dollar-mypointscom/ …    
    
    
    @piercemattiepr AWESOME! Thank you! http://www.piercemattie.com/blog/deal-beauty-lists/ … #beauty #moms    
    
    
    Gorgeous hair color: Sabrina Soto http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799124135/ …    
    
    
    Awesome! Pierce Mattie Communications included A Mom in Red High Heels on their list of blogs "worth looking at".... http://fb.me/3cORWvgh3     
    
    
    Nail It Ring from @JustFab 30% off Jewelry going on now! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799129863/ …    
    
    
    Don't miss out on these wide-calf boots from @JustFabOnline http://amominredhighheels.com/wide-calf-boots-officially-arrived-justfab/ …    
    
    
    Sabrina Soto hair updo http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799129993/ …    
    
    
    @LarryLGibson It is almost a 4 day weekend!  Whoo hoo! Have a great day! xoxo    
    
    
    Three-step beauty looks...can it get any easier??! http://fb.me/LcDe6vNt     
    
    
    So...you love to be in the know, right? As part of the VG Scoop Squad, I will be sharing Victoria Gardens... http://fb.me/161FD76op     
    
    
    If you are not traveling tonight, take advantage of this pre-holiday sale going on at Piperlime! So good!... http://fb.me/QjAdkxwI     
    
    
    All jewelry 30% off at @JustFabOnline http://ow.ly/rfGyM  Get the "Notice Me" ring for high impact holiday style!    
    
    
    Look what's new! What to Wear: Thanksgiving Dinner- A Gorgeous Look for Every Personality http://ow.ly/2BQqj5     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving! xo http://fb.me/3bDX2a8qs     
    
    
    Anyone planning on shopping tonight?    
    
    
    Let the fun begin! You heard it here first!
Victoria Gardens Black Friday 11/29: Day 1 of 26 Days...26 Ways...to... http://fb.me/2gICI8OgT     
    
    
    Remember, if you are buying clothing for yourself this weekend, don't just buy it because it is a good deal!... http://fb.me/32vv1mXzj     
    
    
    Get a free tote with any handbag or shoe purchase today only at @DSWShoeLovers. Shopping online? Use code BLACKFRIDAY    
    
    
    3-Step Quick Beauty Looks To Get You Out The Door And Looking Great - http://amominredhighheels.com/3step-quick-beauty/ …    
    
    
    Shop Black Friday at Ann Taylor: 40% Off EVERYTHING! http://ow.ly/rjo6o     
    
    
    Gorgeous skin on your wish list this year? Check out these deals on Obagi, Latisse + more via @DuncanMilesMD http://ow.ly/rjp75     
    
    
    How to Find Narrow-Calf Boots That Fit http://ow.ly/rjo8V     
    
    
    Day 2 of 26 Days...26 Ways to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens:

Ho Ho Ho! Who is the man in the red... http://fb.me/2C6y5crQf     
    
    
    Shop Suey Boutique is offering 30% off all weekend long! Take advantage of these great savings and get some... http://fb.me/1aOsrVDLC     
    
    
    Charlotte Olympia  ●  Jingle Bell velvet platform pumps #HolidayFun http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799152310/ …    
    
    
    Holiday Dress ● Halston Heritage dress ●  Charlotte Olympia Shoes http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799152312/ …    
    
    
    Pointed Toe Pumps http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799152315/ …    
    
    
    North Island , Seychelles http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799152319/ …    
    
    
    Day 3 of 26 Days...26 Ways...to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens:

Yesterday you had a chance to take a... http://fb.me/ZOaZSofu     
    
    
    Is the cold weather and holiday stress getting to your skin? Proactiv + Complexion Perfecting Hydrator is a... http://fb.me/2Qy5X0caL     
    
    
    Is the cold weather and holiday stress getting to your skin? @Proactiv + Complexion Perfecting Hydrator can help! #MomsLoveProactivPlus #sp    
    
    
    A Cure for Your Damaged Hair (hint: it's not a haircut!) - http://amominredhighheels.com/cure-damaged-hair/ …    
    
    
    Dress + Boots = Winning Day Look - http://amominredhighheels.com/dress-boots-winning-day/ …    
    
    
    Vera Wang- so much beauty drama! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799161801/ …    
    
    
    Going for a more Sarah Jessica Parker inspired shade, colorist Lauren Ashley does an amazing job giv http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799161835/ …    
    
    
    Box No. 216: A Day at the Salon with Nina in LA http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799161844/ …    
    
    
    blonde mid-length http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799161848/ …    
    
    
    6 Genius Products: The Best New Beauty Trends http://ow.ly/rlhEK     
    
    
    #ProactivPlus Complexion Perfecting Hydrator is your skin's defense against winter weather and holiday… http://instagram.com/p/hZ4KeyyKYl/     
    
    
    Look what's new! #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway - Starting today, DSW is giving away 250 pairs of shoes and 250 cop... http://ow.ly/2BUrIZ     
    
    
    Starting today, DSW Designer Shoe Warehouse is giving away 250 pairs of shoes and 250 copies of the NY Times best... http://fb.me/2VEKYJOPE     
    
    
    Glam up the holidays with stunning holiday beauty looks via http://SheKnows.com  Experts... http://fb.me/6iQpR3nKX     
    
    
    @mybelongingblog is hosting today's #DSWShoeHookup contest! FIVE winners receive @DSWShoeLovers shoes! http://ow.ly/rn2C2     
    
    
    Get good skin for the holidays with @Proactiv + Complexion Perfecting Hydrator! It hydrates AND fights acne. Awesome! #MomsLoveProactivPlus    
    
    
    Need a holiday party look? Get inspired on @SheKnows with looks from their beauty experts! http://fb.me/6iQpR3nKX     
    
    
    Day 4 of 26 Days...26 Ways...to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens:
We have the perfect stocking stuffer... http://fb.me/33gkeRX7d     
    
    
    From Dec 1-25, you can enter for the chance to win an indulgent prize courtesy of Ferrero Rocher®. #spon http://soch.us/-Pcpf  #25DaysGold    
    
    
    Gorgeous D'Orsay Pump by Christian Louboutin http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799167835/ …    
    
    
    BCBG Paris Jaze d'Orsay Pump #DSW #shoelover http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799167844/ …    
    
    
    Holiday outfit style- STUNNING! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799167876/ …    
    
    
    Obagi & Latisse Black Friday & Cyber Monday Sale! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799167879/ …    
    
    
    @shoesmitten is giving away FIVE pairs of shoes from @DSWSHOELovers today in the #DSWShoeHookup  Go Enter! http://ow.ly/rn4hW     
    
    
    @MarcellaMakeup Really breathtaking, isn't it?? :)    
    
    
    Anyone else doing some late night Cyber Monday Shopping?? I haven't even started yet! Yikes! Here is my short... http://fb.me/2wvDKULjy     
    
    
    Late Night Cyber Monday Shopping (+ Savings!). Hurry before the night is over! http://icont.ac/26fdJ     
    
    
    Look what's new! Late Night Cyber Monday Shopping (+ Savings!) http://ow.ly/2BV8uW     
    
    
    @VeronicaGlamm Great find! 90 min to go :) Click, click!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @FashionJuice is hosting the @DSWSHOELovers #DSWShoeHookup today! Whoo Hoo! Good Luck! http://ow.ly/rpFxE     
    
    
    Lucky You: 2 For $49.95 at @JustFabOnline is EXTENDED - Ends Tonight! http://ow.ly/rpJfX     
    
    
    Have you signed up for @MyPoints yet? Free rewards for you just for shopping your favorite stores via them! http://ow.ly/rpKmY     
    
    
    @BelledeCouture is also hosting the #DSWShoeHookup today! Double giveaway goodness from @DSWSHOELovers http://ow.ly/rpGne     
    
    
    The third #DSWShoeHookup is hosted by Gentri Lee. Thanks @DSWShoeLovers for so many awesome chances to win! http://ow.ly/rpHbc     
    
    
    Day 6 of 26 Days…26 Ways…to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens:
(YUM!)
What’s a Holiday without sweets?... http://fb.me/347gKlhqa     
    
    
    Look what's new! A FABulous Giveaway from FabKids - Today is a good day. Know why? Well, because my sweet, beauti... http://ow.ly/2BWgwK     
    
    
    #DSWShoeHookup continues! Enter to win @DSWSHOELovers shoes on @AlteratnsNeeded http://ow.ly/rrMwb  Good Luck!    
    
    
    Love what this belt does for the outfit! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799179247/ …    
    
    
    much love, illy is hosting the #DSEShoeHookup today! http://pinterest.com/pin/284219426457161449/ …    
    
    
    @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway is on! Enter daily to win gorgeous outfits for the kiddos!  http://bit.ly/1jda5mH     
    
    
    @DSW Designer Shoe Warehouse gift card bonus! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799179605/ …    
    
    
    I interviewed Sarah Cleghorn - Tapping Into Your Genius today! Love this woman- so inspiring! She offers an... http://fb.me/11KIsF3E1     
    
    
    @TappingGenius shares her tips for success, style and beauty in today's Style & Success interview http://ow.ly/rscC3     
    
    
    Makeover Alert: Julianne Hough Ditched Her Bob For Bedhead Extensions - Daily Makeover (love it or l http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799180207/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Exclusive: Sarah Cleghorn, Energy Coach, Inspires Us With Her Work and Wardrobe http://ow.ly/2BWwUK     
    
    
    Today The 2nd Biggest Online Shopping Day Of The Year: Get discount codes now via @SHEfinds http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799180924/ …    
    
    
    @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway began today! Today's featured outfit is modeled by my daughter! All the… http://instagram.com/p/hhDCi3SKW2/     
    
    
    DSW Shoe Lovers Holiday Lookbook #DSWShoeHookup http://pinterest.com/pin/284219426457162509/ …    
    
    
    feathered Black Bootie- so fab! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799181048/ …    
    
    
    tan pencil skirt, black sweater, black knee-high boots...classic http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799181509/ …    
    
    
    Nina Ricci http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799181540/ …    
    
    
    It's Cyber Week on @MyPoints If you are serious about saving this holiday season, join (for free) and save! http://ow.ly/rsKmO     
    
    
    A FABulous Giveaway from @LoveFabKids ! Enter daily! http://amominredhighheels.com/fabulous-giveaway-fabkids/ …    
    
    
    On my wishlist!! MCQ BY ALEXANDER MCQUEEN - Fringe trim knitted sweater http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799183337/ …    
    
    
    Milly Knit Leather Collar Sweater in Charcoal with detachable leather color! #Versatile #Wishlist http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799183621/ …    
    
    
    ASOS: Cyber Monday all week long! Promo code MOREMOREMORE #Deals http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799183658/ …    
    
    
    Today is an excellent day to enter to win shoes! Visit @DSWSHOELovers to get details on the #DSWShoeHookup http://ow.ly/rsA7s     
    
    
    Day 7 of 26 Days…26 Ways…to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens:

Known for their 100% vegetarian products,... http://fb.me/32T1PMnyI     
    
    
    Look what's new! The Perfect Sweater for Your Body Type - Not all sweaters are created equal. No matter how gorge... http://ow.ly/2BX65C     
    
    
    Not all sweater are created equal! This winter, wear the one that is right for you!

The Perfect Sweater for... http://fb.me/6n3Uq01on     
    
    
    There is a new outfit up so be sure to enter to win for your own FabKid! @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway http://amominredhighheels.com/fabulous-giveaway-fabkids/ …    
    
    
    #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway- DON"T MISS OUT! Join the fun! Enter daily! http://amominredhighheels.com/dswshoehookup-giveaway/ …    
    
    
    Loving the major bling on this wristlet from @ShopSueyBoutiqu It's perfect for holiday events! http://instagram.com/p/hjquzDyKel/     
    
    
    Loving this flapper-esque Mosaic Stone Convertible Soft Headband from @Andrea's Beau . Perfect for N http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799188158/ …    
    
    
    Another chance to win @DSWShoeLovers shoes! @PursuitofShoe is giving away 5 pairs! #DSWShoeHookup http://ow.ly/ruVAy     
    
    
    #ProactivPlus Skin Soothing Exfoliator is the perfect exfoliator. It is gentle enough to use twice a… http://instagram.com/p/hlm9oRyKae/     
    
    
    Proactiv + Skin Smoothing Exfoliator is so gentle, you can use it twice a day! It is an amazing tool for fighting... http://fb.me/6jArwKu09     
    
    
    Get hooked up with @DSWSHOELovers shoes! #DSWShoeHookup giveaway hosted on JadoreFashions today! http://ow.ly/rwCAU     
    
    
    Day 8 of 26 Days…26 Ways…to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens!

It’s Friday and that means Victoria’s Famers... http://fb.me/6jTJaiVZh     
    
    
    Give the gift of good skin this holiday! @Proactiv + Skin Soothing Exfoliator works amazing and feels great! #MomsLoveProactivPlus #sp    
    
    
    @JordanaLorraine shares How to Do the Katniss Braid on Yourself--The Hunger Games - http://amominredhighheels.com/katniss-braid-yourselfthe-hunger-games/ …    
    
    
    Don't go shopping until you read this: The Perfect Sweater for Your Body Type - http://amominredhighheels.com/perfect-sweater-body-type/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! How to Do the Katniss Braid on YourselfThe Hunger Games http://ow.ly/2BXZYh     
    
    
    ADORABLE little one featured on @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway today! Enter to win her outfit! http://bit.ly/1jda5mH     
    
    
    Shop WideCalf boots on @JustFabOnline. Gift them or Keep them, either way, it's a brilliant buy! http://amominredhighheels.com/wide-calf-boots-officially-arrived-justfab/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    You can afford to shop for a Little Black Dresse for the holidays! @thredUp has many pre-owned styles you'll love! http://ow.ly/rwVPx     
    
    
    Shop Suey Boutique is having a Holiday Open House today and tomorrow! If you are local, you should… http://instagram.com/p/hmVH52yKTc/     
    
    
    #DSWShoeHookup is now live on @@melaneeshale http://ow.ly/rxhi6  Check out her look & enter to win @DSWSHOELovers shoes of your own!    
    
    
    Day 9 of 26 Days…26 Ways…to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens (this one starts at 5 PM tonight)

You’ve... http://fb.me/2sIMJdfRY     
    
    
        
    
    
    Giveaway Time! Enter to win the Core System from Proactiv +! This year, give the gift of good skin!... http://fb.me/6trgiLtNg     
    
    
    Look what's new! Proactiv + Skin Care Is The Perfect Holiday Gift for Yourself or Another (+ enter to win) http://ow.ly/2BYGYM     
    
    
    Stopping in @Ulta at @VictoriaGardens for some beauty shopping! #UltaGlam    
    
    
    Enjoying the holiday season at @victoriagardens. The tree is beautiful.. #victoriously http://instagram.com/p/hpH-KgyKYe/     
    
    
    Christmas shopping at @victoriagardens #victoriously http://instagram.com/p/hpJZ9LSKbK/     
    
    
    Win a Proactiv+ Core System! Give the gift of good skin! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799205836/ …    
    
    
    LIKE if you agree :) http://fb.me/1Qwhp0Ep8     
    
    
    GUMBALL DOT Lace Dress http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799206075/ …    
    
    
    Get over to ULTA Beauty's Facebook page where every day, for eight days, they are giving away perfumes in their... http://fb.me/17HYGC62a     
    
    
    @ULTA_Beauty is giving away perfumes in their Scent-sational Giveaway.Starts today w/ a Marc Jacobs Gift Pack #ULTABeauty #ULTAGlam #spon    
    
    
    @TheStyleWord @alywalansky @AriSethCohen @afrobella @alixrose @JuliaConey @BlairEadieBEE @OrvaShoes Thanks! :)    
    
    
    Shoe Lover calendar on sale at Kohl's! $7.99 #GiftGiving http://instagram.com/p/hrLFJCyKQ5/     
    
    
    Sunday afternoon geocaching fun with the family. http://instagram.com/p/hrfN0TSKV9/     
    
    
    Enter to win #ProactivPlus Core System! Contest is live now (link in post) #MomsLoveProactivPlus http://instagram.com/p/hr-XCkSKXw/     
    
    
    Christmas shopping? Shop retailers like Gap, Macys, Pet Co, B&N + more thru @MyPoints to earn rewards while shopping! http://ow.ly/rzEwq     
    
    
    Why Not Turn Heads This Holiday Season! (sale ends tonight) http://ow.ly/rzFj6     
    
    
    Fit Yummy Mummy put  everything you need to look fabulous in your little black dress into a step-by-step workout... http://fb.me/3aHk2Pvjz     
    
    
    See the handsome little guy on the @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway? There is still time to enter to win his outfit! http://bit.ly/1jda5mH     
    
    
    Style Squad: Gifts for the Haute Hostess (+playlist) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799214744/ …    
    
    
    Style Squad: Gifts for Trendsetters (+playlist) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799214747/ …    
    
    
    Why Not Turn Heads This Holiday Season with Get Little Black Dress Ready Workouts! (sale ends tonight) http://ow.ly/rzFkG     
    
    
    Yesterday was the 21st anniversary of our first date! These beauties are from my guy ♥♥ http://instagram.com/p/hsVXRuSKdl/     
    
    
    7 Instant Confidence Boosters | A Mom in Red High Heels http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799214954/ …    
    
    
    Stocking Stuffers for women who like to look good #kohlsbeauty http://pinterest.com/pin/210824826280203134/ …    
    
    
    Stocking stuffers and small gifts from Kohl's beauty department are sure to please any woman this Christmas... http://fb.me/1NgQtzxcJ     
    
    
    Stocking stuffersfrom @Kohls_Official beauty department are sure to please any woman this Christmas! http://fb.me/1NgQtzxcJ  #kohlsbeauty    
    
    
    Look what's new! Small Wonders for Women Who Like To Look Good http://ow.ly/2BZrtV     
    
    
    Earn 25 Points per dollar when you shop AVON via @MyPoints http://ow.ly/rAwXd     
    
    
    #DSWShoeHookup today on @CrystalinMarie! Keep entering for your chance to win @DSWSHOELovers shoes! http://ow.ly/rB00i     
    
    
    Today's little model on @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway is ADORABLE! Enter to win outfit! xo A Mom in Red High Heels  http://ow.ly/rB1Sp     
    
    
    Small Wonders for Women Who Like To Look Good - http://amominredhighheels.com/small-wonders-women-good/ …    
    
    
    GREEN MONDAY SALE! Over 100 items just marked down!  Very limited quantities, one of a kinds and las http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799216699/ …    
    
    
    Adorable sequin holiday dress http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799216703/ …    
    
    
    @KimmyErin hosts a #DSWShoeHookup today! Win @DSWSHOELovers shoes if you win! Enter now! http://ow.ly/rB0Gf     
    
    
    Small Gifts for Women Who Like To Look Good -  #KohlsBeauty http://ow.ly/rB2Ey     
    
    
    Purchase a CVS Gift Card, earn 200 Points at the @MyPoints store (expires 12/23/13) http://ow.ly/rBhSl     
    
    
    Shoe Lovers! ANOTHER #DSWShoeHookup giveaway is up! @sandyalamode is hosting! 5 winners receive @DSWSHOELovers shoes! http://ow.ly/rB1cw     
    
    
    4 Things You Can Do Daily to Slow the Signs of Aging http://ow.ly/rB2Yd     
    
    
    Extra Savings at Shop Suey Boutique today! I found a necklace and hat that I can't live without! http://fb.me/2GNKKrYG0     
    
    
    Ultra CHI All That Glitters Flat Iron adds moisture and shine while reducing frizz! #ULTAGlam http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799217737/ …    
    
    
    Need small beauty gifts for teachers, friends, neighbors? Here are a few ideas..  #KohlsBeauty http://ow.ly/rB2Uc     
    
    
    A stylish gift idea today! (I love a beautiful watch!)
Day 11 of 26 Days...26 Ways...to Shop #Victoriously at... http://fb.me/S4qK9FUD     
    
    
    Did you enter the @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway yet? Enter Daily! Please share that A Mom in Red High Heels sent you http://ow.ly/rB1Sp     
    
    
    Your phone should be as pretty and festive as your makeup, which is why Too Faced created this two-i http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799221559/ …    
    
    
    Small Gifts for Women Who Like To Look Good - http://amominredhighheels.com/small-wonders-women-good/ …    
    
    
    Last chance for today: enter the @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway! Please share that A Mom in Red High Heels sent you http://ow.ly/rB1Sp     
    
    
    Look what's new! Beautiful Finds for Everyone on Your List at ULTA http://ow.ly/2C0eRy     
    
    
    Beautiful Finds for Everyone on Your List at ULTA Beauty http://amominredhighheels.com/gift-giving-ulta/ …... http://fb.me/15p8o6x9Y     
    
    
    @MyOwnBlogReview shares "Riding Into The Holiday Season with a #DSWShoeHook " Enter to win @DSWShoeLovers shoes! http://www.myownblogreview.com/2013/12/riding-into-holiday-season-with.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    How to Style Your Hair into a Faux Bob http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799223219/ …    
    
    
    Need a "guy gift?" Purchase an AMC Movie Bundle, earn 150 Points on @MyPoints http://ow.ly/rDqM4     
    
    
    Looking for the perfect gift for that special someone? @TwistedRocks shares a few of their favorite things! http://ow.ly/rDr86     
    
    
    It's in the bible...ENJOY LIFE!
"So I recommend having fun, because there is nothing better for people in this... http://fb.me/2KFJDyZzM     
    
    
    So You're Feeling Too Fat to Be Photographed... http://huff.to/1eVS2in  via @HuffPostWomen    
    
    
    Enter to win this adorable outfit on @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway. Please share that A Mom in Red H http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799223458/ …    
    
    
    Stocking stuffers and small gift ideas. #kohlsbeauty http://amominredhighheels.com/small-wonders-women-good/ …    
    
    
    OH MY! SUCH CUTENESS! Look at this lil' @lovefabkids girl. Enter to win her outfit today! http://ow.ly/rDuu3     
    
    
    Donna Karan- loving the edginess! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799223671/ …    
    
    
    Holiday lip: MAC Sin Lipstick (Pro) with Currant Lipliner http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799223676/ …    
    
    
    Beautiful Finds for Everyone on Your List at @ULTA_Beauty http://amominredhighheels.com/gift-giving-ulta/ … http://amominredhighheels.com/gift-giving-ulta/ … #ULTAGlam #ULTABeauty    
    
    
    Beautiful Finds for Everyone on Your List at ULTA http://lnkd.in/bs6Sxc6     
    
    
    Skin Benefits of Green Tea http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799223706/ …    
    
    
    @Proactiv + Skin Care Is The Perfect Holiday Gift for Yourself or Another (+ enter to win) - http://amominredhighheels.com/proactiv-skin-care-perfect-holiday-gift-enter-win/ … http://amominredhighheels.com/proactiv-skin-care-perfect-holiday-gift-enter-win/ …    
    
    
    2-in-1 designer inspired handbag http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799223769/ …    
    
    
    eos Lemon Drop Smooth Sphere Lip Balm SPF 15- great stocking stuffer! #ULTABeauty #ULTAGlam http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799224027/ …    
    
    
    Betsey Johnson Rain Boot Liners, Faux Fur Socks #MustHave http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799224040/ …    
    
    
    @LuciaMouet host another #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway today! You need a @DSWSHOELovers reward number to enter. http://ow.ly/rDp7a     
    
    
    Wear a fun sweater and black pants to pair with red heels! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799224210/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Get The Goods: Giveaways Galore! - In case you've been absorbed in holiday shopping, baking and ... http://ow.ly/2C0IGQ     
    
    
    Are you up-to-date on all the giveaways going on? If not, click now and start entering! Many goods are waiting to... http://fb.me/2UJLiCmLy     
    
    
    The most beautiful tree on my daily drive. #fall http://instagram.com/p/hxRfR0yKc_/     
    
    
    Go Places in Style: Gifts for Those Who Love to #Travel http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799230433/ …    
    
    
    LOVE Stiletto Beats look for her #DSWShoeHookup So fabulous! Get over there to enter to win @DSWShoeLovers shoes! http://ow.ly/rFP8Z     
    
    
    Pantone Color of the Year 2014: Radiant Orchid... LOVE IT!    
    
    
    OH! Cute lil' FabKid in a Cool Blue Outfit from @lovefabkids is featured on the Holiday Giveaway today! http://ow.ly/rFPRg  #Giveaway    
    
    
    Triple your Points with a Cheesecake Gift Card when you purchase via The @MyPoints store! http://ow.ly/rFUGu     
    
    
    holiday cheers! (what festive cocktails!) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799230807/ …    
    
    
    holiday glam: Bold red, gorgeous cuff, fun clutch...what could be better to toast the new year in? http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799230811/ …    
    
    
    Estee Lauder Limited Edition Makeup Compact, Blue - Neiman Marcus #Gorgeous #Gift http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799230858/ …    
    
    
    Pinch Provisions Shemergency Kit #StockingStuffer http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799230867/ …    
    
    
    Know someone who loves to travel (maybe you)? Here are some great gift ideas to help them travel in style:... http://fb.me/2mNDiQzla     
    
    
    Go Places in Style: Gifts for Those Who Love to Travel http://lnkd.in/bNnm-u6     
    
    
    Want to make 6-figures being a coach-doing something you love? Join @AliBrown for her FREE webinar on 12/12 @ 3pm ET http://ow.ly/rG3k0     
    
    
    Scored MAJOR savings on @PSfromAero The entire site is 50-70% off! #Gifts #Kids http://ow.ly/rFW0B     
    
    
    Ready for another #DSWShoeHookup giveaway? @CourtyStarr is hosting! http://ow.ly/rFPcQ     
    
    
    Day 13 of 26 Days...26 Ways...to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens:

Buy one, get one FREE all sweaters, all... http://fb.me/6nUjv14gZ     
    
    
    On a Frosty date with my husband ...don't tell the kids! http://instagram.com/p/hzB3SJSKa0/     
    
    
    @AliBrown's free webinar "9 Steps to Growing a Wildly Profitable Coaching Business" is tmrw! Sign up to listen in! http://ow.ly/rG3k0     
    
    
    Did you enter the @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway today? Today's outfit model is adorable! http://ow.ly/rFPRg  #Giveaway    
    
    
    Cranberry Margaritas by gimmesomeoven #Cocktail #Margarita #Cranberry http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799232201/ …    
    
    
    @AliBrown's free webinar "9 Steps to Growing a Wildly Profitable Coaching Business" is tmrw! Don't miss it! http://ow.ly/rG3k0     
    
    
    I did something I've never done tonight...I looked up and used recipes off of Pinterest.  I made Rosemary Pork... http://fb.me/17E0JGsCK     
    
    
    I did something I've never done tonight...I looked up and used recipes off of Pinterest. I made Rosemary Pork... http://fb.me/RhUfkuKZ     
    
    
    Diane von Furstenberg Cat Headphones http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799235232/ …    
    
    
    Looking for a good camo jean? Try these http://ow.ly/rGPCF  Camo is a great neutral!    
    
    
    Look what's new! What to Wear on Mom Days: Camo, Fur and Riding Boots http://ow.ly/2C3HPr     
    
    
    Love makeup? You are going to be excited about today's special at Victoria Gardens! 

Day 14 of 26 Days...26... http://fb.me/23mz0tLq6     
    
    
    Bloggers dish on their favorite stocking stuffers on @SheKnows http://www.sheknows.com/beauty-and-style/articles/1025203/bloggers-favorite-stocking-stuffers …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Today's cool FabBoy models the @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway outfit. Enter to win! http://ow.ly/rFPRg  #Giveaway    
    
    
    What to Wear on Mom Days: Camo, Fur and Riding Boots #DSWShoeHookup http://pinterest.com/pin/284219426457198349/ …    
    
    
    Outfit styled with @Twisted Silver Grace Necklace http://pinterest.com/pin/49680402113674115/ …    
    
    
    Today's FREE webinar w/ @AliBrown "9 Steps to Growing a Wildly Profitable 
Coaching Business" starts in ONE HOUR. http://ow.ly/rIjhf     
    
    
    Holiday doorbuster gifts for your pet via the @MyPoints store. Buy Fido the goods, you get the rewards! http://ow.ly/rIoVt     
    
    
    #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway and style post: AMAZING look from Behind the Seams! #LOVE http://pinterest.com/pin/284219426457198621/ …    
    
    
    @fancythingsblog #DSWShoeHookup giveaway and style post is up! Go enter to win @DSWSHOELovers shoes! http://ow.ly/rIpqs     
    
    
    What to wear on "Mom Days"...on trend and comfortable! #DSWShoeHookup http://fb.me/1Li1NNELu     
    
    
    Enter to win today's @lovefabkids Outfit Giveaway. Select A Mom in Red High Heels as your referrer when entering. xo http://ow.ly/rFPRg     
    
    
    Anyone else feeling kinda pressured to pull it together and get your Christmas shopping done? Wish I had shopped early...    
    
    
    Get your running shoes ready, today's Victoria Gardens Shop Victoriously special is going to go quickly....... http://fb.me/29T6m95Gi     
    
    
    @Maebad is hosting the #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway today! Whoop Whoop! Win @DSWSHOELovers shoes! http://ow.ly/rKtvk     
    
    
    Justice is 60% off this weekend only!! (12/13-16) http://www.pinterest.com/pin/150166968799246137/ …    
    
    
    holiday glam http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799246277/ …    
    
    
    11 days until Christmas!  Extra 35% off everything. 40% off with $300+ purchase at @LastCallNM    
    
    
        
    
    
    Scored some major deals and finished up Christmas shopping today! I can't share what because my husband reads this... http://fb.me/QvaXNhCD     
    
    
    Troop 33 Geocache Hike led by Nick. http://instagram.com/p/h6XcARSKaz/     
    
    
    Sweet lil' FabGirl is wearing a beautiful holiday dress on @lovefabkids Holiday Giveaway. Enter to win the dress! http://ow.ly/rMvbe     
    
    
    Win Cute Holiday Outfits for the Kids, Shoes for You!  http://icont.ac/27PQx     
    
    
    Double Points for The Children's Place Gift Cards when buying through @myPoints store http://ow.ly/rMwVi     
    
    
    An Amazing deal: Get 50% off your ENTIRE purchase at Ann Taylor with code HOLIDAY50    
    
    
    Style Squad: What to Wear for the Holidays: http://youtu.be/MZZm5wgdIEY  via @glam_com    
    
    
    Here's a fabulous giveaway! Wow! How fun it would be to win this!! http://fb.me/6EQIZ1eLt     
    
    
    From Dec 1-25, you can enter for the chance to win an indulgent prize courtesy of Ferrero Rocher® #spon http://soch.us/1f14-0x8Zj  #25DaysGold    
    
    
    Official Rules for the ’25 Days Wrapped in Gold’ Sweepstakes are available at http://soch.us/short-link  #25DaysGold #spon    
    
    
    Enter to win @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway daily. Tell them A Mom in Red High Heels sent you. http://ow.ly/rMveW     
    
    
    The 12 Days of Red High Heels is in full swing! See today's pick:... http://fb.me/1dMns7XeZ     
    
    
    Holiday Style http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799262499/ …    
    
    
    Win this cute red holiday dress for your FabGirl. Good Luck, A Mom in Red High Heels http://ow.ly/rMvnD     
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 3 http://ow.ly/2C9mea     
    
    
    Enter to win @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway daily. Tell them A Mom in Red High Heels sent you. http://ow.ly/rMvso     
    
    
    Enter to win @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway daily. Tell them A Mom in Red High Heels sent you. http://ow.ly/rMvhx     
    
    
    Win a cute red holiday outfit for your FabKid. Good Luck, A Mom in Red High Heels http://ow.ly/rMvxX     
    
    
    Look what's new! Get Your Holiday Glow On! - It's the holiday seasondo you have your glow on? You are attending ev... http://ow.ly/2Ca2n2     
    
    
    Win a cute red holiday outfit for your FabKid. Good Luck, A Mom in Red High Heels http://ow.ly/rMvwt     
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 4 http://ow.ly/2Caz9E     
    
    
    Enter to win @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway daily. Tell them A Mom in Red High Heels sent you. http://ow.ly/rMviO     
    
    
    Get your Holiday Glow On with @Conair_hair http://amominredhighheels.com/holiday-glow/  #Conair    
    
    
    $20 Off $75 + Free Ship Ends 2Day on @PSfromAero #MajorDeals http://ow.ly/rOt51     
    
    
    @FashionNextDoor shares in the #DSWShoeHookup love today! Enter to win @DSWSHOELovers shoes! http://ow.ly/rOvIu     
    
    
    ooh la la! These booties are gorgeous! Sam Edelman Mila Bootie from @DSW Designer Shoe Warehouse http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799269739/ …    
    
    
    @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway is NOT TO BE MISSED today! Win the entire Holiday Collection for your FabKid! http://ow.ly/rOFDG     
    
    
    @kelandkate host a #DSWShoeHookup giveaway today! 5 winner, 5 e-gift cards to @DSWSHOELovers :) http://ow.ly/rOFc6     
    
    
    Studs and Sapphires has her #DSWShoeHookup LIVE! Check out her gorgeous look and enter to win #SHOES http://ow.ly/rPbyK     
    
    
    Check out Britt + Whit's  #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway! http://pinterest.com/pin/284219426457217044/ …    
    
    
    @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway is NOT TO BE MISSED today! Win the entire Holiday Collection for your FabKid! http://ow.ly/rOFIx     
    
    
    On the 4th day of Christmas, my true love gave to me savvy suede dress heels! #12Days #RedHeels… http://instagram.com/p/iAIwmeyKRV/     
    
    
    Enter to win @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway daily. Tell them A Mom in Red High Heels sent you. http://ow.ly/rMvjP     
    
    
    @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway is NOT TO BE MISSED today! Win the entire Holiday Collection for your FabKid! http://ow.ly/rOFKw     
    
    
    I am hosting the #DSWShoeHookup tmrw! Watch for fun to begin in a few short hours!    
    
    
    @msmansk I am looking fwd to seeing it for the clothes :)    
    
    
    In a few short hours I will ne hosting the #DSWShoeHookup giveaway. Prepare yourself. Get signed up for the DSW... http://fb.me/3zUfv2Klp     
    
    
    In a few short hours I will be hosting the #DSWShoeHookup giveaway. Prepare yourself. Get signed up for the DSW... http://fb.me/3j3xd74fO     
    
    
    @LoveFabKids Holiday Giveaway is NOT TO BE MISSED today! Win the entire Holiday Collection for your FabKid! http://ow.ly/rOFNr     
    
    
    #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway is LIVE!! Go enter!!... http://fb.me/2S16DXo5S     
    
    
    Do You Speak Shoe Lover? WIN this book AND a $50 gift card to @DSW Designer Shoe Warehouse today on  http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799276586/ …    
    
    
    #DSWShoeHookup Bloggers: Volume 2 http://pinterest.com/pin/284219426457220590/ …    
    
    
    Good Luck! RT @MelC417: I entered to win the #DSWShoeHookup from @amominred and @DSWShoeLovers http://ow.ly/rOIhX  #win #free #shoes    
    
    
    Good Luck! RT @lazza_zo: “I entered to win the #DSWShoeHookup from @amominred and @DSWShoeLovers http://ow.ly/rOIhX “    
    
    
    Good Luck! RT @LShltn: “I entered to win the #DSWShoeHookup from @amominred and @DSWShoeLovers http://ln.is/ow.ly/DZBO “    
    
    
        
    
    
    Good Luck! RT @BlaqDyemond62: I entered to win the #DSWShoeHookup from @amominred and @DSWShoeLovers http://ow.ly/rOIhX     
    
    
    2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 5 (+ #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799277065/ …    
    
    
    Don't miss your chance to win a $50 gift card to DSW to win SHOES! http://lnkd.in/b2B3zG6     
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 5 (+ #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway) http://ow.ly/2CcJZA     
    
    
        
    
    
    Day 19 of 26 Days…26 Ways to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens

Have you made your way to visit Santa this... http://fb.me/3dPGUCUBh     
    
    
    @NataliaLSimmons @Conair_Hair It was an impressive at-home blowout, right?! #Conair #HolidayBeauty    
    
    
    @fashionhost hosts the #DSWShoeHookup today! Enter now :) http://www.fashionablehostess.com/dsw-shoe-hookup-official-giveaway/ …    
    
    
    Day 19 of 26 Days…26 Ways to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens

Today only, 40% off purchases at Banana... http://fb.me/1EKq7VCkJ     
    
    
    30% OFF JEWELRY CODE on @Shop Suey Boutique - TODAY ONLY! Use Code GEMS30 http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799284918/ …    
    
    
    On my WISH LIST!

Day 6 of the 12 Days of A Mom in Red High Heels. Details and reminder to enter #DSWShoeHookup... http://fb.me/38m5E4uWm     
    
    
        
    
    
    @districtsparkle kicks off her #DSWShoeHookup today! 5 Winners will receive a gift card to shop @DSWSHOELovers shoes! Whoo hoo!    
    
    
    Day 19 of 26 Days…26 Ways to Shop #Victoriously at @VIctoriaGardens : Today only, 40% off at Banana Republic... http://fb.me/1EKq7VCkJ     
    
    
    REMINDER: Enter my #DSWShoeHookup giveaway! Five Winners, $50 GC each to @DSWSHOELovers ! SCORE! http://ow.ly/rOIhX     
    
    
    On the sixth day of Christmas,  my true love gave to me menswear-inspired lace-up shooties! Details on… http://instagram.com/p/iFXTq0SKfl/     
    
    
    Bouclé biker jacket from @MANGO http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799287584/ …    
    
    
    @PromoCodesSave helped me save on these earrings that I'll be gifting this Christmas! http://ow.ly/rUaww  #savings #sticktobudget    
    
    
    Still shopping for gifts? Check out http://PromotionalCodes.com  for discounts on thousands of websites!... http://fb.me/6lyKNurk8     
    
    
    Elizabeth and James Metropolis Triangle Cocktail Ring #Can'tLiveWithout http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799287952/ …    
    
    
    Did you enter my #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway yet?? Don't miss out! http://amominredhighheels.com/2013-edition-12-days-red-high-heels-day-5-dswshoehookup-giveaway/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! Shop Smarter and Save with http://PromotionalCodes.com  http://ow.ly/2CfCpB     
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 7 http://ow.ly/2Cg5WH     
    
    
    Extra 50% off at @MANGO today!! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799292430/ …    
    
    
    Mango Lurex boucle jacket (Extra 50% off today on @MANGO ) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799292474/ …    
    
    
    2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 7
Sexy little pumps with a fun detail! (PLUS enter to win... http://fb.me/Qk66AH4i     
    
    
    2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 7 http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799292605/ …    
    
    
    #DSWShoeHookup Giveaway ends tomorrow! Enter today! http://icont.ac/28qgN     
    
    
    A great question shared by Denise today. I'd like to follow it up with this:

If you don't feel gorgeous, what... http://fb.me/6oOlrt1ve     
    
    
        
    
    
    On the seventh day of Christmas, my true love gave to me pumps with a sexy ribbon detail! Detail and… http://instagram.com/p/iHo-PKSKbQ/     
    
    
    2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 7 & a reminder to enter the #DSWShoeHookup giveaway! http://amominredhighheels.com/2013-edition-12-days-red-high-heels-day-7/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 8 http://ow.ly/2ChXvH     
    
    
    On the eighth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me....... http://fb.me/3AKYnVjU3     
    
    
    On the eighth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me sky high pumps (with a darling bow)! Details… http://instagram.com/p/iJzUO3yKbh/     
    
    
    We are down to the last 10 minutes! Enter the #DSWShoeHookup now for your chance to win a $50 e-gift card to shop... http://fb.me/14fiQWcYo     
    
    
    2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 9

HOT! EDGY! HEAD-TURNING!... http://fb.me/6uefYl4iC     
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 9 http://ow.ly/2CkxmC     
    
    
    2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 10 (+ #DSWShoeHookup Winners!)... http://fb.me/2GhJWds5o     
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 10 (+ #DSWShoeHookup Winners!) http://ow.ly/2ClM2e     
    
    
        
    
    
    How To Look Glam for NYE Even If You Are Staying In
http://amominredhighheels.com/glam-nye-staying/ …
#kohlsBeauty http://fb.me/6xdjB9XzC     
    
    
    A gorgeous hairstyle for a casual NYE http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799322875/ …    
    
    
    A cool way to rock sneakers! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799322994/ …    
    
    
    Leopard Sneakers! #cool Ash (Jungle slip on sneakers) http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799323002/ …    
    
    
    Camo-printed ponyhair low top sneaker detailed with a gold-tone, spike-covered cap toe.  I mean, if  http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799323007/ …    
    
    
    CHIARA FERRAGNI - LIPSTICK GLITTER LOAFERS- how cute! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799323032/ …    
    
    
    Charlotte Olympia Satin Kitty Slippers & Eye Mask Set #WishList http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799323039/ …    
    
    
    My "stay in" NYE outfit, styled with boots from @DSW Designer Shoe Warehouse http://pinterest.com/pin/284219426457247893/ …    
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 11 http://ow.ly/2CmPmj     
    
    
    2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 11
What do you think about these red suede pumps?... http://fb.me/2ClwmVJfu     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6xx49dLiY     
    
    
    Merry Christmas from A Mom in Red High Heels! http://icont.ac/28V2R     
    
    
    Look what's new! 6 Christmas Day Outfits That Show-Off Your Personal Style http://ow.ly/2Cogjp     
    
    
    Day 26 of 26 Days...26 Ways...to Shop #Victoriously at Victoria Gardens:
On this final day, head on over to Guest... http://fb.me/29gaVFqwE     
    
    
    6 Christmas Day Outfits That Show-Off Your Personal Style... http://fb.me/6sMzaE79S     
    
    
    I don't think there is a more festive red heel out there!

2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 12... http://fb.me/250szyGlP     
    
    
    Look what's new! 2013 Edition: The 12 Days of Red High Heels- Day 12 http://ow.ly/2CoPjs     
    
    
    Merry Christmas! xo http://fb.me/6C06efemW     
    
    
    Ingrid Elfver This white dress is SO you!... http://fb.me/6jXIhEdyf     
    
    
    Add bold color during the cold winter months to make everything brighter! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799342905/ …    
    
    
    sexy red heels! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799342910/ …    
    
    
    Giuseppe Zanotti F/W 2013 http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799342918/ …    
    
    
    Accessory Closet http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799342919/ …    
    
    
    Happy New Year! Blue Sparkling Star Champagne Cocktails for New Year's Eve Party: 2 ounces orange in http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799342922/ …    
    
    
    Did you receive gift cards for Christmas? What are you spending them on?  I can't wait to use my hour massage GC!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Enjoying a super yummy Christmas gift from #Neutrogena! Thank you so much! http://instagram.com/p/ihj4-tSKT3/     
    
    
    How about ending 2013 with a great prize from Aquaphor US? Enter to win Aquaphor Healing Ointment and a $50 gift... http://fb.me/2wzQyeFlr     
    
    
    Look what's new! Winter Beauty Tips to Beat Dry Skin (+ Aquaphor Giveaway) http://ow.ly/2CwfYk     
    
    
    Going casual this NYE? Get inspired by these looks:... http://fb.me/3wHjR9YtK     
    
    
    Aquaphor is giving away their awesome Healing Ointment & a $50 Visa GC on A Mom in Red High Heels. Enter now! http://ow.ly/s9tuB     
    
    
        
    
    
    GIVEAWAY! Aquaphor Healing Ointment AND a $50 Visa Gift Card! Enter today! Deadline is 12/31 http://fb.me/2iaWgycdm     
    
    
    @shanie_Lovely Whoo Hoo! Good Luck!    
    
    
    Champagne Margaritas ~ Ring in the new year with the wonderful flavors of champagne and Margaritas i http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799377579/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Had to share this with my heel-loving friends! http://fb.me/6U9b7MQHo     
    
    
    Look what's new! Outfit Inspiration: Dazzling NYE Looks - Have a big New Year's Eve party to hit? Look stellar in ... http://ow.ly/2CxyFk     
    
    
    mémoires de #paris http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799379174/ …    
    
    
    Paris reflection. http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799379179/ …    
    
    
    Try something new in 2014: don't make resolutions – make commitments!

Did you know that by the end of January,... http://fb.me/1b7lGVPfh     
    
    
    Final day to get your entries in everyone!! Start the new year with soft skin and money to spend thx to Aquaphor http://ow.ly/s9tuB     
    
    
        
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/3cuMKH5zd     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2Bh1T9bye     
    
    
    Hmmm, which cocktail to toast the new year in with?? Such a tough decision, they all look so yummy!... http://fb.me/1adiKTCg7     
    
    
    Starting the evening with our annual outside fire. I can rarely get good pics of my son #crazykid http://instagram.com/p/im6nWqSKdN/     
    
    
    And then there is Miss Photogenic. .. :) http://instagram.com/p/im6vCuSKdn/     
    
    
    Happy New Year! http://instagram.com/p/im7AQDSKeJ/     
    
    
    THIS is happening right now! Who is jealous?? #Chihuahuaopoly #familytime #NYE http://instagram.com/p/inSRSSSKWv/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Wedge boots with fringe! http://pinterest.com/pin/150166968799388779/ …    
    
    
    So true! http://fb.me/17fF1ynS0     
    
    
    Saving for Botox. (hint: use Brilliant Distinctions® program!!) http://www.pinterest.com/pin/322922235753295239/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    