Is #Depression Contagious? I think so... http://ht.ly/jlugZ  #psychology    
    
    
    One mistake doesn't define you. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/03/28/one-mistake-doesnt-define-you/ … #psychology    
    
    
    #Twitter addiction advice from a cognitive therapist. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/03/31/twitter-addiction-advice-from-a-cognitive-therapist/ … #socialmedia #psychology    
    
    
    How to Stop Worrying about Worrying.
http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/04/03/how-to-stop-worrying-about-worrying/ … #psychology    
    
    
    Despedido por #Twitter. - http://goo.gl/news/jbfF     
    
    
    How trauma can affect your Body & Mind. http://ht.ly/kdxCd  #psychology    
    
    
    8 Ways to help your aging parents. http://ht.ly/kgyFD  #psychology    
    
    
    How to stimulate curiosity. http://www.psychologicalscience.org/index.php/news/how-to-stimulate-curiosity.html …    
    
    
    Kids and freedom. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/04/24/do-kids-have-too-much-freedom/ … #psychology    
    
    
    How to talk to your kids about #drugs. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/05/02/how-to-talk-to-your-kids-when-you-think-theyre-using-drugs/ … #psychologi    
    
    
    Criminal Genes and Criminal Brains http://ht.ly/kOwEb  #psychology    
    
    
    @labonanni @Santiago_Sanz_L @XaviGasso @j_callejo @RevezNexus @kekasanchez @chdve @Emprenderioja @GanasdeVivir Hi family! hv a g week!! :-)    
    
    
    TwimeMachine: para visualizar tus tweets más antiguos. http://ht.ly/l09fb  #Twitter #SocialMedia    
    
    
    4 Ways #Technology May be Ruining Your Relationship. http://ht.ly/l09lD  #psychology    
    
    
    Happiness is the best medicine. http://ht.ly/l2JFp     
    
    
    Los #Facebook hashtag a punto. :-) http://www.redessociales.es/2013/05/21/los-facebook-hashtags-estan-a-punto/ … #SocialMedia    
    
    
    Self-Love is Not a Crime: Learning to Love Yourself. http://ht.ly/llFM4  #psychology    
    
    
    The Origins of #Anxiety http://ht.ly/llFPw  #psychology    
    
    
    Children learn when adults imitate them. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/05/30/children-learn-when-adults-imitate-them/ … #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: People who talk on the phone & or text more than talking to someone in person are more likely to develop social anxiety"    
    
    
    The Key to a High IQ? Not Getting Distracted http://ht.ly/lGgjm  #psychology    
    
    
    Get Over It Already! Bouncing Back from Your Past http://ht.ly/lGguz  #psychology    
    
    
    7 Pointers for Couples to Prevent & Resolve Misunderstandings http://ht.ly/lII1i  #psychology    
    
    
    Afraid of Being Laughed At? You’re Far From Alone http://ht.ly/lII5q  #psychology    
    
    
    Older Adult Clumsiness Linked to Brain Changes http://ht.ly/lL5u2  #psychology    
    
    
    #Internet Addiction, Sleep Deprivation, or #ADHD? http://ht.ly/lL5yv  #psychology    
    
    
    Depression & Seniors: 5 Ways You Can Help http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/06/06/depression-seniors-5-ways-you-can-help/ … #psychology    
    
    
    5 Things to Do When You Feel Insecure http://ht.ly/lRHb7  #psychology    
    
    
    Baby Names: 2 Reasons We Name Our Kids What We Name Them http://ht.ly/lUj0e  #psychology    
    
    
    What father learned his adult daughter. http://m.psychologytoday.com/blog/the-flip-side/201306/what-father-learned-his-adult-daughter … #psychology    
    
    
    Why Mistakes Aren’t As Bad As You Think. http://ht.ly/m5I6Q  #psychology    
    
    
    The Bad Habits of Good #Negotiators. #Negotiations start with the exchange of information. Are U agree? http://ht.ly/m9uoR  #psychology    
    
    
    "@CognitiveTherap: Pet therapist: Can #dogs get #Alzheimer's disease? http://dlvr.it/3XThPp   - #CT #CBT"    
    
    
    People’s Misconceptions & the Frustations of Adult #ADHD. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/06/18/peoples-misconceptions-the-frustations-of-adult-adhd/ … #psychology    
    
    
    Summer Reading: 20 Mental #Health #Books That Can Change Your Life. http://ht.ly/mfmcm  #psychology    
    
    
    5 Decisions That Can Make You Happier. http://ht.ly/mm1ZU  #psychology    
    
    
    9 Contradictions That Could Increase Your Happiness. http://ht.ly/mKkVI  #psychology    
    
    
    Summertime Good Reads in #Psychology & Mental Health. http://ht.ly/mKlNl     
    
    
    5 Tips for Managing Anxiety During Transition. http://ht.ly/mXuWJ  #psychology    
    
    
    "DysWebxia presenta Software que ayuda a personas con #Dislexia | GeeksRoom" http://feedly.com/k/14UsRI9     
    
    
    "4 Tips for Dealing with Critical or Negative People" http://feedly.com/k/10WdhLr  #psychology    
    
    
    When You Are the Partner of a #Sex Addict, Part 1 http://feedly.com/k/12EQ5m3  #psychology    
    
    
    And When You Are the Partner of a #Sex Addict, Part 2" http://feedly.com/k/17mp4nm  #pychology    
    
    
    Oxytocin May Reduce Anxiety Related to Social Threats, But Only for Some. http://ht.ly/n7aiv  #psychology    
    
    
    What is Effexor (venlafaxine)? an antidepressant?  http://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/263705.php … #medical #depression    
    
    
    Techniques for Teens: How to Cope with Your Emotions. http://ht.ly/nbpdK  #psychology #teens    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: #Depression increases risk of hypersomnia, a disorder that causes a person to sleep entirely too much." #Psychology    
    
    
    Great! :) "The best relationship tends to be with someone who makes you laugh even when you don't feel like smiling" by @itweetfacts    
    
    
    @iTweetFacts You comment so much about women.... :O    
    
    
    Death Happens More Slowly Than Thought. http://news.discovery.com/human/health/death-happens-slower-than-thought-cell-by-cell-130713.htm …    
    
    
    "The many benefits of human-animal interaction" http://feedly.com/k/13d3wVR     
    
    
    7 Small & Simple Habits for a Happy Marriage http://ht.ly/nuawG     
    
    
    How Old Are You Really? http://ht.ly/nuaBu  #psychology    
    
    
    5 Steps to Stop #Drug Addiction Before it Starts. http://ht.ly/nFeTQ  #psychology    
    
    
    Great :-). "@RockChristopher: If you have a dream, don't waste your energies explaining why ~ @paulocoelho #quotes"    
    
    
    7 Small Ways to Live More Mindfully Every Day. http://ht.ly/nHwN4  #meditation #psychology    
    
    
    #Facebook incorpora sutilmente sus TrendingTopics. http://ht.ly/nLQdi  #SocialMedia #RedesSociales #TT    
    
    
    12 Travel Tips for People with #Bipolar Disorder. http://ht.ly/nLRzM  #psychology    
    
    
    "@HarvardBiz: Every person is motivated differently http://s.hbr.org/1biwHgV "    
    
    
    What people expect to #Sexting experience?  http://ht.ly/nSgdm  #Cyberpsychology #psichology    
    
    
    #Anorexia and #autism - are they related? http://ht.ly/nSgnQ     
    
    
    It´s true! Anything can Happen at Any Time. http://ht.ly/nSgwd  #anxiety #psychology    
    
    
    10 Tips to Cultivate Your Creativity #Psychology. http://feedly.com/k/1d6Dj3D     
    
    
    Addictive vs. Healthy Relationships http://ht.ly/o59os     
    
    
    Handling Intrusive Thoughts while Meditating. http://ht.ly/obURI  #meditation #psychology    
    
    
    "What causes schizophrenia? Gene discoveries offer clues" http://feedly.com/k/1dkdNtt  #psychology    
    
    
    "Depressed people have a more accurate perception of time" http://feedly.com/k/1fdCLaB  #psychology #depression    
    
    
    "Words can play a powerful role in what we see" http://feedly.com/k/12KPjUa  #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: Psychology: When she is happy, she can’t stop talking, when she is sad she doesn't say a word."    
    
    
    @iTweetFacts But you can help the others!!! and so you can help to change your world.    
    
    
    "@wwwhatsnew: Dos nuevas formas de crear concursos en Facebook http://wwhts.com/1813o3S "    
    
    
    "@GLaraLopez: If you don't care of your customers someone else will #infografia #infographic #marketing http://dld.bz/cPkuY "    
    
    
    What Parents Need to Know about Childhood #Depression http://feedly.com/k/15HrZe0  #psychology    
    
    
    Free Webinar: 10 Signs That You are Resisting Your Happiness Potential. http://ht.ly/oIULN  #psychology    
    
    
    Cómo crear los mejores posts para #Facebook, #Twitter, #Pinterest, #Google+, Instagram y Vine http://ht.ly/oLjp3  #socialmedia    
    
    
    7 Persistent Myths about Introverts & Extroverts. http://ht.ly/oNwkb  #psychology    
    
    
    Psychologically, washing your hands while you’re thinking through decisions helps you think more clearly, and be more focused @psychology    
    
    
    6 More Ways to Manage Clinical #Depression http://ht.ly/oSu85  #psychology    
    
    
    Explore the Galapagos’ biodiversity with Street View http://ht.ly/oSutP  #Google    
    
    
    5 Cognitive Behavioral Strategies for Losing Weight that Work. http://ht.ly/p0y0t  #psychology    
    
    
    "@Santiago_Sanz_L: #Cuidado Al entrar en algunas webs se descarga el archivo: "widgets-tweet_button.html.torrent" #Virus" cc @mc_system    
    
    
    6 Ways to Manage Autumn #Anxiety http://ht.ly/p6Shn  #psychology    
    
    
    Why You're Braver Than You Think http://ht.ly/p6SAS  #psychology    
    
    
    Talking with Your Teen about Drugs & Alcohol http://ht.ly/p9nWz  #psychology    
    
    
    Married cancer patients 'likely to live longer'. http://ht.ly/pbGEU  #psychology #medical    
    
    
    8 Ways to Help Kids with ADHD Succeed in School http://ht.ly/pe6bs  #psychology    
    
    
    Lack of empathy in psychopaths has a neurological basis http://ht.ly/pgjp7  #psychology    
    
    
    The Good Anxiety: On Challenging Yourself. http://ht.ly/pgjsH  #anxiety #psychology    
    
    
    Recognizing the Signs of Domestic Violence. http://ht.ly/pjpu1  #violence #psychology    
    
    
    Can Early Childhood Factors Predict Addictive Tendencies? http://ht.ly/pn3Ek  #psychology    
    
    
    Testosterone Promotes Reciprocity in the Absence of Competition. http://ht.ly/pn4EG  #psychology    
    
    
    What Does Your #Facebook Profile Really Say About You? http://ht.ly/prS9J  #socialmedia    
    
    
    Before Saying ‘I Do:’ Tips for Discussing Tough Topics http://ht.ly/pucT9     
    
    
    You Don’t Have to Believe Your Thoughts http://ht.ly/pucXM  #psychology    
    
    
    Making eye contact can be 'counterproductive' http://ht.ly/pude5  #medical #psychology    
    
    
    Why Your Smartphone is Trying to Kill You — And What You Can Do to Stop It. http://ht.ly/pB5Mg  #psychology    
    
    
    Make a List, Boost Your Happiness? http://ht.ly/pDlhR  #psychology    
    
    
    Looking to Improve Your Relationship? It Starts With You http://ht.ly/pRqde  #psychology    
    
    
    The Key To Learning: Knowing How Learning Works http://ht.ly/pRrSe  #psychology    
    
    
    Study: Is mom's favorite child always the same? http://ht.ly/pUwVd  #psychology    
    
    
    Why you can’t stop checking your phone http://ht.ly/pUy9D  #psychology    
    
    
    Autistic children look less friendly to peers http://ht.ly/pYjZ6  #autism #psychology    
    
    
    The dangers of Wi-Fi in cars http://ht.ly/pYk0H     
    
    
    The Truth About #Cats and #Dogs. Great! http://ht.ly/pYk8Y  #animals #psychology    
    
    
    3 Ways Your Emotional Brain Can Help You Communicate with Your Partner http://ht.ly/q0HCN     
    
    
    9 Small Ways to Have a Better Day at Work http://ht.ly/q4aAx  #psychology    
    
    
    6 Strategies to Become a Better Communicator http://ht.ly/q6fho  #pyschology    
    
    
    New free expression tools from #Google Ideas http://ht.ly/q6fGS  #psychology    
    
    
    Status Anxiety http://ht.ly/q7GW5  #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: The best portion of your life will be the small, nameless moments you spend smiling with someone who matters to you."    
    
    
    Are you okay? You smell like cytokines. http://ht.ly/qi8jf  #psychology #death    
    
    
    Oh Oh! Moral in the morning, but dishonest in the afternoon... http://ht.ly/qjjVB  #psychology    
    
    
    7 Strategies to Be Productive at Work When You’re Depressed http://ht.ly/qgZDB  #psychology    
    
    
    10 Things We’ve Learned About Negotiation http://ht.ly/qo26H     
    
    
    Specific brain regions can be trained by means of video #games. http://ht.ly/qqare  #psychology    
    
    
    People lie more in the afternoon, study shows http://ht.ly/qqav9  #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: Emotional disconnect is often the main reason in which causes women to suddenly lose interest."    
    
    
    Sweet dreams... specially for someone with the biggest part of the chewing gum...    
    
    
    #Depression is Different for Everyone http://ht.ly/qqEap  #psychology    
    
    
    #Dog heroes help people with dementia live better lives http://feedly.com/k/19rqlMR  #alzheimer #psychology    
    
    
    The correlation between child-centric behavior and parental happiness and fulfillment. http://www.medicalnewstoday.com/releases/268249.php … #psychology    
    
    
    The Only Method You Will Ever Need to Achieve Good Mental #Health http://ht.ly/quSNI  #psychology #psicologia    
    
    
    "@brittneykimbler: Studies show that mothers with kids under age 5 are most active on social media. http://mashable.com/2013/11/05/study-mothers-with-children-under-5-active-social-media/ …"    
    
    
    What Do You Want to Be When You Grow Up? http://ht.ly/qzHBe  #children #family #psychology #niños    
    
    
    If you want it, work for it. It's that simple.    
    
    
    Good news or bad news: which do you want first? http://ht.ly/qB1Kz  #Psychology #health    
    
    
    Sleep Alert: The gravest danger of sleep deprivation is that you'll never realize just how tired you are http://ht.ly/qC5WI  #psychology    
    
    
    5 #Tools to Increase Your #SocialMedia #ROI http://bit.ly/sndeWX  by @jeffbullas    
    
    
    What parents can learn from their kids http://ht.ly/qzHfo  #family #psychology    
    
    
    Social and neurobiological factors linked to alcohol-related aggression http://ht.ly/qGNZL  #neurobiologic #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: People are more happy when kept busy because keeping the mind occupied reduces & prevents you from over thinking things."    
    
    
    The biological basis of highly impulsive and aggressive behaviors: new evidence. http://ht.ly/qMz0E  #psychology #neurology    
    
    
    Dou you want to have a 100 dollars now or 150 dollars in 90 days’ time? http://ht.ly/qMynt  #psychology    
    
    
    3 Reasons Why Not All Mental #Health Professionals are Created Equal http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/11/14/3-reasons-why-not-all-mental-health-professionals-are-created-equal/ … #psychology    
    
    
    No se debe vivir mal =hay q hacer un pensamiento "@EarthBeauties: Surfer and Dolphin playing in the waves, Australia pic.twitter.com/9UDaVp3zMq"    
    
    
    4 Common Sleep Myths that May Help Your #Insomnia http://ht.ly/qV4Sz  #psychology    
    
    
    Dr. Google is Calling & You can (Mostly) Trust Her http://ht.ly/qXI9O  #depression #psychology    
    
    
    #Bulimia and the brain: responses to body image and food. http://ht.ly/qXIoy  #anorexy #psychology #EatingDisorders    
    
    
    Teens Who Drink Alone More Likely To Develop Alcohol Problems as Young Adults  http://ht.ly/qXMZS  #alcoholism #psychology    
    
    
    Recognizing the Signs of Love Addiction http://ht.ly/r2mTX  #psychology #love    
    
    
    @35NextYears Tks for every RT! & Every day! :)    
    
    
    El 85% del #ciberbullying ocurre en #Facebook http://ht.ly/rbxEh  #adolescentes #bullying    
    
    
    Brain region identified that helps you make up your mind http://www.medicalnewstoday.com/releases/269298.php … #psychology #Neuroscience    
    
    
    The Harmful Effects of Toxic #Stress on You & Your #Children http://ht.ly/rgcU1  #psychology    
    
    
    10 Ways parents can help prevent #Cyberbullying http://ht.ly/rmHbf  #psychology #family    
    
    
    Sports Psychology: Training Your Brain to Win http://ht.ly/rooOU  #sport #psychology    
    
    
    Ethical Violations: When One Thing Leads to Another http://ht.ly/rpnk9  #Science #psychology    
    
    
    Women find sexually explicit Ads unappealing, unless the price is right http://ht.ly/rqJb9  #psychology    
    
    
    #Google se ofrece como tu #CommunityManager personal http://ht.ly/rt8lG  #CM #SocialMedia    
    
    
    Have you been good this year on #Twitter? http://socialsanta.co  #SocialMedia    
    
    
    Brain 'wired differently' in men and women http://ht.ly/rt7Kk  #medicine #psychology #neurology    
    
    
    10 Powerful #Psychology #Books to Give. http://ht.ly/rzOAd     
    
    
    9 Small But Significant Ways to Grow Every Day. http://ht.ly/rCB4B  #psychology    
    
    
    "@RevezNexus: Your Friends Actually Want Gift Cards for the Holidays http://ift.tt/1jJsLed  "    
    
    
    Where is the Internet? http://dld.bz/ddPdB  via @GLaraLopez #infografia #infographic #internet    
    
    
    Navigating #Facebook, #SocialMedia So It Doesn’t Sabotage Your Relationship http://ht.ly/rJ9Kq  #psychology    
    
    
    Seasonal affective disorder: could you spot the signs? http://ht.ly/rLj3Y  #psychology #depression #anxiety    
    
    
    Discovery of mechanism controlling Tourette Syndrome tics http://ht.ly/rNFGg  #psychiatry #neurology #psychology #psycologia    
    
    
    El Transtorno Bipolar: http://ht.ly/rQaBE  #psychology #psicologia    
    
    
    Letter to a Loved One When Depressed http://ht.ly/rS7Un  #psychology #depression    
    
    
    "@RevezNexus: What Happens When You Tell a Lie? http://ift.tt/JJTARF  " @psychology    
    
    
    #Buffer for Business; el rival de #Hootsuite y #Tweeckdeck. http://ht.ly/rWJ2H  #SocialMedia    
    
    
    The Sounds of Silence. What can we learn from silences? http://ht.ly/rWJg3     
    
    
    Rethinking Mistakes & Learning From Your Missteps http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/12/26/rethinking-mistakes-learning-from-your-missteps/ … #psychology #psicologia    
    
    
    Last #FF of the year ;-) @labonanni @j_callejo @XaviGasso @christiandve @GanasdeVivir @kekasanchez @Emprenderioja @Santiago_Sanz_L    
    
    
    Güahi... ;-) I believe in you! You can! You are theeeee best! :-)    
    
    
    'Work with #anxiety' rather than seek calm to improve performance http://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/270641.php … #psychology    
    
    
    I am a brand. You are a brand. http://xfru.it/k5oHiI  #branding    
    
    
    "Raising Children With Dogs Can Help Protect Them From Asthma - PawNation" http://feedly.com/k/1dQv1ve     
    
    
    Great! "@n_vpatel: A map of human emotion. Really cool http://blogs.discovermagazine.com/d-brief/2013/12/30/body-atlas-reveals-where-we-feel-happiness-and-shame/#.UsIJIHlrrs8 … pic.twitter.com/q0rxGw8Jqr"    
    
    
    "All in the eyes: corneal reflections in photos can help solve crimes - Medical News Today" http://feedly.com/k/1ckBw6U     
    
    
    "@Econsultancy: Why marketers think #email can become even more efficient | http://ow.ly/rT2eL  #Dec13"    
    
    
    "@jeffbullas: 10 Reasons Why "Liquid" Content Should be Included in Your #SocialMedia #Marketing http://bit.ly/AgIzGa "    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: When someone stares at your mouth during conversation, that person desires to kiss you."    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: Everything that happened in 2013 in one image pic.twitter.com/p9gp1cDnUy"    
    
    
    "Tips for Talking to Your Teen | World of #Psychology" http://feedly.com/k/1lFJ3mm     
    
    
    "The Science of Love" http://feedly.com/k/1dYfxoZ  #psychology    
    
    
    Is #Depression Contagious? I think so... http://ht.ly/jlugZ  #psychology    
    
    
    One mistake doesn't define you. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/03/28/one-mistake-doesnt-define-you/ … #psychology    
    
    
    #Twitter addiction advice from a cognitive therapist. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/03/31/twitter-addiction-advice-from-a-cognitive-therapist/ … #socialmedia #psychology    
    
    
    How to Stop Worrying about Worrying.
http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/04/03/how-to-stop-worrying-about-worrying/ … #psychology    
    
    
    Despedido por #Twitter. - http://goo.gl/news/jbfF     
    
    
    How trauma can affect your Body & Mind. http://ht.ly/kdxCd  #psychology    
    
    
    8 Ways to help your aging parents. http://ht.ly/kgyFD  #psychology    
    
    
    How to stimulate curiosity. http://www.psychologicalscience.org/index.php/news/how-to-stimulate-curiosity.html …    
    
    
    Kids and freedom. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/04/24/do-kids-have-too-much-freedom/ … #psychology    
    
    
    How to talk to your kids about #drugs. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/05/02/how-to-talk-to-your-kids-when-you-think-theyre-using-drugs/ … #psychologi    
    
    
    Criminal Genes and Criminal Brains http://ht.ly/kOwEb  #psychology    
    
    
    @labonanni @Santiago_Sanz_L @XaviGasso @j_callejo @RevezNexus @kekasanchez @chdve @Emprenderioja @GanasdeVivir Hi family! hv a g week!! :-)    
    
    
    TwimeMachine: para visualizar tus tweets más antiguos. http://ht.ly/l09fb  #Twitter #SocialMedia    
    
    
    4 Ways #Technology May be Ruining Your Relationship. http://ht.ly/l09lD  #psychology    
    
    
    Happiness is the best medicine. http://ht.ly/l2JFp     
    
    
    Los #Facebook hashtag a punto. :-) http://www.redessociales.es/2013/05/21/los-facebook-hashtags-estan-a-punto/ … #SocialMedia    
    
    
    Self-Love is Not a Crime: Learning to Love Yourself. http://ht.ly/llFM4  #psychology    
    
    
    The Origins of #Anxiety http://ht.ly/llFPw  #psychology    
    
    
    Children learn when adults imitate them. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/05/30/children-learn-when-adults-imitate-them/ … #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: People who talk on the phone & or text more than talking to someone in person are more likely to develop social anxiety"    
    
    
    The Key to a High IQ? Not Getting Distracted http://ht.ly/lGgjm  #psychology    
    
    
    Get Over It Already! Bouncing Back from Your Past http://ht.ly/lGguz  #psychology    
    
    
    7 Pointers for Couples to Prevent & Resolve Misunderstandings http://ht.ly/lII1i  #psychology    
    
    
    Afraid of Being Laughed At? You’re Far From Alone http://ht.ly/lII5q  #psychology    
    
    
    Older Adult Clumsiness Linked to Brain Changes http://ht.ly/lL5u2  #psychology    
    
    
    #Internet Addiction, Sleep Deprivation, or #ADHD? http://ht.ly/lL5yv  #psychology    
    
    
    Depression & Seniors: 5 Ways You Can Help http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/06/06/depression-seniors-5-ways-you-can-help/ … #psychology    
    
    
    5 Things to Do When You Feel Insecure http://ht.ly/lRHb7  #psychology    
    
    
    Baby Names: 2 Reasons We Name Our Kids What We Name Them http://ht.ly/lUj0e  #psychology    
    
    
    What father learned his adult daughter. http://m.psychologytoday.com/blog/the-flip-side/201306/what-father-learned-his-adult-daughter … #psychology    
    
    
    Why Mistakes Aren’t As Bad As You Think. http://ht.ly/m5I6Q  #psychology    
    
    
    The Bad Habits of Good #Negotiators. #Negotiations start with the exchange of information. Are U agree? http://ht.ly/m9uoR  #psychology    
    
    
    "@CognitiveTherap: Pet therapist: Can #dogs get #Alzheimer's disease? http://dlvr.it/3XThPp   - #CT #CBT"    
    
    
    People’s Misconceptions & the Frustations of Adult #ADHD. http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/06/18/peoples-misconceptions-the-frustations-of-adult-adhd/ … #psychology    
    
    
    Summer Reading: 20 Mental #Health #Books That Can Change Your Life. http://ht.ly/mfmcm  #psychology    
    
    
    5 Decisions That Can Make You Happier. http://ht.ly/mm1ZU  #psychology    
    
    
    9 Contradictions That Could Increase Your Happiness. http://ht.ly/mKkVI  #psychology    
    
    
    Summertime Good Reads in #Psychology & Mental Health. http://ht.ly/mKlNl     
    
    
    5 Tips for Managing Anxiety During Transition. http://ht.ly/mXuWJ  #psychology    
    
    
    "DysWebxia presenta Software que ayuda a personas con #Dislexia | GeeksRoom" http://feedly.com/k/14UsRI9     
    
    
    "4 Tips for Dealing with Critical or Negative People" http://feedly.com/k/10WdhLr  #psychology    
    
    
    When You Are the Partner of a #Sex Addict, Part 1 http://feedly.com/k/12EQ5m3  #psychology    
    
    
    And When You Are the Partner of a #Sex Addict, Part 2" http://feedly.com/k/17mp4nm  #pychology    
    
    
    Oxytocin May Reduce Anxiety Related to Social Threats, But Only for Some. http://ht.ly/n7aiv  #psychology    
    
    
    What is Effexor (venlafaxine)? an antidepressant?  http://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/263705.php … #medical #depression    
    
    
    Techniques for Teens: How to Cope with Your Emotions. http://ht.ly/nbpdK  #psychology #teens    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: #Depression increases risk of hypersomnia, a disorder that causes a person to sleep entirely too much." #Psychology    
    
    
    Great! :) "The best relationship tends to be with someone who makes you laugh even when you don't feel like smiling" by @itweetfacts    
    
    
    @iTweetFacts You comment so much about women.... :O    
    
    
    Death Happens More Slowly Than Thought. http://news.discovery.com/human/health/death-happens-slower-than-thought-cell-by-cell-130713.htm …    
    
    
    "The many benefits of human-animal interaction" http://feedly.com/k/13d3wVR     
    
    
    7 Small & Simple Habits for a Happy Marriage http://ht.ly/nuawG     
    
    
    How Old Are You Really? http://ht.ly/nuaBu  #psychology    
    
    
    5 Steps to Stop #Drug Addiction Before it Starts. http://ht.ly/nFeTQ  #psychology    
    
    
    Great :-). "@RockChristopher: If you have a dream, don't waste your energies explaining why ~ @paulocoelho #quotes"    
    
    
    7 Small Ways to Live More Mindfully Every Day. http://ht.ly/nHwN4  #meditation #psychology    
    
    
    #Facebook incorpora sutilmente sus TrendingTopics. http://ht.ly/nLQdi  #SocialMedia #RedesSociales #TT    
    
    
    12 Travel Tips for People with #Bipolar Disorder. http://ht.ly/nLRzM  #psychology    
    
    
    "@HarvardBiz: Every person is motivated differently http://s.hbr.org/1biwHgV "    
    
    
    What people expect to #Sexting experience?  http://ht.ly/nSgdm  #Cyberpsychology #psichology    
    
    
    #Anorexia and #autism - are they related? http://ht.ly/nSgnQ     
    
    
    It´s true! Anything can Happen at Any Time. http://ht.ly/nSgwd  #anxiety #psychology    
    
    
    10 Tips to Cultivate Your Creativity #Psychology. http://feedly.com/k/1d6Dj3D     
    
    
    Addictive vs. Healthy Relationships http://ht.ly/o59os     
    
    
    Handling Intrusive Thoughts while Meditating. http://ht.ly/obURI  #meditation #psychology    
    
    
    "What causes schizophrenia? Gene discoveries offer clues" http://feedly.com/k/1dkdNtt  #psychology    
    
    
    "Depressed people have a more accurate perception of time" http://feedly.com/k/1fdCLaB  #psychology #depression    
    
    
    "Words can play a powerful role in what we see" http://feedly.com/k/12KPjUa  #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: Psychology: When she is happy, she can’t stop talking, when she is sad she doesn't say a word."    
    
    
    @iTweetFacts But you can help the others!!! and so you can help to change your world.    
    
    
    "@wwwhatsnew: Dos nuevas formas de crear concursos en Facebook http://wwhts.com/1813o3S "    
    
    
    "@GLaraLopez: If you don't care of your customers someone else will #infografia #infographic #marketing http://dld.bz/cPkuY "    
    
    
    What Parents Need to Know about Childhood #Depression http://feedly.com/k/15HrZe0  #psychology    
    
    
    Free Webinar: 10 Signs That You are Resisting Your Happiness Potential. http://ht.ly/oIULN  #psychology    
    
    
    Cómo crear los mejores posts para #Facebook, #Twitter, #Pinterest, #Google+, Instagram y Vine http://ht.ly/oLjp3  #socialmedia    
    
    
    7 Persistent Myths about Introverts & Extroverts. http://ht.ly/oNwkb  #psychology    
    
    
    Psychologically, washing your hands while you’re thinking through decisions helps you think more clearly, and be more focused @psychology    
    
    
    6 More Ways to Manage Clinical #Depression http://ht.ly/oSu85  #psychology    
    
    
    Explore the Galapagos’ biodiversity with Street View http://ht.ly/oSutP  #Google    
    
    
    5 Cognitive Behavioral Strategies for Losing Weight that Work. http://ht.ly/p0y0t  #psychology    
    
    
    "@Santiago_Sanz_L: #Cuidado Al entrar en algunas webs se descarga el archivo: "widgets-tweet_button.html.torrent" #Virus" cc @mc_system    
    
    
    6 Ways to Manage Autumn #Anxiety http://ht.ly/p6Shn  #psychology    
    
    
    Why You're Braver Than You Think http://ht.ly/p6SAS  #psychology    
    
    
    Talking with Your Teen about Drugs & Alcohol http://ht.ly/p9nWz  #psychology    
    
    
    Married cancer patients 'likely to live longer'. http://ht.ly/pbGEU  #psychology #medical    
    
    
    8 Ways to Help Kids with ADHD Succeed in School http://ht.ly/pe6bs  #psychology    
    
    
    Lack of empathy in psychopaths has a neurological basis http://ht.ly/pgjp7  #psychology    
    
    
    The Good Anxiety: On Challenging Yourself. http://ht.ly/pgjsH  #anxiety #psychology    
    
    
    Recognizing the Signs of Domestic Violence. http://ht.ly/pjpu1  #violence #psychology    
    
    
    Can Early Childhood Factors Predict Addictive Tendencies? http://ht.ly/pn3Ek  #psychology    
    
    
    Testosterone Promotes Reciprocity in the Absence of Competition. http://ht.ly/pn4EG  #psychology    
    
    
    What Does Your #Facebook Profile Really Say About You? http://ht.ly/prS9J  #socialmedia    
    
    
    Before Saying ‘I Do:’ Tips for Discussing Tough Topics http://ht.ly/pucT9     
    
    
    You Don’t Have to Believe Your Thoughts http://ht.ly/pucXM  #psychology    
    
    
    Making eye contact can be 'counterproductive' http://ht.ly/pude5  #medical #psychology    
    
    
    Why Your Smartphone is Trying to Kill You — And What You Can Do to Stop It. http://ht.ly/pB5Mg  #psychology    
    
    
    Make a List, Boost Your Happiness? http://ht.ly/pDlhR  #psychology    
    
    
    Looking to Improve Your Relationship? It Starts With You http://ht.ly/pRqde  #psychology    
    
    
    The Key To Learning: Knowing How Learning Works http://ht.ly/pRrSe  #psychology    
    
    
    Study: Is mom's favorite child always the same? http://ht.ly/pUwVd  #psychology    
    
    
    Why you can’t stop checking your phone http://ht.ly/pUy9D  #psychology    
    
    
    Autistic children look less friendly to peers http://ht.ly/pYjZ6  #autism #psychology    
    
    
    The dangers of Wi-Fi in cars http://ht.ly/pYk0H     
    
    
    The Truth About #Cats and #Dogs. Great! http://ht.ly/pYk8Y  #animals #psychology    
    
    
    3 Ways Your Emotional Brain Can Help You Communicate with Your Partner http://ht.ly/q0HCN     
    
    
    9 Small Ways to Have a Better Day at Work http://ht.ly/q4aAx  #psychology    
    
    
    6 Strategies to Become a Better Communicator http://ht.ly/q6fho  #pyschology    
    
    
    New free expression tools from #Google Ideas http://ht.ly/q6fGS  #psychology    
    
    
    Status Anxiety http://ht.ly/q7GW5  #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: The best portion of your life will be the small, nameless moments you spend smiling with someone who matters to you."    
    
    
    Are you okay? You smell like cytokines. http://ht.ly/qi8jf  #psychology #death    
    
    
    Oh Oh! Moral in the morning, but dishonest in the afternoon... http://ht.ly/qjjVB  #psychology    
    
    
    7 Strategies to Be Productive at Work When You’re Depressed http://ht.ly/qgZDB  #psychology    
    
    
    10 Things We’ve Learned About Negotiation http://ht.ly/qo26H     
    
    
    Specific brain regions can be trained by means of video #games. http://ht.ly/qqare  #psychology    
    
    
    People lie more in the afternoon, study shows http://ht.ly/qqav9  #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: Emotional disconnect is often the main reason in which causes women to suddenly lose interest."    
    
    
    Sweet dreams... specially for someone with the biggest part of the chewing gum...    
    
    
    #Depression is Different for Everyone http://ht.ly/qqEap  #psychology    
    
    
    #Dog heroes help people with dementia live better lives http://feedly.com/k/19rqlMR  #alzheimer #psychology    
    
    
    The correlation between child-centric behavior and parental happiness and fulfillment. http://www.medicalnewstoday.com/releases/268249.php … #psychology    
    
    
    The Only Method You Will Ever Need to Achieve Good Mental #Health http://ht.ly/quSNI  #psychology #psicologia    
    
    
    "@brittneykimbler: Studies show that mothers with kids under age 5 are most active on social media. http://mashable.com/2013/11/05/study-mothers-with-children-under-5-active-social-media/ …"    
    
    
    What Do You Want to Be When You Grow Up? http://ht.ly/qzHBe  #children #family #psychology #niños    
    
    
    If you want it, work for it. It's that simple.    
    
    
    Good news or bad news: which do you want first? http://ht.ly/qB1Kz  #Psychology #health    
    
    
    Sleep Alert: The gravest danger of sleep deprivation is that you'll never realize just how tired you are http://ht.ly/qC5WI  #psychology    
    
    
    5 #Tools to Increase Your #SocialMedia #ROI http://bit.ly/sndeWX  by @jeffbullas    
    
    
    What parents can learn from their kids http://ht.ly/qzHfo  #family #psychology    
    
    
    Social and neurobiological factors linked to alcohol-related aggression http://ht.ly/qGNZL  #neurobiologic #psychology    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: People are more happy when kept busy because keeping the mind occupied reduces & prevents you from over thinking things."    
    
    
    The biological basis of highly impulsive and aggressive behaviors: new evidence. http://ht.ly/qMz0E  #psychology #neurology    
    
    
    Dou you want to have a 100 dollars now or 150 dollars in 90 days’ time? http://ht.ly/qMynt  #psychology    
    
    
    3 Reasons Why Not All Mental #Health Professionals are Created Equal http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/11/14/3-reasons-why-not-all-mental-health-professionals-are-created-equal/ … #psychology    
    
    
    No se debe vivir mal =hay q hacer un pensamiento "@EarthBeauties: Surfer and Dolphin playing in the waves, Australia pic.twitter.com/9UDaVp3zMq"    
    
    
    4 Common Sleep Myths that May Help Your #Insomnia http://ht.ly/qV4Sz  #psychology    
    
    
    Dr. Google is Calling & You can (Mostly) Trust Her http://ht.ly/qXI9O  #depression #psychology    
    
    
    #Bulimia and the brain: responses to body image and food. http://ht.ly/qXIoy  #anorexy #psychology #EatingDisorders    
    
    
    Teens Who Drink Alone More Likely To Develop Alcohol Problems as Young Adults  http://ht.ly/qXMZS  #alcoholism #psychology    
    
    
    Recognizing the Signs of Love Addiction http://ht.ly/r2mTX  #psychology #love    
    
    
    @35NextYears Tks for every RT! & Every day! :)    
    
    
    El 85% del #ciberbullying ocurre en #Facebook http://ht.ly/rbxEh  #adolescentes #bullying    
    
    
    Brain region identified that helps you make up your mind http://www.medicalnewstoday.com/releases/269298.php … #psychology #Neuroscience    
    
    
    The Harmful Effects of Toxic #Stress on You & Your #Children http://ht.ly/rgcU1  #psychology    
    
    
    10 Ways parents can help prevent #Cyberbullying http://ht.ly/rmHbf  #psychology #family    
    
    
    Sports Psychology: Training Your Brain to Win http://ht.ly/rooOU  #sport #psychology    
    
    
    Ethical Violations: When One Thing Leads to Another http://ht.ly/rpnk9  #Science #psychology    
    
    
    Women find sexually explicit Ads unappealing, unless the price is right http://ht.ly/rqJb9  #psychology    
    
    
    #Google se ofrece como tu #CommunityManager personal http://ht.ly/rt8lG  #CM #SocialMedia    
    
    
    Have you been good this year on #Twitter? http://socialsanta.co  #SocialMedia    
    
    
    Brain 'wired differently' in men and women http://ht.ly/rt7Kk  #medicine #psychology #neurology    
    
    
    10 Powerful #Psychology #Books to Give. http://ht.ly/rzOAd     
    
    
    9 Small But Significant Ways to Grow Every Day. http://ht.ly/rCB4B  #psychology    
    
    
    "@RevezNexus: Your Friends Actually Want Gift Cards for the Holidays http://ift.tt/1jJsLed  "    
    
    
    Where is the Internet? http://dld.bz/ddPdB  via @GLaraLopez #infografia #infographic #internet    
    
    
    Navigating #Facebook, #SocialMedia So It Doesn’t Sabotage Your Relationship http://ht.ly/rJ9Kq  #psychology    
    
    
    Seasonal affective disorder: could you spot the signs? http://ht.ly/rLj3Y  #psychology #depression #anxiety    
    
    
    Discovery of mechanism controlling Tourette Syndrome tics http://ht.ly/rNFGg  #psychiatry #neurology #psychology #psycologia    
    
    
    El Transtorno Bipolar: http://ht.ly/rQaBE  #psychology #psicologia    
    
    
    Letter to a Loved One When Depressed http://ht.ly/rS7Un  #psychology #depression    
    
    
    "@RevezNexus: What Happens When You Tell a Lie? http://ift.tt/JJTARF  " @psychology    
    
    
    #Buffer for Business; el rival de #Hootsuite y #Tweeckdeck. http://ht.ly/rWJ2H  #SocialMedia    
    
    
    The Sounds of Silence. What can we learn from silences? http://ht.ly/rWJg3     
    
    
    Rethinking Mistakes & Learning From Your Missteps http://psychcentral.com/blog/archives/2013/12/26/rethinking-mistakes-learning-from-your-missteps/ … #psychology #psicologia    
    
    
    Last #FF of the year ;-) @labonanni @j_callejo @XaviGasso @christiandve @GanasdeVivir @kekasanchez @Emprenderioja @Santiago_Sanz_L    
    
    
    Güahi... ;-) I believe in you! You can! You are theeeee best! :-)    
    
    
    'Work with #anxiety' rather than seek calm to improve performance http://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/270641.php … #psychology    
    
    
    I am a brand. You are a brand. http://xfru.it/k5oHiI  #branding    
    
    
    "Raising Children With Dogs Can Help Protect Them From Asthma - PawNation" http://feedly.com/k/1dQv1ve     
    
    
    Great! "@n_vpatel: A map of human emotion. Really cool http://blogs.discovermagazine.com/d-brief/2013/12/30/body-atlas-reveals-where-we-feel-happiness-and-shame/#.UsIJIHlrrs8 … pic.twitter.com/q0rxGw8Jqr"    
    
    
    "All in the eyes: corneal reflections in photos can help solve crimes - Medical News Today" http://feedly.com/k/1ckBw6U     
    
    
    "@Econsultancy: Why marketers think #email can become even more efficient | http://ow.ly/rT2eL  #Dec13"    
    
    
    "@jeffbullas: 10 Reasons Why "Liquid" Content Should be Included in Your #SocialMedia #Marketing http://bit.ly/AgIzGa "    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: When someone stares at your mouth during conversation, that person desires to kiss you."    
    
    
    "@iTweetFacts: Everything that happened in 2013 in one image pic.twitter.com/p9gp1cDnUy"    
    
    
    "Tips for Talking to Your Teen | World of #Psychology" http://feedly.com/k/1lFJ3mm     
    
    
    "The Science of Love" http://feedly.com/k/1dYfxoZ  #psychology    
    
    
    