Thinking About Fast Food and Flavor http://huff.to/17NhAs6  via @HuffPostTaste    
    
    
    Man Sues Parker for Life ‘Wasted’ Drinking ‘Overpriced’ Wine http://tabletograve.com/man-sues-parker-life-wasted-drinking-overpriced-wine/ …    
    
    
    In Sanlucar de Barrameda at the Feria de Manzanilla with Javier Hidalgo of La Gitana. Eating toritillitas de camarones, salpicon de mariscos    
    
    
    And salmorejo, exceptional fried fish, stuffed squid.  Casa Bigote is better than ever, amazing food.    
    
    
    More reports coming from Barcelona, Priorat, Zaragoza, Navarra, La Rioja, Arlanza, Bierzo, amazing wine in Valdeorras, Ribeira Sacra . . .    
    
    
    More from Ribeiro, Riras Baixas, Madrid, Valencia, Alicante, Granada, Ronda and the Pueblos Blancos.    
    
    
    Gerry Dawes, Pat Martin of  Martin's Bar-B-Que Joint & Kay Balun at The  Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/njNg0iuJZFjIyR8R6Ef6QnEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Ribs at Blue Smoke, The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/L_aazfYsQZnqBciQknJjfXEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    John Sconzo, son Michael & pitmaster Kenny Callaghan, Blue Smoke & co-founder of The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013 https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/9b3NwW5J3pnpSXrrEnMvc3Eztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    One of the Roark family stars at Ubons, Yazoo City, MI  at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/xBnc9tRmL8c_0LpgKghftXEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mike 'Pappy' Emerson of Pappy's Smokehouse, St. Louis, MO at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/xdQsrhg9Nqd-Q3hLrmMF43Eztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Big Ed Mitchell of Mtichell's BBQ in North Carolina at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/wAbUPFAFZwZWQiDvIJNU5HEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    17th Street BBQ logo at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ljM2hTWE624lOxAVqQxo2nEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chef Michael Romano & Union Square Hospitality Grp Exec David Swinghamer at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/XpOQseYUGjwYds3gIoFJtXEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Dave Knight, owner of Ole Hickory BBQ Pits, with an Ole Hickory colleague at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/v3GhwT0RpBnwfhIsdtoUWnEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chris Lilly, Big Bob  Gibson's BBQ pours sauce on his chopped pork 'cue at The Big  Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/yUVLD2nHXMEUzAVo8RBTlnEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Patrick Martin, Martin's Bar-B-Que Joint, Nashville, John Sconzo & son Michael, Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/CGd0VPB1gPIsfrNuVapICnEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mike Mills,17th St. Bar & Grill / Memphis Champ BBQ working on a hog at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ECOS9J0gSm3KG-wz4JazRHEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @UbonsBBQ Hi, Folks, go to my Facebook.  I need an ID on the young Roark star wearing a straw hat.    
    
    
    Food Arts May 2013 Chiarello Article (Quoted about talking Michael Chiarello to Spain) https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/FoodArtsMay2013ChiarelloArticle?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCISOt8__kvutKg&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Skip Steele and Mike 'Pappy' Emerson at Pappy's Smokehouse tent at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/OelUX3byEyglvtxZUFgbb3Eztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Hare Krishna procession passing through pig smoke during The Big Apple BBQ Block Party,  NYC.   https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/JqJly0PTT1qlTeexJnG2MHEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    L. J. Sconzo, John Sconzo and Michael Sconzo at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/e2vhD2E1kYQjGDUmj5E1jXEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    A whole hog arriving on a forklift for Mike Mill's 17th St. Bar & Grill team, Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/shhATh7NtPMhamJU78rHI3Eztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mike Mills of 17th St. Bar & Grill / Memphis Championship Barbecue supervising the dissection of a hog, Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC    
    
    
    Photo Album, Big Apple Barbecue Block Party, NYC June 8, 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/NewYorkBigAppleBBQBlockPartyJune82013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCLfkw_nQicvDvAE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Top selling Menu Gerry Dawes 55 Euros for 8 yrs now, Taberna del Gourmet, Alicante.  Photo: Chef M. Jose San Roman  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/uTQETo2yDN1yM2UEjbLfjL9m8T4tOxHIuRjT9V6jQrc?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mike Mills, 17th St. Bar & Grill/Memphis Championship Barbecue  working on a hog, Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013 NYC https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/qoz0YHExnndA_kDhRpz8lHEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC Photo Album.
https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/NewYorkBigAppleBBQBlockPartyJune82013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCLfkw_nQicvDvAE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Albufera, Valencia, boat and crane. Photo copyright by Gerry Dawes 2012. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/0ZX6C54MQEQ_e04zBOLlNiW-4FQ9_L3FYeFBSaHY_-o?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Interview in Spanish in Cepas y Vinos, a new publication about Galician wines. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/CepasYVinosGaliciaInterview2013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCJ274uGMnd-7sgE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    A Morning's Pleasure: Running the Bulls at Pamplona (An Excerpt from Homage to Iberia by Gerry Dawes) http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2008/07/mornings-pleasure-running-bulls-at.html …    
    
    
    Pamplona Portraits from the Past: Alice Hall, Matt Carney, Big Dave Pierce, Joe Distler, Jimmy Hollander & More http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2012/01/pamplona-portraits-from-past-alice-hall.html …    
    
    
    Noel Chandler, The Champagne Count  San Fermín.  “It was amazing champagne.”  Ernest Hemingway, The Sun Also Rises  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2010/07/noel-chandler-champagne-count-of-san.html …    
    
    
    Highly Recommended Book: Pamplona--Running the Bulls, Bars and Barrios in Fiesta de San Fermín by Ray Mouton.  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2010/07/highly-recommended-book-pamplona.html …    
    
    
    Tiger lilly, Cushman Road, Patterson, New York. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/lntC_djmfaskF0JIbQLqD4ab0OOeafpwigF1Da603pM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chicory and tiger lilly, Cushman Road, Patterson, New York.  Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 / gerrydawes@aol.com. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ORUfafd1Spc3jsOKCImKQIab0OOeafpwigF1Da603pM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Dragonfly, Cushman Road, Patterson, New York.  Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 / gerrydawes@aol.com. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/XubGJXtaGBtmdOLQcdWoGYab0OOeafpwigF1Da603pM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Bee & wasp on a chicory flower, Mooney Hill Road, Patterson, NY. Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 / gerrydawes@aol.com. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/VTeduh7_Rou57h13OHsAOoab0OOeafpwigF1Da603pM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Patatas bravas at the original patatas bravas bar, Las Bravas. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/cvcId9JQeVvHBhHE_kxg4iIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Kay at one of the famous tile murals at Villa Rosa in Madrid, this one depicting the Roman bridge in Córdoba. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/CEOmGtUXTYA9CLZ4myMlvyIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Tile mural at La Chata, Cava Baja, Madrid.  Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 / gerrydawes@aol.com https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/7csTyAXMJ71eMPrXWQRJaiIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Tile mural at La Chata, Cava Baja, Madrid.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/zJQ657niVlj2X_EQCULWuCIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Balancing act, street performers, Puerta del Sol, Madrid.  It's a trick, don't ask!  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/Mdl7FXP2xagpKcopoWvgeCIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Kay Balun at Kilometer '0,' Puerta del Sol, Madrid.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/norA7WgZLTUXoICXPJG3TCIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Cafe con leche and chocolate con churros, Maestro Churrero, just off La Puerta del Sol, Madrid. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/p7yboslE_10Yg9NB2x6BhSIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Don Quixote and Sancho Panza approaching a table of food at an inn in La Mancha.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/XNAx_0dqssN_P5tbt9YEg6ciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mural depicting two kitchen workers carrying roast suckling pig at La Balconada, Chinchón, Madrid province.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/9-XvxQJTSmB38dmB7vanpqciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Cochinillo asado, roast suckling pig at Casa Botín in Madrid.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/zMxWGz3eXqRO8-2cp1Nvc6ciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Iconic Wine & Food Experiences. Tasting albariño wine from the Bodegueros Artesanos in Galicia.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/mcBD7-XrD2uC1vCv8Z55gqciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @tomcolicchio @davidchang Langostinos & La Gitana Manzanilla, Sanlúcar de Barrameda. Chefs From Hell trip? https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/waqIECxZ64FtNpyHxqtylKciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink … …    
    
    
    Spain’s government: Another blow | The Economist http://econ.st/14UrDNh     
    
    
    A BS piece: Has Ferran Adrià Had a 'Catastrophic Effect on the Younger Generation of Chefs'? http://eater.cc/18aUE8w  via @Eater    
    
    
    The Genesis of The Spanish Artisan Wine Group & the Documentary Robert Parker's Bitch http://www.spanishartisanwinegroup.com/2011/12/parkers-bitch-movie-do-critics-still.html …    
    
    
    Adega Manuel Formigo Grand Cru Quality Treixadura-based White Wines from Ribeiro (Galicia) http://www.spanishartisanwinegroup.com/2011/08/adegas-manuel-formigo-grand-cru-quality_15.html …    
    
    
    Printable List of Monsanto Owned “Food” Producers | http://REALfarmacy.com  | Healthy News and Information http://po.st/zpyTSM  via @po_st    
    
    
    Portraits of Water-Walkers Bring the Magic — Without the Photoshop On Valencia's Albufera lagoon.  http://www.wired.com/rawfile/2013/07/cataloging-a-diversity-of-human-species-in-one-rural-area-of-spain/ …    
    
    
    @Lord_of_Q Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip  The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html …    
    
    
    @martinsbbq Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @DinoBBQNYC @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @17thstreetbbq @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @BlueSmokeBBQ @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @UbonsBBQ Hi, Garry, sorry about the multiple tweets.  A SNAFU on this end. My best, Gerry    
    
    
    @Food4SouthSoul Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @ThePitMasterEdM @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    Madrid Classics: Lhardy, one of Madrid's greatest delicatessens.   Photo by Docsconz, John Sconzo. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/madrid-classics-lhardy-one-of-madrids.html …    
    
    
    @UbonsBBQ Garry, please get back ot me at gerrydawes@aol.com about the Spain BBQ tour.  Should be a phenomenal trip. Another view of pig.    
    
    
    Madrid Classic: Painting at the original Las Bravas, Madrid, the place where patatas bravas originated. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/madrid-classic-painting-at-original-las.html …    
    
    
    Al Andalus Train, Camino de Santiago Itinerary begins July 21.  1st stop, Zaragoza: Virgen del Pilar & Goya.  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/al-andalus-train-new-camino-de-santiago.html …    
    
    
    Back in Black - New York Versus Texas http://on.cc.com/13lGKzc  via @TheDailyShow    
    
    
    Quoted in Spain's financial crisis gobbling up top eateries By Harold Heckle July 22, 2013 http://www.businessweek.com/ap/2013-07-22/spains-financial-crisis-gobbling-up-top-eateries …    
    
    
    Weird being in the Santiago de Compostela train station tonight, sleeping on train..  No activity, but the train wreck just 3 kms. away.    
    
    
    Unbelievable that we were on a train in the station at Santiago the night of this horrific train crash. http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/07/24/spain-train-crash_n_3647580.html …    
    
    
    The 120mph Spanish train crash mystery: Why was the driver travelling at twice the recommended speed on bend? http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/the-120mph-spanish-train-crash-mystery-why-was-the-driver-travelling-at-twice-the-recommended-speed-on-bend-8732727.html …    
    
    
    Madrid classics, cochinillo asado (roast suckling pig) at Casa Botin, one of Ernest Hemingway's favorite restaurants https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo     
    
    
    From PBurgh: My beloved Pirates have taken FOUR of FOUR so far from the Redbirds, in 1st place by 2 1/2 games & best record in baseball.    
    
    
    Madrid Classics Barrio de Las Letras (Literary Quarter) - Gerry Dawes's Spain
http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2011/03/madrids-barrio-de-letras-literary.html …    
    
    
    Mejillones, mussels, plucked from the Galician rías.  On the Al Andalus Camino de Santiago Tren de Lujo adventure. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/_xIQgnrLKBdqZOufSZV4AB3EXA80NHvsu0OmSeoUuh4?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Update:  Heavenly Nights in Old Castile: Adventures with Ambrosio Molinos, of Michael Paterniti's "The Telling Room"  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/08/heavenly-nights-in-old-castile.html …    
    
    
    Iconic Spanish Dishes: Langostinos (prawns) de Sanlúcar de Barrameda with La Gitana manzanilla from Casa Bigote. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/-EEwm5_ybzYq77nNdZbKyNBJ-jBc0pODZfO6htD3xsM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Cigalas (Dublin Bay prawns) at the Mercado de San Miguel, Madrid. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/nfaif1mQdYpaDZHdr6HszdBJ-jBc0pODZfO6htD3xsM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Cigalas (Dublin Bay prawns) at a restaurant in Galicia.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/kLz6FB18sgUkwtuxPa-GjdBJ-jBc0pODZfO6htD3xsM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Santiaguiño, steamed Galician lobster- like crustacean with the cross of Santiago on its tail.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/IgTNJtzMC9sfkkcuziGQG9BJ-jBc0pODZfO6htD3xsM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Roberto Clemente plaque on the Roberto Clemente Bridge in Pittsburgh.  Photo by Gerry Dawes copyright 2013 https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/mGodkXz_fHOs2N8Z0Y5tDbxspYzsVr3W_XNjvyELGAU?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Salmorejo Cordobes with hard-cooked egg, Iberico ham & olive oil-fried eggplant strips). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/hsd2L1UwFdjAhG1uJBWiZVe1Lq4B48fgu4d7puEf-Bg?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Pittsburgh Pirates - Cardinals July 29 PNC Park.  1st of 5, won by Pirates. My first ever Pirates game in Pburgh.  https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/PittsburghPiratesCardinalsJuly292013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCOmb68aJ-bzpaw&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Raise the Jolly Roger, Pirates win again.  9-2 on a homestand for the 1st time since 2005. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/gr4CcsQ1JHz9OymqnX2jMbxspYzsVr3W_XNjvyELGAU?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Pittsburgh Monongahela Incline July 2013 https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/PittsburghMonongahelaInclineJuly2013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCLGJpd_Q1bfm3gE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Pittsburgh Duquesne Incline July 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/PittsburghDuquesneInclineJuly2013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCIu7-aPv99XwbA&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gin-tonic at sunset on the terrace of the Alhambra Palace Hotel in Granada. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/klxEpla5hJ5g7g53FCF7VTFWgSutTGVAlTZ-0AvDJUM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    In Ronda with my friend (seriously), the great Antonio Ordoñez, el maestro de Ronda. Photo by Kay Balun.
https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/gXdp3I-98wJZsb0CmtwqySPx82HuMEyujlS0Ja-4HrI?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    My sweetheart, Kay, in the shade of bougainvillea at Bodegas Hidalgo La Gitana, Sanlúcar de Barrameda.  May 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/FhW29410UkKBydj-Vrew36QqajkXovVkp7pHFMjIz6w?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Flowers and scenes from walks on Cushman & Mooney Hill Roads, Patterson, Putnam County, New York.  Aug 4-12 2013.  https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/CushmanMooneyHillRoadsAug4122013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCK7y-YfjwrGkIg&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Vines, winery, San Andrés church and the Cantabrian mountains at Marqués de Riscal, El Ciego, La Rioja Alavesa.   https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/YsL4Y6PGgQXWMeECd7juaVkgLv6S_qpPX7tpDhWkMiE?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Heinz Ketchup bottle on the right center field fence at PNC Park, Pittsburgh. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/tvssAQNk_pYucc8woo3sM7xspYzsVr3W_XNjvyELGAU?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @howardggoldberg  For those of you barbarians who put ketchup instead of mustard on your hamburgers, I suppose.    
    
    
    Mike Paterniti's The Telling Room http://instagram.com/p/dAFMkQBXz6/     
    
    
    Mike Paterniti in The New York Times: An American Man’s Quest to Become an Old Castilian http://nyti.ms/15yV4Ve     
    
    
    Presa Ibérica (tender well-marbled shoulder cut of meat from Ibérico pigs). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/OGtSCZAD4uYN0zna1kAe66lnyKCiZyyMaJyjf35HCU0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Queso Pimentón de Cabra (goats’ milk cheese from Cáceres, Extremadura, with a Spanish paprika rind). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/qY7a5X4d4phZD_3l47tqUqlnyKCiZyyMaJyjf35HCU0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    2 minutes of truth: What happened to the middle class? From @RBReich (via @Upworthy) http://www.upworthy.com/you-may-not-have-heard-of-robert-reich-his-upcoming-movie-about-the-middle-class-will-change-that-5?g=2&c=upw1 …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes.  Breakfast: Fresh tomatoes and basil, coarse sea salt, Navarra EVOO, garlic, for ciabatta bread.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ZIEaXZLKiGtng0D6wsJNY5FOTgCobhLFgUGBuShcWM0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @VictordelaSerna Thanks, Victor, I had not fixed on the fact that it was Mingote's drawing. I will put that into the captions to reflect it    
    
    
    Madrid Classics:  Pavement plaques for long-time Madrid establishments. Lhardy, est. 1839, off La Puerta del Sol. 
https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/-is94b7GZgzB5BNtI2kR8mAHhFkzR5pPeMQLgyybn3k?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Galo, Restaurante De Galo, with lechazo asado, suckling lamb to be roasted. Covarrubias (Burgos). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/fdTn63-sC3xngHbN93A84ypSgDDI5HwGFpaZgIXlXBI?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chimenea serrana, Restaurante De Galo. Covarrubias. The fire was in the middle with benches around the perimeter. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/TA1l3Ac_uwdj2zEU2NhuMypSgDDI5HwGFpaZgIXlXBI?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Lechazo (suckling lamb) going into the brick oven for roasting.  Restaurante De Galo. Covarrubias (Burgos).  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/XJ6ymzOcTcvakGPRoJDX4ypSgDDI5HwGFpaZgIXlXBI?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Two giants of Basque gastronomy, Pedro Subijana and Juan Mari Arzak, in Madrid, 2007. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/gCKBxWf0qpFnq8UBcyEVetMTjNZETYmyPJy0liipFm0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Fresh local tomatoes, house-grown basil, mozarella, sel de mar, Oro de Bailen EVOO, Sherry Vinegar. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/_XCGx3S-kJQUd1-4aXEzAFbwIpyWpYbqZwqDyHDoDFY?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Wild bay scalllops,  Sp. EVOO; corn-off-the-cob, red pepper, leeks, over farfalle D. Berna Godello. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/7I3x9HvJ3XVH2xbQidL8cVbwIpyWpYbqZwqDyHDoDFY?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry Dawes & John Ewing, drinking from a jug of Pacharan from Hartza restaurant. Sanfermines, 1995, Pamplona. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ILqU9pYblwLt9nZMkNLJO9icAJrfOVgjI0yBdSGm6ew?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    The Mihrab in Córdoba's Mezquita (former mosque during the Moorish occupation of Spain). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/Dl6kXfR_aYG7lA9vEJsui-kSVegVj8GVcn-Pb3utXuM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Córdoba's Mezquita (former mosque during the Moorish occupation of Spain). Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/gpmTJa8J7cadUR84Q1mSoukSVegVj8GVcn-Pb3utXuM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Salmorejo with chopped jamón Ibérico and egg at Taberna Juan Peña, Córdoba. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/UbzISb64hnk6bKrXkk8DZukSVegVj8GVcn-Pb3utXuM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Churrasco, grilled pork loin, El Churrasco restaurant, Córdoba. Photo Gerry Dawes©2013 Canon 6D/Tokina 17-35mm f/4. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/wREq4s3I2y3W1n57Z1igNukSVegVj8GVcn-Pb3utXuM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Huevo marinero, shrimp, monkfish & manzanilla, brought bubbling with a fresh egg on top Casa Bigote, Sanlúcar. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/KKIoz9hBTl4WCg6vuwXEysHvSFRVqvsDoEqAitzGNjM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Very sorry to hear this morning of the passing of Penelope Casas, whose books on Spanish Cuisine paved the way. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/08/the-passing-of-great-spanish-food.html …    
    
    
    The Passing of the Great Spanish Food Writer Penelope Casas, Que Descanse en Paz. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/08/the-passing-of-great-spanish-food.html …    
    
    
    Viña Magaña Gran Reserva 1982 Navarra, Merlot-Cabernet blend, my cellar, 8- 18-2013.  In superb condition. 94 pts. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/J1_WRxJlYLhlg3pCvFDYvxVycQQnvHhvK395F25yb7c?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @MarthaStewart Want to talk about Spain and Spanish food.  Let me know and I will give you a call. Great season for gazpacho and salmorejo.    
    
    
    @KarenAndAndrew @GaelGreene Without Penny's books, American would have had no real reliable reference to Spanish cuisine back then.    
    
    
    @KarenAndAndrew @GaelGreene The Passing of the Great Spanish Food Writer Penelope Casas, Que Descanse en Paz. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/08/the-passing-of-great-spanish-food.html … … Pix    
    
    
    Anniversary of the Death of Federico García Lorca, Murdered by Nationalist Forces,Granada on August 19, 1936.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/RWItUCT_SX6dcU60Hkp-crcjnLv4ylYY5AF4cVjakd8?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @Mike Paterniti @ChefChiarello Michael, a great book about my Spanish cheesemaker buddy, Ambrosio Molinos.  Mike Paterniti's a friend.    
    
    
    @MikePaterniti Here is the article about Penelope Casas, Mike.    
    
    
    @MikePaterniti Lorca    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Local tomatoes with lime-cilantro allioli, house basil, sal de mar gorda and Oro de Bailen EVOO.https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/3_073bZXgK_hDxTbpSTIxacGL0VspK5Be-JFM65SX0M?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Kay above the Sil River valley on the way to Seadur, where Pepe Rodríguez at O'Barreiro, produces a great Godello.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/2cWmpUlv2cIlChS9tFdo-Y32gL5Ril4kxzbmn-wTU0c?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Empanada at Pepe Rodríguez's cave at Adegas O'Barreiro, Valdeorras. Pepe makes a great terroir-driven Godello. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/3EeUE4DaZnfnkm0n7o7o1o32gL5Ril4kxzbmn-wTU0c?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Ribeira Sacra: Perfect Lunch at O Grelo: Tomatoes, Tetilla cheese, zamburiñas al horno (small scallops) & Godello.  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2009/07/ribeira-sacra-perfect-lunch-with.html …    
    
    
    The Many Faces of Ferran Adria: Photos taken over the past 17 years. Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 (Pinterest) http://pinterest.com/gerrydawes/the-many-faces-of-ferran-adria-photos-taken-over-t/ …    
    
    
    More Spanish cheeses, cheesemakers, cows, goats, Gamoneu, Cabrales, La Peral and more. (Pinterest)  http://pinterest.com/gerrydawes/spanish-cheeses/ …    
    
    
    @RandallGrahm Especially when there is no window you can open for fresh air.  Have to use it sometimes, seldom, rather not. Hate canned air    
    
    
    @RandallGrahm Earplugs!! ;-)    
    
    
    Baby goats being fed by Jesús Gútierrez at la Chivita, Asturias. Photograph by Gerry Dawes©2010.   https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/_YXIhXzeJoyGtsOuaXTDPX0Sy_14ewguUWEup6VIzD4?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    More Spanish Cheeses: Spain has a wide variety of superb cheeses made from the milk of cows, sheep and goats. http://pinterest.com/gerrydawes/spanish-cheeses/ …    
    
    
    @17thstreetbbq @bpwise De nada!    
    
    
    The Many Faces of Ferran Adria:  Photos taken over the past 17 years by Gerry Dawes http://pinterest.com/gerrydawes/ ...    
    
    
    Malaga's traditional wines and wine bars http://www.spain-holiday.com/Malaga-city/articles/malagas-traditional-wines-and-wine-bars …    
    
    
    Pinchos, or tapas, on the bar at The Basque Market in the Basque Block section of downtown Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/q9AvnRlN2Us-CdGggqRbmVQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Basque mural in the Basque Block section of downtown Boise, Idaho.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/MPpdFiTZHSC2SrrN81NDflQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Pavement stone with the music to the song, Gernikado Arbola (Tree of Gernika), Basque Block section of Boise, Idaho  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/xdEd3vQCuyiUvdXrRZHc41QEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Bilbao Brand Chorizo, cured meats at The Basque Market in the Basque Block section of downtown Boise, Idaho.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/0d4QVepJdSb3zGpEOUN401QEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    The Basque Market, a store specializing in products from Iberian Peninsula, Basque Block section of Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/0bAtaN4IRuqoNEvtISiUEFQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Idaho trout in corn meal and Spanish olive oil with pieces of local smoked bacon in the belly, Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/A7og6XDUHAK5h5WXybn_MCoqfRzQ8Pnh3_ug7K-QiQA?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Cooking Idaho trout in corn meal & Spanish olive oil w/ local smoked bacon, Bon Hartline's, Idaho.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/bnavCjJS8YI_ope5f1K-KSoqfRzQ8Pnh3_ug7K-QiQA?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Jamones de Joselito y Ferran Adria.  Can't wait to see this.  Joselito Jamon Lab with Ferran. http://vimeo.com/jamonjoselito/httpvimeocomjoselitolabteaser …    
    
    
    My buddy  El Jay Sconzo drinking red wine from a porrón in Barcelona, May 2013 - - at breakfast!  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/2DMz2elM3lJsQjZHXLovhCGOyIhszzSxF_mq_5PQp-0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Excellent "secret recipe" deviled crab at Daufuskie Island Crab Company, Daufuskie Island, South Carolina. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo     
    
    
    Went to Paula Deen's the Lady & Sons in Savannah and she came out to greet me personally, as you can see. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/HLFjhOPmjDNShKQkS5zpjJV3wX6xh-Vpa2MngNDhNrk?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @chefjoseandres @HHFoundation !Enhorabuena, Jose!!!    
    
    
    Jim 'N Nick's Bar-B-Q, Bluffton, South Carolina. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/JimNNicksBarBQBlufftonSouthCarolina942013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCNDwyr6_le2pzAE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Bar Gernika, in the Basque Block section of downtown Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/2GXUpUy0k2pLWppRuz2gKVQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Paella in the street in the Basque Block section of Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/iF3Tx4j0lknmPCF85JKEEVQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Breakfast at Goldy's, an institution in downtown Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/BoiseDowntownGoldySAug262013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCMyinMSk1-bvggE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @VictordelaSerna I met two Basques sitting in front of the Boise Basque Center, Jose Luis and Simon, who came from near Lekeitio, in 1948!    
    
    
    @albertochicote Tortilla de patatas.  No se hace con una patata sola. ?Cual es la proxima pregunta: patata brava o patatas bravas?  ;-)    
    
    
    Jewish Savannah & Charleston Sept 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/JewishSavannahCharlestonSept2013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCIjC16fd95KcjQE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Monsoon getting ready to hit Alburquerque on Sept. 12, 2013. Part of the system that devastated parts of Colorado.https://picasaweb.google.com/ ...    
    
    
    The monsoon in the normally dry high dessert country of northern New Mexico, Sept. 12, 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/ ...    
    
    
    What I did on 9/11:  EWR-PHX-ABQ.  Phoenix, waiting for Southwest plane to ABQ, Sept. 11, 2011. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/MyLYSDsX3Tcy4GSwMLIlAY4TlhHGiJa3OPGG5AMySK0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Finally getting to read Bob Spitz's 'Dearie' about Julia and love the book.  Can't wait to turn it over to Kay, who was a Smithie!    
    
    
    Last gazpacho of summer, with scallion, hard-cooked egg, tomato, cucumber, crouton, red pepper guarnicion. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/9O3KLzZWNxWsQbWeFnrICxdZNtilJWHnuM8J83cl6Us?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    The great ZZ Ward at The Telluride Blues & Brews Festival. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/rdlBc6f7aui0bOReUzLerUhvo9EL7dLeDRJ_d8V2-oo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Fiesta goers.  St. Louis Cardinals fan at the Telluride Blues & Brews Festival.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/GEhZwRyyyuFa2OVwZE8IjEhvo9EL7dLeDRJ_d8V2-oo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Fiesta goers. The damned lying press told us Jerry Garcia was dead. Duhh! Telluride Blues & Brews Festival. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/mVr0nABLFGR6yEmaIM9qrkhvo9EL7dLeDRJ_d8V2-oo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    The great ZZ Ward at The Telluride Blues & Brews Festival. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/SwhsgqHXsC6oJ89xPwf3QEhvo9EL7dLeDRJ_d8V2-oo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Fat Alley BBQ, Telluride Blues & Brews Festival. I had the Carolina-style pulled pork sandwich, messy, but delicious https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/W-GxLJidAD6wFemucgC2oEhvo9EL7dLeDRJ_d8V2-oo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @Tertulia_NYC !Que alegria!  Nos veremos pronto.    
    
    
    Spanish White Anchovies (boquerones) w herb oil, new Bravas Bar de Tapas,  Healdsburg, California, Sept. 16, 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/WzkKbv6QtwSi7DBJhG1RJZbLfFN2nRFYwJutsaFdGng?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Sea scallops with romesco and leeks with three wines from The Spanish Artisan Wine Group, Bravas, Healdsburg, CA. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/LPl40kN1J8sl-wtAVqqUtJbLfFN2nRFYwJutsaFdGng?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Newlyweds Executive Chef Ryan Mcilwraith & wife Tasha at Coqueta,  San Francisco, Sept. 16, 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/WRqLD0TuyrGrU5AJT5NtkN7IA0PWBJoNf_7t74ABeFA?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chef Ryan Mcilwraith's superb version of gazpacho,Coqueta, Michael Chiarello's  tapas bar in San Francisco. 9-16-13.
https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/3Q84aszT8jNNm0UMrEzfD97IA0PWBJoNf_7t74ABeFA?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Roy Face, my great baseball hero, signs  photographs for me.  I gave him 2 of my wines--one for Bill Mazeroski.   https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/_vJJCVRok2uJ0sWyIgrSMl3tKKbP02LJ3I1vdtAvU5M?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    With my all-time favorite baseball player, Pittsburgh Pirate Elroy Face. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/3M6DQnDZTkPdfBYCGg0yOl3tKKbP02LJ3I1vdtAvU5M?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Picasso's Gernika & Reina Sofia Museum in Madrid. Commonwealth Club of California Taste of Spain Tour 2013. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/10/i-just-returned-from-more-than-three.html#.Umpv-98C1Rc.twitter …    
    
    
    Two guys from Anna-Jonesboro, Illinois, Bon Hartline & Gerry Dawes, in Ribeira Sacra, Oct. 2, 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/g52INxqiNpYUv67Qt3WsQ8bg_a2921j69Ga7DWK-L4c?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @kratsinger & Jorge Mas at one of seven Mas jamón & embutidos shopsJorge has in La Boquería in Barcelona. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/v0J8Kar3TgL7YE3g9yLAuYi_CHkov9_nkYbeiYKLru8?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry Dawes and Keith Hernandez at the Alhambra in Granada, Spain, Oct. 17, 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/nf8bDe9hlweT8ar-RJSd1wAcTvo9TnQ8NghhZGvUe28?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Keith Hernandez & Kay Balun, Oro de Bailén olive oil producer, Jaén (Andalucía), where Keith's grandfather was from. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/Y6gE_sEAxkjC4lbG3J-O7XqCWt6ymlb0xAw8ccJ9yw0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Calçotada: Cooking Calçots for a Festival in a Plaza in the Barrio of Sarría in Barcelona / Dishes with Romesco. http://fb.me/2Kt9l5nRT     
    
    
    @wineguru @winedogboy Very sad about Sommelier Journal, The Wine News, etc.  I enjoyed working with both.    
    
    
    Famed Chicago chef Charlie Trotter found dead http://fb.me/1z3ppo09y     
    
    
        
    
    
    Charlie Trotter: Food world mourns shocking death http://fb.me/1WHolgr7y     
    
    
    A Remembrance of Charlie Trotter: Tapas Hopping in Madrid http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/11/a-remembrance-of-charlie-trotter-tapas.html …    
    
    
    A Remembrance of Charlie Trotter: Tapas Hopping in Madrid http://fb.me/29yRn3HU1     
    
    
    Some more photos of that night at Rafa.  The group included Charlie and his then fiancee (later wife) Rochelle... http://fb.me/6J8sZvN8A     
    
    
    12 HOTTEST FOOD & BEVERAGE TRENDS FOR RESTAURANTS AND HOTEL DINING FOR 2014 + 30 BUZZWORDS

Consultants... http://fb.me/6z04UGCcq     
    
    
    MICHAEL WHITEMAN'S 12 HOTTEST FOOD & BEVERAGE TRENDS FOR RESTAURANTS AND HOTEL DINING FOR 2014 + 30 BUZZWORDS http://baumwhiteman.com/2014TrendForecast.pdf …    
    
    
    New York Times writer and long-time wine columnist, Frank Prial, died a year ago today. http://fb.me/3blWExMfM     
    
    
    Tapas Hopping with Charlie Trotter, Tetsuya Wakuda, Norman Van Aken and others at Casa Rafa, Madrid. https://www.facebook.com/gerry.dawes/media_set?set=a.200107844190.126829.535454190&type=1 …    
    
    
    On Becoming China’s Farm Team
By Mark Bittman

The taxpayer underwritten Smithfield pork business gets sold to the... http://fb.me/TVIHlDyS     
    
    
    Charlie Trotter with Spanish chef Sergi Arola at Madrid Fusion 2006. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/4bAaCNkbl7mzYGDT6q48GhpfXNaYe03s8YHChYTEVlc?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Charlie Trotter with Spanish chef Sergi Arola at Madrid Fusion 2006. http://fb.me/Mg99eFrr     
    
    
    Charlie Trotter at the Top Ten Most Influential Chefs of the Past Decade announcement ceremony, Madrid Fusion 2006. 
https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/JrToIR9naoUMvK3Z4rW8LBpfXNaYe03s8YHChYTEVlc?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Charlie Trotter with Spanish chef Sergi Arola as the Top Ten Most Influential Chefs of the Past Decade were... http://fb.me/YdluXhdi     
    
    
    Norman Van Aken, Charlie Trotter, Michael Batterberry, and other American culinary stars at Madrid Fusion 2006.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/Qcj5cP3-VESOItJ06ip95hpfXNaYe03s8YHChYTEVlc?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Norman & Janet Van Aken, Juan Suarez, José Andrés, Mark Miller, Harold McGee and Esmeralda Capel in the kitchen... http://fb.me/3urh8G3Ts     
    
    
    Flamenco performance at the Museo del Baile Flamenco in Sevilla, October 13, 2013. http://fb.me/16syQpdVt     
    
    
    Flamenco performance at the Museo del Baile Flamenco in Sevilla, October 13, 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/MuseoDelBaileFlamencoSevillaOctober132013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCJfW97yC2vS9Rw&feat=directlink …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Cathedral and La Giralda (under Moorish rule a minaret), Sevilla. http://fb.me/2FMWDN9mc     
    
    
    El Real Alcázar de Sevilla, Commonwealth Club Taste of Spain Tour 2013, organized & led by G.D.  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/11/el-real-alcazar-de-sevilla-commonwealth.html …    
    
    
    El Real Alcázar de Sevilla, Commonwealth Club of California Taste of Spain Tour 2013, the group tour I organized... http://fb.me/1qrLInire     
    
    
    @viveandalucia El Real Alcázar de Sevilla, Commonwealth Club Taste of Spain Tour 2013, organized & led by G.D. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/11/el-rea     
    
    
    @viveandalucia    
    
    
    http://fb.me/3mn8yN06Q     
    
    
    This from a friend who says:  "I have not taken the time to verify the statements made in the graphic; however, I... http://fb.me/TwIPSta1     
    
    
    All of a sudden my Facebook page is not coming up.  Goes right along with my wonderful Dell computer, which is... http://fb.me/1UMKujH6E     
    
    
    If you speak Spanish and know anything about Spain, this musical parody video is a hoot.  They say that the... http://fb.me/1DaB7rCAD     
    
    
    http://fb.me/ZopEJFUp     
    
    
    Ibérico pig meat cuts chart, DeRaza Carne de Ibérico.  Secreto, pluma, presa, lomo, etc. http://fb.me/6vFB0NJ3G     
    
    
    Going to Albuquerque or Santa Fe.  Stop in and see James Campbell Caruso at his new tapas y vinos restaurant Mas... http://fb.me/1aceXoPFH     
    
    
    From Ike, no less! http://fb.me/XZIlRz6k     
    
    
    Read all about it: The 12 hottest food trends for 2014. Check out the story on the Huffington Post.   Read... http://fb.me/6LWbmRHRn     
    
    
    All that white, a little green & just a touch of red, Patterson, Putnam County, NY, Nov. 12, 2013.   https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/1FK7SNhgzNwKEu1BhBITg9eWLKV68fn_ZayBeID-oig?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Geranium (indoors) backed by seaon's first snowfall (outdoors), Patterson, Putnam County, NY, Nov. 12, 2013.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/yXh7fFtvSwsYZd_uywi5kNeWLKV68fn_ZayBeID-oig?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Geranium (indoors) backed by seaon's first snowfall (outdoors), Patterson, Putnam County, NY, Nov. 12, 2013. http://fb.me/32wvCzMOc     
    
    
    My new Toyota RAV4 covered in its first snow,  Patterson, Putnam County, NY, Nov. 12, 2013. http://fb.me/142O9bJgN     
    
    
    Erica Catherine Alicia Dawes in 1978 in a Left Bank cafe in Paris with her mother Diana, who is reading the... http://fb.me/24aI1Neni     
    
    
    Tom Weitzner, Antonio's wife Pilar Lezcano, Antonio Ordoñez and Gerry Dawes at Doc's Restaurant, Upper West Side,... http://fb.me/23BlnbQF3     
    
    
    @NExSpain Links to DavidsBeenHere Galicia Restaurant story does not work.    
    
    
    Yesterday at Manzanilla Restaurant in Manhattan, two grandes of modern Spanish wine, Victor de la Serna of Finca... http://fb.me/1FSWVlreK     
    
    
    I have been pissed off, but never THIS pissed off!  I reject the school of thought that calls for nailing one's... http://fb.me/3Bpv0ye7x     
    
    
    My daughter, Maria Estrella Diana Dawes and my granddaughter, Makayla in Phoenix at the airport, Sept. 14, 2013. http://fb.me/NXjMIfTj     
    
    
    Ernest Hemingway's old hangout, Cervecería Alemana, on Plaza Santa Ana, Madrid. http://fb.me/6nR3P10lO     
    
    
    Setas (mushrooms), grillled and served with foie gras and an egg yolk as a sauce, Ganbarra, Casco Viejo (old... http://fb.me/2t7xeW3Iw     
    
    
    Roast kid with patatas panaderas and the wines of Carlos Aliaga at El Crucero Restaurante, Corella (Navarra). http://fb.me/6o4ay8xk9     
    
    
    Restraining Order!! http://fb.me/6rP5EKOBV     
    
    
    Add to the list of things I will NOT be doing any time soon: 
1) Nailing my scrotum to a paving stone in Red... http://fb.me/6LJhylDaq     
    
    
    A superb flan at Asturianos, Madrid. http://fb.me/NZ0tIMwd     
    
    
    O Trobo Mel do ValaDouro Mel de Flores (wildflower honey from the Valadouro in the wilds of Galicia). One of the... http://fb.me/6ntpzXyEG     
    
    
    My buddy, Chef James Campbell Caruso, opens his new Mas Tapas y Vino restaurant in the renovated Hotel Andaluz en... http://fb.me/2BKQZVyU4     
    
    
    Chipironcitos (young squid), grilled and served on a piece of slate with a Canary Islands inspired green... http://fb.me/10bpAyf3N     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Oven-finished frittata with onions, bell peppers, scallions, cilantro, eggs and Monterey Jack... http://fb.me/6nVLcPTS2     
    
    
    My grandson Trace Pollard, Elena and Brandon's son, at The Telluride Blues and Brews Festival on Sept. 13. http://fb.me/6A1pfAm0P     
    
    
    Grandson Graham in a Telluride firetruck, Telluride Blues and Brews Festival on Sept. 13. http://fb.me/2AG59EkTW     
    
    
    I have 6-8 places left on a chefs' tour of Spain Jan 12-19.  Barcelona, Priorat, Valencia, Alicante, La Mancha,... http://fb.me/1TTQnjpTx     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6zSWwgrak     
    
    
    Flamenco dancer, Sevilla. Oct. 12, 2013 http://fb.me/Y2eOXvRf     
    
    
    With chef-owner Fernando Hermoso and Tom Burkhardt at Casa Bigote in Sanlúcar de Barrameda on the Commonwealth... http://fb.me/6DHiILSBn     
    
    
    http://fb.me/238vuNadF     
    
    
    From my friend, Janet Mendel. http://fb.me/1GibSjUKG     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2a4eMSiqz     
    
    
    http://fb.me/136MFS3gs     
    
    
    Lunch at Bodegas Campos, Córdoba, Commonwealth Club of California Gerry Dawes Taste of Spain Tour 2013.  Oct. 11,... http://fb.me/UO6aCIEi     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Espinacas con garbanzos, garbanzo stew with spinach, cumin, saffrón, pimentón (Spanish paprika),... http://fb.me/6yNgVyBIB     
    
    
    Toasting with the Pago del Ama Pinot Noir of chef-owner Adolfo Muñoz at his cigarral overlooking Toledo,... http://fb.me/2cipmEH6q     
    
    
        
    
    
    Commonwealth Club of California's Taste of Spain Tour 2013.  Visit to the Coto de Doñana wildlife preserve across... http://fb.me/XLeM4VpO     
    
    
    With Raúl García Domínguez, the excellent driver of our Esteban Rivas bus on the Commonwealth Club of... http://fb.me/1sV6ZOh4a     
    
    
    Madrid Classics: Casa González, founded in 1931, is a bar-deli-gourmet food and wine shop with a wonderful... http://fb.me/3nG60st2l     
    
    
    Chef Dani García's New Taberna Ibérica, La Huevería del Ganso, (The Hen House of the Gander!) on Calle Echegaray... http://fb.me/2JfLQNN07     
    
    
    Lengthening shadows of a fence on a country road on a beautiful fall day in Putnam County. http://fb.me/PjjsQn7O     
    
    
    @FrankBruni Were any Cheney clan members issued real hearts to begin with?  Cheney calculation and callousness?  Surely you jest.    
    
    
    @FrankBruni Any idea how much money the Cheneys made from Halliburton off the billions they stole from the American taxpayers in Iraq?    
    
    
    8 Reasons Why Employees Never Want To Leave This Amazing Company.  Gee, a corporation with a heart!  In North... http://fb.me/2CuiCwfh0     
    
    
    Keith Hernandez's shoes and socks, parked while he and his gin-tonic take a barefoot nap at the outdoor bar on... http://fb.me/1bennIlsM     
    
    
    A laid-back barefoot Keith Hernandez napping with his gin-tonic at the bar on the roof of the Hotel Inglaterra in... http://fb.me/ViiisJGl     
    
    
    Jingle Balls!  Brilliant and Hilarious. Controversy Erupts Over Kmart's Joe Boxer Christmas Commercial   What... http://fb.me/2IKOxl2fs     
    
    
    Calçotada: Cooking Calçots  It is official, the calçotada season has officially begun in Valls (Tarragona),... http://fb.me/2MSYsQhH6     
    
    
    Or course, I realize that you are all perfectly fluent in Catalan, but this is the report about some 50... http://fb.me/2rY64walf     
    
    
    Mimicking these guys and in sympathy with the guy in Moscow who nailed his scrotum to a paving stone in Red... http://fb.me/O4nr5r1O     
    
    
    Dana Staley (l), two other the El Colmado crew and L. J. Sconzo (r) with his shorts in a knot at the opening of... http://fb.me/2CARUBqSI     
    
    
    Gil Avital, partner in Tertulia and El Colmado, L. J. Sconzo (r) with his shorts in a knot at the opening of El... http://fb.me/10f8RV43u     
    
    
    The roster of establishments in The Gotham West Market, 11th Av. @ 45th St., Manhattan, which officially opens... http://fb.me/2YrWzkMMn     
    
    
    Same great tapas at El Colmado, Tertulia's Seamus Mullen's and Gil Avital's new restaurant in The Gotham West... http://fb.me/N63yMYgO     
    
    
    he Brooklyn Kitchen Food Store in Gotham West Market, 11th Av. @ 45th St., Manhattan, Nov. 19 2013.  The Gotham... http://fb.me/1GKidJHOq     
    
    
    The Canibal Hell's Kitchen, a new restaurant in The Gotham West Market, 11th Av. @ 45th St., Manhattan, which... http://fb.me/2yWtKlokh     
    
    
    Can't wait to try the food at Genuine Roadside.  Besides pulled pork BBQ, they offer fish tacos and ceviche... http://fb.me/16onb17OG     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://fb.me/PogsSyT2     
    
    
    David Muñoz of Diverxo in Madrid is awarded a third Michelin star.  Even though I think Michelin continually... http://fb.me/1M30ONFkx     
    
    
    Jeremiah Tower at a Mexican Hole-in-the-Wall: Taqueria CangrejitoFood & Wine. http://fb.me/2D7ySHBTX     
    
    
    Entitlement reform?  You really mean, Peter Kaminsky, says: SCREWING WITH SOCIAL SECURITY AND MEDICARE! http://fb.me/WdgNWAdV     
    
    
    I have an idea.  Let's require drug (and alcohol) tests for Congressmen before they get any more benefits! http://fb.me/18U2GG2B2     
    
    
    Commonwealth Club of California Taste of Spain Tour 2013.  Crypt in the Cathedral of Cádiz where the great... http://fb.me/2aosYkGrw     
    
    
    This afternoon, 50 years ago, I was hitchhiking home-some 20 miles away-from Southern Illinois University, out in... http://fb.me/22bnTnwZy     
    
    
    Van Aken, Trotter, and Lagasse Cook for Julia Child http://fb.me/2vWnt5tqA     
    
    
    Benghazi was an attack by Muslim radicals in a lawless war zone.  Our Ambassador and others were killed, for which... http://fb.me/NJ0A4CWg     
    
    
        
    
    
    Mind-boggling stupidity! http://fb.me/3aIcseXh0     
    
    
    Satire Disclaimer
"Free Wood Post is a news and political satire web publication, which may or may not use real... http://fb.me/2J7JZcPco     
    
    
    What a depressing, gray day, with all these reports on the 50th Anniversary of the assassination of JFK.    
    
    
    "If by a 'Liberal' they mean someone who looks ahead and not behind, someone who welcomes new ideas without rigid... http://fb.me/2d8DGQbeM     
    
    
    Rôtisserie Georgette. Georgette Farkas's new place. http://fb.me/1uUsf1MMJ     
    
    
    A new board that I just started on jamones, embutidos, pig dishes and pig products from Spain. (Many more photos... http://fb.me/23nm5RkyA     
    
    
    Some additions to The Many Faces of Ferran Adrià Pinterest Album. http://fb.me/1UFZd9z6i     
    
    
    Some additions to The Many Faces of Ferran Adrià Pinterest Album. http://fb.me/17vcBGVOp     
    
    
    Gerry Dawes's Photographic Gallery of American Chefs and Food Personalities http://fb.me/2Lu1o3ubS     
    
    
    On an awfully cold day like today, with the wind cutting like a knife and making it feel 15 degrees colder than... http://fb.me/363igI0rR     
    
    
    http://fb.me/121hjvPIZ     
    
    
    Wealth distribution in America.  Indeed mind-blowing! http://fb.me/2HDXceqv1     
    
    
    The Daily Meal’s latest report, 35 Best Airport Restaurants Around the World. http://fb.me/1rWnnIuuv     
    
    
    Some new additions to Food & Drink in America on Pinterest. http://fb.me/Pz0XtHWN     
    
    
    Keith Hernandez contemplates our paella at Oro de Bailén olive oil producers' almazara, near Bailén (Jaén),... http://fb.me/30YRgNGoD     
    
    
    Jazz great Wynton Marsalis and my old friend Spanish cookbook-author and chef Teresa Barrenechea, Master of... http://fb.me/3qKZBf4i6     
    
    
    Experience Gerry Dawes's Spain: Specialized Food, Wine Cultural & Photographic Tours of Spain & Tour Advice.

I... http://fb.me/1sWweeqmC     
    
    
    The Photography equipment I use for the photos I place on my Facebook page. http://fb.me/2rN2T5hbM     
    
    
    Cooking tonight for Thanksgiving.  Did garbanzos con espinacas for a side dish.  

Worked on mussels for ceviche,... http://fb.me/OZODjuJv     
    
    
    Galicia - Ribadavia Old Jewish Quarter. http://fb.me/6oxMMztqw     
    
    
    Mejillones, mussels, plucked from the Galician rías. http://fb.me/22JRsBYIU     
    
    
    Ronald Reagan and Socialized Medicine!!  Why can't we all just get along?  Unfathomable (as in knows no depth)... http://fb.me/2cFtIj3CX     
    
    
    This morning, I am down 18 pounds from my heaviest weight.  I still have 7-12 lbs. to go to lose the 10 kilos or... http://fb.me/QUekvlpv     
    
    
    La Quiemada in Galicia (With some new slides of the Flaming Pumpkin)

The Quiemada Incantation:
 
"Demons,... http://fb.me/3fNQaywno     
    
    
    Quiemada with the orujo flaming. Besides the liquor, this concoction contains sugar, coffee, coffee beans and... http://fb.me/12e6nDLgO     
    
    
    Gerry's dishes, cranberry relish with Meyer lemon, pomegranate seeds, Torres licor de naranja and rum.  Baked... http://fb.me/1X7ACRPLM     
    
    
    Boquerones en vinagre (fresh anchovies in a vinagreta), some of the very best in Madrid, and olivas gordas (fat... http://fb.me/3tJ2rNUCB     
    
    
    Darwin Award Candidates Practicing Rocket Science with a big turkey and a too-small pot. http://fb.me/6FgUwPuUm     
    
    
        
    
    
    Tortillitas de camarones (tiny shrimp-filled fritters), one of the great seafood dishes of Andalucía and fabulous... http://fb.me/2hsqZ0lOq     
    
    
    Tortillitas de camarones (tiny shrimp-filled fritters), one of the great seafood dishes of Andalucía and fabulous... http://fb.me/6GlJN9XnE     
    
    
    Tortillitas de camarones (tiny shrimp-filled fritters), one of the great seafood dishes of Andalucía and fabulous... http://fb.me/6yzcW5ONX     
    
    
    A little girl goes up a puts a coin in what she thinks is a street musician's hat.  The rest is very cool.  In... http://fb.me/2OgA4eR99     
    
    
    The great George Carlin. http://fb.me/OhfSkGzh     
    
    
    Is Obama really a big spender? http://fb.me/6DxJLWlEQ     
    
    
    Ted Cruz was born in Kenya, not Canada, of a black mother and an Hispanic Canadian father who brought him to... http://fb.me/3cFnZb4ie     
    
    
    Watch 11 Explosive Deep-Fried Turkey Disaster Videos http://fb.me/3sHqOH7q3     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving, everyone.  Here are some "Royal Turkeys," Pavos Reales as they are called in Spanish,... http://fb.me/1cfIpttbB     
    
    
    Jeff Bezos and http://Amazon.com .  Got to re-think my boycott list, which is topped by Wal-Mart. http://fb.me/2NloEPy8G     
    
    
    Second Bill of Rights. http://fb.me/OcmUfmiq     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013:  Ceviche appetizer with shrimp, mussels, sliced scallops, corn-off-the-cob,... http://fb.me/29ZTSIUZO     
    
    
    Thanksgiving 2013 at Kay's & Gerry's place, Patterson, NY:  Rozanne Gold's roasted turkey. http://fb.me/2yzmm6svT     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013, Patterson, NY: Anazazi beans from Dove Creek, Colorado, first cooked, then... http://fb.me/2ToF1W2M9     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes Thanksgiving 2013:  Espinacas con garbanzos, garbanzo stew with spinach, cumin, saffrón, pimentón... http://fb.me/PPLgfteF     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013, Patterson, NY:  Mushrooms sautéed with Spanish extra virgen olive oil and... http://fb.me/2yGgSHXlB     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013, Patterson, NY:  Fresh-made duck egg  mayonnaise from eggs from ducks at a... http://fb.me/10ofDOsiB     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013:  Cornbread with sliced scallions, chopped jalapeño, dried black currants and... http://fb.me/6wpTgIyvp     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013:  Mashed potatoes with leeks, celery and garlic, Spanish extra virgen olive... http://fb.me/1GO2r4VO9     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013:  Sweet potatoes and pumpkin seasoned with curry and cumin, glazed with... http://fb.me/2P4wxJtdq     
    
    
    Thanksgiving 2013 at Kay and Gerry's home, Patterson, NY:  O'Forrollo Albariño 2011 Rias Baixas, Adolfo Viñedos... http://fb.me/1K53BMRKN     
    
    
    Gerry Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013:  Frozen orange shells hollowed out and filled with orange cream sorbet with... http://fb.me/2bjWLQYJ0     
    
    
    One of Kay's pumpkin pies for Thanksgiving 2013. http://fb.me/1xljoS0Gz     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013:  Sweet potatoes and pumpkin seasoned with curry and cumin, glazed with... http://fb.me/6BIOnNv2a     
    
    
    Booze to go into the Thanksgiving Day Galician Quiemada. http://fb.me/2RI6I6nDw     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes, Thanksgiving 2013:  Galician Quiemada. A pumpkin hollowed out and filled with Galician orujo... http://fb.me/118GFCi5q     
    
    
    Quiemada with the orujo flaming. Besides the liquor, this concoction contains sugar, coffee, coffee beans and... http://fb.me/QLGITIoY     
    
    
        
    
    
    Post-Thanksgiving breakfast, a bagel with crème fraîche, smoked salmon, minced red onion, scrambled eggs and capers. http://fb.me/3jUTpFT55     
    
    
    http://fb.me/22vxNM153     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2yEPqec3b     
    
    
    Hobby Lobby and China!! http://fb.me/6zvLeE7AU     
    
    
        
    
    
    From David Downie
This just in from Anton Gill, everyone's favorite thriller writer, author of City of Gold! "How... http://fb.me/2AFGzOKw0     
    
    
    Ten's, a new Barcelona tapas restaurant from budding superstar chef, Jordi Cruz. http://fb.me/2ENvRlAp1     
    
    
    From my daughter, Erica, in Southwestern Colorado. http://fb.me/PbWhYxKC     
    
    
    Plaque in the center of Sanlúcar de Barrameda, honoring Fernando de Magallanes (Magellan) and Basque Juan... http://fb.me/1VOS0eIlu     
    
    
    Churros at Churrería Doña Carmen, Sanlúcar de Barrameda (Cádiz), in the street just outside the muncipal market.... http://fb.me/2nctNEWK6     
    
    
    Egg and arrope meloja (a syrup made with honey, pumpkin, orange and anís) seller, who doesn't like to be... http://fb.me/1vYqRA5Ik     
    
    
    Tortillitas de camarones (tiny shrimp-filled fritters), one of the great seafood dishes of Andalucía and fabulous... http://fb.me/31DGA2mit     
    
    
    Chef-owner of Casa Bigote Fernando Hermoso, who began cooking on fishing boats.  Sanlúcar de Barrameda. http://fb.me/21jWiuV5L     
    
    
    With chef-owner Fernando Hermoso and Tom Burkhardt at Casa Bigote in Sanlúcar de Barrameda on the Commonwealth... http://fb.me/2uKCGNhIb     
    
    
    Collecting bi-valves and other edible marine life at low tide on Bajo de Guía beach at Sanlúcar de Barrameda, a... http://fb.me/6wOCToLGi     
    
    
    Attention Photo Editors:  Looking for photos of Spain--food, chefs, restaurants, wine, travel, historic sights,... http://fb.me/LBilJDFx     
    
    
    If you are thinking of purchasing a crash-mobile computer from Dell, think twice.  I recently purchased a Dell... http://fb.me/2wMR0FLEQ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6q4rWFvPV     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2x4FMdKDI     
    
    
    An amazing book (in Spanish) from Carmencita, the Spanish food-spice company.  This book tells about the history... http://fb.me/3BF8z6k2P     
    
    
    A blowfish hanging from the ceiling, along with Roman amphoras brought up in fishermen's nets over the years, at... http://fb.me/35WhrQgcw     
    
    
    Meetin the great Stan Musial at Southern Illinois University, 1964, when I interviewed Stan as the sports writer... http://fb.me/12j77lUJW     
    
    
    Remembering my former wife, Diana Valenti Dawes Bower, who died a year ago Thanksgiving. http://fb.me/6mMh1RhIx     
    
    
    Gerry Dawes's Photographic Gallery of American Chefs and Food Personalities - Some new additions http://fb.me/2h2K3v194     
    
    
    Rozanne Gold and Michael Whiteman. http://fb.me/2vh3CJEcU     
    
    
    Sheila Lukins was a member of my Chefs From Hell Acrobatic Unicyclists and Winetasters Club. http://fb.me/6vIoocc8P     
    
    
    Nobu & Ferran, Madrid Fusión 2004. Photograph by Gerry Dawes©2004. Reproduction prohibited without permission.... http://fb.me/6vGj5M7Zy     
    
    
    Joël Robuchon and Ferran Adrià in Cuenca. http://fb.me/2ftFqMGGL     
    
    
    Travel Spain with Gerry Dawes – January 12th-19th, 2014
Posted on December 5, 2013 by John Sconzo 
This from... http://fb.me/1T8OatmVg     
    
    
    Join Michael Pollan in calling for fairness for fast-food workers http://fb.me/6tjzBD2aL     
    
    
    New York - New Canaan CT Roger Sherman Inn Marie Daleys Gig Dec 2013.  Kay, her son Robert and his girlfriend... http://fb.me/2dcC6S1tn     
    
    
    Overflow parking all the way up the hill from the station at Southeast after the fatal Metro North crash on the... http://fb.me/6osha5olJ     
    
    
    A Night With Janis Joplin at the Lyceum Theatre.  The second substitute singer, Alison Cusano, brought the house... http://fb.me/QpqOxPWQ     
    
    
    Yesterday evening before we went to the Spanish Institute where the late Spanish cookbook author, Penelope Casas,... http://fb.me/1020a4XUM     
    
    
    The fog in Patterson, Putnam County, New York all day today.  Reminds me of Germany!  Dec. 5, 2013. http://fb.me/Q5jNgrvU     
    
    
        
    
    
    Kay in Chinchón with some pastries she just bought, May 2013. The bakery has been there since 1941. http://fb.me/2ngt9Fjr9     
    
    
    Detail of tiles depicting one of Cordoban artist Julio Romero de Torrres's most famous paintings, Cante Hondo, at... http://fb.me/33ozmWTse     
    
    
    The famous pulpo at Las Bravas, where patatas bravas (the patented sauce for crispy fried Spanish potatoes) was... http://fb.me/2KSon1z4e     
    
    
    Just got a couple more travelers and can accommodate 3-4 more.

Travel Spain with Gerry Dawes – January... http://fb.me/35kvkQwQd     
    
    
    A shellfish paella with gambas (shrimp), langostinos (prawns) and cigalas (Dublin bay prawns, also called... http://fb.me/35VKOMLqT     
    
    
    Quim de la Boqueria, flash deep-fried artichoke slices with Maldon salt. http://fb.me/2viOzU93G     
    
    
    Arrós con conejo y caracoles (rice with wild rabbit and snails) cooked over grape vine cuttings at Casa Elias,... http://fb.me/2119hHnOG     
    
    
        
    
    
    Kokotxas de merluza rebozada, battered and pan-fried hake "cheeks," Ganbara, Casco Viejo (old quarter), San... http://fb.me/20JIGgH65     
    
    
    Setas (mushrooms), grillled and served with foie gras and an egg yolk as a sauce, Ganbarra, Casco Viejo (old... http://fb.me/OIQgcBLl     
    
    
    Dessert, helado de queso con fresas y pimienta negra, cheese ice cream with strawberry and black peppercorn... http://fb.me/6p1wffeK2     
    
    
    Iconic Spanish Wine & Food Experiences. Whole turbot grilling at Elkano, one of Spain's greatest fish... http://fb.me/6BM4HX6tO     
    
    
    Once again, the Lifetime President Emeritus of the Lower Than Snake Shit Club chimes in:  "Dick Cheney Didn't... http://fb.me/AvlMpJP4     
    
    
    Look at this very high megapixel photo and zoom in.  It is amazing how clearly you can see individual faces.... http://fb.me/2sR5yuoA6     
    
    
    For less than ten bucks, you can get this "Not To Be Used for Bribing Politicians, Traditional Wood Handle Stamp"... http://fb.me/14wqid2nq     
    
    
    Roast kid with patatas panaderas and the wines of Carlos Aliaga at El Crucero Restaurante, Corella (Navarra). http://fb.me/2zUg9HGeo     
    
    
    Cardos, cardoons, with the house's own extra virgin olive oil from Navarra, El Crucero Restaurante, Corella... http://fb.me/6AD4igze6     
    
    
    Roast kid with patatas panaderas and the wines of Carlos Aliaga at El Crucero Restaurante, Corella (Navarra). http://fb.me/3c3R36lnz     
    
    
    Pochas, one of the best beans on the planet, at El Crucero Restaurante, Corella (Navarra). http://fb.me/ZUccFO8V     
    
    
    Superb, heavenly bacalao with peppers and tomatoes.  El Crucero Restaurante, Corella (Navarra). http://fb.me/1atvGOLei     
    
    
    Polenta with melted Swiss cheese and Mexican salsa verde for breakfast - lunch late this morning, along with a... http://fb.me/6k2e3QIqN     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Oven-finished frittata with potatoes, small yellow peppers, jalapeños, chopped Vidalia and red... http://fb.me/10riDqagZ     
    
    
    Javier Hidalgo, Bodegas Hidalgo, La Gitana, Sanlúcar de Barrameda explains his Sherries to travelers on the... http://fb.me/6GHs56e1k     
    
    
    Juli Soler, elBulli, and Chef-author Teresa Barrenechea, formerly at Marichu in New York, in Madrid. http://fb.me/2GyayN5AJ     
    
    
    Paco Torreblanca and Ferran Adrià in New York. http://fb.me/ScRhFSmm     
    
    
    Juan Mari Arzak & Alexandra Forbes at San Sebastián Gastronomika. http://fb.me/2Q7B3YxzS     
    
    
    Three-star chef Joan Roca, El Celler de Can Roca, rated by the panel of Restaurant Magazine (UK) as the best... http://fb.me/2QSWzkaAx     
    
    
    Three-star Michelin Chefs Juan Mari Arzak & Thomas Keller at San Sebastián Gastronomika 2010.  I first introduced... http://fb.me/3cJzqzYgp     
    
    
    Two of the top chefs in the world, both Catalans, Ferran Adrià with Joan Roca in the background at Madrid Fusión... http://fb.me/1J6IiBKAx     
    
    
    Ferran, José Gómez (Joselito the Jamón king), and Gerry Dawes at San Sebastián Gastronomika. http://fb.me/QWkmIDqq     
    
    
    Phyllis Feder, Julia Child and Ben Feder at the  JBF Birthday Dinner, Rockefeller Center, June 5, 1995. http://fb.me/AyqnhqJp     
    
    
    Julia Child, JBF Birthday Dinner, Rockefeller Center, June 5, 1995. http://fb.me/W15AqTRL     
    
    
    Janis Joplin singing "Ball and Chain" at the Monterey Pope Festival in 1967.  I was there and experienced this.... http://fb.me/6C8rLA9Ei     
    
    
    Monterey Pop Festival 1967 Gracie Slick and the Jefferson Airplane- "Somebody To Love"  Begins at minute 48:24.  I... http://fb.me/MphhIYu7     
    
    
    Christian Escribà and José Andrés at Christian creative offices in Barcelona. http://fb.me/2Bi96t27g     
    
    
    Albert Adrià at Tickets, June 2011. http://fb.me/2z6r7L7f5     
    
    
    My friend Mel Master, with Jane Master, at Bodegas Hidalgo La Gitana and Casa Bigote, Sanlúcar de Barrameda.  Dec.... http://fb.me/T0FxliUD     
    
    
    El Celler de Can Roca Announces 2014 World Tour http://fb.me/6Ciodfnk1     
    
    
    So happy that I got a Dell Crash-a-billy computer and laptop from Texas.  Not!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Chefs From Hell announcement supporting an AIWF Marketplace Tasting in the early 1990s: Gerry Dawes (Founder &... http://fb.me/6lXQrbTzq     
    
    
    Cara de Silva's Newsday article, "Chefs From Hell: A club with a taste wine and deviltry."  Newsday, Feb. 21, 1990. http://fb.me/2dZpYc2Nu     
    
    
    For chefs and serious culinarians, I still have a couple of places left on my Chefs Tour of Mediterranean Spain,... http://fb.me/6rawYFGGO     
    
    
    Benefit 25 de noviembre in Barcelona, 4ª Gala Sida Barcelona, Battle Against AIDS Foundation Gala dinner:  Star... http://fb.me/2PIl3A6No     
    
    
    Murphysboro, Illinois (where I was born, only hospital in the area then)

"The barbecue in southern Illinois... http://fb.me/16raSglEM     
    
    
    If you have any birdbrain relatives or friends who like to use crayons, this could be the perfect gift for them.... http://fb.me/1lPdfyyD1     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6qXGCeDCI     
    
    
    Wandering and wondering through boxes of memory inducing photos, clippings, books and the like.  It's a trip,... http://fb.me/2wvfrkdVa     
    
    
    Proud of old friend and one of the original members of the Chefs From Hell Acrobatic Unicyclists and Winetasters... http://fb.me/36xZgS1n0     
    
    
    Snow, Patterson, Putnam County, New York, Tuesday, Dec. 10, 2013. http://fb.me/2WqUHazZo     
    
    
    The geraniums remind me of southern Spain, the snow doesn't.  Snow, Patterson, Putnam County, New York, Tuesday,... http://fb.me/T15oO6tS     
    
    
    Anybody want to sit around the firepit tonight? Snow, Patterson, Putnam County, New York, Tuesday, Dec. 10, 2013. http://fb.me/33s3zWjKA     
    
    
    @joantxo Great, Joantxo, mil gracias!!    
    
    
    Artesanado ceiling, El Real Alcázar de Sevilla, originally a Moorish fortress, is now a royal palace in Sevilla.... http://fb.me/PGW5JTIe     
    
    
    Inequality in America. http://fb.me/156T5Ai5w     
    
    
    I first came to Spain in January 1969 in the United States Navy and had the good luck to be stationed in Rota, Spain. http://fb.me/241WalcA1     
    
    
    I first came to Spain in January 1968 in the United States Navy and had the good luck to be stationed in Rota,... http://fb.me/2BJTyZ3TR     
    
    
    Kay Balun, my fiancee, in Chinchón with some pastries she just bought, May 2013. The bakery has been there since... http://fb.me/14GmvF77x     
    
    
    Dreaming of a better tomato, from my buddy James Campbell Caruso in Santa Fe and now in Alburquerque with his new... http://fb.me/2TS2xEbI6     
    
    
    Patriotic millionaires, the movement is growing. http://fb.me/R19Nji8x     
    
    
    Guess who took the Mithra (the bull god) out of Mithramas?  I mean I am going to celebrate Christmas with a... http://fb.me/1xeVOuIQN     
    
    
    Shades of Doctor Zhivago. Dawn on a winter's morning, West Patterson, Putnam County, New York. http://fb.me/2wRgIn6ER     
    
    
    Shades of Doctor Zhivago. Dawn on a winter morning, West Patterson, Putnam County, New York. http://fb.me/6ybawtfXb     
    
    
    Shades of Doctor Zhivago. Dawn on a winter morning, West Patterson, Putnam County, New York. http://fb.me/1ixfkZxIz     
    
    
    Shades of Doctor Zhivago. Dawn on a winter morning, West Patterson, Putnam County, New York. http://fb.me/1Ipy87uYW     
    
    
    This could have been filmed in Patterson.  Just saying. http://fb.me/2jfXHsSLm     
    
    
    All the photos in this post should be credited: Photo by Gerry Dawes©2011 http://fb.me/1QnobqjPC     
    
    
    Just finished Bob Spitz's, Dearie, his monumental biography of Julia Child and I very highly recommend that if... http://fb.me/2DBg5JQre     
    
    
    Begoña, street stand in Madrid off the Plaza Mayor, offering roasted maíz (corn), batata (sweet potato) and... http://fb.me/3l5MHbadV     
    
    
    Begoña, street stand in Madrid off the Plaza Mayor, offering roasted maíz (corn), batata (sweet potato) and... http://fb.me/1R6TDymlm     
    
    
    Gerry Dawes reading the last pages of The Sun Also Rises as Hemingway closes the book at Casa Botin.  Photo by... http://fb.me/3dUHgcxkh     
    
    
    At Cafe de Chinitas, Madrid.  Photo by John Sconzo. http://fb.me/6BeBf1ibS     
    
    
    Yours truly, John Sconzo and Georges Mendes at Casa Botin, Madrid, Jan. 23, 2013.  Photo by L. J. Sconzo. http://fb.me/1x9Ye8Jr8     
    
    
    Breakfast in Barcelona.  Photo by L. J. Sconzo http://fb.me/1RKc7zmYB     
    
    
    My buddy L.J. Sconzo, on a Spanish Artisan Wine & Spirits Group trip, drinking red wine from a porrón in... http://fb.me/6oS9iQAgF     
    
    
    Chestnuts roasting over an open fire. In the snow, La Castañera, the chestnut roaster, a bronze statue in Burgos,... http://fb.me/WPX6d7hN     
    
    
    With Pepe Rodriguez of Bodega O Barreiro, Valdeorras. http://fb.me/6vUOc53lA     
    
    
    With Pepe Rodriguez of Bodega O Barreiro and El Jay Sconzo in Pepe's cave in Seadur, with a little orujo... http://fb.me/6xm1LDQhm     
    
    
        
    
    
    In Zaragoza with Juan Barbacil and Brad Haskel, giving a talk on vino in Spanish.  Photo by El Jay Sconzo http://fb.me/2ykijuQQX     
    
    
    Waiting to go onstage at Madrid Fusión 2013. — with George Mendes and Gerry Dawes.  Photo by John Sconzo http://fb.me/2fGbMuWYD     
    
    
    Introductions by Gerry onstage at Madrid Fusion 2013, Jan. 2013.  Photo by John Sconzo http://fb.me/37XbCrszH     
    
    
    Stay tuned for highlights on the program for the upcoming Madrid Fusion 2014.

Onstage at Madrid Fusión 2013. —... http://fb.me/2F389ay7c     
    
    
    With Gerry Dawes and Patrick Martin at Madison Square Park at the Big Apple Barbecue Block Party 2013. Photo by... http://fb.me/RQjbalWJ     
    
    
    Finally, a Pope who returns to the philosophy of Jesus Christ. http://fb.me/37TlXaFK6     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2yj7hLnww     
    
    
    Catch hits a big home run on Ellen! http://fb.me/2RrMWYRv7     
    
    
    My friend Mel Master, with Jane Master, at Bodegas Hidalgo La Gitana and Casa Bigote, Sanlúcar de Barrameda. Dec.... http://fb.me/2wp94ceQ7     
    
    
    For chefs and serious culinarians, I still have a couple of places left on my Chefs Tour of Mediterranean Spain,... http://fb.me/2tNcrVI0z     
    
    
    For chefs and serious culinarians, I still have a couple of places left on my Chefs Tour of Mediterranean Spain,... http://fb.me/36xbirQg6     
    
    
    Wandering and wondering through boxes of memory inducing photos, clippings, books and the like. It's a trip, part... http://fb.me/1PYO1goR2     
    
    
    Photo by Gerry Dawes http://fb.me/6BlbaAbP8     
    
    
    Photo by Gerry Dawes http://fb.me/QnmWMmYX     
    
    
    Kay Balun, my fiancee, in Chinchón with some pastries she just bought, May 2013. The bakery has been there since... http://fb.me/18FlAods9     
    
    
    All the photos in this post should be credited: Photo by Gerry Dawes©2011 http://fb.me/CpNUKqPQ     
    
    
    Begoña, street stand in Madrid off the Plaza Mayor, offering roasted maíz (corn), batata (sweet potato) and... http://fb.me/6qz7ovlbu     
    
    
    Chef Mark Kiffin, The Compound, Santa Fe, NM:  "Don't go to Spain without Gerry Dawes!" today on Gerry Dawes's... http://fb.me/KAz5Mye1     
    
    
    Still have some places left on this trip, which leaves Jan. 12. We have some great visits lined up. http://fb.me/36JoSOCtv     
    
    
    In the old La Bretxa fish market (when it was on the second floor) in San Sebastian, summer 1989.  
Photo by Diana... http://fb.me/ROP9EchS     
    
    
    Tom Colicchio, Gerry Dawes and Bobby Flay at Chefs Night Out, JBF House, New York, May 1992. http://fb.me/3dF9dRKFk     
    
    
    Camencita Paella Party at new York's' Institute of Culinary Education (NYC) with Paella Maestro Paul Vella of... http://fb.me/6wmJ1K5IW     
    
    
    Phyllis Feder, Julia Child and Ben Feder at the  JBF Birthday Dinner, Rockefeller Center, June 5, 1995. http://fb.me/10pB7EK77     
    
    
    Gerry Dawes & Chef Michael Lomonaco at The Beard House, NYC.  Mid-1990s. http://fb.me/10GlqqvSC     
    
    
    Chefs From Hell at The River Cafe:  Brendan Walsh (Arizona 206), Joey Dee (Wine Director, The River Cafe), Phil... http://fb.me/6BndxpdBL     
    
    
    Chefs From Hell on opening day at Shea Stadium on April 8, 1991 (Mets behind Doc Gooden beat the Phillies 2-1).... http://fb.me/6iQxEW3EP     
    
    
    Mas Jamón. — with George Mendes, El Jay Sconzo and Gerry Dawes at Mercado de San Miguel.  Photo by John Sconzo http://fb.me/2UaFWdZ2X     
    
    
    ¡Carabineros! — with George Mendes and Gerry Dawes at Mercado de San Miguel.   Photo by John Sconzo http://fb.me/1agncXOjD     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6FqQTYZPQ     
    
    
    Pope Francis Attacks Super Rich For Getting Mega-Salaries And Leaving ‘Crumbs’ For The Poor http://fb.me/15Wvdlj36     
    
    
    Show me that Kenyan birth certificate one more time, Donnie J. Trump!! http://fb.me/38ogoq4CB     
    
    
    Reading the Chefs From Hell rules at Martha Stewart's place in Greenwich,  CT.  Identifiable Participants (l to... http://fb.me/2UF8KPirE     
    
    
    Mario Batali laughing / grimacing (?) as Gerry Dawes reads the Chefs From Hell rules at Martha Stewart's place in... http://fb.me/2SsdxU6kP     
    
    
        
    
    
    Drew Nieporent poses with a giant wisk at the San Sebastián Gastronomika 2010 opening reception. http://fb.me/Q0tn5yTD     
    
    
    Mario Batali In New York. http://fb.me/2kvjyEI8S     
    
    
    I mean really put Elvis back in Christmas.  The King sings Blue Christmas! http://fb.me/2Ap2tdGoK     
    
    
    Pierre Franey and Barbara Poole Fenzl JBF event 1992. http://fb.me/X6Xctw8U     
    
    
    Jacques Pepin and Gerry Dawes with his whisk bowtie at City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday event,... http://fb.me/6l81RVDmP     
    
    
    Drew Nieporent's 40th birthday cake, served during a party held in a parking lot near Tribeca Grill, June 4, 1995. http://fb.me/UPoOvDrF     
    
    
    Drew Nieporent with his cake at his 40th birthday party, held in a parking lot near Tribeca Grill, June 4, 1995. http://fb.me/11kwMv45r     
    
    
    Drew Nieporent and Nobu Matsuhisha with Drew's cake at his 40th birthday party, held in a parking lot near... http://fb.me/2v111VBB1     
    
    
    Drew Nieporent with a Cuban Cohiba cigar at his 40th birthday party, held in a parking lot near Tribeca Grill,... http://fb.me/2tVRiTWDr     
    
    
    Drew Nieporent with John Fischer (now an instructor at the CIA-Hyde Park) in a conga line at his 40th birthday... http://fb.me/6wrmCXd4i     
    
    
    CBS's Ed Bradley and Daniel Johnnes at Drew Nieporent's 40th birthday party, held in a parking lot near Tribeca... http://fb.me/1cXrtMwbR     
    
    
    David Michael Cane and Rachel Cane, Matter of Taste Radio Program, San Francisco, at Drew Nieporent's 40th... http://fb.me/Qv28YsJM     
    
    
    Corby Kummer and Thomas Keller at Chef's Night Out, Chelsea Market, May 8, 2011. http://fb.me/XECG4cN4     
    
    
    Susur Lee & Betty Fussel, New York, 2009. http://fb.me/KVtERHA8     
    
    
    José Andrés, Thomas Keller, Carolyn O'Neil, Daniel Boulud, Chefs' Night Out 2003. http://fb.me/2HVVn92Sc     
    
    
    Daniel Boulud in his kitchen at Restaurant Daniel. http://fb.me/2V5C7yzyh     
    
    
    Jan 28, 2010 - American author on Spanish cuisine, Janet Mendel, and Juan Mari Arzak at Madrid Fusión 2010. http://fb.me/6luWFbT2L     
    
    
    One of my longest running friendships, cookbook author and long-time resident of Mijas, Spain, Janet Mendel.... http://fb.me/RY37KAwS     
    
    
    Toño Perez, chef-partner of two-star Atrio restaurant (in its former location) in Cáceres. http://fb.me/6xVQbeUcw     
    
    
    The late Santi Santamaria and his wife Angels at their 25th Anniversary (and their restaurant's 25th), El Racó de... http://fb.me/2UUXllSmb     
    
    
    Mauro Maccione, Le Cirque, and Julián Serrano, Picasso (Las Vegas), at the James Beard Awards 2011. http://fb.me/16bfnzC0r     
    
    
    Teresa Barrenechea with the late photographer, Gordon Parks, in New York City, 2003. http://fb.me/36pTGv6cx     
    
    
    Rachel Zemser, the Intrepid Culinologist, shows us how to eat a carabinero (scarlet prawn) at the Mercado de San... http://fb.me/6n24F3yBr     
    
    
    Julia Child and her producer Geof Drummond at the James Beard Birthday Dinner at Rockefeller Center, June 5, 1995. http://fb.me/2cxMbvKI9     
    
    
    Andre Soltner at the James Beard Birthday Dinner at Rockefeller Center, June 5, 1995. http://fb.me/6DdHShIMx     
    
    
    David Bouley and his wife Nicole in San Sebastián. http://fb.me/3jWaeZGbU     
    
    
    Norman Van Aken at CIA-Greystone, Napa Valley. http://fb.me/28Eu8fKXM     
    
    
    Joyce Goldstein and Paula Wolfert, two girls From Brooklyn, in the Kitchens at CIA-Greystone, Napa Valley. http://fb.me/1xPjhC2Du     
    
    
    José Andrés and an unidentified food writer at the Bar Basque, New York. http://fb.me/2gXjlysdM     
    
    
    Paula Wolfert and Mark Miller at CIA Worlds of Flavor 2009. Photo by Gerry Dawes©2009. Contact gerrydawes@aol.com. http://fb.me/6u0Niu0y5     
    
    
    Ruth Reichl and Michael Batterberry, a man I greatly miss, at Per Se opening, April 2004. http://fb.me/2CiVWoFkA     
    
    
    Greg Grossman and Gerry Dawes at the James Beard Foundation Awards 2011. http://fb.me/PCp0MfLD     
    
    
    Paul Bolles-Beaven and Danny Meyer of Union Square Hospitality Group celebrating their trifecta--Eleven Madison... http://fb.me/2Uf068axG     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1SpvLi8wU     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2AkKy35x0     
    
    
    Uncorking the City: Amy Dixon leaves little doubt as to her profession and her physical state http://fb.me/2YbqO0uDd     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1c0CA6AvI     
    
    
        
    
    
    You gotta see this, priceless!  Yeh, we CAN all get along!! http://fb.me/6xb8cqOUM     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2K6JGoi9z     
    
    
    Step Into the Lush, Eclectic World of New American Cuisine Founder Norman Van Aken http://fb.me/3dedS9xPl     
    
    
    New York food personalities, author Arthur Schwartz and cookbook author-food writer, Rozanne Gold, one of my... http://fb.me/121994k7H     
    
    
    Gil Avital, General-Manager/Partner (and like the chef, formerly at Boqueria) at Chef Seamus Mullen's Tertulia... http://fb.me/6pBgFPhib     
    
    
        
    
    
    Jimi Hendrix playing at the Monterey Pop Festival 1967. http://fb.me/1bIQW6SIj     
    
    
    Two-star Chefs Paco Roncero, Ramón Freixa, Dani García and Toño Pérez, the four Iberia Airlines Business Class... http://fb.me/2FXO48fHO     
    
    
    The liquid fat between the muscles layers of this Pedroches jamón Ibérico de bellota comes from the acorns... http://fb.me/6kQeFnMC3     
    
    
    Elizabeth Warren tells it like it is!! http://fb.me/131Fgr0Pf     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1BIjLi3fb     
    
    
    Amazing story about insurance companies scamming their customers, by cancelling customers' substandard policies... http://fb.me/3cWWiaQf8     
    
    
    Another shot at Faux News. http://fb.me/3hKfHkVKl     
    
    
    Legislators want teachers to be judged on performance.  How about judging legislators and adjusting their pay... http://fb.me/2CLTwAmc8     
    
    
    Amazing and true!! http://fb.me/1bc5IwLSb     
    
    
    Snowstorm, Dec. 14, 2013, Patterson, Putnam County, New York.  My new RAV4, after cleaning off the snow twice! http://fb.me/6xMeo04yd     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Alcachofas con jamón, glass-jarred artichokes cooked with white wine, leeks and tacos de jamón... http://fb.me/18EbcAgHv     
    
    
    The great Peter O'Toole (on Letterman).  R.I.P. http://fb.me/M1FKhmNx     
    
    
    This is very odd.  For some reason, yesterday I was having a look a old Johnny Carson segments and I watched this... http://fb.me/TX4jjqa5     
    
    
    Martha Stewart in her chicken coop at Martha's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at her place in Greenwich, CT, 1995. http://fb.me/6wJU1Zr0d     
    
    
    BEWARE OF 'IMPORTANT' GOOGLE DOC E-MAILS:
Message to all my Facebook friends who also get e-mail from me.  Some... http://fb.me/17oHcZ205     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6y19qhwtf     
    
    
    One of the greatest tapas restaurants in Spain, La Taberna del Gourmets in Alicante. http://fb.me/30KfIj7BS     
    
    
    That God, Climate change has now been confined to Europe, the Middle East and, errr, Africa!! http://fb.me/15XLmHANp     
    
    
    Jimmy Chin, owner of Chin-Chin Restaurant, New York and a  friend of at least 30 years, and Gerry Dawes at... http://fb.me/1QdgOy7eb     
    
    
    Some new photos added to my Photo Gallery of American Chefs and Food Personalities. http://fb.me/13tIbzEjN     
    
    
    Paul Prudhomme at Madrid Fusion 2006. http://fb.me/24Maj7r7N     
    
    
    Cindy Pawlcyn and Mark Miller at Coyote Cafe, Santa Fe, New Year's Eve 2003. http://fb.me/2UVyJ1pXd     
    
    
    Chef Tom Valenti at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in Greenwich, CT, 1995. http://fb.me/36EXE93e9     
    
    
    Susan Samson of Sakonnet Vineyards and Mario Batali at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's... http://fb.me/3d5JKERcM     
    
    
    Steve Frankel, Brendan Walsh and Tom Valenti at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in... http://fb.me/1JRXBMAFa     
    
    
    Susan Magrino at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in Greenwich, CT, 1995. http://fb.me/2Z4fL8hlX     
    
    
    Chefs Anne Rozenzweig and Phil McGrath at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in... http://fb.me/6zxzQiYrq     
    
    
    Martha Stewart and her cat at the Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in Greenwich, CT, 1995. http://fb.me/1wZYUWg6X     
    
    
    Chef Anne Rosenzweig (Arcadia) at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in Greenwich, CT, 1995. http://fb.me/2BWufP0dR     
    
    
    Chef Mario Batali at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in Greenwich, CT, 1995. http://fb.me/2wKhK6lvQ     
    
    
    Chef Waldy Malouf at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in Greenwich, CT, 1995. http://fb.me/3duB1ikZr     
    
    
    Chefs Quint Smith, Mario Batali and Bobby Flay at Martha Stewart's Chefs From Hell Luncheon at Martha's place in... http://fb.me/6umHHaLDL     
    
    
    Chef Matthew Tivy (now chef-owner of Cafe du Soleil, NYC)  cooking a Chefs From Hell luncheon at our home in... http://fb.me/X5Xs3zZZ     
    
    
    Chef Steve Lyle (Odeon, NYC) cooking a Chefs From Hell luncheon at our home in Suffern, NY. http://fb.me/2KpQwRazz     
    
    
    Husband-and-wife chef team, Catherine Alexandrou and Michel Boudreau of Chez Catherine at Martha Stewart's Chefs... http://fb.me/3wEH0C0ja     
    
    
    http://fb.me/RzSOPCCO     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1Z76Z1HbJ     
    
    
    From my friend Harold Heckle in Madrid. http://fb.me/T5NhL7B9     
    
    
    Patterson County, New York, by Francisco de Goya.  Me, Kay, Jake the dog and some neighbors coming back from a... http://fb.me/Q4AMxCo0     
    
    
    The shameless Port Authority of NY & NJ, coupled with the total lack of help from the New York City Traffic... http://fb.me/1ca2huSq2     
    
    
    @howardggoldberg Going to the remains of Forbes Field Oct. 13 to listen to the replay of the final game of the 1960 World Series    
    
    
    Gael Greene (please wear red!) and actress Kathleen Turner (emcee for Gael's tribute) at Gael's 80th Birthday... http://fb.me/11dSBUlZl     
    
    
    Charlie Baum clutching a couple of glasses of bubbly at Gael Greene's 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 Trattoria... http://fb.me/2HjiwJxqm     
    
    
    Michael Whiteman, Rozanne Gold and Tim Zagat at Gael Greene's 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 Trattoria in the... http://fb.me/RJ83TaVv     
    
    
    Drew Nieporent toasting Gael Greene at Gael's 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 in the Macy's building at Herald... http://fb.me/1bPQCOXcx     
    
    
    @jacquestorres Had your chocolates last night from the goodie bag at Gael Greene's birthday party.  Delicious!!    
    
    
    @HillaryClinton @tomcolicchio Keep up the good fight!  People need you.  Saw you on MSNBC, Tom.  Great appearance.  Abrazos, G    
    
    
    Gerry Dawes and Gael Greene at her 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 in the Macy's building at Herald Square, NYC,... http://fb.me/1WOTpEBdE     
    
    
    Karen Page, Kathleen Balun and Andrew Dornenburg at Gael Greene's 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 Trattoria in... http://fb.me/2jUdVBk56     
    
    
    Gael Greene with a piece of her birthday cake at her 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 Trattoria in the Macy's... http://fb.me/2A8WmgRgO     
    
    
    Janice Mehlman, sculptor Ron Mehlman and Gael Greene (please wear red!) at Gael's 80th Birthday Party at Stella... http://fb.me/1b3pDYZYF     
    
    
    @GaelGreene Michael Whiteman, Rozanne Gold and Tim Zagat at Gael Greene's 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 Trattoria http://fb.me/RJ83TaVv     
    
    
    Sculptor Ron Mehlman and actress Kathleen Turner, emcee for the tribute to Gael, at Gael Greene's 80th Birthday... http://fb.me/1fkakrZU6     
    
    
    Some new additions to my Photo Gallery of American Chefs and Food Personalities. http://fb.me/2JcZme5RB     
    
    
    Some more new additions to my Photographic Gallery of Spanish Chefs & Food Personalities. http://fb.me/6D2xKEUdx     
    
    
    Karen Page, Barry Wine and his fiancee Maryann Hoffman, and Andrew Dornenburg at Gael Greene's 80th Birthday... http://fb.me/1xkTfOhjg     
    
    
    Dorothy Kretchmer and Kathleen Balun at Gael Greene's 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 Trattoria in the Macy's... http://fb.me/1dtTseWOT     
    
    
    Sculptor Ron Mehlman and Kathleen Balun at Gael Green's 80th Birthday Party at Stella 34 Trattoria in the Macy's... http://fb.me/QcBmXiwv     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2Xz65GTLI     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3j5lCOyv0     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2AitSrJOY     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1c0EYxzlA     
    
    
    What a hoot! http://fb.me/6ipENYzjT     
    
    
    http://fb.me/Zu3jjzGK     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3ci9TRh1M     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3vGB0VlmA     
    
    
    @meigul Adventures with Ambrosio Molinos, Maestro Cheesemaker and Subject of Michael Paterniti's "The Telling Room" http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013_09_01_archive.html …    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2ZFbxiEFb     
    
    
    http://fb.me/QXfdWVOY     
    
    
    Rice dish with gambitas, small shrimp, and fish at La Taberna del Gourmet in Alicante. http://fb.me/2z8BRqI6l     
    
    
        
    
    
    Apparently, although he bashes the law day in and day out, Marco Rubio loves the new benefits of Obamacare... http://fb.me/1VZufSOSv     
    
    
    A homeless dog living in a trash pile gets rescued, and then does something amazing http://fb.me/2PrYilTGL     
    
    
    Pennsylvania Judge Sentenced For 28 Years For Selling Kids to the Prison System.  Is there a spot in Hell hot... http://fb.me/OyBIHoCa     
    
    
    Drew Nieporent, Daniel Boulud, Paul Bartolotto, JBF Awards 2010. http://fb.me/6lP9SpY8v     
    
    
    Ventresca de bonito con piquillos (tuna belly with piquillo peppers), on the terrace of Hotel El Puerto, Mundaka,... http://fb.me/2Owc6gLyG     
    
    
    Anchoas (house-cured anchovies) and txakoli,on the terrace of Hotel El Puerto, Mundaka, Vizkaya, Basque Country,... http://fb.me/364MVHKRN     
    
    
    Salmonetes (red mullet) bought at the fish market at Mundaka, cooked a la parilla over hot coals at Juana... http://fb.me/6pHySMLTT     
    
    
    Begi ondi (calamares con ojo grande / "big-eyed" squid) bought at the fish market at Mundaka, cooked a la parilla... http://fb.me/18x5kPqML     
    
    
    Boquerones en vinagre-aceite (fresh anchovies cured in vinegar and oil) Restaurante Serrantes II, Bilbao. http://fb.me/RyOmvoZ5     
    
    
    Calamar with peppers and squid ink sauce, Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/2yBmzBGAO     
    
    
    Huevo (egg) over piquillo peppers, Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/2xkhlnl2I     
    
    
    Foraged setas / hongos (mushrooms), Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/26DabBn3G     
    
    
    Pochas (beans) con almejas (clams), Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/2dOEldadp     
    
    
    Guindillas, the classic condiment for pochas, Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/2xnSLHH7C     
    
    
    Mikel Bustinza, owner, Horma Ondo, and Pepe
Barrena, Founder-Director of CineGourLand, with a Chuletón (rib-eye... http://fb.me/1PF9PYFBM     
    
    
    Chuletón (rib-eye steak) on a grill brought to the table, Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia,... http://fb.me/2REkBe9fQ     
    
    
    A slice of chuletón (rib-eye steak) on a grill brought to the table, Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa,... http://fb.me/VCYl0tLU     
    
    
    Chuletón (rib-eye steak) on a grill brought to the table, Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia,... http://fb.me/2ZSluK54v     
    
    
    Mikel Bustinza, owner, Horma Ondo, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/1upsp0B7W     
    
    
    Later that evening a group of us were treated to a veggie dinner.  Frying pimientos del Padrón, Caserio Legina... http://fb.me/2NBq1Q7Vn     
    
    
    Pochas, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/17bpCIk5p     
    
    
    Veggie dinner for friends at Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/2AIRhrr9J     
    
    
    Veggie dinner for friends, cebolletas (scallions), Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/19VcG0FwI     
    
    
    Veggie dinner, tomatoes at Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/6lutMgszc     
    
    
    Veggie dinner, cogollos de Tudela, Romaine lettuce hearts, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/29RKsmpfV     
    
    
    Veggie dinner for friends, cebolletas (scallions) with Maldon salt, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia,... http://fb.me/6qizN1RD7     
    
    
    Stewed cebollas (onions) at the evening veggie meal for guests, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/1d5VdAE6i     
    
    
    Pochas with borrajas (borrage) at the evening veggie meal for guests, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia,... http://fb.me/Ql2XFvbM     
    
    
    Dessert, fresh picota cherries in ice water, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/6up6Cb5u3     
    
    
    The post-prandial Patxaran (house-made sloeberry anisette) Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/2SWdWedL6     
    
    
    Javier, who cooked our evening veggie meal for guests, Caserio Legina Goikoa, Larrabetzu, Bizkaia, Spain. http://fb.me/1dGVNwXnT     
    
    
    Dawn on a winter morning, West Patterson, Putnam County, New York. The tundra in Putnam County, New York is now... http://fb.me/1TsFvHvmB     
    
    
    God to know that The New York Times is quoting unidentified experts on the economy about the impact of Obamacare.... http://fb.me/3lrdYvocE     
    
    
    @thecaucus @nytimes This piece is junk journalism.  Who the Hell is Cat Ping of Indianapolis to say that Obamacare is wrecking the economy?    
    
    
    Fray Luis (Ponce) de León, statue in Cuenca, Castilla-La Mancha.  The Inquisition imprisioned Fray Luís, who was... http://fb.me/2TdEdOcRD     
    
    
    Joe Baum and George Lang.  Photo by Gerry Dawes, 1990s. http://fb.me/6BCH8iNkY     
    
    
    More photos to my gallery of American Chefs and Food Personalities added. http://fb.me/34VmoLt2Q     
    
    
    More photos added to my Gallery of American Chefs and Food Personalities. http://fb.me/6BZH9vshV     
    
    
    Adolfo García, Río Mar Restaurant, New Orleans, with calamares en su tinta, squid in its own ink. http://fb.me/2hGu9WedD     
    
    
    Chip Apperson, formerly owner of Shelby in New York, now owner of the High Hat Café in New Orleans. http://fb.me/356e3jIFT     
    
    
    Mark Miller at Coyote Cafe, Dec 29, 2009. http://fb.me/2KCjLV8jW     
    
    
    @ChefAdolfo  Hi, Adolfo, did you find the photos of you and Chip in the Gallery?  When are we doing another gig in NOLA?  I'm ready.    
    
    
    @ChefAdolfo  Adolfo García, Río Mar Restaurant, New Orleans, with calamares en su tinta, squid in its own ink. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/vMU7-t84c6h2nBaQ9QqdRwIGFAxM17eeKQZvYOk_au4?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Roque Garcia, Roque's Carnitas food cart parked in a corner of The Plaza in Santa Fe, New Mexico. http://fb.me/2uyCKn8px     
    
    
    James Campbell Caruso, Chef-owner, La Boca and La Boca Taberna Spanish Tapas Tavern in Santa Fe, New Mexico. http://fb.me/2awhlGfLx     
    
    
    Chip Apperson, formerly owner of Shelby in New York, now owner of Cecil's Hi-Hat Café in New Orleans. http://fb.me/156MLK5ol     
    
    
    The brilliant Roser Torras, the head of Grupo GSR and one of world's greatest organizers of gastronomic conferences. http://fb.me/17OQiwxyc     
    
    
    From architect Ricardo Bofill, in Mont-Rás (Girona), Spain. http://fb.me/2YKaWkCsj     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6vDqMWfpd     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2tRjpRsex     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1vV3mzrPN     
    
    
    "Pope Francis finally has had enough of the hypocrisy spewing from leaders in the Christian community, and is... http://fb.me/2H0U2BOmk     
    
    
    NY Post’s Racist ‘Obama Selfie’ Front Page Goes Too Far (The Lower Than Snake Shit Club's official new rag stoops... http://fb.me/3rF5fN4Ax     
    
    
    This one is a hoot! http://fb.me/2EBl2Eofd     
    
    
    What Is Duck Dynasty and What Does It Have to Do With a Man's Anus? http://fb.me/2auXOKGnM     
    
    
    Basque chef Karlos Arguiñano, a major culinary television star in Spain, with the late Albert Asín of Pinotxo, the... http://fb.me/XksIJT35     
    
    
    Gerry Dawes and Melvyn Master (Jams), red socks, red shoes, City Meals on Wheels Birthday Dinner 1986,... http://fb.me/3lpGhn0wm     
    
    
    Melvyn and Jane Master, Jerry Goldstein (Acacia Winery), City Meals on Wheels Birthday Dinner 1986, Rockefeller... http://fb.me/12BVXCBSc     
    
    
    Melvyn and Jane Master, City Meals on Wheels Birthday Dinner 1986, Rockefeller Center. http://fb.me/6AEr5LS97     
    
    
    Gerry Dawes and Melvyn Master (Jams), red socks, red shoes, City Meals on Wheels Birthday Dinner 1986,... http://fb.me/6wWjeczA1     
    
    
    Chef Brendan Walsh (Arizona 206 / mentor Paula Wolfert), City Meals on Wheels Birthday Dinner 1986, Rockefeller... http://fb.me/125d3vNNi     
    
    
    Chef Brendan Walsh (Arizona 206 / mentor Paula Wolfert), City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner 1986,... http://fb.me/2SrOGHwNE     
    
    
    Chef Bradley Ogden basting a haunch of hog on a spit, City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner 1986,... http://fb.me/6iCsFEYvP     
    
    
    Chef Felipe Rojas Lombardi with 'Cheese Soup Posing as a Bread" at City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday... http://fb.me/17v4Z5Avh     
    
    
    Chef Paul Prudhomme, Paul's Louisiana Kitchen, Mentor Hazel Reed Purdhomme, at City Meals on Wheels James Beard... http://fb.me/25Bve59a5     
    
    
    Chef Jonathan Waxman, Jams, at City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner 1986, Rockefeller Center.  Photo... http://fb.me/18HIYckRg     
    
    
    Chef Paul Prudhomme, Paul's Louisiana Kitchen, and Melvyn Master, Jams, at City Meals on Wheels James Beard... http://fb.me/6zB23TPiu     
    
    
    Alice Waters, Chez Panisse and Cafe Fanny, Mentor Richard Olney, at City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday... http://fb.me/6ih1HXCgN     
    
    
    Chef Paul Prudhomme, Paul's Louisiana Kitchen, and television personality Al Rokkor at City Meals on Wheels James... http://fb.me/Psg5zUq2     
    
    
    Arcadia, Chefs Anne Rozenzweig and Andy Pforzheimer, at City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner,... http://fb.me/2vpde9rb3     
    
    
    Culinary Heaven! Pictures from the Paella Party for Carmencita with Bisila Bokoko, Gerry Dawes, and Chef Paul... http://fb.me/XCsg1oFF     
    
    
    Travel Spain with Gerry Dawes – January 12th-19th, 2014  gerrydawes@aol.com  A Chefs' / Serious Food... http://fb.me/6mxKi2wrb     
    
    
    Torta del Casar cheese: my friend and Spanish Food and Wine Guru, Gerry Dawes lovingly describes one of the best... http://fb.me/S2VZYibc     
    
    
    EO Agency's 7 Days, 7 Nights: Beyond Paella, A Video Culinary, Wine & Travel Adventure in Valencia & Alicante... http://fb.me/190cAaMWP     
    
    
    http://fb.me/YNvjrWfU     
    
    
    Dear Phil (duck dynasty) Robertson, (who has been defended by both Sarah Palin [off at a Mensa meeting again?]... http://fb.me/20OLn7vBT     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6iHEPgfJZ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/RIr3GQAB     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2tE3kL5yP     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1cRevTjre     
    
    
    The great, as in great, Danny Meyer. http://fb.me/3dkf7SKzf     
    
    
    Christian Escriba, the Catalan postres maestro, works his magic with turrones. http://fb.me/2wConVt68     
    
    
    Chef Paul Prudhomme, Paul's Louisiana Kitchen, at City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner, Rockefeller... http://fb.me/RoRIcV3n     
    
    
    Arcadia, Chefs Anne Rozenzweig and Andy Pforzheimer, at City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner,... http://fb.me/6zR79susE     
    
    
    Chef From Hell Tom Valenti, Alison on Dominick, Share Our Strength,  World Yacht April 1991. http://fb.me/2XCn3M2C7     
    
    
    Fred Reno, William Hilll Winery, and Chef From Hell Anne Rosenzweig, Share Our Strength World Yacht April 1991. http://fb.me/35bL4qvvU     
    
    
    Felidia Bastianich, Felidia Ristorante,  Share Our Strength World Yacht April 1991. http://fb.me/U3KAKrkG     
    
    
    Chef From Hell Rick Moonen, The Water Club, Share Our Strength World Yacht April 1991. http://fb.me/27EEYBPX3     
    
    
    Edna Lewis, City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner, Rockefeller Center, June 1991. http://fb.me/2F7Vk7E6M     
    
    
    Jonathan Waxman, Jams, City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner, Rockefeller Center, June 1991. http://fb.me/21u1D2QnL     
    
    
    Paul Prudhomme and Alice Waters, City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner, Rockefeller Center, NYC.  June... http://fb.me/6pjFxy4MB     
    
    
    New York Times Food Writer Florence Fabricant and David Keh (Auntie Yuan), City Meals on Wheels James Beard... http://fb.me/2fnuLGRr4     
    
    
    Gerry Dawes with a bottle of William Hill Chardonnay, City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner, June... http://fb.me/2dzK5SL9l     
    
    
    Joe Baum and Chef Gerard Pangaud, Aurora Restaurant, City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner, June 1986,... http://fb.me/6z3hze3Mt     
    
    
    Amazing, see the Duck Dynasty clan as they really are.  It is all a show, folks, one that makes them very rich... http://fb.me/6liTMISAF     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2VKC9ONLZ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2XQ5A3wnI     
    
    
    Found this in my storage boxes.  It is a poem I wrote about my daughter, Elena, who was playing Little League... http://fb.me/13JWEf458     
    
    
    My daughter Elena Laura Courtney Dawes was so eager to come into the world that she showed up in the middle of... http://fb.me/33OTtN29L     
    
    
    NYPD Officers George Repetti and Mario Russo with Elena Dawes, in whose birth at home on Feb. 27, 2013 these two... http://fb.me/2EqeRyGVV     
    
    
    NYPD Officers George Repetti and Mario Russo with Elena Dawes, whom they helped into the world, and Diana Valenti... http://fb.me/6lJhcCwnG     
    
    
    Elena Dawes Pollard http://fb.me/2BWw6RZj3     
    
    
    Duck Dynasty rules to live by:

76 things banned in Leviticus

Here’s chapter and verse on a more-or-less... http://fb.me/2Br8RcRvF     
    
    
    Thierry Rautureau, nicknamed The Chef In The Hat, is the chef/owner of Rover's and Luc Restaurants in Seattle,... http://fb.me/TnKeSkdA     
    
    
    Harold McGee, Alex Guarneschelli and Bobby Flay at Chef's Night Out, Chelsea Market, May 8, 2011. http://fb.me/2HFm8nGMF     
    
    
    Mike Mills of 17th Street Bar & Grill/Memphis Bar & Grill with Calvin Trillin at the Snapple Big Apple Barbecue... http://fb.me/2ArrL0GNT     
    
    
    Please follow me on Pinterest.  Lots of interesting shots from here and from Spain. http://fb.me/1ckDAgyvj     
    
    
    Melvyn Master gets a Champagne dousing, City Meals on Wheels James Beard Birthday Dinner. Rockefeller Center,... http://fb.me/2KJUsa9QI     
    
    
    Pope Francis Rails Against Conservative Christians’ Superiority Complex (VIDEO) http://fb.me/2X2BffggC     
    
    
    The Joseph Report: Fools and their money - thoughts on wine fakery & the Rudy Kurniawan case http://fb.me/13QuhGBie     
    
    
    The Saga of Justine Sacco, Twitter's Accidental Racist
Hi, I'm white and I'm brilliant.  Tweet, tweet. http://fb.me/11tvVloHr     
    
    
    The legendary Matador Manuel Benitez, El Cordobés (subject of 'Or I'll Dress You in Mourning'), and Alfonso... http://fb.me/6Rvi7kKur     
    
    
    http://fb.me/Rd65UZQi     
    
    
    http://fb.me/QdkWq502     
    
    
    Wine's brave new world is vintage Lynch http://fb.me/AwEdrrZe     
    
    
        
    
    
    This situation exists because Congress has been bribed to let the airlines get away with it. I will not fly... http://fb.me/1dUsMVP9k     
    
    
    My daughter, Elena's cioppino on Christmas Eve!! http://fb.me/1etjZNnMj     
    
    
    Much love to all my family and friends on Christmas Eve from Kay and me.    
    
    
    Without a Catalan cagader in your nativity scene, in Catalunya it just ain't Christmas. Cagader figure shitting a... http://fb.me/ArPYCjFw     
    
    
    http://fb.me/124JN7yvi     
    
    
    Kay Balun with ajo blanco, white almond-garlic gazpacho, at outdoor terrace cafe at Casa Ortega in Ronda, Oct.... http://fb.me/1P9W81ByV     
    
    
    Shades of Doctor Zhivago. Dawn on a winter morning, West Patterson, Putnam County, New York. http://fb.me/SDjdYwIN     
    
    
    I always try to take the first picture with a new camera or a new lens of Kay.  The first photo from my new Canon... http://fb.me/2PtSqdP7o     
    
    
    Enough of a dusting of snow on Christmas Eve to make for a White Christmas.  Patterson, Putnam County, NY. http://fb.me/6j4KE35ft     
    
    
    Kay Balun, Brad Haskel, Pilar Haskel, Robert Balun, Bianca Boragi and Jessica Balun with Pol Roger Champagne,... http://fb.me/356N1qa19     
    
    
    Family Christmas in Patterson, NY.  Kay, Jessica, Bianca and Robert. http://fb.me/3ctPlkn0N     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Setas con puerros y piquillo, Hidalgo Extra Viejo Oloroso Sherry (mushrooms with leeks, piquillo... http://fb.me/1IwnlAYex     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Shrimp, clams, fish, leeks, garlic and white wine over pasta triangles filled with goat cheese... http://fb.me/6rZ5OK5NC     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Christmas brunch frittata / torilla con puerros (leeks), patatas, calabacín (zucchini),... http://fb.me/1Bbt9QaeI     
    
    
    Christmas Eve, Kay and Gerry's, Patterson, New York.  A torchon of foie gras, topped with fig gelée brought by... http://fb.me/2DX0yzYf4     
    
    
    Moulin Touchais Anjou 1964, very old Loire Valley white wine, superb paired which the torchon de foie gras.... http://fb.me/2z1NwZZ7Y     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Ceviche with shrimp, langoustine tails and mussels with leeks, jalapeños, avocado, habaneros,... http://fb.me/28Z4gFGol     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Chuletas de cordero al la parilla, grilled lamb chops, Christmas Eve at Kay and Gerry's,... http://fb.me/1ze96A7ZS     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Chuletas de cordero al la parilla, grilled lamb chops with duck egg ailioli.   Christmas Eve at... http://fb.me/6BXePNRkO     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Chuletas de cordero al la parrilla, grilled lamb chops, Christmas Eve at Kay and Gerry's,... http://fb.me/T8ZEHAxc     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Chuletas de cordero al la parrilla, grilled lamb chops with duck egg ailioli.  Christmas Eve at... http://fb.me/2WkW0fNQe     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Steamed, cubed celery root with sauteed celery and leeks to accompany the grilled lamb chops.... http://fb.me/2fL9pkOFL     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2xYdaqynR     
    
    
    http://fb.me/14pfs4RKV     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1dKdB32M0     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2OtZv63b3     
    
    
    Journalists Win $3.75 Million Settlement Against Sheriff Joe Arpaio For False Arrests http://fb.me/12MPvVFcG     
    
    
    @howardggoldberg  No twas the short arm of my friend, Haskel the Jew, who helped make the sinful shellfish.  Good thing there was no pork.    
    
    
    Bodegón con Peces, Still Life with Fish, Luís Meléndez 1772. http://fb.me/18RupUTZs     
    
    
    National Gallery of Art. Bodegón caja de dulce, rosca y  otras objetos, Still Life of Sweetmeats box, pan de... http://fb.me/10xun412S     
    
    
    Having seen both "American Hustle" and, especially, "The Wolf of Wall Street," this week, two examples of who the... http://fb.me/2sK3IsoDE     
    
    
    Because they keep on, through gerrymandering and ignorance, voting against their own best interests and keep... http://fb.me/ZueUHZ7n     
    
    
    http://fb.me/UKywefCU     
    
    
    Ohio Wife Torches Husband’s Truck After Getting Crock Pot and Cheap Lingerie for Xmas.  He bought himself a truck... http://fb.me/RmuhUZ9h     
    
    
    Serious recommendation.  If you want to stay in the Christmas / Holiday spirit, wait until after the holidays to... http://fb.me/2z3Dh2y5A     
    
    
    L'Escaleta in Cocentaina, Alicante gets its third Repsol 'sun."  Well deserved. http://fb.me/1LCsRnEAW     
    
    
        
    
    
    Or for a 24/7 view of 'American Hustle', 'Wolf of Wall Street (3 hours long!) and a riff on Jimmy Buffet's "Let's... http://fb.me/3wSSB6gpB     
    
    
    Bodegón de Fruta y Jarra, Still Life of Fruit (cherries and peaches) with a ceramics jar, Luís Meléndez c1765. http://fb.me/2eLPboDCO     
    
    
    Bringing new meaning to "Rockie Mountain High."  Colorado New Year’s expected to bring historic marijuana sales!... http://fb.me/2NCQkmeFj     
    
    
    This just in from the Cortez, Colorado Police Blotter, which is some of the best reading in America:  Tuesday,... http://fb.me/1RjpqYP69     
    
    
    Prado Museum. Bodegón Naranjas y Nueces, Still Life with Oranges and Walnuts, Luís Meléndez. http://fb.me/1aRvyYWV2     
    
    
    Damn that tragic case out in OH-HI-HO, home of John Boner, where that crockpot and crotchless panties gal burned... http://fb.me/6xjiDXtou     
    
    
    More news from between the coasts.  Friday the 13th indeed in the town of Dolores, Colorado where my daughter and... http://fb.me/2FkGpUt72     
    
    
    Speaking of great lyrics (and the great Lucinda Williams)! 

Lyrics to The Night's Too Long :
Sylvia was working... http://fb.me/13Z9G2Vwj     
    
    
    Ever have a relationship that made you feel like this Delbert McClinton song?  Had one once, but not now, thank... http://fb.me/2HUV4djj7     
    
    
    Still have a couple of spots left for chefs, culinarians and serious foodies on this marvelous culinary... http://fb.me/1LIMQEuT2     
    
    
    Saturday, Dec. 14 The Crime Wave in Cortez, Colorado Continues

From the Sheriff's Blotter:

An officer observed... http://fb.me/2QrZsEEMz     
    
    
    Flores fritas (fried "flowers), also called flor de azúcar (sugared flowers), made with flour, egg, sugar,... http://fb.me/2Hdy3DmhM     
    
    
    Panderia (bakery) offering pelotas de fraile,"priest's balls," the classic Castilian dessert leche frita... http://fb.me/XHd2LvoM     
    
    
    http://fb.me/33eo2RElq     
    
    
    Very proud to have been tapped by Michael Chiarello to take him and chef Ryan McIlwraith on a two-week... http://fb.me/3wvO4aEQq     
    
    
    Burgos, Spain in winter. http://fb.me/14ns6Vjlr     
    
    
    http://fb.me/18gy6Aw77     
    
    
    Shameful!! http://fb.me/YJVxjqrM     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2BOHbeyZH     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  Trader Joe's pasta triangles with goat cheese and sun-dried tomatoes, dressed with butter,... http://fb.me/6no2jq6HD     
    
    
    Final Police Report Tells Chilling Story Of Sandy Hook Murders http://fb.me/2AKQ4w0qy     
    
    
    An Open Letter to the Makers of The Wolf of Wall Street, and the Wolf Himself http://fb.me/YnLohRjL     
    
    
    Obamacare is projected to cut the national deficit by over $200 billion during its first 10 years and over $1... http://fb.me/1beMbj9xD     
    
    
    Being Eighty is Scary. But Forty Was fun. Times Two, Why Not? By Gael Greene, Insatiable Critic, Bite: My... http://fb.me/1UgfNNAkK     
    
    
    Makayla and Kay on a Dolphin fleet whale-seeking boat out of Provincetown, Cape Cod.  Jun 26, 2013. http://fb.me/3lk33Dufx     
    
    
    My grandaughter Makayla eating ice and mama Maria on a Dolphin fleet whale boat leaving Provincetown, Cape Cod.... http://fb.me/2yBM0e63G     
    
    
    http://fb.me/35BrSudEz     
    
    
    My buddy, John Sconzo, aka Docsonz, featured on Eater National with his 15 Best Dishes of 2013, two of which--the... http://fb.me/3hYpqMche     
    
    
    We Saw 'Wolf Of Wall Street' With A Bunch Of Wall Street Dudes And It Was Disturbing http://fb.me/2YTAKWw8I     
    
    
    Geometrical progression. http://fb.me/3gpxvO6RV     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6shQ24aLB     
    
    
    My great, long-time friend and soul buddy, Rozanne Gold, has a birthday today, Jan 1, 2014.  Happy Birthday.... http://fb.me/3EnRDoJTq     
    
    
    Happy New Year to all you crazy bastards, like Duck Dynasy tsar Phil Robertson.  What a disgraceful human being. http://fb.me/15pLSQ7Hz     
    
    
    Back to celebrating New Year's Eve with Kay and Pol Roger (every year since 1976).  Reading the stuff on Facebook makes me crazy!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday, Melanie Young.  Besos, Gerry Dawes    
    
    
        
    
    
    How A Wealthy, Clean-Cut 'Duck Dynasty' Tricked The World For Publicity http://fb.me/2Bsb9xcpL     
    
    
    Well, the New Year is off to a great start.  My shit Dell computer crashed on me in the middle of a post.  I had... http://fb.me/1u9nwj9Y3     
    
    
    Happy New Year 2014 / ¡Féliz Año Nuevo!  I hope all my friends and acquaintances on Facebook have a terrific,... http://fb.me/6CnE42Ijy     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2G7maQXiY     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3EJmoPPZH     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1gblezkd7     
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes:  New Year's Eve Dinner, bacalao (fresh cod), cooked with clams, white wine, garlic, scallions,... http://fb.me/19e0mSvIq     
    
    
    Aaron Rodgers: 'I'm Not Gay. I Really, Really Like Women'   But, he is into besitality, he sure screwed the... http://fb.me/1y7mPutJE     
    
    
    Commonwealth Club Taste of Spain 2013 Photos Madrid Oct 9 & 10.  Days one and two of the tour I led to Spain in... http://fb.me/6GJlDkr0E     
    
    
        
    
    
    International More: Iceland Fraud
Iceland Has Hired An Ex-Cop To Hunt Down The Bankers Who Wrecked Its Economy... http://fb.me/2BnFY6u7k     
    
    
    Commonwealth Club Taste of Spain 2013 La Mancha - Cordoba Oct 11 http://fb.me/12kqKB9g4     
    
    
    This evening I made a txangurro souffle, txangurro being an exceptional Basque crab dish of legend.  The base was... http://fb.me/6zpxab6lH     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2fiPUctPF     
    
    
    Some of my dishes cooked at home, in Boise, Idaho, Hilton Head, etc. http://fb.me/2Iy5MnuMm     
    
    
    Commonwealth Club Taste of Spain 2013 Photos Sevilla Oct 12 & 13.  More photos of the tour I led in October. http://fb.me/13B1A3Era     
    
    
        
    
    
    The New York Times, The Guardian Urge Obama To Help Edward Snowden http://fb.me/2C6l87dVZ     
    
    
    East Coast Could See More Than A Foot Of Snow During Winter Storm.  Oh, boy, can't wait!  Laying in firewood in... http://fb.me/6BNwpZVxZ     
    
    
    Again, proud to say that two of Docsconz's top 25 meals were at restaurants I took him to. http://fb.me/2XgFklDPA     
    
    
    Commonwealth Club Taste of Spain 2013 Photos Ronda Oct 16 http://fb.me/34ROXUbTK     
    
    
    The Wolves of Wall Street, The Ducks of Louisiana.  Now they have a line of guns "back to our roots", pre-civil... http://fb.me/6ydcQAvbC     
    
    
    Can't us the Norway Doorway, the sliding door to the deck, to keep my vino, hard cider, regular cider and cooking... http://fb.me/2gXAaFdZI     
    
    
    At 7 a.m., it is 4 degrees out with the wind howling, going even lower in temperature by this evening.  The good... http://fb.me/2OE4UPz5a     
    
    
    Photo by Gerry Dawes http://fb.me/OQjBFfi4     
    
    
    The blizzard (so far not as bad here as predicted, but the Arctic wind chill is now 8 below zero) of Jan. 2 & 3,... http://fb.me/6yWLPZoUS     
    
    
    Anyone for the fire pit?  The blizzard (so far not as bad here as predicted, but the Arctic wind chill is now 8... http://fb.me/2yj5mcAze     
    
    
        
    
    
    From Christmas / Gerry's Dishes:  Navel orange filled with orange cream sorbet, with a chocolate-Torres Licor de... http://fb.me/BdFYBfvj     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1Nov2XYkK     
    
    
    http://fb.me/RQf1ZTYp     
    
    
    http://fb.me/Yoc17MIQ     
    
    
    James Campbell Caruso's new tapas bar, Mas, in the Hotel Andaluz, Albuquerque. http://fb.me/2GdOdNj8B     
    
    
    http://fb.me/12mFXJWhq     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2zFHex8CU     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2Dsc3W7Sx     
    
    
    http://fb.me/10ag4F4At     
    
    
    http://fb.me/170p8FhUJ     
    
    
    Not to mention that this dickhead governor's company profits from drug testing. http://fb.me/6TnaEzfWY     
    
    
    Most Underreported Stories of 2013 http://fb.me/YRxPIpIZ     
    
    
    Commonwealth Club Taste of Spain 2013 Photos Granada Oct 17 & 18. http://fb.me/2mxG2wvgP     
    
    
        
    
    
    Commonwealth Club Taste of Spain 2013 Oro Bailen Olive Oil - Almagro - Toledo - Chinchon Oct 18-19 http://fb.me/6rQSkCTqC     
    
    
    "All of this is all wrong in ways that have all been explained before. So just a few brief observations:

1.... http://fb.me/6EI7D3HGD     
    
    
    Espana: Exploring the Flavors of Spain http://fb.me/O6QaXs39     
    
    
    Monday, high 49 degrees, low 2 degrees.  What the Hell is this?    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1g4R4kMns     
    
    
    http://fb.me/28W8m3lu1     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3FJKJTuYM     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6yFgCvX5k     
    
    
    http://fb.me/RuxYx0FK     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2mnhRFwZv     
    
    
    Thinking About Fast Food and Flavor http://huff.to/17NhAs6  via @HuffPostTaste    
    
    
    Man Sues Parker for Life ‘Wasted’ Drinking ‘Overpriced’ Wine http://tabletograve.com/man-sues-parker-life-wasted-drinking-overpriced-wine/ …    
    
    
    In Sanlucar de Barrameda at the Feria de Manzanilla with Javier Hidalgo of La Gitana. Eating toritillitas de camarones, salpicon de mariscos    
    
    
    And salmorejo, exceptional fried fish, stuffed squid.  Casa Bigote is better than ever, amazing food.    
    
    
    More reports coming from Barcelona, Priorat, Zaragoza, Navarra, La Rioja, Arlanza, Bierzo, amazing wine in Valdeorras, Ribeira Sacra . . .    
    
    
    More from Ribeiro, Riras Baixas, Madrid, Valencia, Alicante, Granada, Ronda and the Pueblos Blancos.    
    
    
    Gerry Dawes, Pat Martin of  Martin's Bar-B-Que Joint & Kay Balun at The  Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/njNg0iuJZFjIyR8R6Ef6QnEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Ribs at Blue Smoke, The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/L_aazfYsQZnqBciQknJjfXEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    John Sconzo, son Michael & pitmaster Kenny Callaghan, Blue Smoke & co-founder of The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013 https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/9b3NwW5J3pnpSXrrEnMvc3Eztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    One of the Roark family stars at Ubons, Yazoo City, MI  at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/xBnc9tRmL8c_0LpgKghftXEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mike 'Pappy' Emerson of Pappy's Smokehouse, St. Louis, MO at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/xdQsrhg9Nqd-Q3hLrmMF43Eztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Big Ed Mitchell of Mtichell's BBQ in North Carolina at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/wAbUPFAFZwZWQiDvIJNU5HEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    17th Street BBQ logo at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ljM2hTWE624lOxAVqQxo2nEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chef Michael Romano & Union Square Hospitality Grp Exec David Swinghamer at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/XpOQseYUGjwYds3gIoFJtXEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Dave Knight, owner of Ole Hickory BBQ Pits, with an Ole Hickory colleague at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/v3GhwT0RpBnwfhIsdtoUWnEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chris Lilly, Big Bob  Gibson's BBQ pours sauce on his chopped pork 'cue at The Big  Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/yUVLD2nHXMEUzAVo8RBTlnEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Patrick Martin, Martin's Bar-B-Que Joint, Nashville, John Sconzo & son Michael, Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/CGd0VPB1gPIsfrNuVapICnEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mike Mills,17th St. Bar & Grill / Memphis Champ BBQ working on a hog at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ECOS9J0gSm3KG-wz4JazRHEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @UbonsBBQ Hi, Folks, go to my Facebook.  I need an ID on the young Roark star wearing a straw hat.    
    
    
    Food Arts May 2013 Chiarello Article (Quoted about talking Michael Chiarello to Spain) https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/FoodArtsMay2013ChiarelloArticle?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCISOt8__kvutKg&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Skip Steele and Mike 'Pappy' Emerson at Pappy's Smokehouse tent at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/OelUX3byEyglvtxZUFgbb3Eztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Hare Krishna procession passing through pig smoke during The Big Apple BBQ Block Party,  NYC.   https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/JqJly0PTT1qlTeexJnG2MHEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    L. J. Sconzo, John Sconzo and Michael Sconzo at The Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, New York City.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/e2vhD2E1kYQjGDUmj5E1jXEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    A whole hog arriving on a forklift for Mike Mill's 17th St. Bar & Grill team, Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/shhATh7NtPMhamJU78rHI3Eztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mike Mills of 17th St. Bar & Grill / Memphis Championship Barbecue supervising the dissection of a hog, Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC    
    
    
    Photo Album, Big Apple Barbecue Block Party, NYC June 8, 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/NewYorkBigAppleBBQBlockPartyJune82013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCLfkw_nQicvDvAE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Top selling Menu Gerry Dawes 55 Euros for 8 yrs now, Taberna del Gourmet, Alicante.  Photo: Chef M. Jose San Roman  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/uTQETo2yDN1yM2UEjbLfjL9m8T4tOxHIuRjT9V6jQrc?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mike Mills, 17th St. Bar & Grill/Memphis Championship Barbecue  working on a hog, Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013 NYC https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/qoz0YHExnndA_kDhRpz8lHEztpli4x0DpRWQlrHHRAo?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Big Apple BBQ Block Party 2013, NYC Photo Album.
https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/NewYorkBigAppleBBQBlockPartyJune82013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCLfkw_nQicvDvAE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Albufera, Valencia, boat and crane. Photo copyright by Gerry Dawes 2012. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/0ZX6C54MQEQ_e04zBOLlNiW-4FQ9_L3FYeFBSaHY_-o?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Interview in Spanish in Cepas y Vinos, a new publication about Galician wines. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/CepasYVinosGaliciaInterview2013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCJ274uGMnd-7sgE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    A Morning's Pleasure: Running the Bulls at Pamplona (An Excerpt from Homage to Iberia by Gerry Dawes) http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2008/07/mornings-pleasure-running-bulls-at.html …    
    
    
    Pamplona Portraits from the Past: Alice Hall, Matt Carney, Big Dave Pierce, Joe Distler, Jimmy Hollander & More http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2012/01/pamplona-portraits-from-past-alice-hall.html …    
    
    
    Noel Chandler, The Champagne Count  San Fermín.  “It was amazing champagne.”  Ernest Hemingway, The Sun Also Rises  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2010/07/noel-chandler-champagne-count-of-san.html …    
    
    
    Highly Recommended Book: Pamplona--Running the Bulls, Bars and Barrios in Fiesta de San Fermín by Ray Mouton.  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2010/07/highly-recommended-book-pamplona.html …    
    
    
    Tiger lilly, Cushman Road, Patterson, New York. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/lntC_djmfaskF0JIbQLqD4ab0OOeafpwigF1Da603pM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chicory and tiger lilly, Cushman Road, Patterson, New York.  Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 / gerrydawes@aol.com. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ORUfafd1Spc3jsOKCImKQIab0OOeafpwigF1Da603pM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Dragonfly, Cushman Road, Patterson, New York.  Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 / gerrydawes@aol.com. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/XubGJXtaGBtmdOLQcdWoGYab0OOeafpwigF1Da603pM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Bee & wasp on a chicory flower, Mooney Hill Road, Patterson, NY. Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 / gerrydawes@aol.com. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/VTeduh7_Rou57h13OHsAOoab0OOeafpwigF1Da603pM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Patatas bravas at the original patatas bravas bar, Las Bravas. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/cvcId9JQeVvHBhHE_kxg4iIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Kay at one of the famous tile murals at Villa Rosa in Madrid, this one depicting the Roman bridge in Córdoba. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/CEOmGtUXTYA9CLZ4myMlvyIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Tile mural at La Chata, Cava Baja, Madrid.  Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 / gerrydawes@aol.com https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/7csTyAXMJ71eMPrXWQRJaiIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Tile mural at La Chata, Cava Baja, Madrid.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/zJQ657niVlj2X_EQCULWuCIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Balancing act, street performers, Puerta del Sol, Madrid.  It's a trick, don't ask!  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/Mdl7FXP2xagpKcopoWvgeCIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Kay Balun at Kilometer '0,' Puerta del Sol, Madrid.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/norA7WgZLTUXoICXPJG3TCIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Cafe con leche and chocolate con churros, Maestro Churrero, just off La Puerta del Sol, Madrid. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/p7yboslE_10Yg9NB2x6BhSIRtRn4jXRmWbWvU6QnlAM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Don Quixote and Sancho Panza approaching a table of food at an inn in La Mancha.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/XNAx_0dqssN_P5tbt9YEg6ciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Mural depicting two kitchen workers carrying roast suckling pig at La Balconada, Chinchón, Madrid province.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/9-XvxQJTSmB38dmB7vanpqciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Cochinillo asado, roast suckling pig at Casa Botín in Madrid.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/zMxWGz3eXqRO8-2cp1Nvc6ciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Iconic Wine & Food Experiences. Tasting albariño wine from the Bodegueros Artesanos in Galicia.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/mcBD7-XrD2uC1vCv8Z55gqciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @tomcolicchio @davidchang Langostinos & La Gitana Manzanilla, Sanlúcar de Barrameda. Chefs From Hell trip? https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/waqIECxZ64FtNpyHxqtylKciNlTkGYx5b59VNnivDF0?feat=directlink … …    
    
    
    Spain’s government: Another blow | The Economist http://econ.st/14UrDNh     
    
    
    A BS piece: Has Ferran Adrià Had a 'Catastrophic Effect on the Younger Generation of Chefs'? http://eater.cc/18aUE8w  via @Eater    
    
    
    The Genesis of The Spanish Artisan Wine Group & the Documentary Robert Parker's Bitch http://www.spanishartisanwinegroup.com/2011/12/parkers-bitch-movie-do-critics-still.html …    
    
    
    Adega Manuel Formigo Grand Cru Quality Treixadura-based White Wines from Ribeiro (Galicia) http://www.spanishartisanwinegroup.com/2011/08/adegas-manuel-formigo-grand-cru-quality_15.html …    
    
    
    Printable List of Monsanto Owned “Food” Producers | http://REALfarmacy.com  | Healthy News and Information http://po.st/zpyTSM  via @po_st    
    
    
    Portraits of Water-Walkers Bring the Magic — Without the Photoshop On Valencia's Albufera lagoon.  http://www.wired.com/rawfile/2013/07/cataloging-a-diversity-of-human-species-in-one-rural-area-of-spain/ …    
    
    
    @Lord_of_Q Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip  The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html …    
    
    
    @martinsbbq Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @DinoBBQNYC @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @17thstreetbbq @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @BlueSmokeBBQ @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @UbonsBBQ Hi, Garry, sorry about the multiple tweets.  A SNAFU on this end. My best, Gerry    
    
    
    @Food4SouthSoul Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    @ThePitMasterEdM @UbonsBBQ Barbecue Stars Exclusive Trip The Grand Jamón Ibérico & Pig Tasting Tour of Spain 2014 http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/barbecue-stars-exclusive-trip-grand.html … …    
    
    
    Madrid Classics: Lhardy, one of Madrid's greatest delicatessens.   Photo by Docsconz, John Sconzo. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/madrid-classics-lhardy-one-of-madrids.html …    
    
    
    @UbonsBBQ Garry, please get back ot me at gerrydawes@aol.com about the Spain BBQ tour.  Should be a phenomenal trip. Another view of pig.    
    
    
    Madrid Classic: Painting at the original Las Bravas, Madrid, the place where patatas bravas originated. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/madrid-classic-painting-at-original-las.html …    
    
    
    Al Andalus Train, Camino de Santiago Itinerary begins July 21.  1st stop, Zaragoza: Virgen del Pilar & Goya.  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/07/al-andalus-train-new-camino-de-santiago.html …    
    
    
    Back in Black - New York Versus Texas http://on.cc.com/13lGKzc  via @TheDailyShow    
    
    
    Quoted in Spain's financial crisis gobbling up top eateries By Harold Heckle July 22, 2013 http://www.businessweek.com/ap/2013-07-22/spains-financial-crisis-gobbling-up-top-eateries …    
    
    
    Weird being in the Santiago de Compostela train station tonight, sleeping on train..  No activity, but the train wreck just 3 kms. away.    
    
    
    Unbelievable that we were on a train in the station at Santiago the night of this horrific train crash. http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/07/24/spain-train-crash_n_3647580.html …    
    
    
    The 120mph Spanish train crash mystery: Why was the driver travelling at twice the recommended speed on bend? http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/the-120mph-spanish-train-crash-mystery-why-was-the-driver-travelling-at-twice-the-recommended-speed-on-bend-8732727.html …    
    
    
    Madrid classics, cochinillo asado (roast suckling pig) at Casa Botin, one of Ernest Hemingway's favorite restaurants https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo     
    
    
    From PBurgh: My beloved Pirates have taken FOUR of FOUR so far from the Redbirds, in 1st place by 2 1/2 games & best record in baseball.    
    
    
    Madrid Classics Barrio de Las Letras (Literary Quarter) - Gerry Dawes's Spain
http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2011/03/madrids-barrio-de-letras-literary.html …    
    
    
    Mejillones, mussels, plucked from the Galician rías.  On the Al Andalus Camino de Santiago Tren de Lujo adventure. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/_xIQgnrLKBdqZOufSZV4AB3EXA80NHvsu0OmSeoUuh4?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Update:  Heavenly Nights in Old Castile: Adventures with Ambrosio Molinos, of Michael Paterniti's "The Telling Room"  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/08/heavenly-nights-in-old-castile.html …    
    
    
    Iconic Spanish Dishes: Langostinos (prawns) de Sanlúcar de Barrameda with La Gitana manzanilla from Casa Bigote. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/-EEwm5_ybzYq77nNdZbKyNBJ-jBc0pODZfO6htD3xsM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Cigalas (Dublin Bay prawns) at the Mercado de San Miguel, Madrid. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/nfaif1mQdYpaDZHdr6HszdBJ-jBc0pODZfO6htD3xsM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Cigalas (Dublin Bay prawns) at a restaurant in Galicia.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/kLz6FB18sgUkwtuxPa-GjdBJ-jBc0pODZfO6htD3xsM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Santiaguiño, steamed Galician lobster- like crustacean with the cross of Santiago on its tail.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/IgTNJtzMC9sfkkcuziGQG9BJ-jBc0pODZfO6htD3xsM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Roberto Clemente plaque on the Roberto Clemente Bridge in Pittsburgh.  Photo by Gerry Dawes copyright 2013 https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/mGodkXz_fHOs2N8Z0Y5tDbxspYzsVr3W_XNjvyELGAU?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Salmorejo Cordobes with hard-cooked egg, Iberico ham & olive oil-fried eggplant strips). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/hsd2L1UwFdjAhG1uJBWiZVe1Lq4B48fgu4d7puEf-Bg?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Pittsburgh Pirates - Cardinals July 29 PNC Park.  1st of 5, won by Pirates. My first ever Pirates game in Pburgh.  https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/PittsburghPiratesCardinalsJuly292013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCOmb68aJ-bzpaw&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Raise the Jolly Roger, Pirates win again.  9-2 on a homestand for the 1st time since 2005. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/gr4CcsQ1JHz9OymqnX2jMbxspYzsVr3W_XNjvyELGAU?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Pittsburgh Monongahela Incline July 2013 https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/PittsburghMonongahelaInclineJuly2013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCLGJpd_Q1bfm3gE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Pittsburgh Duquesne Incline July 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/PittsburghDuquesneInclineJuly2013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCIu7-aPv99XwbA&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gin-tonic at sunset on the terrace of the Alhambra Palace Hotel in Granada. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/klxEpla5hJ5g7g53FCF7VTFWgSutTGVAlTZ-0AvDJUM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    In Ronda with my friend (seriously), the great Antonio Ordoñez, el maestro de Ronda. Photo by Kay Balun.
https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/gXdp3I-98wJZsb0CmtwqySPx82HuMEyujlS0Ja-4HrI?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    My sweetheart, Kay, in the shade of bougainvillea at Bodegas Hidalgo La Gitana, Sanlúcar de Barrameda.  May 2013. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/FhW29410UkKBydj-Vrew36QqajkXovVkp7pHFMjIz6w?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Flowers and scenes from walks on Cushman & Mooney Hill Roads, Patterson, Putnam County, New York.  Aug 4-12 2013.  https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/CushmanMooneyHillRoadsAug4122013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCK7y-YfjwrGkIg&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Vines, winery, San Andrés church and the Cantabrian mountains at Marqués de Riscal, El Ciego, La Rioja Alavesa.   https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/YsL4Y6PGgQXWMeECd7juaVkgLv6S_qpPX7tpDhWkMiE?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Heinz Ketchup bottle on the right center field fence at PNC Park, Pittsburgh. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/tvssAQNk_pYucc8woo3sM7xspYzsVr3W_XNjvyELGAU?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @howardggoldberg  For those of you barbarians who put ketchup instead of mustard on your hamburgers, I suppose.    
    
    
    Mike Paterniti's The Telling Room http://instagram.com/p/dAFMkQBXz6/     
    
    
    Mike Paterniti in The New York Times: An American Man’s Quest to Become an Old Castilian http://nyti.ms/15yV4Ve     
    
    
    Presa Ibérica (tender well-marbled shoulder cut of meat from Ibérico pigs). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/OGtSCZAD4uYN0zna1kAe66lnyKCiZyyMaJyjf35HCU0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Queso Pimentón de Cabra (goats’ milk cheese from Cáceres, Extremadura, with a Spanish paprika rind). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/qY7a5X4d4phZD_3l47tqUqlnyKCiZyyMaJyjf35HCU0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    2 minutes of truth: What happened to the middle class? From @RBReich (via @Upworthy) http://www.upworthy.com/you-may-not-have-heard-of-robert-reich-his-upcoming-movie-about-the-middle-class-will-change-that-5?g=2&c=upw1 …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes.  Breakfast: Fresh tomatoes and basil, coarse sea salt, Navarra EVOO, garlic, for ciabatta bread.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ZIEaXZLKiGtng0D6wsJNY5FOTgCobhLFgUGBuShcWM0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @VictordelaSerna Thanks, Victor, I had not fixed on the fact that it was Mingote's drawing. I will put that into the captions to reflect it    
    
    
    Madrid Classics:  Pavement plaques for long-time Madrid establishments. Lhardy, est. 1839, off La Puerta del Sol. 
https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/-is94b7GZgzB5BNtI2kR8mAHhFkzR5pPeMQLgyybn3k?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Galo, Restaurante De Galo, with lechazo asado, suckling lamb to be roasted. Covarrubias (Burgos). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/fdTn63-sC3xngHbN93A84ypSgDDI5HwGFpaZgIXlXBI?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Chimenea serrana, Restaurante De Galo. Covarrubias. The fire was in the middle with benches around the perimeter. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/TA1l3Ac_uwdj2zEU2NhuMypSgDDI5HwGFpaZgIXlXBI?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Lechazo (suckling lamb) going into the brick oven for roasting.  Restaurante De Galo. Covarrubias (Burgos).  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/XJ6ymzOcTcvakGPRoJDX4ypSgDDI5HwGFpaZgIXlXBI?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Two giants of Basque gastronomy, Pedro Subijana and Juan Mari Arzak, in Madrid, 2007. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/gCKBxWf0qpFnq8UBcyEVetMTjNZETYmyPJy0liipFm0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Fresh local tomatoes, house-grown basil, mozarella, sel de mar, Oro de Bailen EVOO, Sherry Vinegar. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/_XCGx3S-kJQUd1-4aXEzAFbwIpyWpYbqZwqDyHDoDFY?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Wild bay scalllops,  Sp. EVOO; corn-off-the-cob, red pepper, leeks, over farfalle D. Berna Godello. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/7I3x9HvJ3XVH2xbQidL8cVbwIpyWpYbqZwqDyHDoDFY?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry Dawes & John Ewing, drinking from a jug of Pacharan from Hartza restaurant. Sanfermines, 1995, Pamplona. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ILqU9pYblwLt9nZMkNLJO9icAJrfOVgjI0yBdSGm6ew?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    The Mihrab in Córdoba's Mezquita (former mosque during the Moorish occupation of Spain). https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/Dl6kXfR_aYG7lA9vEJsui-kSVegVj8GVcn-Pb3utXuM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Córdoba's Mezquita (former mosque during the Moorish occupation of Spain). Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/gpmTJa8J7cadUR84Q1mSoukSVegVj8GVcn-Pb3utXuM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Salmorejo with chopped jamón Ibérico and egg at Taberna Juan Peña, Córdoba. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/UbzISb64hnk6bKrXkk8DZukSVegVj8GVcn-Pb3utXuM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Churrasco, grilled pork loin, El Churrasco restaurant, Córdoba. Photo Gerry Dawes©2013 Canon 6D/Tokina 17-35mm f/4. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/wREq4s3I2y3W1n57Z1igNukSVegVj8GVcn-Pb3utXuM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Huevo marinero, shrimp, monkfish & manzanilla, brought bubbling with a fresh egg on top Casa Bigote, Sanlúcar. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/KKIoz9hBTl4WCg6vuwXEysHvSFRVqvsDoEqAitzGNjM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Very sorry to hear this morning of the passing of Penelope Casas, whose books on Spanish Cuisine paved the way. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/08/the-passing-of-great-spanish-food.html …    
    
    
    The Passing of the Great Spanish Food Writer Penelope Casas, Que Descanse en Paz. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/08/the-passing-of-great-spanish-food.html …    
    
    
    Viña Magaña Gran Reserva 1982 Navarra, Merlot-Cabernet blend, my cellar, 8- 18-2013.  In superb condition. 94 pts. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/J1_WRxJlYLhlg3pCvFDYvxVycQQnvHhvK395F25yb7c?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @MarthaStewart Want to talk about Spain and Spanish food.  Let me know and I will give you a call. Great season for gazpacho and salmorejo.    
    
    
    @KarenAndAndrew @GaelGreene Without Penny's books, American would have had no real reliable reference to Spanish cuisine back then.    
    
    
    @KarenAndAndrew @GaelGreene The Passing of the Great Spanish Food Writer Penelope Casas, Que Descanse en Paz. http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2013/08/the-passing-of-great-spanish-food.html … … Pix    
    
    
    Anniversary of the Death of Federico García Lorca, Murdered by Nationalist Forces,Granada on August 19, 1936.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/RWItUCT_SX6dcU60Hkp-crcjnLv4ylYY5AF4cVjakd8?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @Mike Paterniti @ChefChiarello Michael, a great book about my Spanish cheesemaker buddy, Ambrosio Molinos.  Mike Paterniti's a friend.    
    
    
    @MikePaterniti Here is the article about Penelope Casas, Mike.    
    
    
    @MikePaterniti Lorca    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Local tomatoes with lime-cilantro allioli, house basil, sal de mar gorda and Oro de Bailen EVOO.https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/3_073bZXgK_hDxTbpSTIxacGL0VspK5Be-JFM65SX0M?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Kay above the Sil River valley on the way to Seadur, where Pepe Rodríguez at O'Barreiro, produces a great Godello.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/2cWmpUlv2cIlChS9tFdo-Y32gL5Ril4kxzbmn-wTU0c?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Empanada at Pepe Rodríguez's cave at Adegas O'Barreiro, Valdeorras. Pepe makes a great terroir-driven Godello. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/3EeUE4DaZnfnkm0n7o7o1o32gL5Ril4kxzbmn-wTU0c?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Ribeira Sacra: Perfect Lunch at O Grelo: Tomatoes, Tetilla cheese, zamburiñas al horno (small scallops) & Godello.  http://www.gerrydawesspain.com/2009/07/ribeira-sacra-perfect-lunch-with.html …    
    
    
    The Many Faces of Ferran Adria: Photos taken over the past 17 years. Photo by Gerry Dawes©2013 (Pinterest) http://pinterest.com/gerrydawes/the-many-faces-of-ferran-adria-photos-taken-over-t/ …    
    
    
    More Spanish cheeses, cheesemakers, cows, goats, Gamoneu, Cabrales, La Peral and more. (Pinterest)  http://pinterest.com/gerrydawes/spanish-cheeses/ …    
    
    
    @RandallGrahm Especially when there is no window you can open for fresh air.  Have to use it sometimes, seldom, rather not. Hate canned air    
    
    
    @RandallGrahm Earplugs!! ;-)    
    
    
    Baby goats being fed by Jesús Gútierrez at la Chivita, Asturias. Photograph by Gerry Dawes©2010.   https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/_YXIhXzeJoyGtsOuaXTDPX0Sy_14ewguUWEup6VIzD4?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    More Spanish Cheeses: Spain has a wide variety of superb cheeses made from the milk of cows, sheep and goats. http://pinterest.com/gerrydawes/spanish-cheeses/ …    
    
    
    @17thstreetbbq @bpwise De nada!    
    
    
    The Many Faces of Ferran Adria:  Photos taken over the past 17 years by Gerry Dawes http://pinterest.com/gerrydawes/ ...    
    
    
    Malaga's traditional wines and wine bars http://www.spain-holiday.com/Malaga-city/articles/malagas-traditional-wines-and-wine-bars …    
    
    
    Pinchos, or tapas, on the bar at The Basque Market in the Basque Block section of downtown Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/q9AvnRlN2Us-CdGggqRbmVQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Basque mural in the Basque Block section of downtown Boise, Idaho.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/MPpdFiTZHSC2SrrN81NDflQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Pavement stone with the music to the song, Gernikado Arbola (Tree of Gernika), Basque Block section of Boise, Idaho  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/xdEd3vQCuyiUvdXrRZHc41QEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Bilbao Brand Chorizo, cured meats at The Basque Market in the Basque Block section of downtown Boise, Idaho.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/0d4QVepJdSb3zGpEOUN401QEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    The Basque Market, a store specializing in products from Iberian Peninsula, Basque Block section of Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/0bAtaN4IRuqoNEvtISiUEFQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Idaho trout in corn meal and Spanish olive oil with pieces of local smoked bacon in the belly, Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/A7og6XDUHAK5h5WXybn_MCoqfRzQ8Pnh3_ug7K-QiQA?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Gerry's Dishes: Cooking Idaho trout in corn meal & Spanish olive oil w/ local smoked bacon, Bon Hartline's, Idaho.  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/bnavCjJS8YI_ope5f1K-KSoqfRzQ8Pnh3_ug7K-QiQA?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Jamones de Joselito y Ferran Adria.  Can't wait to see this.  Joselito Jamon Lab with Ferran. http://vimeo.com/jamonjoselito/httpvimeocomjoselitolabteaser …    
    
    
    My buddy  El Jay Sconzo drinking red wine from a porrón in Barcelona, May 2013 - - at breakfast!  https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/2DMz2elM3lJsQjZHXLovhCGOyIhszzSxF_mq_5PQp-0?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Excellent "secret recipe" deviled crab at Daufuskie Island Crab Company, Daufuskie Island, South Carolina. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo     
    
    
    Went to Paula Deen's the Lady & Sons in Savannah and she came out to greet me personally, as you can see. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/HLFjhOPmjDNShKQkS5zpjJV3wX6xh-Vpa2MngNDhNrk?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    @chefjoseandres @HHFoundation !Enhorabuena, Jose!!!    
    
    
    Jim 'N Nick's Bar-B-Q, Bluffton, South Carolina. https://picasaweb.google.com/112779314756438115778/JimNNicksBarBQBlufftonSouthCarolina942013?authuser=0&authkey=Gv1sRgCNDwyr6_le2pzAE&feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Bar Gernika, in the Basque Block section of downtown Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/2GXUpUy0k2pLWppRuz2gKVQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    Paella in the street in the Basque Block section of Boise, Idaho. https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/iF3Tx4j0lknmPCF85JKEEVQEHJaiwIpHUB7oMZgwmbM?feat=directlink …    
    
    
    