At a party full of models. I'm eating a burger. #happy4th    
    
    
    I love when @JohnWMcCarthy tells me that these fashion models aren't as skinny or pretty as me. #keeper    
    
    
    I am so homesick.    
    
    
    How I got dragged out of bed for breakfast this morning is a miracle.    
    
    
    I'm at Pete's Diner (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/17S3ojH     
    
    
    This day: 👎    
    
    
    The flag on the Shrine is actually shredded. Someone end the fortnight and take the poor thing down. COME ON.    
    
    
    I can really only be lured out of bed at 4am for fishing trips. Or like work or something but it's Saturdayyyyyy 😎😁🎣🍻🚤    
    
    
    I'm at Breezy Point Beach and Campground (Chesapeake Beach, MD) http://4sq.com/128I3hD     
    
    
    Just cleaning while watching wedding shows.. Listening to men say their wives are "fun goin. down ta earf."    
    
    
    @caroline_mac4 stop knocking her hustle    
    
    
    Miss America and all related pageants are everything that's wrong with this country and the women in it.    
    
    
    I'm at The John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts - @kencen (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/12zDqNy     
    
    
    looking for vacuums on amazon because i'm a really cool and exciting adult.    
    
    
    Really missing my gym buddy @melanieee529 here in DC...    
    
    
    It's cute that you wait til 9 at night to answer my emails... when I'm no where near my office network and everyone's calendars. #BYE    
    
    
    I think I bleached every single thing in my apartment and now I can't breathe in here.    
    
    
    I keep puffing and getting rashes on my stomach from some food allergy? I'm not even worried I'm just excited about my first allergy.. 🎉😵    
    
    
    Yep, I wanted to be soaked and freezing all day. Thanks for that, DC.    
    
    
    And my skirt is see through. Heyyyyyy.    
    
    
    @mikejpratt my office is about 20 degrees :(    
    
    
    @mikejpratt it deserves the blame for making me soaked in the first place. There was sun out when I left my apartment. 🌞    
    
    
    @chrisconsalvy there is nothing worse than when that lemon doesn't come. or when it comes in a large glass of pepsi..    
    
    
    Twitter and snapchat are making me feel bad for every human trying to take the metro. #woof    
    
    
    ☺👍    
    
    
    Just had popcorn cut out of my diet so I'm probably going to cry all day.    
    
    
    Long phone calls with my dad make me so so so homesick 😢✈🏡    
    
    
    @Olivianuzzi JUSTICE FOR TRAYVON    
    
    
    I CANNOT believe I'm missing @RyanCabrera tonight in stamf at @AliveAtFiveCT #hatingmyself    
    
    
    RYAN. CABRERA. HOW DID I MESS THIS UP?    
    
    
    Know what doesn't fit? Your suit jacket that's coming up over your belly button.    
    
    
    Very serious business meeting. (at @Caribou_Coffee) http://4sq.com/15kFCKL     
    
    
    I'm at Elephant & Castle Pub and Restaurant (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/135YuKz     
    
    
    Hey Stamford none of you instagrammed Ryan Cabrera so naturally all of our friendships are hereby suspended.    
    
    
    Shark Week is so close yet so far...    
    
    
    Chrons Disease is like having every eating disorder at once.    
    
    
    @Olivianuzzi with trayvon...    
    
    
    Happy happy birthday to @jlewDistrict ! #newevangelization    
    
    
    I'm at Maryland State House (Annapolis, MD) http://4sq.com/1duXFRz     
    
    
    Heyo (@ Annapolis Irish Festival - @annapirishfest w/ 18 others) http://4sq.com/13dJ86G     
    
    
    I'm at Lost Society w/ @johnwmccarthy http://4sq.com/10TYile     
    
    
    "What are you doing later? Text me, I might need a ride." -@31Murray genuinely wants to hang out...    
    
    
    A day of adventure and Advil for @KaitlinSchiele 's first mani/pedi! #goteam    
    
    
    I always want pink nail polish on my toes and then I remember that I think it makes them look fat 😡    
    
    
    Death by milkshakes.    
    
    
    I followed the Zimmerman trial the whole time and NO ONE wanted to talk with me about it. NOW no one will shut up..and I wish everyone would    
    
    
    So proud of little @Armaine4 going off to face the big working world in her little pink sweater! Missing you alreadyyyy.    
    
    
    Between @mint and @trello my life has become completely app dependent.    
    
    
    At some point all of my friends find it necessary to leave the country for long periods of time and I DON'T like it.    
    
    
    Sometimes you meet a pug named Hercules and it just makes your day.    
    
    
    I'm at Rayburn House Office Building (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/12tSwV9     
    
    
    Standing room only at the #competencyed briefing! -- friends on the Hill, come check out our tablet! pic.twitter.com/hGAIPqnwpz    
    
    
    Because I think I still work here. (@ Longworth House Office Building) http://4sq.com/17iW8fN     
    
    
    Full house at @DCYoungAdult Theology on Tap tonight with Fr. Greg Gresko! (@ Buffalo Billiards - @buffalobilldc) http://4sq.com/15Lu1qz     
    
    
    I'm the only person in the room that 100% doesn't think it's funny to dump your fiancée to become a priest. #sorry    
    
    
    Almost rear-ended the Secret Service. Gooooood morning Washington!    
    
    
    Pandora keeps giving me ads to "get a body that will make my ex cry"... Apparently my music selection screams fat and dumped.    
    
    
    I hate, always have hated, and always will hate, the song "Brown Eyed Girl". #butilovevanmorrison #dilemma    
    
    
    I GREW AN INCH SINCE HIGH SCHOOL! #model    
    
    
    Just when I thought Sen. Frank Lautenberg was the cutest human ever, I met his wife. ADORABLE AHHH.    
    
    
    Watching dads walk their kids to camp/school/whatever in the morning makes my day every day. SO CUTE.    
    
    
    How anyone can smoke cigarettes in this heat I'll never understand.    
    
    
    If you aren't drinking @Starbucks Peach Green Tea Lemonade, you're doing it wrong.    
    
    
    Pretty sure my life is about to get exponentially better now that I've ordered an ergonomic keyboard.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 and I talk about coffee and creamers all. day. long. #somanyflavors #solittletime    
    
    
    If you make lovey dovey lyrics your Facebook status and then tag your significant other, you need to do so much less.    
    
    
    I hate when I'm trying to send funny snapchats and the intern is judging me.    
    
    
    @Olivianuzzi @jaynuzz there is a lot of very important information on that site. i follow it religiously.    
    
    
    Congressman Trey Radel: Why I’m A Hip Hop Conservative http://www.buzzfeed.com/treyradel/trey-radel-hip-hop-conservative-ah8y … via @treyradel    
    
    
    What is this weird thunder situation?    
    
    
    I'm at @Cantina_Marina w/ @katrinamarie8 @lisettepylant @kaitlinschiele http://4sq.com/12M0Frs     
    
    
    I'm at Kastles Stadium at The Wharf (Washington, DC) w/ 8 others http://4sq.com/15MUMsm     
    
    
    Hey if you're at the Kastles game rambling about your expertise on all things DC in the row behind me please shut up. #PSA    
    
    
    Made a new friend.. @ Kastles Stadium at The Wharf http://instagram.com/p/b7Sea0guoe/     
    
    
    Best night of my life. @ Kastles Stadium at The Wharf http://instagram.com/p/b7fyN-guvR/     
    
    
    @meagan_prescott crackle on anyone's nails is not okay...    
    
    
    I'm at Kelly's Irish Times - @irishtimesdc w/ @johnwmccarthy @kaitlinschiele http://4sq.com/16OIHST     
    
    
    Watching "She's All That" for the first time ever..    
    
    
    I trip on these brick sidewalks every single day.    
    
    
    There is NOTHING better than the raspberry lemonade at Eastern Market.    
    
    
    I'm at @UnionMarketDc w/ @kaitlinschiele http://4sq.com/12WdxeJ     
    
    
    The dancing snapchat ghost is such a fun little guy.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 #hotcocoa #flannelpajamas ⛄    
    
    
    I seriously only come to work for the french vanilla coffee mate...    
    
    
    Trying to think of things I care about less than the royal baby... This is a tough one.    
    
    
    Unless the royal baby is named Angela then I don't care what it's name is going to be. #hearditherefirst    
    
    
    People judge when I keep my sunglasses on in metro tunnels but I'm just not tryna look atcha ✋    
    
    
    So the girl from Pitch Perfect is or isn't the girl from House of Cards?    
    
    
    There is no worse feeling than not being able to screenshot phenomenal snapchats.    
    
    
    @jayschaef lots of twitter activity between us lately. I think it's time for a reunion. #separationanxiety #mojitos    
    
    
    @ConnerGuyer just sent the snapchat video of the century.    
    
    
    I forgot to put on jewlery today and I literally feel naked.    
    
    
    Of all the emojis, I think I send the little knife the most 🔪    
    
    
    Just walking around like I'm all levels of challenged, scratching the mosquito but in my ankle while walking.. Heyyyy party people.    
    
    
    Dinner rendezvous at places I can't eat 😉(@ sweetgreen) http://4sq.com/11estn8     
    
    
    I'm at @HanksOysterBar (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/1c3MbGM     
    
    
    I'm at National Museum of Natural History - @nmnh (Washington, DC) w/ 14 others http://4sq.com/13e7XRh     
    
    
    The weather is flawless today in our nation's capital 😎🇺🇸    
    
    
    Wishing a very homesick happy birthday to my #1!  ❤ http://instagram.com/p/cMXUIMgulv/     
    
    
    I'm at The Front Page - @frontpagedc w/ @kaitlinschiele http://4sq.com/146n9Gu     
    
    
    @LisettePylant the thing is you have to see me with a crown at least 3 times a day.    
    
    
    Just cut my whole toe open on the exposed brick we love so much... @Armaine4    
    
    
    @jayschaef it's only 2:00! stay tuned.    
    
    
    @amytyburski incoming request, please hold.    
    
    
    @KatrinaMarie8 thank goodness you screenshotted that, i was particularly proud of that one.    
    
    
    But actually who in DC has never worked "at state" arghhhh shut upppppp.    
    
    
    Drive in movie night with some of the greatest people I know. http://instagram.com/p/cQB_jMAulG/     
    
    
    I'm at @UnionMarketDc w/ @kaitlinschiele http://4sq.com/14hPbYl     
    
    
    Uncle Jesse and Becky are THE cutest couple.    
    
    
    @DevenMcCarthy YOU'RE ADORABLE    
    
    
    @CaralineGrace literally Yankees twilight zone    
    
    
    "@AWSmith51 can you get out and help me with this windshield oil?" -@Armaine4    
    
    
    WHEN DID THE HILLS GO OFF NETFLIX? WHAT EVEN IS MY LIFE NOW?!    
    
    
    I'm going to die from inhaling gas fumes from this stove installation so bye cruel world.    
    
    
    There are a select few members of Congress that restore my faith in the government.    
    
    
    I definitely watch too many wedding shows but like why are there so many offensive dresses/ceremonies?    
    
    
    Mulan before bed is really never a bad idea. #teammushu    
    
    
    Mulan naming her dog "little brother" is effing weird.    
    
    
    I sing emotional songs when things happen in my life too and I guess I blame Disney.    
    
    
    Mulan cuts her hair with a sword and it looks better than mine ever does.    
    
    
    I think angsty tswift music makes me walk faster in the morning.    
    
    
    😖    
    
    
    I'm at One Judiciary Square (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/13vjEmQ     
    
    
    "Is anyone in here in HR?" "I'm familiar with the I9." Yes thank you we've all filled out that form, fearless leader. #teacherspet    
    
    
    Clearly the "helpdesk" doesn't understand that if I don't have access to Outlook I can do 0% of my job. But sure. Take your time.    
    
    
    I'm so over the DC government it's not even funny. YOU. ARE. FAKE. YOU ARE NOT A STATE.    
    
    
    I have the greatest boyfriend in all the land.    
    
    
    I'm at @1776Campus (Washington, DC) w/ 31 others http://4sq.com/13zsxvB     
    
    
    For your viewing pleasure @ 1776 Campus http://instagram.com/p/cfenEpAuqY/     
    
    
    Just missing one! http://instagram.com/p/cfghRpAut6/     
    
    
    @sweetkaroline91 NOT a mango Popsicle. #lossipop    
    
    
    @ohhemGINA 💔💔💔💔💔miss you every. single. day.    
    
    
    Today might be the day I become a DC resident 😖    
    
    
    @lyft is legitimately my new favorite thing. So glad they're in DC now! Much more affordable/enjoyable than taxis...    
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy "Duncan" ... Dunkin's classier older brother.    
    
    
    Somehow I end up circling the White House like once a week. The Secret Service isn't into it.    
    
    
    Am I still allowed to wear black nail polish now that I've graduated? #decisions    
    
    
    @Lcgilbert I have no words for this.    
    
    
    I'm at Pasara Restaurant and Lounge - @pasarathai (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/13MjPcu     
    
    
    SHARK WEEK!    
    
    
    For the next 7 days I have no desire to do anything but watch #sharkweek    
    
    
    #SharkWeek should revert to normal Discovery Channel at night so I can get some sleep. #sharkafterdark    
    
    
    Okay listen, I'm no expert (except I kind of am) but this megaladon is fake and is interfering with everything I love about #SharkWeek    
    
    
    If you fill shark infested water with bloody fish guts and then decide it's a good idea to swim and look for a dinosaur then you're a moron.    
    
    
    "there is nothing me and pandora can't do." - @Armaine4 is so inspirational.    
    
    
    There are reasons you're not supposed to watch The West Wing at work... Like when CJ's Secret Service lover gets killed and you start crying    
    
    
    Is this sore throat kidding? It's summer..    
    
    
    Maybe it's the Connecticut in me, but I don't think there's anything cuter than little huskies.    
    
    
    I have an uncanny ability to find the hot metro car.    
    
    
    @jayschaef i don't work in the capitol..    
    
    
    Entering a happy place now before I embark on a journey back to the northeast this afternoon. #trafficmagnet    
    
    
    @jayschaef I've been promised mojito reunions and you just never deliver.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 so THAT'S where you went...    
    
    
    Being romanced by @johnwmccarthy http://instagram.com/p/csmvesguli/     
    
    
    People actually yelling at each other over train seats. Oh northeast how I've missed you.    
    
    
    Business trips are a scam. It's 9:30 and I've already done like 3x the work I would have done in the office today.    
    
    
    Good morning New York! (@ New York Penn Station w/ 58 others) http://4sq.com/14jqorm     
    
    
    HOW CUTE ARE THESE GIRLS DRESSED LIKE THEIR AMERICAN DOLLS ON THEIR WAY TO THE STORE    
    
    
    I'm at Club Quarters Hotel (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/19akJZk     
    
    
    This cab driver hasn't been sober in years. He's definitely fun though.    
    
    
    I'm at @Amplify (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/13jVvj9     
    
    
    There are few things worse than when Excel decides to screw up at the end of your project. Go home, formulas, you're drunk.    
    
    
    When you ask to go to the upper east side you can pretty much rest assured you're gonna go the longest route possible. #profiling    
    
    
    Just saw my life flash before my eyes.    
    
    
    But really I'm never leaving (@ Club Quarters Hotel w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/13OwQ6r     
    
    
    I think if anyone checked my phone they'd think my boss was my best friend. We call, text, and email all day and all night.    
    
    
    🐷(@ Long Island Bagel Cafe - @libagelnyc w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/14o4PpE     
    
    
    I'm at @Amplify (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/1cOkvWE     
    
    
    I'm at @EastRiverFerry Terminal Wall Street/Pier 11 (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/19eOmss     
    
    
    I probably only like this hotel so much because they call me "Miss Chiappetta with the News Corporation" but I think that's a good reason.    
    
    
    I should be more afraid of sharks than I am. I just want to be their friend. #sharkweek    
    
    
    I want a pet hammerhead.    
    
    
    I can get cuisine from 4 different countries on the late night room service menu but I can't get ice cream..    
    
    
    The concierge offered to go out and get some but that's like slavery.. Is that even allowed? #adventuresingrowingup    
    
    
    I'm calling for Oprah's resignation.    
    
    
    2 hours of sleep really wasn't sufficient for all of the traveling I need to do today..    
    
    
    I'm at New York Penn Station (New York, NY) w/ 66 others http://4sq.com/1cQxk2Y     
    
    
    Say what you want about New Jersey, but the NJ Transit area is the nicest part of Penn Station.    
    
    
    Hey #njtransit I've done nothing but compliment you and now I'm trapped on some train in the middle of no where stopped WHAT IS YOUR DEAL?    
    
    
    This is the LAST time I drive to CT. You heard it here first.    
    
    
    Hey stamf long time no see 😎    
    
    
    Dad telling me about how he used to go to the "discotech" #home    
    
    
    Since the Super Bowl is in NJ this year and the @Patriots will obviously be there I'm gonna need some people to commit to coming with me...    
    
    
    You'd think going after going abroad I could handle east coast travel. Nope. I'm literally jet lagged.    
    
    
    @DevenMcCarthy that scenario is all I want for us. If the Giants can pull it off... Hope you're ready 😎🎉🏉    
    
    
    I literally cannot wait to go to Stew Leonard's today. #home    
    
    
    If there is ONE thing I miss about Stamford.. (@ Donut Delight) http://4sq.com/17EEa5G     
    
    
    Happy happy happy happy (@ South Norwalk Boat Club) http://4sq.com/11UnGI0     
    
    
    Newark 😷    
    
    
    295 traffic are you kidding? It's 10:30,..    
    
    
    Blasting country music on Bladensburg at night probably isn't the best idea..    
    
    
    The hardest part of having a roommate is waking up before them on a weekend and wanting to play. @armaine4 can we get up now pleaseeeee :)    
    
    
    Coffee and Baileys and bagels and eggs and champagne. Because we feel like vomiting today. @sweetkaroline91 @armaine4    
    
    
    Don't let @sweetkaroline91 tell you she's good at technology.    
    
    
    We've been to Safeway 3 times today.    
    
    
    A small child just ran up to me and pretended to shoot me. Welcome to Washington.    
    
    
    I'm really trying to go to Vegas but I'm saving up for Liechtenstein. #struggle    
    
    
    Also all I want is to see the Backstreet Boys this week. WHY is my life so expensive?    
    
    
    And naturally the day I need to be up early and have a 12 hour workday ahead of me I wake up with a sore throat.    
    
    
    @NETFLIX PUT THE HILLS AND LAGUNA BEACH BACK ON. IT'S ALL I EVER WANT TO GO HOME TO AT NIGHT. PLEASEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE.    
    
    
    @DevenMcCarthy it was never a thing.    
    
    
    I'm at @VidaFitnessDc (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/13vMrI7     
    
    
    "I took the night" just came on my workout playlist and I could cry from how much I miss @ohhemGINA    
    
    
    😣    
    
    
    I'm curled up in @Armaine4 's bed in all her piles of clothes she's packing. I'm literally a pet.    
    
    
    Trying to ease the pain of carbon monoxide poisoning. http://instagram.com/p/c7z3Izguvu/     
    
    
    You should get carded to buy sleepytime tea. It's actually a drug.    
    
    
    I'm infinitely more productive when I go to worry early with @Armaine4    
    
    
    It isn't very Catholic to steal people's ideas. JUST SAYING. It's probably not Catholic to passively tweet about it either but whatever.    
    
    
    It's funny that the people in my office are looking to me to move a bunch of furniture. Like actual desks. That's gonna be a no..#doityoself    
    
    
    Just bought car insurance and was told it'd be cheaper if I was 25 and/or married. AS IF BUYING INSURANCE DIDN'T MAKE ME FEEL OLD ENOUGH.    
    
    
    @jlewDistrict I have to work late and I need to fix the carbon monoxide in my apartment :( I'll be there next week!    
    
    
    I'm going to start attaching pictures of my boss' kids to emails when people are mean about him being away. #guilt #lethimplay    
    
    
    "If we lose power I am gonna hold my breath and kill myself"    
    
    
    Shmory shmooker    
    
    
    Should be an interesting day. (@ District of Columbia Department of Motor Vehicles - @dcdmv) http://4sq.com/18uAxBE     
    
    
    Can I get fake license plates the way people get fake IDs? Anybody know a guy? #adventuresatthedmv    
    
    
    ROUNDING HOUR 4 AND I'M NEXT IN LINE GO TEAM    
    
    
    I don't know who you need to bribe to be in the "H" line but I'll be an organ donor if they let me in that one.    
    
    
    When I'm done here I'm just going to cry all day from withdrawal. #CTFOREVER    
    
    
    It's car day. (@ Jiffy Lube) http://4sq.com/19tpJbN     
    
    
    I hate my new plates and I hate my new license and I hate the price of gas and oil and the tax on cars but I also hate the metro. #Positive    
    
    
    @jayschaef I may hate DC but no part of me wants to be a Maryland native. I also hate crab.    
    
    
    I'm at @CavaMezze (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/13liBeF     
    
    
    Whyyyyyyy must there be work emails at night? Well I'm not even bringing my work phone to Backstreet Boys tomorrow so HA. #leavemealone    
    
    
    Gas gods PLEASE let me have enough gas to get to NJ... I can't afford it anywhere else 🙏    
    
    
    @camBALLLLLIN duh anytime you want! I didn't know you were officially moved in!    
    
    
    Working remotely today and it's a lot less lonely than my office! http://instagram.com/p/dC8u_uAug8/     
    
    
    Enjoying my quarter life crisis by drinking 4Loko and seeing the BACKSTREET BOYS with @DevenMcCarthy    
    
    
    My level of excitement for backstreet boys is OMG OMG OMG    
    
    
    @johanaaa_gutie do you have lawn seats? Tryna see youuuuuu    
    
    
    I'm at PNC Bank Arts Center Park and Ride for Backstreet Boys+Jesse McCartney+DJ Pauly D (Holmdel, NJ) w/ 53 others http://4sq.com/13oxSLI     
    
    
    I don't even know what to do with myself because last night was the best night of my life.    
    
    
    I just remembered @DevenMcCarthy and I were doing the wop with strangers last night. No regrets.    
    
    
    The furniture salesman just told me my company's floor plans are sometimes "as useless as tits on a boar hog" ... Is that allowed?    
    
    
    Everyone I know is at the Pats game, John Mayer, or the Goo Goo Dolls/Matchbox 20 tonight. #whitegirlproblems    
    
    
    Omg @camBALLLLLIN I just got your josh groban snapchat and cried.    
    
    
    Wanted to make a comment about CT politics but I guess I don't get to do that anymore. I hate being a DC resident more and more each day.    
    
    
    @camBALLLLLIN truly a night to remember.    
    
    
    As I was putting my earrings in, I bumped into the dresser and a gavel fell on my foot. Just a gentle reminder I'm dating @JohnWMcCarthy    
    
    
    I'm at Asbury Park Boardwalk - @apboardwalk (Asbury Park, NJ) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/1cNPEfs     
    
    
    I think I'm in favor of climate change..    
    
    
    The universe doesn't want me to have a Lauren Conrad bow dress and I just don't know why    
    
    
    Pandora, when I type in Backstreet Boys WHAT makes you think I want to hear "No Strings Attached"?    
    
    
    I have absolutely no motivation to do any work today.    
    
    
    Seeing boots on cars gives me a horrible sinking feeling inside.    
    
    
    @itskevinblais gives me goosebumps    
    
    
    My formal apologies for bothering everyone at work today. You can blame the one email I'm waiting for that's holding me up.    
    
    
    I'm at @UnionPub (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/152T742     
    
    
    I can't tell you the last time I had a grilled cheese.    
    
    
    I don't think any of the Obama dogs are that cute. Just my unsolicited twitter opinion.    
    
    
    Just saw on @gregslistdc the @FONZNationalZoo rock and ROAR and I want NOTHING more than to go! http://gregslistdc.com/event/2013/rock-n-roar-acoustic-performance-oar …    
    
    
    @jayschaef remember when we were supposed to hang out today?    
    
    
    My whole face is puffy and pink and I'm convinced it's from carbon monoxide.    
    
    
    The people who live above me are having a drum and guitar circle in their meth lab.    
    
    
    Why I still walk to work when I can park in all of zone 6 is beyond me.    
    
    
    Our office supplier just told me the reason I don't know about cardboard boxes is because I probably just say "hubby, get to work" ... Oh.    
    
    
    The United States Postal Service is the most useless system this country has.    
    
    
    @USPS WHY ARE ALL OF YOUR DC OFFICES SO UNHELPFUL? Day ruined. And it's not even lunchtime.    
    
    
    NOOOOOOOOOOOO DON'T LEAVE ME (and yes I included the sad piece of paper when I mailed them back) http://instagram.com/p/dSGMW-guvI/     
    
    
    I have so many offensive things to say today that I feel like I should delete my social media.    
    
    
    Brb about to take a four hour lunch break.    
    
    
    "Isn't everyone in Italy old? Like isn't there no new life?" -@Prescigno is so cultured.    
    
    
    Between telling scary stories and watching SVU at work I'm officially afraid to even go outside. #movingtothemountains    
    
    
    Why is "Blurred Lines" so effing good?    
    
    
    I'm at The Front Page - @frontpagedc (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/15evA0f     
    
    
    @Prescigno WHAT ELSE CAN I DO WITH IT LEAVE ME ALONE    
    
    
    Backstreet Boys just came on at the bar and I felt the need to explain to everyone that the concert was the best night of my life..    
    
    
    Somehow @Prescigno thinks it's okay to pick policy fights every time he goes out...    
    
    
    Glory glory hallelujahhhhh (@ Thomas Foolery w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/19N4BgM     
    
    
    The only thing better than congressional parking in this city is a zone 6 sticker 👌    
    
    
    @APdubs @Prescigno hahaha I actually believe this was tweeted around the time of the fracking argument    
    
    
    Meanwhile, someone in front of Union Station just asked me which way the Capitol is.....    
    
    
    Had to order a gift from @TiffanyAndCo for work and now I can't get off the website. #nevergetsold    
    
    
    I know it's a group office happy hour but can I take the card and start first? I'm the only one done with my work...    
    
    
    I'm at Dubliner Restaurant & Pub - @dublinerpubdc (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/14MwFZQ     
    
    
    I'm at Lola's Barracks Bar & Grill - @lolasdc (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/1daY9S2     
    
    
    I never want to be the girl alone reading a book with wine at a bar on Friday night. That's all other nights in the privacy of my own home.    
    
    
    Just ordered a drink that makes my face shake.    
    
    
    I'm about 90% certain this is what roofies feel like.    
    
    
    All I want is a good bagel but those don't exist in DC.    
    
    
    @ohhemGINA EVERYTHING ABOUT THIS AHHHHHHHHHH    
    
    
    When blurred lines comes on I lose it 💃    
    
    
    @sendemtotheMORG they really do always get weird...    
    
    
    I'm at The Star and Shamrock - @starshamrock (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/1dFEbMZ     
    
    
    Good morning http://instagram.com/p/dcTz5jguku/     
    
    
    All the people on the VMAs are famous? Are we sure? #whoaretheteens    
    
    
    Lady Gaga looks like an egg hehe    
    
    
    Wait people are booing gaga? What's happening..    
    
    
    So many leggings on stage. Lotta spandex..    
    
    
    MILEYYYYYYYY    
    
    
    You can all hate on Miley but we've ALL been blackout tequila drunk before. It looks the same.    
    
    
    Meanwhile Rhianna is the biggest hater at the VMAs..    
    
    
    @armaine4 yelling at the TV that drake should be in a wheelchair..    
    
    
    "Throwing shade" I'm not sure what it means but I think we're throwing shade in this apartment. @Armaine4 @LisettePylant    
    
    
    @ohhemGINA we hate her.    
    
    
    @JillianMMT salty betches throwing shade    
    
    
    Know what hurts? When you scream into auto tune. Where's your kid?    
    
    
    @JillianMMT yeah where's your kid daddyo?    
    
    
    BYE RHIANNA.    
    
    
    YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS    
    
    
    NO TURN OFF SUIT AND TIE WHERE'S LANCE BASS WHERE'S CHRIS STOP IT BRING IT BACK NO NO NO    
    
    
    I've never hated Justin more than in this moment. BACKSTREET BOYS FOREVER I HATE YOU AND YOUR FAKE 30 SECOND FAKE CONCERT.    
    
    
    Who's in charge of washing Gaga's chair? #icky #undies    
    
    
    Maybe more than 2 hours of sleep would have been good for this day.    
    
    
    This is my very first day of not school since I learned to walk.    
    
    
    @Prescigno always looking out. Truly a great lunch buddy.    
    
    
    I'm so tired but my body is so awake. My limbs are tingling. I think I have west nile cause the only thing wrong with me is bug bites..    
    
    
    @Armaine4 @sweetkaroline91 who is angchp    
    
    
    Wait insomnia is so real. You can actually go 2 days without sleeping. You can. And it hurts.    
    
    
    DC you are so hot and annoying today ✋    
    
    
    Hey Angela welcome to DC, stop getting lost someday.    
    
    
    I just circled union station 4 times I hate Georgetown and I hate summer heat and I hate whoever is outside with petitions and I hate maps.    
    
    
    Don't ask to sit next to me and then lean on me, creep. You smell like latex...    
    
    
    Dad and I exchange emails we want the NSA to see. #conservativefamilyvalues    
    
    
    Mom just asked if anything was stressing me out. I told her I'm still pretty pissed Romney lost..    
    
    
    HA insomnia. I tricked you with NyQuil. I win.    
    
    
    Bailey's French Vanilla coffee creamer is the creamer of the gods.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 but you AREN'T a DC resident. #lucky #proudofyou    
    
    
    I'm at Sign Of The Whale (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/1a08MWt     
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy and I are screaming arguing with everyone in this bar that @Paula_Deen isn't racist. #meantforeachother    
    
    
    Last night was college.    
    
    
    My first time actually falling asleep all week and I feel like the world is a different place.    
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy you can just tag me next time.    
    
    
    I'm the only person on Twitter willing to admit I'm not the resident expert on Syria. Good job watching CNN, though. #sassy #annoyed    
    
    
    I've never seen so many cars in one place as DC right now.    
    
    
    I can't believe I missed the St. Leo's fair.    
    
    
    This whole not sleeping at night sleeping during the day thing is messing me up. I don't know how vampires do it.    
    
    
    Has anyone tweeted "wake me up when September ends"? Am I first?    
    
    
    This is punishment for spending 22 years judging the hell out of people who don't sleep. It is a real thing. And I have no NyQuil. #gonnadie    
    
    
    In other news I'd like to apologize for tweeting so much about my lack of sleep and not enough about politics and indiscretions. #partyfoul    
    
    
    The bob-o-pedic is both the best and the worst investment you can make. DO NOT MAKE ME LEAVE THIS BED. #alreadylate #goteamgo #sickdaymaybe    
    
    
    This Tuesday feels oddly like a Monday.. NICE TRY I STILL HATE YOU.    
    
    
    We put a man on the moon but we haven't invented alarm clocks that physically drag your sorry behind out of bed in the morning? #late    
    
    
    Best happy hour in town (at @CavaMezze) http://4sq.com/15BGSrq     
    
    
    Since these humans like to bully me when my boss is gone, yours truly wore heels to work today so desk moving just ain't gonna be my job✋    
    
    
    I'm at @BarLouie Gallery Place (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/1dHYhYs     
    
    
    My least favorite part of living in DC is that everyone wants to talk about Syria #ugh    
    
    
    @ohhemGINA platos then Dunkin... After a night of chicken fingers at times. GET READY IT'S HAPPENING.    
    
    
    The glory of twitter is being able to subtweet. But the person I'm trying to bully doesn't even follow me. #ugh    
    
    
    I think if you go long enough without sleeping you die. I think death is coming for me. If it isn't then can it? 😳    
    
    
    #tbt #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/d4aohqgunO/     
    
    
    I'm at @BullfeathersDc (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/162T7BC     
    
    
    SUBTWEET. I REPEAT. THIS IS A SUBTWEET.    
    
    
    I'm at Kelly's Irish Times - @irishtimesdc (Washington, DC) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/14ohnzI     
    
    
    I'm at Dubliner Restaurant & Pub - @dublinerpubdc (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/163kgV2     
    
    
    This is the scheduling day from hell.    
    
    
    We seriously can't find a way to make phone calls work on the metro? What century is this?    
    
    
    Call Me Maybe came on my shuffle and I thought my phone was ringing... Is it lame that's still my ringtone? #trendy    
    
    
    @RebeccaRougier I loled at this tweet    
    
    
    If DC really thought it was going to host the Olympics then it's even dumber than I thought.    
    
    
    Yes. (@ Basilica of the National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception w/ @capierno) http://4sq.com/17it7Sw     
    
    
    @AWSmith51 or a city that has more than a 5 mile radius.    
    
    
    I am going to pass out and die in this tower    
    
    
    If I ever build a shrine, remind me to make it so you can go outside at the top. I'm getting heat… http://instagram.com/p/eAesx8gumW/     
    
    
    @Armaine4 Cinderella time.    
    
    
    Insomnia is worst on Sundays. I can only watch Amish people in cities for so long. Sleepytime tea I wish you were ambien.    
    
    
    I went to this Gaelic language night once (months ago) and I can only remember like 3 words. I'be picked tonight to search for the packet.    
    
    
    @DevenMcCarthy😏    
    
    
    @DevenMcCarthy that was actually mean of me, I'm just in withdrawal from our rivalry. It's been a while. 🏉🙈🙌    
    
    
    A morning's not a morning around here until someone calls you a "f***ing white ass bitch". DC is such a charming little city.    
    
    
    Told some guy at union I was picking up "Congressman McCarthy" so I could stay parked illegally. @JohnWMcCarthy hurry before the jig is up..    
    
    
    I'm at @DistrictCommons (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/18JWNam     
    
    
    When you plan for a night of sitting so you wear heels, but then you end up going somewhere else and walking and standing... 😳🔫    
    
    
    Tonight @JohnWMcCarthy let me wear his shoes to the metro because my heels gave me blisters. He is the greatest man I have ever known.    
    
    
    @EmilyBagnell I am the luckiest girl in the world.    
    
    
    My heart goes out to the guy whose car is broken down in the middle of 395..    
    
    
    Just now laughing at the fact that @AWSmith51 and I went to Times on graduation night in sweatshirts. #stillnotsorry    
    
    
    Today I got my boss a free pizza with his hotel room. I'd say today was a success.    
    
    
    I'm at The John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts - @kencen (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/18SHQBt     
    
    
    2013 Common Sense Media Awards! With @johnwmccarthy :) (@ Kennedy Center- Terrace Theatre) http://4sq.com/15OWaKx     
    
    
    @AWSmith51 @Armaine4 and I are way ahead of you hahah. This is the ONLY explanation of Syria I have understood. #notjoking    
    
    
    This weather is horrendous.    
    
    
    Ugh yawn    
    
    
    @jayschaef so close yet so far    
    
    
    @Prescigno at least that's an amazing smell...    
    
    
    I don't know why everyone is so shocked that Russia thinks we're wimps. Russians are SCARY. You couldn't pay me to go to Russia. 👻👺    
    
    
    @camBALLLLLIN YES YES YES    
    
    
    @camBALLLLLIN Yes meaning I support it, not that it's "too early" #nevertooearly    
    
    
    Setting up camp in my office until the apocalypse is over. #DC    
    
    
    My heart is breaking for New Jersey right now. The shore can't catch a break. And at RUSH HOUR? That's just mean, nature 😡    
    
    
    If I've learned anything today it's that people have NO idea about the education system(s) in this country. Scary.    
    
    
    @amplify on the Early Show 😎    
    
    
    Can't wait to leave town tonight with @KaitlinSchiele and @Prescigno    
    
    
    I've been mildly obsessed with my job for the past 24 hours.    
    
    
    If I had a genie, one of my wishes would be to rid the world of bicycles. Except for cute little kids.    
    
    
    Joel Klein discusses mobile learning device http://www.myfoxny.com/video?autoStart=true&topVideoCatNo=default&clipId=9285544#.UjNqaGPF-TA.twitter …    
    
    
    @Prescigno but actually the only senior in the class, flooded with freshman. It was a 9:35am. Left when I realized there was math...    
    
    
    There are 5 different kinds cell phones in this car and 2 different providers and only 3 people.. Oh.    
    
    
    @Prescigno literally listening to sexual healing lying down in the back seat... Oh.    
    
    
    @Prescigno ATTENTION: THE SONG WAS BABY GET BACK. LET THE RECORD SHOW I WAS MISTAKEN (You're still lying in the back listening to sec music)    
    
    
    "I think God put me on this earth to do bad things to bad people" - @KaitlinSchiele    
    
    
    Irish Festival! And I've already been called out for being Italian... (@ Sea Girt Beach - Military and Police Access) http://4sq.com/1ddwht0     
    
    
    Ahem @DevenMcCarthy what's your ETA...    
    
    
    I've had approximately 0 Irish beers today 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸    
    
    
    Today is awesome.    
    
    
    💆    
    
    
    I'm at Bayshore Senior Center (Keansburg, NJ) http://4sq.com/19Vpoun     
    
    
    @amtomasello missing you already!    
    
    
    I ate more this weekend than any Miss America contestant has this year.    
    
    
    No one is pointing out the obvious fact that "Miss America" and everything involved, directly or indirectly, is a colossal waste of time...    
    
    
    @KatrinaMarie8 I also feel that way about US Virgin Islands AND Miss DC. It'd be awesome if they were just states. Now ANYONE is invited.    
    
    
    Is Miss America the same as "Miss American Pie?" If yes I retract all my comments. #drovemychevytothelevy    
    
    
    @cabwill girl WHERE have you been for 5 years? #twitterreunion    
    
    
    @KatrinaMarie8 if you're not a star on the flag, you don't count. #usfactsbyangela    
    
    
    This weekend was literally St. Patrick's Day.    
    
    
    The reporting on this Navy Yard situation is TERRIBLE.    
    
    
    Sirens coming from EVERY direction. If DC does anything right, it's emergency response. #NavyYardShooting    
    
    
    The ONE time I would be okay with delays on the metro and it's "running normally". Metro is the strangest most backward system ever.    
    
    
    I'm afraid to go home while tourists are fighting to get close to the scene to get pictures and info. THIS cat is not the LEAST bit curious.    
    
    
    So there's people getting killed by my apartment and i just burned 2 bags of popcorn. Happy Monday.    
    
    
    US Capitol Police wielding some very large guns today. Can one of you come to my house? Even just a little guy?    
    
    
    My whole heart is in #Stamford. So thankful no one was hurt. Praying responders stay safe!    
    
    
    I'm at @CavaMezze (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/18vkVvn     
    
    
    I'm at Capitol Lounge (Washington, DC) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/1511tf4     
    
    
    Hump day 🐫🐪🐫    
    
    
    I don't care how Eco friendly or healthy you think you are, nobody wants to see you ride a bike in a spandex pencil skirt.    
    
    
    It's Wednesday and I'm not wearing pink. Obviously my whole day is thrown off.    
    
    
    But like IS there a better gchat contact than @ohhemGINA ?    
    
    
    I know most girls love shoes but I literally hate wearing shoes 100% of the time.    
    
    
    John Boehner came out for @beeka_chu on her birthday. THAT'S Ohio dedication. http://instagram.com/p/ea0cYSguj5/     
    
    
    I'm forever impressed by sunsets, the Capitol, and the love of my life. It never. Gets. Old. @ Library… http://instagram.com/p/ea47lngurL/     
    
    
    I'm at @HawknDoveDc w/ @katrinamarie8 http://4sq.com/19fh8oj     
    
    
    I just poured boiling water down my leg. Happy Thursday.    
    
    
    Because obviously the metro doesn't want to run properly at rush hour. Why should it? Take your time, no one has anywhere to be.    
    
    
    10 minutes between trains? REALLY? YOU HAVE LITERALLY 4 HOURS A DAY YOU NEED TO FUNCTION PROPERLY. YOU HAVE ALL DAY TO BE SLOW. #hate    
    
    
    Excuse me tourists, you only get stupidity preference on weekends. It's Thursday. #youcantsitwithus    
    
    
    I hate conference calls. I hate scheduling them, I hate being on them, I hate watching other people on them. Like WHY? Send an email.    
    
    
    I want to smack every single commuter tonight. Especially the gentleman that just whacked me with his laptop. I'm coming for you.    
    
    
    I'm at Four Seasons Hotel Washington DC - @fswashington (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/18Fdf9R     
    
    
    To the bartender that has introduced me to shaken Grey Goose and cranberry with 2 lemons, you'll be in my heart forever.    
    
    
    What is my life? (@ International Spy Museum w/ @johnwmccarthy) http://4sq.com/158xRfY     
    
    
    My boyfriend is dancing with a 60 year old to single ladies soooooo    
    
    
    I'm so glad my boss thinks I'm funny cause I'm actually just sassy as hell.    
    
    
    So glad @alyssabadolato is here. That is all.    
    
    
    #nofilter #jkonefilter http://instagram.com/p/eggfKwAutF/     
    
    
    @LisettePylant pizza bagels are my kryptonite. #worthit    
    
    
    Plans to run in the morning make growing up too real.    
    
    
    @backstreetboys pandora always reminds me of how that concert was the best day of my life.    
    
    
    If it's the last thing I do, I'll have a vacation home in Jackson Hole, Wyoming. It's the only place I ever want to beeeee.    
    
    
    I have had about 10 big tervis tumblers full of water today. Apparently my body thinks it's in a desert.    
    
    
    If you don't think @MileyCyrus songs are SO effing catchy, you're lying. Stop psychoanalyzing. It's annoying.    
    
    
    So I'm just saying if this guy doesn't play "kinky boots" I'm never coming back to the Dubliner.    
    
    
    @tedcruz should probably just go to @irishtimesdc at 12 when he's done and just keep em flowing all afternoon.    
    
    
    Ugh Harry Reid..............................................................................................................................    
    
    
    I'm at Half Street Fairgrounds (Washington, DC) w/ 23 others http://4sq.com/16rIYRY     
    
    
    @ohhemGINA DOORS OPENIN ON THE LEFT    
    
    
    Slipping in the shower AFTER my medically inclined roommate left for work was not my best move this morning. I literally need LifeAlert.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 #wheresmir #roommatedown    
    
    
    With homecoming just around the corner, I think it's time we all start talking about this again  #tbt… http://instagram.com/p/eugqBkgunW/     
    
    
    This is homecoming. Happy Thursday everybody! http://instagram.com/p/evqCN0Aulm/     
    
    
    I'm at Kelly's Irish Times - @irishtimesdc w/ @johnwmccarthy http://4sq.com/1h7292L     
    
    
    @Prescigno is in club swerve alone. That is all. #cua    
    
    
    This is going to be the longest work day in history. #CUAHoCo2013    
    
    
    Why is it so effing hot?    
    
    
    @maggieburke19 HAHAHAHAHAHAHH    
    
    
    My boss just came into my office and said "I'm leaving. Go drink." Hellooooooo homecoming.    
    
    
    Oh hai (@ Edward J. Pryzbyla University Center - @cuapryz w/ @kaitlinschiele) http://4sq.com/19GjwEK     
    
    
    There's a woman here calling me "baby in the green shirt" it's a dress but like, okayyyy    
    
    
    I'm at Kelly's Irish Times - @irishtimesdc w/ @katrinamarie8 @tomhorsman @kaitlinschiele http://4sq.com/18wFLhW     
    
    
    @sweetkaroline91 GET AT ME    
    
    
    @sweetkaroline91 done and done    
    
    
    I'm at Kelly's Irish Times - @irishtimesdc (Washington, DC) w/ 6 others http://4sq.com/1bRyjRL     
    
    
    Line down the road and @ohhemGINA strolls into the bar VIP I mean you can't make it up.    
    
    
    Just wanting to say hi to @PRyan our new breakfast buddy. (@ Pete's Diner w/ @armaine4 @63perrone) http://4sq.com/1aCfX3i     
    
    
    Is there an amount of NyQuil and water that can make tomorrow okay? Never know until you try.    
    
    
    The @Patriots are my favorite part of any day.    
    
    
    Dead    
    
    
    Literally teething. Pain like no other.    
    
    
    #shutdownpickuplines is the best part of this day.    
    
    
    Being forced to watch Barbara Boxer makes me want to rip my entire head off. What a witchy long winded old bat.    
    
    
    After a day that makes you wanna hate Washington, the view driving home from @JohnWMcCarthy and @Prescigno 's reminds you why you love it..    
    
    
    I think this is what dying feels like.    
    
    
    So when does parking enforcement stop? If there's gonna be a government shutdown I'm gonna enjoy it.    
    
    
    Brb having my tooth sawed out. Special thanks to @prescigno for bringing my drunk chipmunk self home in an hour. Bye everyone.    
    
    
    CVS IS THE WORST PLACE ON EARTH. Thanks Obama.    
    
    
    Witnessing obamacare first hand. I'm going to kill myself.    
    
    
    @Prescigno ALWAYS ALWAYS ALWAYS there when I need you. Hahah nervous where I'll end up next, but THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME TODAY!    
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy pulling through with the softest blanket and appleTV making me the comfiest of all the chipmunks. Have fun in Texas! 🐻✈    
    
    
    Please be safe Hill friends :(    
    
    
    @camBALLLLLIN I'd say your fears are rational    
    
    
    I am the only person on twitter not watching Scandal OR the Rangers game. #hipster    
    
    
    @TomHorsman to say the least.    
    
    
    Rallying after wisdom tooth surgery. @BobbyMcKeys here we come! @JohnWMcCarthy @Prescigno    
    
    
    @BobbyMcKeys charging $3.25 for seltzer? I mean that's a little... Unheard of. AND THE BARTENDER JUDGED ME. #icantdrinkonpainmeds #rude    
    
    
    Don't worry @BobbyMcKeys I still love you. It's our friends' first time here and they're loving it!!    
    
    
    @Armaine4 whaaaaaaat    
    
    
    I'm at The Pretzel Bakery (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/17KltBn     
    
    
    I had a dream that I wore my uniform to school on dress down day so obviously I'm very stressed out..    
    
    
    If you don't know the Hoedown Throwdown then what are you even doing with your life? CC: @MileyCyrus    
    
    
    @FCLorg If DC's budget runs out, parking is free! #perks    
    
    
    So late for work after stopping at the AWESOME Ocean Spray marketing campaign at Union Station! http://instagram.com/p/fP7AhlguuY/     
    
    
    Why is no one talking about how @ohhemGINA used to (had to) go to science camp?    
    
    
    Seriously cannot wait to get right back into my bed after work. This rain MUST be kidding.    
    
    
    My dad just said he's looking forward to when Christie is no longer governor so that @JohnWMcCarthy can take over. #reachingacrosspartylines    
    
    
    Just for some context, my dad is a Tea Party Republican, NRA member, who is still a birther... #oneineveryfamily    
    
    
    I would like to thank @ohhemGINA for experiencing the end of this day with me. #gossipgirl    
    
    
    Glee and wine is not going to end well..    
    
    
    ALL IN BLACK I CANT    
    
    
    CORY NOOOOOOOOOO OMG FINN PLEASE COME BACK OMG    
    
    
    Glee. I'm already crying.    
    
    
    We are WEEPING in 1230 right now.    
    
    
    #Glee is the emotional purge we all didn't know we needed. #missingcory    
    
    
    Cory then Terry McAuliffe. Coooooool Fox.    
    
    
    @msleamichele is everything.    
    
    
    I don't think I've ever had such genuine tears for a television episode.. #RememberingCory    
    
    
    @31Murray LIZ TONIGHT ISN'T ABOUT YOU IT'S ABOUT CORY.    
    
    
    @nkolenberg94 it's all I ever want in life.    
    
    
    CLOGGING THE BELTWAY WITH TRUCKS IS SO EFFING RUDE. THAT ISN'T A PROTEST. THE BELTWAY ALREADY SUCKS. THAT'S. RUDE.    
    
    
    Just some lobbying. @rebeccarougier (at @PJClarkes) http://4sq.com/16C7vSg     
    
    
    I'm at Kelly's Irish Times - @irishtimesdc w/ @johnwmccarthy http://4sq.com/19Gh19p     
    
    
    I'm at Four Seasons Hotel Washington DC - @fswashington (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/1hMhl5C     
    
    
    I'm at The Hay-Adams Hotel (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/162vlbA     
    
    
    Since seeing Titanic for the first time last night I've done nothing but look up information on it. I'm so upset about that boat.    
    
    
    I'm at St. Peter's Catholic Church (Washington, DC) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/GW0RwP     
    
    
    @DevenMcCarthy hahaha at least we know not to start at the front... 🚶💪    
    
    
    "Your uber is arriving now" texts are the biggest lie ever.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 just paged me on our house phone. Literally my phone was further away from me than she is.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 @ohhemGINA yeah Gina holla at us    
    
    
    Learn something new every day.. (@ Embassy Of The Hashemite Kingdom Of Jordan w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/18qsdF4     
    
    
    I'm at Kelly's Irish Times - @irishtimesdc w/ @johnwmccarthy http://4sq.com/16SC0n2     
    
    
    I am going to fall asleep right on this desk.    
    
    
    I'm at Three Fox Vineyards - @3foxvineyards (Delaplane, VA) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/1ezGy3o     
    
    
    Pumpkins in God's country VA 🎃http://instagram.com/p/fqUxeeAujn/     
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy😘    
    
    
    I have been drinking wine for 7 hours..    
    
    
    Me: we need to set aside some time soon to exclusively talk about Titanic.
@ohhemGINA : how about 9-5 on gchat every day next week?    
    
    
    @Armaine4 literally yelling in Tagalog in the next room 👸    
    
    
    @Armaine4 teamwork.    
    
    
    Running outside in the morning is the biggest and coldest game changer there is. I'm not cut out for this. #needatredmill    
    
    
    @Armaine4 loves board meetings! #houseonfire #butshelooksawesome    
    
    
    It went from fall to winter pretty quickly.    
    
    
    Today has been nothing but frustrating and it's only 11:00.    
    
    
    So. Angry.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 is the only person not parked like an ASSHOLE on Independence Ave right now. Seriously not pleased. And I hate cursing on twitter.    
    
    
    I'm realizing that waking up when it's still dark is really not making me happy. Also that I want to move to Hawaii.    
    
    
    Some points on Pre-K "By age 18 months, poor children haven't learned as many words as their wealthier counterparts" http://nyti.ms/GZ0L6R     
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy hates my newfound love for Titanic.    
    
    
    I'm at The Mayflower Renaissance Washington, DC Hotel - @renhotels (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/1icgqvw     
    
    
    @KatrinaMarie8 I NEED THAT    
    
    
    So great to see @IngrahamAngle at the Catholic Information Center dinner tonight!    
    
    
    @IngrahamAngle and @AnnCoulter in DC tonight! I'm the luckiest republican girl..    
    
    
    I just want to move to Hawaii. See you never.    
    
    
    There is no human on this earth as cute as my boss' daughter. #onwednesdayswewearpink    
    
    
    Locking my keys in my car at Times last night was a personal best.    
    
    
    Wasn't prepared for this cold weather.    
    
    
    This week seriously cannot end soon enough.    
    
    
    Wild night at the Wilson! (@ District of Columbia Government — John A. Wilson Building w/ @armaine4) http://4sq.com/HeAjGX     
    
    
    @Armaine4 and I just found literally all the ingredients for a pumpkin pie in our cabinet... Including canned pumpkin?    
    
    
    Heated blanket season is upon us ☺️🔥    
    
    
    To the human whose truck I just boxed into a parallel parking space, I'm sorry. Please don't wreck my bumper too much on your way out 😽    
    
    
    Just watched a full grown man in a suit subtly cut the Starbucks line. So sneaky ya assssssssssss 😾😒    
    
    
    How has "Took the Night" never been on my running playlist until now? Obvs blasting in my office.. @Armaine4 @ohhemGINA @chrisconsalvy    
    
    
    If someone can confirm that there are NJ bagels at this finish line I might finish in record time..    
    
    
    My fave 5K selfie doesn't even need a filter. http://instagram.com/p/f72gx3AusT/     
    
    
    I still can't get over how proud I am of my and @DevenMcCarthy 's first 5K time.. And how proud I am that we bullied other runners 😏    
    
    
    @amtomasello THERE IS NO SHAME IN THAT    
    
    
    @amtomasello life changing. Glad to share in those moments with you. 🚢    
    
    
    #rockygram http://instagram.com/p/f_FxSXAuql/     
    
    
    Not being able to sleep when I'm SO tired is the most baffling thing. Also the most annoying. 😳    
    
    
    Here's to hoping 1.5 hours of sleep was enough to get me through this day. Good morning to you too, Monday.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 SEE YOU NEVER. #mad    
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy @Prescigno always a pleasure, gentlemen!    
    
    
    THE PSYCHOS UPSTAIRS ARE STILL SINGING AND PLAYING PIANO. IT IS 10PM, PAVOROTTI, GIVE IT UP AND GET A JOB. #hate    
    
    
    Walking past a school and I'm SO glad to see LLBean backpacks are still a thing.    
    
    
    @LaurenConrad is perfect.    
    
    
    Swore I just saw @Alats2 on the metro platform. What a cruel world :(    
    
    
    Republicans for Fecteau! (@ MOVA) http://4sq.com/16JI51J     
    
    
    @Armaine4 @KatrinaMarie8 @ohhemGINA beautiful.    
    
    
    The X8 bus just almost demolished my car. OPEN. YOUR. EYES. I hate DC.    
    
    
    USPS ruined my Halloween. My adorable little grandma sent an integral piece of my costume that is naturally lost. Happy Halloween, morons.    
    
    
    @KatrinaMarie8 @redurbano why aren't you guys bbming...    
    
    
    Boyfriend of the week award goes to @JohnWMcCarthy in case you were wondering.    
    
    
    #tbt some sophomore year halloween realness #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/gI20aCAuuP/     
    
    
    I'm at W Washington D.C. - @whoteldc (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/19gT4nn     
    
    
    ❤️ @ P.O.V. Rooftop Lounge and Terrace http://instagram.com/p/gKGC_ggujv/     
    
    
    Church bells just reminded me of mass and now it's too late. Real life has made me such a terrible Catholic.    
    
    
    IF EVERYONE ALREADY KNEW TITANIC WAS ON NETFLIX AND DIDN'T TELL ME THEN I HATE YOU. 

Gonna watch it in my office now and cry. See ya.    
    
    
    Every time I watch this movie I get so pissed. IT WAS THE SHIP OF DREAMS.    
    
    
    I don't know why I shop anywhere other than @Nordstrom -- unparalleled customer service!    
    
    
    Happppppy Birthday Erin! (at @SaxWdc w/ @johnwmccarthy) http://4sq.com/1avXFEx     
    
    
    Happy Birthday to my one and only spirit animal. You're the best! ekilroy @ Sax http://instagram.com/p/gPNVilAujo/     
    
    
    Happening. @ Sax http://instagram.com/p/gPR5dLAurf/     
    
    
    NYC I'm coming for ya (@ Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA) - @dcafoodandshops w/ 48 others) http://4sq.com/1eaAH7s     
    
    
    I kept asking myself why I didn't fly anymore and forgot the answer was security lines..    
    
    
    it's been a while! (@ LaGuardia Airport (LGA) w/ 174 others) http://4sq.com/1eb5Ibf     
    
    
    It's amazing how my DC work picks up an NYC pace literally the second I land. This is going to be one hell of a day..    
    
    
    I'm at @Amplify (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/Hr0oT4     
    
    
    @KatrinaMarie8 @Armaine4 I'd say mine is the best one in that list but that's just me..    
    
    
    New York City is so tall...    
    
    
    I know I've failed several math classes in my time but I think it'd be the coolest to work at the NYSE.    
    
    
    So I mean first stop tomorrow is Tiffany's since the back of my bow earring just went down the drain and I feel lost in the world..    
    
    
    So weird being in NYC on Election Day. Literally no one is talking about it. DC I miss you!    
    
    
    I don't know what my work life would be without @Uber ... I've taken like 12 in the past 2 days. They need a rewards program.    
    
    
    😍(at @LaBagelDelight1) http://4sq.com/174RsJz     
    
    
    Brooklyn office, it's been real. http://instagram.com/p/gWDx74guj0/     
    
    
    I'm at Delta Marine Air Terminal TSA Screening (NY) http://4sq.com/HI0Xrc     
    
    
    See you next month New York✌️    
    
    
    @nkolenberg94 STAMFORD REPUBLICANS 4EVA    
    
    
    #romneyryan2012    
    
    
    Mitt Romney style.    
    
    
    Also no one in NOVA even reallllly lives in VA. They're all DC people. Posers.    
    
    
    BREAKING: VA currently kicking themselves for electing a governor that stiffs his supporters with cash bars.. #VoteVA    
    
    
    Cooch is a Republican and Terry's a Cardinal. Either way I win tonight. #applause    
    
    
        
    
    
    @SeRoKeVA trust me.. My friends are totally uninterested in my inability to take care of and operate my motor vehicle.    
    
    
    @gcmclaughlin there's no good reason this tweet isn't trending.    
    
    
    All I think about is jumbo slices and titanic.    
    
    
    I'm at Embassy of France - @franceintheus w/ @johnwmccarthy http://4sq.com/16KRnxD     
    
    
    @BobbyMcKeys never ever disappoints. #alwaysagoodidea    
    
    
    I'm at @BobbyMcKeys w/ @johnwmccarthy http://4sq.com/HGTOYM     
    
    
    She's backkkkkkkk @ Bobby McKey's http://instagram.com/p/ge1D4YAup0/     
    
    
    THERE IS NOTHING WORSE THAN THE ROCK CREEK PARKWAY. I HAVE BEEN LOST FOR AN HOUR.. Seriously send help.    
    
    
    A giant handful of pills and I am conference ready! I also have an empty gas tank and 2 pairs of ripped tights so it's been quite a morning.    
    
    
    Thanks Catholic Volunteer Network for the great presentations and exhibits. Awesome program! http://4sq.com/1hW2Z5n     
    
    
    I'm at Rock & Roll Hotel - @bearnonsense (Washington, DC) w/ 12 others http://4sq.com/1eyT06s     
    
    
    I'm at @CesarsDiner (Arlington, VA) http://4sq.com/HLihfR     
    
    
    So DC. (@ United States Capitol - @visitthecapitol) http://4sq.com/17ZKdXe     
    
    
    MOC for a day. @ Longworth House Office Building http://instagram.com/p/glSdLrAuvZ/     
    
    
    @CUAproblems awkward.. every theology graduate I know (most of them)  is employed. Cardinal Station is significantly worse.    
    
    
    @Prescigno I'm sorry I'm an enabler. On hour 6.    
    
    
    Was looking to end my SVU binge with an ep I could fall asleep during. Melissa Joan Heart is in this one so I definitely failed..    
    
    
    IF YOU ARE ON SPEAKER PHONE ON A CONFERENCE CALL WITH YOUR DOOR OPEN THEN YOU ARE THE WORST.    
    
    
    I CANT HELP MYSELF I NEED A PEPPERMINT WHITE MOCHA. #selfcontrolgone    
    
    
    Just found out I can't go to jail for not paying my student loans. Best news I've heard all day.    
    
    
    Obamacare numbers are embarrassing.    
    
    
    I'm at USCCB (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/1ePNM6l     
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy do one of them have the gnome? #wheresthegnome    
    
    
    Not our best but Aunt Zelda is our hero.. http://instagram.com/p/gtvaAwguno/     
    
    
    Brb jumping out of the car.    
    
    
    This is the hardest Monday ever.    
    
    
    Commiserating with my uber driver about DC traffic laws.    
    
    
    I'm at Starbucks (Falls Church, VA) http://4sq.com/IcmCbp     
    
    
    The cool thing about my job is that I can prioritize what I do based on how much I like the person requesting it. #chief    
    
    
    Fell asleep with the TV on and woke up to a show about giving birth. Needless to say I'm totally traumatized.    
    
    
    Fever is a great thing to have on what's supposed to be a really productive day. Also I'm traveling tomorrow. #dead    
    
    
    I actually don't care one bit what anyone says, Trey Radel is my favorite member of congress.    
    
    
    SEVERAL members of Congress would do well to follow Trey's example in seeking help for addictions. He is certainly far from being alone.    
    
    
    Watching wedding shows has made me realize how rich I wanna be before I get married. Because I need a huge Swarovski bow on my dress 💃💒🎀    
    
    
    Aaaaaand we're off again! (@ Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA) - @dcafoodandshops w/ 32 others) http://4sq.com/1iugfi5     
    
    
    Found a @DunkinDonuts in the US Airways terminal. It's like seeing the face of God.    
    
    
    In the heartland for some NCYC/NCCC action! First time in Indiana! (@ Indianapolis International Airport (IND)) http://4sq.com/1fhPP3r     
    
    
    So. Many. Catholic. Things. (@ Indiana Convention Center - @indianacc) http://4sq.com/17qi1fp     
    
    
    Finally in bed. Already thinking about that perfect Starbucks cup in my hand in the morning.    
    
    
    Today @angchip is trying to take a picture with groups from all 50 states! Stop by our booth at #NCYC… http://instagram.com/p/hBSItTwAoO/     
    
    
    #5: Salina, KANSAS in the lime green today! #NCYC http://instagram.com/p/hBseUCguio/     
    
    
    A break from our hunt for all 50 states as @capierno gives an intro to our session on apostleship.… http://instagram.com/p/hBzcjrwAkP/     
    
    
    Indiana is the coldest state in America.    
    
    
    Last night in Indianapolis! (at @StElmo Steak House w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/17FQdnD     
    
    
    That last glass of wine always seems like a better idea at the time. Especially when early morning travel is in play 😴    
    
    
    Catch you in two years, Indiana! (@ Indianapolis International Airport (IND) - @indairport w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/17HxIiw     
    
    
    Get me to my bed immediatelyyyyy (@ Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA) - @dcafoodandshops w/ 41 others) http://4sq.com/1fzZz97     
    
    
    ...When your boyfriend won't take time out of his workday to watch a vine about a kitten. BAH HUMBUG. #priorites #subtweet    
    
    
    Only know you've been high when you're feeling low, only hate the road when you're missing home.    
    
    
    Some old stomping grounds (@ The Italian Center of Stamford) http://4sq.com/18m2YXk     
    
    
    I've been in 7 states and a district in the past 72 hours.. #adult    
    
    
    Watching my brother do algebra homework makes me SO happy high school has been over for so long.    
    
    
    I haven't read Cosmo in so long that I forgot how trashy and wonderful it is. #guiltypleasure    
    
    
    I still can't believe I'm going out tonight. #sohighschool    
    
    
    @LordandTaylor customer service just really can't compete with Nordstrom. It's not even the employees, it's the outdated system. #frustrated    
    
    
    I'm at @BartacoPc (Stamford, CT) http://4sq.com/1gjB262     
    
    
    I'm at BarQ (Stamford, CT) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/1esfKBK     
    
    
    America wants to know where @justinbieber is.. Why isn't he in this parade?    
    
    
    AINT NO CHIMNAYYYYSSSSSS ... in the projects.    
    
    
    @AlexBoucher @Capierno i want to be one of the dancing traffic signs that were on earlier. preferably "no U turn"    
    
    
    Who is driving the driedel?    
    
    
    Chubby ladies running in pant suits. This is America.    
    
    
    @Olivianuzzi #patriots    
    
    
    Loving the cornucopias at the Purina Dog Show. It's that kind of attention to detail that makes a great Thanksgiving.    
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy I'm almost personally offended that you're not watching the Purina Dog Show...    
    
    
    @gcmclaughlin it's actually shameful that there isn't anything remembering titanic. A COFOUNDER OF MACYS DIED ON THAT SHIP!    
    
    
    FIZZY FOR THE WIN! #HuskyNation    
    
    
    #teamfizzy    
    
    
    @gcmclaughlin I lost that battle this morning. I literally argued for an hour about why we shouldn't have to get dressed.    
    
    
    My family is getting ready for Thanksgiving and I have established that my role is watching the dog show. Nothing further.    
    
    
    King Charles Spaniel got ROBBED.    
    
    
    @johanaaa_gutie cleaning rooms is NOT on the thanksgiving agenda. Pilgrims watched people cook, they didn't clean rooms.    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving all! From kec427 and myself. http://instagram.com/p/hRdrzDAusp/     
    
    
    It's been a heck of a year, and I'm so thankful for my amazing friends, being able to spend time with my family, and for so much to come.    
    
    
    YESSSSSSS (@ Lakeside Diner) http://4sq.com/1j16PL3     
    
    
    My kidneys hurt. Is that a side effect of turkey? Drinking? Both?    
    
    
    @Olivianuzzi imagine the awareness organizations that would come after... MOMS AGAINST THANKSGIVING TRADITIONS.    
    
    
    Somehow I go out 5 nights a week in DC, but it's like pulling teeth to get me to go out at home. Bed is calling me.    
    
    
    Out with my locals 👌(@ BarQ w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/1eySMsW     
    
    
    If you don't live for the applause you're doing it wrong.    
    
    
    The best friend pic lives on! http://instagram.com/p/hU4WFSAuhC/     
    
    
    "I live in the real world. You live in.. I don't even know.. Disneyland." - Dad    
    
    
    I'm not watching any games... All I know is that I love to say ROLL TIDE!    
    
    
    I actually don't think I've ever been this sad to leave Stamford.    
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy and I are eating a cheese spread in my car as another car anxiously awaits for my parking spot. #oops    
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy GIDDY UP JINGLE HORSE PICK UP YOUR FEET    
    
    
    But actually have I ever had a bigger rage blackout than the one I just had on gchat with @gcmclaughlin ?    
    
    
    @JohnWMcCarthy laugh it up, but when you see that your present is actually a breadbox don't come crying to meeeee.    
    
    
    Is there anything worse than busses?    
    
    
    John has almost killed me 3 times on the way here. But I'm hoping Edward Snowden makes a surprise appearance. http://4sq.com/1arTkMV     
    
    
    Russian Embassy ready for Christmas! http://instagram.com/p/hcH66qguqq/     
    
    
    America and Russia would get along perfectly if we could all just agree that vodka is perfect.    
    
    
    This has got to be the best night of my life. Russia seriously knows how to throw an event.    
    
    
    Rule #1: always make friends with the bartender.    
    
    
    I love it here and all, but I have never missed my friends from home so much.    
    
    
    Also just walked in front of moving traffic so if that isn't representative of this day then I don't know what is.    
    
    
    Christmas parties on Christmas parties (at @Newseum w/ @armaine4) http://4sq.com/1awoyCC     
    
    
    Just told my boss I've been out every night this week. Is that allowed?    
    
    
    I'm at Cathedral Of Saint Matthew the Apostle (Washington, DC) http://4sq.com/18mgFmq     
    
    
    A morning's not a morning unless @Armaine4 is talking to you about "blunt force trauma to the head"    
    
    
    The old ball and chain. (@ Basilica of the National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception) http://4sq.com/IX3mzV     
    
    
    Annual Christmas Concert for Charity and some Cardinal Wuerl handshaking action. @ Basilica of the… http://instagram.com/p/hma0A2Augq/     
    
    
    http://spoti.fi/1f1ThvH  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Well. This happened tonight at the DGA Holiday Party.. @ Union Station http://instagram.com/p/huToDwAuqK/     
    
    
    Just posted a photo @ Union Station http://instagram.com/p/huUq8Ygurd/     
    
    
    @kpwalling @ Union Station http://instagram.com/p/hueCZXAuoH/     
    
    
    #praisejc for this snow day because what even was my night last night..    
    
    
    This is a subtweet to anyone and everyone who feels inferior because of Victoria's Secret. Also if you don't do 5 for 27 who even are you.    
    
    
    Victoria's Secret Fashion Show done right. http://instagram.com/p/hxAR7XAuog/     
    
    
    I feel like I have 1000 fevers.    
    
    
    I feel like scraping off my car in the morning is God punishing me for being too poor for a garage.    
    
    
    Living a secret life as a New Jersean (@ Washington Court Hotel w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/18VhzZS     
    
    
    Young and the Guest List (@ Carnegie Library at Mount Vernon Square w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/J7RESw     
    
    
    @kpwalling our dance song is playing at the Carnegie Library! Where are you?! #allnight    
    
    
    DC dance floor that I NEED. @ Carnegie Library at Mount Vernon Square http://instagram.com/p/hzdcc8AusW/     
    
    
    #nofilter @ Carnegie Library at Mount Vernon Square http://instagram.com/p/hzh9MsAuju/     
    
    
    My car is sitting dead on Capitol Hill. My biggest fear is someone saying it's a suspicious package.    
    
    
    I never should have left my house today.    
    
    
    @Armaine4 #welikeitthatway    
    
    
    In the past 24 hours, my membership has more than paid for itself. And awesome customer service as I wait for a tow truck! @AAAnews    
    
    
    How was YOUR morning? http://instagram.com/p/h3ePDXguoy/     
    
    
    I literally wouldn't know a spark plug if I fell over one but I'm hoping that's what's wrong with my car. I hear they're cheap 👌💸    
    
    
    I was having a bad day until @AWSmith51 reminded me that Paul Ryan is in this world. All is right.    
    
    
    @Prescigno thinks he just had a spice drop candy that was "mystery" flavor.    
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagram.com/p/h6QgD0Aug4/     
    
    
    RIP HFR. I'll love you forever. And 1-877-CARS4KIDS is gonna love the angchip addition courtesy of… http://instagram.com/p/h6l9t1gujN/     
    
    
    I have never been so pointlessly tired in my entire life.    
    
    
    🎄(@ Warner Theatre w/ @armaine4) http://4sq.com/JviyEM     
    
    
    DC METRO IS SO UNRELIABLE I CANT EVEN TAKE IT    
    
    
    I'm not a violent person but DC Metro makes me want to hit everyone around me. And also break things.    
    
    
    @jlewDistrict #moving #alsoconverting    
    
    
    Thanks to my fave roommate for getting us tickets to the Washington Ballet's very DC Nutcracker!… http://instagram.com/p/h9KzpRguo-/     
    
    
    @kevinrichardson @backstreetboys YOU GUYS ARE IN DC?! WHERE WHERE WHERE?!    
    
    
    1230 advent wreath. #betterlatethannever http://instagram.com/p/h94o5OAutx/     
    
    
    Merry Christmas! From all of us at 1230. #ohchristmastree http://instagram.com/p/h9_pgQAunb/     
    
    
    I entered to win 2 tickets from @gregslistdc to @CBENYE2014 http://bit.ly/1bHXctB     
    
    
    DC metro and its night time riders remind me why I will NEVER raise a family here.. And why Georgetown doesn't have a stop.    
    
    
    It's 70 degrees in Honolulu today. Just saying.    
    
    
    When the dog bites, when the bee stings, when I'm feeling sad, I simply remember my favorite things and then I don't feel so bad.    
    
    
    @Dave_Nasty @d0llface_ @Alyssa_Marie626 @sayscutter @Nerdypanda22 This is perfect.    
    
    
    I have never felt so trapped as I do in this city without a car.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I forgot my Advil Cold and Sinus so this is going to be a rough day.    
    
    
    I'm at Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA) - @dcafoodandshops w/ @katrinamarie8 http://4sq.com/JAZu7r     
    
    
    Flight delays 😒    
    
    
    Christmas music on my @Delta flight! Such a cute way to start my trip!    
    
    
    I've taxied more than I've flown at this point. (@ LaGuardia Airport (LGA) w/ 125 others) http://4sq.com/JBIvSk     
    
    
    I'm at W New York - Times Square - @spg (New York, NY) w/ 13 others http://4sq.com/JE0Ii8     
    
    
    Last night marked my final holiday party. I'm officially only drinking and eating water until New Year's Eve.    
    
    
    I'm at @DumboKitchen (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/1ce2Ppj     
    
    
    Always nice to get molested and treated like a criminal. Merry Christmas to you, too, TSA.    
    
    
    Delays on delays on delays...    
    
    
    Go team. (@ Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA) - @dcafoodandshops w/ 107 others) http://4sq.com/1i5dBRh     
    
    
    I am literally 100 degrees and my heat is off and my outside door is open. If I die, bury me in my bow necklace. 🙀🔥😿    
    
    
    Wishing a VERY happy birthday to Dick Wolf today! Thanks for making the greatest show on television. @nbcsvu    
    
    
    Really excited for engagement season to be over.. I had no idea that's what Christmas is when you're old.    
    
    
    All I want for Christmas is for Mariah Carey to do less.    
    
    
    Back in Stamf and planning on sleeping til Christmas Eve.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm an idiot for being in NYC a couple days ago and not going to see the tree and the windows. Bah Humbug to me :(    
    
    
    @Alats2 wearing cashmere to a bar. #dontstopgetitgetit    
    
    
    No energy for Stamvegas tonight.    
    
    
    Becoming a staple (@ BarQ w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/JfJzLk     
    
    
    Wagon Wheel just came on in this bar and I'm literally crying.    
    
    
    Locked out of my own Netflix because I give my password to all my loved ones. #oops    
    
    
    @LaurenConrad on the cover of @Cosmopolitan so obviously I need it.    
    
    
    I'm about halfway through the book "Skinny Bitch" and it's life changing.    
    
    
    Growing up teaches you what Christmas is really about: naps and watching people get engaged. Also diets.    
    
    
    Keeping Up Appearances is such an underrated show. BBC killin it.    
    
    
    Just upgraded my Netflix to 4 screens. Merry Christmas to everyone with my password!    
    
    
    PACKED (@ Donut Delight) http://4sq.com/JnyXdn     
    
    
    I want to tweet about being excited for mass tonight but people have RUINED religious tweeting for me.    
    
    
    In the crying room because I'm allergic to incense. Happens every year. (@ Saint Cornelius RC Church) http://4sq.com/1gV5kyY     
    
    
    Merry Christmas ya filthy animals    
    
    
    Titanic is on A&E. MERRY CHRISTMAS!    
    
    
    Forcing @NicholasJ0seph to watch Titanic with me so he's obv 100% thrilled to have me home for Christmas..    
    
    
        
    
    
    Christmas again today with the other side of the family and again over the weekend with @JohnWMcCarthy and @Prescigno #CantStopWontStop    
    
    
    PA Turnpike is a parking lot. Kwanzaa traffic is the worst.    
    
    
    2 hours later finally in NJ. A HUNDRED STATES TO GO WE'RE NEVER GONNA MAKE IT WAHHH (@ Woodrow Wilson Service Area) http://4sq.com/1cBTTKL     
    
    
    So very excited to see @JohnWMcCarthy tomorrow ☺️    
    
    
    I'm at Stamford Transportation Center Bus/Train (STM) @MetroNorth & Amtrak (Stamford, CT) http://4sq.com/1cEKsu0     
    
    
    I want so bad to like Amtrak. But every time I take it SOMETHING stupid happens. Like my train going 2mph and stopping and being so late.    
    
    
    @johnwmccarthy nailed it with Christmas presents this year 👌😻http://instagram.com/p/ibtS3dgunT/     
    
    
    Secret life as an Irish person (@ Dublin House Pub w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/1cGU6MT     
    
    
    I think it's so cute when people who can't pronounce my last name just call me "Miss Angela"💁    
    
    
    Well, here goes nothing..    
    
    
    Puppy slippers, Full House, Goldfish.. I don't want to live to see a time when these things don't cure my bad days.    
    
    
    @KaitlinSchiele loves to look like Diana Ross in the morning 👹😽💃    
    
    
    2 years ago same time I love kaitlinschiele http://instagram.com/p/im5DIeguiE/     
    
    
    The only place I want to be!! (at @BobbyMcKeys w/ @kaitlinschiele) http://4sq.com/1cGQ0mm     
    
    
    Just stole the mayorship of @bobbymckeys on @foursquare! Crown me! http://4sq.com/1cGQ0mm  pic.twitter.com/fYbXiyJkDl    
    
    
    How do you moderate your alcohol before midnight? Is there an answer? #nope    
    
    
    Some New Years planes (@ Gravelly Point Park) http://4sq.com/1cITNPT     
    
    
    In 2014 I'm planning on going on as many game shows as possible.    
    
    
    Starting with Wheel of Fortune because I'm tryna win both cash and a car.    
    
    
    Currently KILLING IT at Jeopardy though.    
    
    
    All I wanted today was a snow day.    
    
    
    Is there anything worse than Morgan saying "rad" on Laguna Beach?    
    
    
    I literally don't even know where I am this morning. I think I got dressed while I was still sleeping. Where are my credit cards..    
    
    
    DC can cancel life tomorrow at ANY time.    
    
    
    Of course on a day when it's actually bad out everything is open. DC is the worst.    
    
    
    About 3 inches of ice between us and seeing the road. Could have used a delay! @myfoxdc pic.twitter.com/wSqMQRic65    
    
    
    