meet Karen Lee! :D    
    
    
    crazystupidlove.    
    
    
    Hunger Games! shortest sneak peek everrrr...    
    
    
    @xo_vw now we can txt & tweet each other! lol.    
    
    
    @xo_vw hahahahah, that's hilarious. but I am now that school is back up! (:    
    
    
    @xo_vw why do you need that many followers? lol, just cause?    
    
    
    Being unproductive, - is something that I’ve mastered this entire week. It’s killing me and for some reason I... http://tumblr.com/xcp7sygzz    
    
    
    haha > lol    
    
    
    watching worlds strongest man with family, intense stuff.    
    
    
    is welcoming back troops, what an awesome experience!    
    
    
    Dallas bound!    
    
    
    @uroosakhalid you're fine! I didn't think you were at all :D    
    
    
    Photo: Did I mention how excited I am to see this movie? http://tumblr.com/xcp86vzwh    
    
    
    Photo: “An extraordinary 11-part event, narrated by Oprah Winfrey, sundays 8PM.” http://tumblr.com/xcp86w3c3    
    
    
    Photo: alyssaaajeann: I totally watched this movie yesterday! It gets me everytime. http://tumblr.com/xcp86w774    
    
    
    "Baby, what’s your sign - tell me yours, I’ll tell you mine." - Timbaland, If We Ever Meet Again http://tumblr.com/xcp87wja9    
    
    
    Man, I miss football.    
    
    
    Video: major props kids, props. http://tumblr.com/xcp8cflem    
    
    
    Video: If you haven’t seen this yet, do it now. HAHAHAHA… http://tumblr.com/xcp8clfgd    
    
    
    Video: Soooo…. I’m totally determined to learn how to do this. This is so flipping beast. Skillz. (: http://tumblr.com/xcp8fca0z    
    
    
    Photo: Thee cutest thing. http://tumblr.com/xcp8fnkzg    
    
    
    Video: PIXELS. Amazing visual effects. This is legit stuff, right here. http://tumblr.com/xcp8fo9wt    
    
    
    4AM, and my cell explodes. It txtbombed itself, holding back all the txts sent to my cell since 12AM. wow, definite fail.    
    
    
    "Congratulations! You’ve been selected to the 2009-2010 KTBB Scholastic All-Stars Team." http://tumblr.com/xcp8vm2uu    
    
    
    Q:when r u coming back to visit ca? A:June 6th to the 23rd! woo. I will see you then? (:... http://formspring.me/julieannluna/q/451045007    
    
    
    Q:the question was...you know...pile.. A:Hahahaha, ummm well yes I do know someone by that ... http://formspring.me/julieannluna/q/451060589    
    
    
    Q:who's pumped for prooom?! :D A:Meee(: & I'm pretty sure my friend Antley is pretty pumped... http://formspring.me/julieannluna/q/451074127    
    
    
    @uroosakhalid ahhh, I know! I feel so bad that I couldn't be there :P    
    
    
    & HAPPY BIRTHDAY (: @uroosakhalid    
    
    
    is so outofhermind bored that she has resulted to twitter as a way of escape.    
    
    
    This lack of focus is killing me.    
    
    
    @xo_vw duhhh, I always go ;D ...haha.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 hahaha. It was soo good to see yo face!    
    
    
    @jamiafbabyy sorry, I suck at this. Same goes for #dancemovement, it's been too long!    
    
    
    Video: This… is… depressing… or really funny, i’m not so sure? http://tumblr.com/xcp97qev3    
    
    
    looking at lookbook.nu    
    
    
    so I just update here?    
    
    
    RIP, mt.    
    
    
    facebooking.    
    
    
    http://ohmythatsawesome.com/    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/dgswcd    
    
    
    I've literally seen five cars pulled over in the last ten minutes, dang...    
    
    
    CHill @ the Cowboy's stadium! Let's gooooo(;    
    
    
    #NP, Patrot Singers & University Chorale.& sitting with Katlyn Willingham!(: http://twitpic.com/3ffdj7    
    
    
    I freaking love Philip DeFranco.    
    
    
    @uroosakhalid awww, yay (: "what's going on?!"    
    
    
    @Gamer_Ely thanks Ely!!!! :D but I have no idea what you were referring to in that last tweet, lol.    
    
    
    @Gamer_Ely I know! I'm really bad with twitter.    
    
    
    Audio: Eight days, until that California sun. This is unbelieveable. http://tumblr.com/xcpany9gg    
    
    
    They're finally showing summer movie trailers!!! #soexcited    
    
    
    "What do you think of when I say Wild Wild West?" "Texas" "...which is in the South."    
    
    
    has an AWESOME guy friend that bought lunch for her, how sweet (:    
    
    
    is so ready for summer vacation!    
    
    
    is trying out txt twittering?    
    
    
    likes you a lot lot - thinks you're really hot hot.    
    
    
    Getting my teeth cleaned! :D    
    
    
    Q:Where are you going in Cali?  A:The bay area! (: Visting my home town, probably stopping by San Francisco. I miss ... http://4ms.me/929yPI    
    
    
    Q:I LOVE YOU!!!!! A:& that makes you awesome, I probably love you too. Haha. http://4ms.me/aJ8MKA    
    
    
    Packing for California, I promise I didn't procrastinate! I have a legitimate reason to why I haven't yet!    
    
    
    in Dallas, four hours from now I will be in CA. How I love my parents (:    
    
    
    About to  start boarding the plane to CA! (:    
    
    
    is in El Paso, Texas.    
    
    
    I just saw a 40ish year old blonde woman with a purple stripe in her hair! BEAST! (;    
    
    
    & I just saw another 40ish blonde girl IN A ROMPER! LMAO! No lie! HAHAHAHAHA!    
    
    
    I have the cutest little boy behind me on this flight to San Jose! I like this flight already! (:    
    
    
    Guys - an appropriately sized polo, black fitted jeans, plus awesome kicks = one badask outfit (;    
    
    
    ...extremely bored    
    
    
    I'm sorry California, 102.3 is better then 94.9 (;    
    
    
    I spent way too much money at GREAT MALL!    
    
    
    tired of stress    
    
    
    @hyperblonde428:  does this work?    
    
    
    @hyperblonde428: Hmmm. I wonder, what's so cool about twitter anyways?    
    
    
    ready to get this week over with...    
    
    
    Personality Pageant, today - be there.    
    
    
    I got that Boom Boom Pow.    
    
    
    Highlighter try-outs. Wish me luck.    
    
    
    Taylor Lautner & Selena Gomez, say it ain't so :(    
    
    
    Lazy, lazy, lazy.    
    
    
    LASICK SURGERY, gives me chills...    
    
    
    chilling at Lake Tyler.    
    
    
    The early bird, gets the worm.    
    
    
    Officially a High School Aerospace Scholar (:    
    
    
    Whytheheck am I tearing up at Logan's graduation?    
    
    
    AP testing!! joy...    
    
    
    Short hair or long hair? (:    
    
    
    @hyperblonde428: ha ha ha (:    
    
    
    @hyperblonde428: I Love You!    
    
    
    & then, I fell in love with NYC.    
    
    
    @weirdnews: What IS that!?    
    
    
    "Just do it.. you’re never going to see these people again!" - Facebook likes http://tumblr.com/xcpbz13qj    
    
    
    @mikeyphillips: Hey!    
    
    
    EPIC FAIL!    
    
    
    Cute Shoes: http://tinyurl.com/awesome001    
    
    
    & just Gorilla Zoe, I'm goneeeeeeeeeeeeeeee - and you're alone in my eh-echo eh-eh-ehco.    
    
    
    My Fave Actresses: Angelina Jolie, Jennifer Connelly, Megan Fox, Jessica Stroup and Jessica Lowndes.    
    
    
    is the Queen of Justice. Cause I'm marching in a parade ;D    
    
    
    EPIC FAIL!!!!! part two!    
    
    
    Long night, fun night ;D    
    
    
    My poor shoulder is supersore...    
    
    
    My Fortune Cookie: "Accept the challenge, so that you may feel the exhilaration of victory."    
    
    
    forgot how hot Texas weather is… http://tumblr.com/xcpc5iqe2    
    
    
    is studying, a lot :(    
    
    
    10 things Ryloves understand... - Elves will capture giants. We play tag, elbow style. Okay, this tree is a... http://tumblr.com/xcpc8xpgy    
    
    
    Photo: tmrw, tmrw, tmrw, tmrw, tmrw, tmrw. http://tumblr.com/xcpccrrp5    
    
    
    has an hour before Eclipse! (: http://tumblr.com/xcpcfvfaz    
    
    
    @RealLadyGaga: The Fame / Boys, boys, boys    
    
    
    Break Bad Habits: http://tinyurl.com/awesome002    
    
    
    spring break, I need you ...now.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 Yea! I saw it the Friday it came out, got the soundtrack forsurre! lol, what didya think?    
    
    
    Bitten by an ant :(    
    
    
    "Love is what you live for." - Angelina Jolie http://tumblr.com/xcpdh5byz    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 ohmygaaa!!! I just saw this :D :D :D #bestfriends    
    
    
    Freshman orientation totally reminds me of RYLA, I’m thinking I made the right college choice (; http://tumblr.com/xcpdk472o    
    
    
    @ImStillCam & I know where you work!! haha.    
    
    
    @joesum_32 haha, thanks (:    
    
    
    @tweetlessjenna = turntopdog394    
    
    
    Research paper? Exam? Group project? done. http://pinterest.com/pin/168462842281594971/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    @God_is_real25 lies.    
    
    
    @God_is_real25 hahahahahaha.    
    
    
    @God_is_real25 traitor? what are you talking about!    
    
    
    @jjcastmoney @997now @LettyBRadio you deserve those tickets!    
    
    
    trippy... http://lights.elliegoulding.com     
    
    
    hahaha, someone do this with me! greatest workout ever <3 http://pinterest.com/pin/168462842281640043/ …    
    
    
    fyi, if you've ever written me a card/letter or made me something. I probably still have it hidden somewhere (; #reminiscing    
    
    
    internet connection is sooooooo slow #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    Sara Bareilles makes my day #NP #goodmorningsongs    
    
    
    Billie Jean is not my lover, she's just a girl that thinks I'm the one. But the kid is not my son. #throwback #wooh #heee #NP    
    
    
    @ScottKGood No! What album is that one from?    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 I miss ab workouts with ya!    
    
    
    @ScottKGood I'll definitely listen to it when I get the chance! I'll probably love it too, haha.    
    
    
    #fouledout    
    
    
    hahahahahahaha, ohmygod @ScottKGood, you made my week! you're right, hilarious!    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 gahh! ditto (: I will visit soon, promise.    
    
    
    @__Mr__Wrong tell me more! lol.    
    
    
    Using @NBA via twitter to keep up with the game #notv, this depresses me.    
    
    
    A good way to spend a saturday night #beales #streetflippers #peoplearecrazy    
    
    
    @sarah_lynn504 (: yessss! reunion.    
    
    
    New sidewalks? Look at you @UTTyler #upgrade pic.twitter.com/dISLvm0N    
    
    
    I feel like I just went back in time #nostalgia #timeline    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 hahaha, woops. #sorrybro    
    
    
    astronomical numbers with @JordanAntley1 #becareful    
    
    
    Scream, Usher #np #ohbabybaby #myjam    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 rrrrright? lol. This is why we're #friendsforevaa!    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 #sooohgoood    
    
    
    <3! Bring on more movies RT @GeekTyrant: Ryan Reynolds is Officially THE HIGHLANDER http://rant.to/MzLyGp  by @JoeyPaur at @GeekTyrant    
    
    
    Movie News - ‘Jack the Giant Killer’ Writer Tackling ‘Carmen Sandiego’... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyOCiVi0     
    
    
    Overheard: Tim Burton: So, I was thinking of making a movie about... Johnny Depp: Yes. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyOEr3BF     
    
    
    "@katrinajflores: #SYTYCD TOP 20 TONIGHT!!!" <3! so sxcited!    
    
    
    What do I stand for? Most nights, I don't know anymore... #np #somenights #fun #andthatsalright    
    
    
    family bonding time #dallasbound    
    
    
    Why I love IKEA :D #cutefurniture #500daysofsummer #food #furniturenames #karlsted #flurge    
    
    
    Who has a WhatsApp Messenger? #letmeknow #downloadit http://whatsapp.com/dl/     
    
    
    Thanks @tweetlessjenna for the #whatsapp recommendation ;D #thisisfun    
    
    
    @rc903holmes that's deep thinking! haha.    
    
    
    @rc903holmes haha, I feelya!!    
    
    
    Soooooo excited! (: "Where does a monster go to become a top scarer? Monsters University, of course." http://di.sn/l08     
    
    
    sunday morning (: #howsweetthesound    
    
    
    @Buntacular haha, #ifeelya. I unfriend people when their statuses make me question their sentence structure capabilities...    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1, I bet I know what your plans are for the night...    
    
    
    Watched Men in Black 3 today! #willsmith still has it :D bring on #moremovies, please. #faveactor <3    
    
    
    Baby, oh baby. My sweet baby, you're the one. #np #backintime    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 say whaaat? #shock #noway #unbelievable #idontthinkyourereallygoingtobed    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 #seeitoldyou    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 #insomnia #biologicalclock    
    
    
    @Joz25 hahaha, I'm in that same boat :P    
    
    
    replacing old contacts with new ones #icansee #helloworld #thatsbetter    
    
    
    My phone just deleted all my texts #wellthatsjustgreat    
    
    
    @rc903holmes hahaha, I did have an ipod at one point. that counts right? ;D    
    
    
    yay! @SarahAnnBaker1 (: follow her!    
    
    
    Happy 4th of July! To celebrate, I'll watch Independence Day (; http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l31UUl5SyXk …    
    
    
    #doitforamerica    
    
    
    Why am I up? #gobacktosleep    
    
    
    Spider Man was #freakingamazing! Andrew Garfield  was brillant. #newfave    
    
    
    Got a condo on my wrist girl, I'm chasin' out #NP "@CerromeRussell: I'm cashin out? I'm outta cash I know that for sure"    
    
    
    Seriously just had the longest conversation with a complete stranger. #howisthatpossible    
    
    
    @_Jay9_ watcha reading?    
    
    
    What's so new about #NewTwitter?    
    
    
    Nevermind. Oh man, that's legit.    
    
    
    Woop, headed to Dallas! It's been awhile since I booked a shoot #work    
    
    
    @66JakeMartin I can't decide whether you're being sarcastic or not, haha.    
    
    
    Song for the Legend by Caitlin Timmins #np #youtubefind    
    
    
    gahh! representation in New York? pleasepleaseplease. #fingerscrossed    
    
    
    @JayJudeh haha, uhmm. Well, my agency is helping me (hopefully) sign a contract with a modeling agency in New York! so exciting (:    
    
    
    Thank you, Facebook for informing me when my friends get engaged. What's next... "So & so is now pregnant." Fantastic.    
    
    
    @justinmagdale (: aw, thank you! how are things?!    
    
    
    I've been up since 4AM, this is sad... #goodmorning #notreally    
    
    
    I'm dying ...@Insanity    
    
    
    @justinmagdale Same here! I'm good. With school around the corner, things better be good!    
    
    
    I like how Christopher Nolan pretty much re-casted his Inception actors for #DarkKnightRises.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 I noticed during the movie! I just wanted to make sure I wasn't the only one, haha.    
    
    
    When I feel like going on a shopping spree -- I go to the dollar store, atleast I do less damage there...    
    
    
    I've embraced the fact that I'm gonna die everyday for the next month or so @Insanity #killsme #everytime    
    
    
    Ha! @GoDJ23, you & I both know you don't really believe that statement.    
    
    
    @SCsoph I haven't had this good of a workout in a long time! & getting easier? Not soon, that's for sure. Give me your willpower!!    
    
    
    No Church in the Wild, workout jams #np @Insanity, Day 6 #iworkout #itry #idie    
    
    
    @CbeezyBaby forrealz?    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 @kneecoleM #twitterlessparker I am in August!(: Remember, I promised I'd visit.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 @kneecoleM ...a random date? But I might have given you that estimate. haha, that's a good estimated time of arrival.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 K! Sounds like a plan @kneecoleM - can you visit later that month?!    
    
    
    @CbeezyBaby Woop! Good for you!    
    
    
    @kneecoleM @GoDJ23 Austin! :D    
    
    
    Float on, Modest Mouse #np #andwellallfloaton #anyway    
    
    
    refusing to leave the house because it's way too hot to go outside #texasprobs #summerprobs    
    
    
    Before @Insanity was cool, there was Hip Hop Abs with Shaun T! #whodhavethunkit http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyQTH7Br     
    
    
    @Insanity #weworkout ...at 11PM @SarahAnnBaker1 @twitterlessamanda @twitterlessdevon    
    
    
    oooh Dallas radio stations, Lovers & Friends #np #oldschool #throwback    
    
    
    @rc903holmes are you here?!!    
    
    
    @rc903holmes come say hiiii!    
    
    
    @cooljunior13 I know (: let's do it again!    
    
    
    Watching Youtube videos of #sxephil and #kevjamba, I'm probably only going to get an hours worth of sleep. Ugh, no sleep fail.    
    
    
    lol, I need to start watching the amazing race #TeamJamba (:    
    
    
    This has been one crazy weekend...    
    
    
    #rushhour...    
    
    
    I'm trying to sleep but my thoughts are like, "Muahaha, NEVERRR!!" #ineednyquil    
    
    
    @tweetlessjenna I need to get you addicted to twitter, follow @EW or something for pop culture updates! #yourkryptonite    
    
    
    I hear birds chirping ...tweeting(; I guess it wouldn't hurt to get some sleep.    
    
    
    "Do you model for Victoria's Secret?" -VS Associate & random customer #whomeee? #mademyday (:    
    
    
    @Joz25 Haha, watcha talking about?    
    
    
    @NeetaJoseph what in the world are you tweeting about?! Haha.    
    
    
    @Joz25 I tweet alll the time!!    
    
    
    @NeetaJoseph ewww, hahaha. I was like, whaat is she watching?!!    
    
    
    You'd think I'd learn my lesson on waiting last minute to buy a parking permit...    
    
    
    @erickamichellee hahaha, #sosad #sotrue    
    
    
    @rc903holmes hahaha, you found another tall asian?!    
    
    
    "@mayelacat: @julieannluna Expansion facebook rage right now >>>" <3 <3 <3    
    
    
    @ChaCrazy1904 real talk tho, real talk forsuree. Haha.    
    
    
    It's all about who you know #learnit #liveit    
    
    
    last person in the library #responsiblestudentpoints    
    
    
    @ChaCrazy1904 @ToddKnowles oooh, no problem! you're welcome, you're welcome. haha.    
    
    
    So excited for my photoshoot with Edwin Watson! On my way @FordModels ;D    
    
    
    I'm texting at the gas station. Guy goes, "wanna real number to put in your phone?" #pickuplines #ohplease    
    
    
    @ImStillCam I agree, definitely #ladykilla    
    
    
    @Jared_Tucker oh man, I'm in love! Hahaha.    
    
    
    it's snowing in Dallas!    
    
    
    slowly... dwindling... away... D: @SarahAnnBaker1    
    
    
    "@GoDJ23: I have no idea why Native Americans interest me so damn much, but they do #possibleancestors" @twitterlessparker    
    
    
    @cooljunior13 once in a blue moon! #fullmoon #supaacool    
    
    
    Floating the Comal! #whyisalltherumgone    
    
    
    Breakfast at Tiffany's (:    
    
    
    Me & @ColleenMcDeezy will now proceed with giving @SarahAnnBaker1  the silent treatment...    
    
    
    Rin on the Rox (:    
    
    
    I've auditioned for Leah Clearwater.    
    
    
    #nightowl    
    
    
    VMAs (:    
    
    
    Awwww, I love #ladygaga    
    
    
    Thinks @RinontheRox are amazing! Rin looks like Kimora (:    
    
    
    Making posters with my Expansion loves for College Night at Oliveto! <3<3<3.    
    
    
    I plan to use twitter more.    
    
    
    Ellen's 8th season premiere :D    
    
    
    Get on my level @rc903holmes!    
    
    
    @rc903holmes No drink in hand!!    
    
    
    8 drunk guys vs. a flat tire. Who wins?    
    
    
    My SGA campaign websites are now open for business ;D    
    
    
    I swear, I eat like 8 meals a day #yumm #foooood #dontjudge    
    
    
    All means, if you wanna listen to My Humps in your big red truck. Cool. Blasting it out your windows while alone... #impressionswillbemade    
    
    
    Expansion is Going Greek! <3<3<3 love my girls (:    
    
    
    @SarahAnnBaker1 singleeee partayyy guurlz! #iaintnowifey #ladies&thedrinks    
    
    
    #ionlycamefortheb*tches&thedrinks    
    
    
    @Blake_Bristow thank you! (:    
    
    
    Passing out handbills is such an interesting way to spend time, haha.    
    
    
    @SweetHeart_212 (: (: (: thank you! if only my hair was as cool as yours :P    
    
    
    There was way too much contact in that flag football game tonight, haha.    
    
    
    The 4G network is ridiculously fast in Dallas.    
    
    
    @rc903holmes Hahahaha, should've been playing!    
    
    
    @ImStillCam y'all already know it ;D    
    
    
    @rc903holmes you, as in me? Why am I getting hurt?    
    
    
    @ImStillCam can't help it! Haha #allstar #mvp ...just kidding.    
    
    
    @rc903holmes lol, don't get hurt! Everyone else is like half your size.    
    
    
    "@mayelacat: @julieannluna #phonetag -_-;" we're too good at that game :P    
    
    
    A yellow camaro isn't cool unless it has its black stripes #bumbleebee    
    
    
    @MikeaHoIic are you still playing intramural football with @ImStillCam & me!?    
    
    
    Just spent an hour in Sephora <3    
    
    
    "Girl, you look exactly like Kimora Lee Simmons!" Awww, thanks (:    
    
    
    @SarahAnnBaker1 we are so opposites right now! haha.    
    
    
    #whenlifegivesyoulemonsaddvodka    
    
    
    @Ale__Sanchez haha, I wonder why!? Doesn't @ashleyaparicio3 look familiar too?    
    
    
    VOTING STARTS NOW! http://tumblr.com/xzujbhea0    
    
    
    VOTE JULIE ANN APODERADO FOR FRESHMAN/BUSINESS SENATOR >> http://tumblr.com/xzujbht97    
    
    
    @TimoCampbell & @Sainandan: Cool you have Twitter! (:    
    
    
    I need longer weekends #notexcitedformonday    
    
    
    Finally watching The Michael Jackson Memorial on the DVR.    
    
    
    ...after being inside for hours #ohmygodthisweatherisbeautiful    
    
    
    Goodbye social life, I must get my priorities in order.    
    
    
    It took every ounce of will power I had to drag myself out of bed this morning #goodmorning #whyyyyy #idontwanna    
    
    
    @ImStillCam better watch his back! haha. Where were you @MikeaHoIic !?    
    
    
    Not sleepy :/    
    
    
    I've forgotten what sleep is... #bringonthemidterms    
    
    
    @NeimanJohnson heyhey! :D I can't see your emoiji #teamandroid    
    
    
    #NP 2 Reasons #ladies&thedrinks ...how is this song not number 1 on the charts!!!?    
    
    
    @JambaJuice needs a loyalty program! #strawberrieswild & #parmesanpretzels ...yummz. I'd be drowning in points.    
    
    
    Without caffeine, I would die. @Pepsi addict.    
    
    
    I have never seen these many tall guys under one roof in my life...    
    
    
    "@Ale__Sanchez: Myy new friend @julieannluna and uhhh @ashleyaparicio3 :P still love you lol pic.twitter.com/rJPk3dtW" yay! :D    
    
    
    @ashleyaparicio3 @lxve_x_lxgacy @kshberrystudmuf @twill012 @arobyadigg Monday Funday!! White or brown??    
    
    
    happybirthday! @rc903holmes (: #birthdaycake    
    
    
    Ryan Reynolds is Greenlantern! (:    
    
    
    lol, "The Green Lantern is now following you on Twitter" (:    
    
    
    I was supposed to be extra productive this morning ...there goes that plan. #storyofmylife    
    
    
    "@Ale__Sanchez: Every time I see @julieannluna she has a huge smile on her face. #happyallthetime" Hahaha, you do too!    
    
    
    @xxjamia ...where's your girlfriend at? Imma get her!    
    
    
    @WhatIsJoeDoing good job tonight!!    
    
    
    Round 2! Where ya at?! @ashleyaparicio3 @twitterlessramiro? @twill012 @kshberrystudmuf @lxve_x_lxgacy @twill012 @ArobYaDigg @BrandonOrtega30    
    
    
    @kshberrystudmuf @ArobYaDigg @ashleyaparicio3 @BrandonOrtega30 @lxve_x_lxgacy @twill012 who!? get back over here!    
    
    
    @ArobYaDigg @ashleyaparicio3 @twill012 @kshberrystudmuf @lxve_x_lxgacy @BrandonOrtega30 I approve!    
    
    
    @lxve_x_lxgacy @ashleyaparicio3 @twill012 @kshberrystudmuf @ArobYaDigg @BrandonOrtega30 Do you even have to ask?    
    
    
    @_blessedsince92 OH hiii, yes I do remember you! Haha.    
    
    
    @_blessedsince92 good! How are you?    
    
    
    Happy Halloween, let's get dressed up! http://instagr.am/p/Rcz6W-M-CY/     
    
    
    @_blessedsince92 I try to! It's just too much of a distraction #collegestudentprobz haha.    
    
    
    @P4ULON4V4RRO lol, extremely happy. Haha, I was at a runway casting at my agency. Sooo many of them! :P    
    
    
    @ToddKnowles @Blake_Bristow @ChaCrazy1904 @dylangroce Hoped you stocked up on candy!! Shenandoah doesn't play games with #trickortreating    
    
    
    @JennaEmmert soooooo adorbs!    
    
    
    Ambition is sexy (; #getsome    
    
    
    Social media & class should never mix... @ColleenMcDeezy @_JessicaRaee @youngestdoingit    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 seeeee you soon!?    
    
    
    Enjoying this nice weather.    
    
    
    The Proposal again, today (:    
    
    
    Mooyahh with my girls!  @NeimanJohnson @TwitterlessToni    
    
    
    I want to do something lifechanging.    
    
    
    @JeffreyPang I know right? lol.    
    
    
    4th Largest Mall in the US of A (:    
    
    
    #BlackFriday work shift, I need a red bull.    
    
    
    Jaycee's Christmas Parade! Cold & waiting for @jamie2596 yay, haha. #TylerPride    
    
    
    #Lincoln is doing great in theaters? #ohtheirony    
    
    
    VSFS Drinking Game, I'm down. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyYgEB2O     
    
    
    @GoDJ23 #phoneproblems? I feel ya.    
    
    
    #childsitdown, lmao lmao lmao.    
    
    
    @aubryroach @tyrabanks Aw, thanks Aubry! It's all thanks to your awesome photography skills.    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 highlight of my day, yayaya :D    
    
    
    Spent 5+ hours walking around Fry's Electronics with my dad #whattateam #techlove    
    
    
    We were headed out to Dallas, changed our minds #TexasSnow #WhiteChristmas @ I20 http://instagr.am/p/TrRwI4M-Mc/     
    
    
    Merry Christmas y'alllll #babyitscoldoutside http://instagr.am/p/TrU5z_s-BC/     
    
    
    Ohmygosh, it's freaking cold...    
    
    
    Pulled an all nighter for a LOTR marathon #ThanksHobbit    
    
    
    My cousins got a yorkie puppy! #sofluffyimgonnadie  johannah111 jamieapoderado http://instagr.am/p/UC75A_s-BD/     
    
    
    @morganmthompson @aubryroach forsure! I'm in, I must see you both asap :D    
    
    
    Pray for me. I'm spending my 21st bday weekend on 6th street @SarahAnnBaker1 @Amanda_Lynn1209    
    
    
    #ForOneDayIWishICouldHangWith: Bumblebee, Will Smith, Angelina Jolie, Walt Disney, Michael Bay, Santa Claus, John Lasseter, Ellen DeGeneres.    
    
    
    tweet.    
    
    
    Willow Smith is sooooo adorable!    
    
    
    Boo, school. C'mon springgg breaaak! @Amanda_Lynn1209 @SarahAnnBaker1    
    
    
    @JambaJuice #Healthy habits sweepstakes! A year of #Jamba Smoothies, sign me up!! http://bit.ly/Yuy8VV     
    
    
    #ifihadglass I'd be broke. Does anyone want to donate $1,500? I'll follow you around and help you google things that need googling (:    
    
    
    @mileszeorlin snoooowboarding <3!!    
    
    
    So.....Julia Jones as Leah?    
    
    
    @SarahAnnBaker1 maybe because we were all asleep, haha.    
    
    
    @tweetlessjenna 45 DAYS!! (:    
    
    
    @lilhoite08 where you at!?    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 yeesssssss!    
    
    
    @SnapBackMac92 thee bestest!    
    
    
    "@Blackjack_Billy: It's 7:55am if ur just now stumbling home you definitely need to download The Booze Cruise." I second this statement.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 I am never going to see you again... ):    
    
    
    #confession: I have an irrational fear of dentists.    
    
    
    It's kinda disturbing how slow my day is going... thanks #SpringBreak.    
    
    
    Beer Pong for Dummies: http://bit.ly/13cmWk1  #saveafreshman    
    
    
    CVS coupons for stomach remedies, pain relief, vitamins, and body washes. #SpringBreak discounts? Haha.    
    
    
    I have to be Dallas bound in 4 hours. #whydoidothistomyself #noctural    
    
    
    Starting the day right with @JambaJuice #strawberrieswild    
    
    
    A trip to Dallas isn't complete without going to @innoutburger #daymade #myfave    
    
    
    "@NatGeo: Exploring the cloud forests of Monteverde in Costa Rica: http://on.natgeo.com/WHadRl " Done! The sights were surreal. #headintheclouds    
    
    
    @KsigFernie YES! But I had to work the entire day. Next time I'm in town we're catching up!!    
    
    
    Tyler's @Outback staff was extra nice to me tonight, I wonder why? #goodtipforyou    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 Haha, they were all female! I felt like I was a food critic or something #icouldgetusedtothis    
    
    
    Stolen from @blackjack_billy's twitter. Shooting for #TheBoozeCruise! Check them out (: #MyJam… http://instagram.com/p/XQktiFs-OP/     
    
    
    If we wait until we're ready, we'll be waiting for the rest of our lives. #lemonysnicket #favequote #lifeplans #go    
    
    
    Oh, Texas weather you slay me #icantfeelmyfingers    
    
    
    Photo: yes, please. #chocolatechip #cookiemonster #foodsplurge http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyhASDK8     
    
    
    "Julie's Phone: where texts go to die & be forgotten." #youresofunny #nottrue #okaymaybealittletrue    
    
    
    Mooar @passionpit please? #crylikeaghost #nowplaying #jammin    
    
    
    #StudyPods Blog: 25 Techniques to Help You Study http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyhFJlj4     
    
    
    Photo: Why, hello there. #smile #hair #goodhairday #happy http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyhLvDUg     
    
    
    Photo: Kappa Sig Semi-Formal (: http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyhVD6ay     
    
    
    I actually really liked #TheHost. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyhcIoPB     
    
    
    The best #AprilFools Day video, pretty hilarious. http://bit.ly/X8LMfA  #gotcha #prank #funny #ithinkitshilarious    
    
    
    Photo: 21st with the birthday girl (: #yamato #dinner #happybirthday #letscelebrate #woopwoop http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyhma0dg     
    
    
    You know it's true. http://instagram.com/p/XTiJnCRPGY/  #collegesmarts #sleepprobz    
    
    
    Idk, my bff @jordanantley1. #reunion #fave #missyou #wearetan http://instagram.com/p/XsZf7os-Ag/     
    
    
    Figuring out how to use this baby. #helloworld http://dblr.me/s/1fn3QX  @Dubbler    
    
    
    @Gamer_Ely Ouch. Not cool.    
    
    
    "@hitRECordJoe: Alright folks, lunch is over.  Pleasure conversing with you all <3" Crap. I missed it!!    
    
    
    Some people just have to learn lessons the hard way. #lessonlearned    
    
    
    It's a Monday... #icouldcry    
    
    
    Driving to Dallas is kicking my butt. #youwin #thankyoucruisecontrol    
    
    
    I'm gonna take this itty bitty world by storm. And I'm just getting warm. #mamasaidknockyouout #np    
    
    
    It's like riding a bike, you never forget. Except now, you notice the seat is significantly less… http://instagram.com/p/X51pSRM-Bn/     
    
    
    "Wanna see how animals eat their food?" HAHAHAHA! #animalseatingfood http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyiKboEm     
    
    
    Now this is just getting awkward.    
    
    
    #CurrentPlaylist: Cruise @FLAGALine, Born to Ride @Blackjack_Billy, Perfect Girl @moonshineband. Um, what's happening? #whendidigocountry <3    
    
    
    Carpe Diem, right? #seizethday #imalloverthat    
    
    
    #nowplaying @alt_J Do you know where the wild things go? #Breezeblocks #lalalala    
    
    
    @JesseBerger1 me too! #teamandroid    
    
    
    "@mychereseamour: @julieannluna Hi, I miss you. <3" (:(:(: Miss you more!! It's been too long.    
    
    
    I am not an #earlybird.    
    
    
    Or a #morningperson.    
    
    
    "@ellehcimnehs: #cheerstotheweekend" yes.    
    
    
    Photo: Goodbye @pinkclover06 with @stachelschweinn @emili2488. #goodbyeparty #missyou #houstonbound... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyiWWCPo     
    
    
    I may live in a small town, but that doesn't make me a small town girl.    
    
    
    Just had the most interesting convo of my life. Ha, life just throwing those dang curveballs. #thingsjustgotinteresting    
    
    
    Awesome shoot with edwin_watson today! Followed by a fun night to the tune of his DJ jamz.… http://instagram.com/p/YE65ItM-F5/     
    
    
    @PhillyD when will you start looking for new interns??    
    
    
    @PhillyD Also, if you weren't a famous youtuber what would you be doing with your life?    
    
    
    Having close medical aide prob saved a lot of lives. Warmed my <3 to see who rushed to help. Don't lose faith in humanity. #BostonMarathon    
    
    
    Photo: Life tips & giant jenga at #Barcadia. Left a note. #dallasagain #fun #bamf http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyioj276     
    
    
    Darkness cannot drive out darkness, only light can do that.    
    
    
    @J_Bell91 um, hello. Remember me? Haha. #nonexistentfriend    
    
    
    "I'm tryna get up in your frame like a photograph."    
    
    
    My wildest dream is coming true!!! I'm moving to Japan. http://m.hollywoodreporter.com/news/iron-man-3-become-first-440359 …    
    
    
    Yes. All men must die. But we are not men. @GameOfThrones, you are my tv addiction.    
    
    
    @aubryroach #preach    
    
    
    7 days until New York and @tweetlessjenna (: #besties #ilovenewyork    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 Me!? Noooo. I have no recollection of that incident... #ohwait, ahmm @tweetlessjenna...    
    
    
    Drink. More. Water. #lifegoal #chugchugchug    
    
    
    Why is everything exploding!? Factory explosion in Waco, TX. #StaySafe #Waco #TexasStrong (Explosion at :28) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ROrpKx3aIjA&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    @morganmthompson same here!! We need to do that more often (: I demand more of you and @aubryroach in my life!    
    
    
    @aubryroach @morganmthompson <3<3<3!    
    
    
    Watching the game, watching the news, on twitter. #toomuch #multitasker    
    
    
    @P4ULON4V4RRO #icanbreathenow    
    
    
    Hang in there world. You've had a rough week.    
    
    
    All I can say is 'MERICA. #Boston #Hospitals http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyi-0C9M     
    
    
    Well, that's infuriating. Seriously people? #youhadonejob    
    
    
    Eh, no big deal... didn't miss much at Coachella, looks lame. #imlying #wishiwasthere #coachellavated #bringmenext https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8NFDlOwM6zY&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    I don't know where you're going but do you got room for one more troubled soul? @falloutboy #instantreplay #nowplaying    
    
    
    If you ever get cold, you just have to hack it. Cause I'll be cold too if I gave you my jacket. #stillmyjam @TheRealRyanHiga @kevjumba    
    
    
    I should just move to Australia... #problemsolved #nocturnal #insomnia    
    
    
    @Blackjack_Billy I'm both excited & terrified to finally see this final cut! Haha. Super excited for you guys!!    
    
    
    Photo: #NYC in the morning! Can’t wait to see my favorite. I should probably finish packing… #excited... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyjQ7SV3     
    
    
    Ok, seriously. Packing now. #NYC here I come. #procrastination at its finest.    
    
    
    Packed. And headed to the airport. Spending the next couple of hours on @SouthwestAir! #NYCbound #thebigapple #imback    
    
    
    @rbmattson @DallasLoveField I was just about to tweet the same thing! #majorupgrade    
    
    
    (: #NewYorkNewYork    
    
    
    Totally forgot about the time change. Thought I had another hour left on this plane. #imfree #yes    
    
    
    Accents make everything better. #keeptalking #please    
    
    
    @mDolinsk needs to use twitter more often!    
    
    
    Having awesome guy friends beats having a jerk boyfriend, anyday (;    
    
    
    Photo: Just strolling on the Highline. All I’m missing is a cute puppy. #nyc #justchilling #iwanticecream http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyjWsqrq     
    
    
    Photo: Look what I got! Red Velvet Cakemelt. #ifoundicecream #youlookdelicious #yumm #nyc http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyjW_Xhr     
    
    
    Photo: Happy 21st Birthday @jennsteroni #happybirthday #woopwoop #yourelegal #chugchugchug #21 #drank http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyjZGWGo     
    
    
    @bjl314 #alcoholics    
    
    
    Wait, I know that girl... #Music video debut of #TheBoozeCruise by @blackjack_billy! It'll be your new… http://instagram.com/p/YlKVSps-AX/     
    
    
    @P4ULON4V4RRO ):    
    
    
    #ohheythere    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 #sleepisfortheweak    
    
    
    lights just went out in the UC, lmao.    
    
    
    A drunk couple heard us talking about @GameOfThrones at a bar, told me I HAD to watch this. New York, you slay me.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vEg4SEch27w&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    Late lunch at #ShakeShack. Super delish. #waitedforhours #yumm #foodstagram http://instagram.com/p/Yqbex-M-L6/     
    
    
    Tired, sore, sleepy, and hungry...    
    
    
    Photo: See ya later #NYC. It’s been a blast. The hoodie felt like appropriate travel attire. #obvioustourist... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyjpILYX     
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 Are you from Tennessee? Cause you're the only ten I see... ;D #soclose yet #sofar    
    
    
        
    
    
    Photo: I couldn’t resist… #funny #hilarious #rayj #kimkardashian #ihititfirst #interview http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyjqj0Xs     
    
    
    I have the patience of a 5 year old. Can't wait to get my hands on #googleglass. I can't handle the anticipation. #glassexplorer    
    
    
    Photo: I am so happy and honored to finally share with everyone that today I officially signed with Click... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyjx6tgp     
    
    
    My favorite youtubers visit #NYC after I leave... @PhillyD @Traphik ):    
    
    
    "@pratik33: @julieannluna Congratulations! This summer's going to be unforgettable." You're saying yes to me all summer! Haha.    
    
    
    @bjl314 sooooon! Still hashing out details (:    
    
    
    "There is no remote for your life. If you don't like what you're seeing, get up and change it."    
    
    
    I might have a @reddit #addiction. What have you done, internet? #narwhalbacon    
    
    
    I think @J_Bell91 found his calling. Who would've thought it would involve working with children!? #coach #soccer #gameday #yay    
    
    
    Senioritis kicked in two semesters ago. #imdoomed #finals    
    
    
    Photo: Nobody pinch me. #thisishappening #clickmodels #nyc http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRykYm2CN     
    
    
    30 facts about @GameofThrones the show left out - http://goo.gl/sSNs9     
    
    
    @tompolska92 haha, no! Spoiler free!!    
    
    
    @carolynnwuester Haha, thanks (: technically I am, I'm not a size 2 or 0!    
    
    
    summmmmmmmer!    
    
    
    @lokang_ read my mind!! ;D    
    
    
    Hmmmmmm. Cupcakes or cookies for breakfast? #questionoftheday    
    
    
    The Great Gatsby was amazing, from the great acting to the stylistic cinematography. Had a killer soundtrack too.    
    
    
    Photo: My Netflix account knows me so well. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRykmRQVy     
    
    
    Video: I. Want. This. Dog. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyknnJw4     
    
    
    Don't let that fine girl pass you by. Look real close cause strobe lights lie. #nowplaying #youtubeinspired    
    
    
    Technically, she's the Mother of Dragons... so watching @GameOfThrones counts as a celebration. #justified #mothersday #bearandthemaidenfair    
    
    
    Photo: New watch! #jcp #newfave http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRykzvRpO     
    
    
    Photo: So glad to see her face before she leaves the country!! You’re gonna have so much fun (:... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyk-e_bf     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyl0prV6     
    
    
    Finishing up Ender's Game via audio book. The #bookworm in me feels cheated, such a good read.    
    
    
    #nowplaying I just wanna have a good time. Can I have fun for the rest of my life? #yesplease #thegreatgatsby #soundtrack    
    
    
    @EChaney10 then you have good taste, haha. It was so great. Hopefully the movie won't let us down!    
    
    
    I legitimately want to go to @DallasComicCon this weekend. #dontjudge    
    
    
    Photoset:  http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRylB8th0     
    
    
    J.Mendal for Neiman Marcus. http://instagram.com/p/ZbAiSYs-A0/     
    
    
    anything open today is just ridiculous.    
    
    
    Stopped in traffic on a Dallas bridge. Uhm... Why is it shaking? #dangerzone    
    
    
    Photo: Like #GreatGatsby? I think so. #want #alittleparty #oldsport http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRylfcnIc     
    
    
    #Whoa.    
    
    
    Yes. It is possible to put a contact on top of a contact. #imanidiot #myeyes    
    
    
    Thought about you, @GoDJ23! http://bit.ly/1aG2pCw  #sofresh #dancemovement    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 why are even you tweeting right now? #getyourprioritiesstraight    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 @sdaigle89 @bekah_frazier Wool woop! Let the weekend commence #happyfriday    
    
    
    Photo: This is how I greet my dad Happy Father’s Day! http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRynVeUWd     
    
    
    #HappyBirthday to this 21 year old! #letscelebrate #beachtime #partytime #charleston #recuperating http://instagram.com/p/arDg_fM-E3/     
    
    
    Thanks for killing my liver Charleston, SC. #recuperating #waterfordays #birthdayboys @JordanAntley1 @bekah_frazier @sdaigle89    
    
    
    @bekah_frazier @JordanAntley1 @sdaigle89 but your liver is a victim of Charleston though. Haha.    
    
    
    Cellphone-less until Wednesday. DM me.    
    
    
    @aubryroach I nominate us for the "Most Likely to Eventually Maybe See Each Other Again Sometime in the Future" award. Easy win. #NoContest    
    
    
    @morganmthompson I expect to see you soon eventually sometime like def. near future too!! (:    
    
    
    Photo: Being extra #asian for a harajuku #beautyshoot with @aubryroachofficial. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRypQEa-4     
    
    
    Nothing is more upsetting then trying to watch a movie while an obnoxious conversation takes place right behind you. #movieetiquette    
    
    
    Viva Las Vegas. Goodbye #littlemunchkins! http://instagram.com/p/cIOBp7s-F-/     
    
    
    Photo: Fat Tuesday with @franciskoichi, then up to the Stratosphere! #lasvegas #picsfromlastnight http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyqVrPaz     
    
    
    Vegas strip, Vegas strip, Vegas strip!!    
    
    
    Visiting Fat Tuesday on a Wednesday. #freedrinks and #cherrybombs, I could get used to this.    
    
    
    Baba's Tsi-bugan for breakfast. Yumm. #filipinofood http://instagram.com/p/cM0dDes-GZ/     
    
    
    Winning versus losing. #lasvegas #wizardofoz http://instagram.com/p/cOGCAzM-MT/     
    
    
    @SnapBackMac92 hahaha, got it!    
    
    
    And now I know why my flight to #lasvegas was filled with basketball players! @usabasketball #USABMNT pic.twitter.com/Lp7Ji8ADR9    
    
    
    Photo: Ellie Goulding’s DJ Debut at #SurrenderVegas! #starryeyed #toomanypeople http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyqjMXLJ     
    
    
    #LIGHT tonight at Mandalay Bay! #danceallnight #guestlisting #partayy    
    
    
    LIGHT at Mandalay Bay! #freedrinks #crazylights #circdusoliel #smokyphoto http://instagram.com/p/cTPKkjM-FJ/     
    
    
    I may never leave #Vegas! I could do this all month. #dayclub #deadmau5 #wetrepublic    
    
    
    So glad I got to see franciskoichi and celebrate his belated 21st #birthday! It's been real, Vegas.… http://instagram.com/p/cZ2K6Ks-GV/     
    
    
    I think I left my voice back in Vegas. It's been 3 days... #lostvoice #raspy    
    
    
    Oh oh. I want some more. Oh oh. What you waiting for? #takeabite of my heart tonight. @neontrees #np    
    
    
    Is it too soon to say Home, Sweet Home? #NewYork #concretejungle #movingday    
    
    
    Isn't akorichard super talented?!  #photography #photoshoot #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/cuckjHM-N5/     
    
    
    At the #NYPL getting a library card. Woop. #bookworm #studytime    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 Bahahaha, yes!    
    
    
    I was planning on running every morning but I feel like getting around this city is exercise enough! #nyc #professionalwalkers    
    
    
    Photo: These little munchkins amuse me. #tbt #advancedreaders http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyrsEmgW     
    
    
        
    
    
    eeeeeverybody, rock that booody. #backstreetsback #np    
    
    
    Soo what's so awesome about being #twitterfamous or #instafamous? Is there some #internetprize I don't know about!?    
    
    
    Please note there is a difference between being nice & being naive.    
    
    
    @rc903holmes pshaa, there's no such thing as a stupid question!    
    
    
    "'Maleficent': Angelina Jolie says she terrified real children as Disney villainess: http://bit.ly/1eAu9ug  via @EW" I am soooo excited.    
    
    
    Boom boom boom, even brighter then the moon moon moon.    
    
    
    ohemgeee, too cute. #awww https://vine.co/v/hbQXrhighqA     
    
    
    Photo: Got a sample pair of green contacts the other day …#yaaaatheyrenatural. Haha. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRys6j7qw     
    
    
    Shut up & put your money where your mouth is, that's what you get for waking up in #Vegas. @katyperry #np    
    
    
    Actually, I pretty much have every @katyperry song on my #np list right now.    
    
    
    Video: What to expect when you add me on Snapchat. #lipsync #eeerrybody #backstreetsback #instavideo http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRys8b3mL     
    
    
    "@totalfratmove: "You should have gotten it in writing." #TFM" Actually, everyone should be doing this... #responsiblepersonmove    
    
    
    @J_Bell91 Haha, we'd get along! #prohaggler #bargainshopper    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 hahaha, oops!    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 It kinda scares me how similar we are sometimes. #toomuchalike #maleform #stahpbeinga... (:    
    
    
    @Amanda_Lynn1209 ditched me! #hatechuu -___-    
    
    
    @Amanda_Lynn1209 gotta point there... #pass    
    
    
    Photo: My current mobile gaming addiction. It’s got me hooked. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRysCwTPT     
    
    
    Photoset: campbellmodels: Fun behind the scenes photos of Campbell Talent for a Sprint commercial! First... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRysD2zow     
    
    
    Anonymous asked: How were you discovered? What was your one big break, your defining moment that started... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRysDHAPQ     
    
    
    Photo: I think Google Now watched my Backstreet Boys instavideo… http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRysD_MZ2     
    
    
    That's a bad move. Bad meaning good though. @ZeyiSays #np #talent #getthisguyalabel    
    
    
    "Mama always said, “nice guys finish last.” Beat him at his own game, “honey, take the cash." - Acapella,... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRysFT_nR     
    
    
    Princess Diana #wcw http://instagram.com/p/dADRxWs-AT/     
    
    
    It's official! Signed with @msawomen today, I'm way too excited for my own good. #nyc #newagency #werk http://instagram.com/p/dANOUHs-B2/     
    
    
    @erickambryant Bahaha! That's kinda the goal here ;D #morethemerrier #missssssyou    
    
    
    It feels so good to have a @hm a few blocks away from home. #loveit    
    
    
    @erickambryant you know I want to!    
    
    
    I'm pretty sure Bumblebee just hit on me. #timessquare #mascot    
    
    
    Campbell talent on the set for a Sprint commercial. #tbt #soccer #facepaint http://instagram.com/p/dCZGNhs-Go/     
    
    
    Excuse the baby talk. #tbt #adorable #asian #baby #imissvegas ): http://instagram.com/p/dDZ6pkM-Et/     
    
    
    #ladadedadee    
    
    
    Ahhhh! @PhillyD & @LinzLuvs are getting #married, sooooo happy for them! That proposal was too perfect.    
    
    
    I could put a little stardust in your eyes, put a little sunshine in your life. #MIKAmonday #newfave… http://instagram.com/p/dMxw5Es-HN/     
    
    
    It's internet official! @msawomen #newyork #timessquare #7thave #model http://instagram.com/p/dNnlW1s-N5/     
    
    
    There is no way I'm going to balance school with work in this city. What have I gotten myself into? #notenoughtime #imisssleep #mightdie    
    
    
    Walking is overrated. #imissmycar ...I'm kidding. I'll get used to this eventually. #NYC #publictransportation    
    
    
    Why am I awake? #routine #earlymorning    
    
    
    @LinMargaret11 Yes! for the semester. Wanted to pursue modeling out in #newyork (:    
    
    
    Super excited! #techinmotion    
    
    
    Panelist at #techinmotion just said Twitter is the front page of the internet. How do you feel about that @reddit?    
    
    
    #whoawhoawhoa #holdup "TX voted the least-liked state in America. CA most liked. http://read.bi/155pxLb  pic.twitter.com/DMzUsqyykc"    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 OHMYGOD. #gohomeyouredrunk    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 ...someone needs to take your phone away. Calling @sdaigle89 & @bekah_frazier #getchaboy    
    
    
    About 3 years ago, I came to #NYC for the first time with my drill team and had a blast at this… http://instagram.com/p/dXHXCbM-Ep/     
    
    
    Middle America packed in. Came to see me in my black skin. #np @kanyewest #faveofyeezus #myjam    
    
    
    @JambaJuice time. #everyday #youaremystarbucks    
    
    
    Cheers to the freaking weekend. #friday #heyyladies #allaboutthatnightlife #getlucky http://instagram.com/p/dYd1y9s-AJ/     
    
    
    This furball is a Great Pyrenees Mountain named #Snowball. He's the runt of the litter and weighs 150… http://instagram.com/p/dZvYBSs-PD/     
    
    
    "You look really pretty in that picture! You don't even look asian!!" Oh, thanks! ...wait... #backhandedcompliment #saywhaat    
    
    
    Why yes, I do over analyze everything. #stopitbrain #truewoman    
    
    
    My pride keeps telling me I'm self-sufficient and oh man, that'll be my #downfall.    
    
    
    First NYC photoshoot in the AM. I can't sleep.    
    
    
    Role call! <3 it #everywoman #projectgravitas http://instagram.com/p/dmhpBns-MR/     
    
    
    From the @projectgravitas #photoshoot! Hair by Lauren & Make up by deney_adam. Life is better with… http://instagram.com/p/dp_hrgM-Fx/     
    
    
    Wardrobe surgery with kacey95 & stephcasarotto. #youdabest #nyc #fashiondesign #instagay #gayboy http://instagram.com/p/d3OisjM-Hp/     
    
    
    Foxcroft photoshoot. #poloinspired #fashion #photography #work http://instagram.com/p/d92DDQs-PT/     
    
    
    New York fam <3 #familydinner #latergram #dontleaveme #love #toomuchfun http://instagram.com/p/eA7oGus-Dk/     
    
    
    On the way to ADAM Models #NYFW party. #picsfromtheweekend #partypeople #meatpacking http://instagram.com/p/eA8b_QM-E5/     
    
    
    nickbibs headshot photography! Get with us. #dreamteam #teamwork #photographer #model #werk http://instagram.com/p/eBJzzKs-MB/     
    
    
    @J_Bell91 Also, chemistry lessons!! #itswhatido    
    
    
    I'm listening to an A&F track outside of work. Should I be concerned? #np #catchy #boomboom by Ray Foxx & Rachel Collier    
    
    
    Rude airport attendants. Didn't warn me about the flight change. 12:05 and 12:50 look pretty similar. #lastminutebooking #texasbound #rush    
    
    
    toga toga toga! Reunited! yay, miss her <3 #toga #biffles #truelove #bacardi #party #asian #happy #texas http://instagram.com/p/eRdCOjs-Fk/     
    
    
    Togas with #pikappaphi. Got to see some of my fave people. #sincefreshmen #godblesstexas http://instagram.com/p/eSl7F1M-Or/     
    
    
    I love flying. From #Texas to #NYC (: #travel #beautiful #sunrise #wanderlust http://instagram.com/p/eUnbN_M-Fz/     
    
    
    Dang it #NYC. Last time I was here we were still getting 80 degree weather. Signed, #idiotintheshorts.    
    
    
    @PrezySuavez I expected to see you the night before wearing a toga! Glad I ran into you though, your look of surprise was great! Haha.    
    
    
    Backstage Meetup @ Van Diemens Bar #acting #backstage #networking #openbar #nyc http://instagram.com/p/ebShzls-Ny/     
    
    
    "In my time, the average model’s size was a four or six. Today you are expected to be a size zero." - Tyra... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyvSv6iZ     
    
    
    Happy Birthday Boram! #dinner #friends #birthday #happybirthday #hot #hotties #model #fun http://instagram.com/p/edxKe_M-MW/     
    
    
    Twinning for training! #bubbagump #hostesswiththemostess #lifeislikeaboxofchocolates http://instagram.com/p/ef74ZcM-EM/     
    
    
    This cathedral is breathtaking. #SaintPatricks #SundayMass #catholic #neogothic http://instagram.com/p/elIt9Ys-NE/     
    
    
    Why I'm still up at 5AM... #college #nyc & #jobs http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyvzHABT     
    
    
    To celebrate my little sister's birthday here's some rare footage of us getting along ;D… http://instagram.com/p/esNB3hM-HQ/     
    
    
    herculestrophy Event with @JasonHillard #since4AM #goodmorning #HerculesTrophy #leggo #teambuilding #nyc http://instagram.com/p/ezU7-3M-Cs/     
    
    
    Winter coats with @michaelkors. #winter #leather #fur #fashion #neimanmarcus http://instagram.com/p/fDWmjHM-As/     
    
    
    More #michaekors! #yellow #bright #winter #coat http://instagram.com/p/fDan84s-Gh/     
    
    
    Everything's bigger in Texas. #bighair #curls #lonestar #yaa http://instagram.com/p/fMAJemM-PK/     
    
    
    Sneak peek of our #nyc rooftop video! Videophone Choreography by the oh so talented @bobbynewberry!… http://instagram.com/p/fOahuUM-PY/     
    
    
    Happy Birthday, Cassie! #partyallnight #instabestfriend #birfday #nyc http://instagram.com/p/fUHvBCs-C_/     
    
    
    Party rockers in the house tonight.  #roomies #brassmonkey #picsfromlastnight http://instagram.com/p/fVQCUjM-Jv/     
    
    
    On set for M is for Mixology. Sexy vampire minions. #saturday #featuredextras #shortfilm #acting #dance http://instagram.com/p/fYLtJOM-Kk/     
    
    
    Some of my favorite homies. #fambam #faves #international #loves http://instagram.com/p/fZG-VvM-K5/     
    
    
    Hello Pittsburgh. #homecoming #eastcoasting #itstheweekend http://instagram.com/p/foEmbvs-PG/     
    
    
    That beat at 1:12... #lovelovelove #dance #newfave #katyperry #darkhorse #prism http://instagram.com/p/fybCqns-Fz/     
    
    
    Dance addicts. #heyladies #tgif #goodtimes #night #dance #girls http://instagram.com/p/f7QK3Ts-GE/     
    
    
    Lana Kane, Kitten, Sailor, Cleopatra. #mainchicks #roomies #party #faves #VIP #loves #turntup http://instagram.com/p/f9UGBHM-NN/     
    
    
    Excited for the VMAs!    
    
    
    TAYLOR LAUTNER! (:    
    
    
    It's market season! #fashion #bluejeans #levis #dockers #model #work http://instagram.com/p/gNwEYxM-EJ/     
    
    
    *I will go to the VMAs live one day! (:?    
    
    
    OMG! That was hilarious!    
    
    
    Katy Perry! I love her (:    
    
    
    Out with the girlies. #leopardcubs #giraffe #kitten #halloween #roomies #love http://instagram.com/p/gOVJlBs-Mo/     
    
    
    Ellen should have TSwift on her show! (:    
    
    
    I'm digging this weather.    
    
    
    Definite #tbt! Buzzkill owned. #CHill #highschool #3yrs #seniors #youknow #icroppedoutsomepeople #sorry http://instagram.com/p/gb1jYIM-P5/     
    
    
    Excited for gossipgirl!    
    
    
    All of Times Square. #XBoxOne #NYC #Midnight http://instagram.com/p/hARM9js-BA/     
    
    
    I love these girls. #roomies #love #goodtimes #goodcompany #nyc http://instagram.com/p/hmGyt4s-Ev/     
    
    
    Ciao, arrivederci! I miss you already.<3 #italian #asian #instafriends #BBFF #seeyousoon http://instagram.com/p/hmHQuBM-Fd/     
    
    
    Ladies of the haus. #lastnightinNYC #goodbye #party http://instagram.com/p/hmHh9WM-F4/     
    
    
    Dang it, #TX. Why are you colder than #NYC? #snow #ice #frozen #white http://instagram.com/p/hmKZrMs-LB/     
    
    
    NYC won't be the same without you guys. #clique #family #missingsome #goodtimes #goodcompany #wedabest http://instagram.com/p/hmJNobs-JQ/     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Titan @ Six Flags #overtexas #rollercoaster #cousinbonding #holidayinthepark http://instagram.com/p/ifkFojs-I5/     
    
    
    IHOP for a midnight dinner, delish.    
    
    
    Took on those bleachers in HPC, good workout right there.    
    
    
    heyyyyy, @Joz25! :D    
    
    
    @Joz25 I've had one since forever, I just never use it! How about you?    
    
    
    @Joz25 haha, but you already know all about it! lol. I don't think I've ever had a twitter convo before, haha.    
    
    
    #SuckerPunch is out today! & I can't watch this opening weekend, soo don't talk to me if you've already seen it!    
    
    
    much needed familytime (:    
    
    
    @Joz25 Yup, a few more years and I'm outta here! lol, where are you at?    
    
    
    JCP work in Dallas!(:    
    
    
    It's my dad's Happy Birthday (:    
    
    
    @teejaria thanks for helping me with my April Fools joke! :D    
    
    
    Dinner at Olivetos, http://twitpic.com/382rn8. Harry Potter, you're next!    
    
    
    JCP Headquarters, it's reeaal nice (:    
    
    
        
    
    
    Patriot Days at @UTTyler, CAB Splattered Paint Party tonight!    
    
    
    @ScottKGood lol, and setting up! haha.    
    
    
    @ScottKGood hahaha, sweeeet. And (I might) MC a contest next fall, whaat?! haha.    
    
    
    @ScottKGood yea! that thing, I couldn't think of the name.    
    
    
    Renewing your passport is JUST as bad as going to the DPS, the #onlydifference is the room is smaller...    
    
    
    @FollowMasat0 Even though that was posted forever ago, I totally just finished listening to that song.    
    
    
    FREE HAMBURGERS at Harvey Deck at 4:00PM hosted by ISO, water balloon fight too (:    
    
    
    SGA Foam Party from 8:00 to 11:00 tonight! Don't forget your ID (;    
    
    
    Girl's basketball game @UTTyler.    
    
    
    @UTTyler Students! Let us know what you want for #Homecoming2011: http://tinyurl.com/uttylerhomecoming … (:    
    
    
    Should've went with Suddenlink @WhatIsJoeDoing. Get connected, hahaha.    
    
    
    LMAO. "I'm sooo glad I could share this moment with you!" -Lily Davidson    
    
    
    I didn't know until now but, they're turning Stephenie Meyer's book #TheHost into a movie! http://bit.ly/4pgfLt    
    
    
    Poison Study was a good read http://twitpic.com/38zyp0 (:    
    
    
    "@katyperry: I'm laying in bed thinking of what an in-n-out burger would taste like right now." I miss in&out soooo much.    
    
    
    Hulu is my bestfriend(:    
    
    
    Stat final, ohmy goodness.    
    
    
    Next time, I will pay someone to wait for me at the dps...    
    
    
    tgisummer!(:    
    
    
    sleep is definitely not in my future.    
    
    
    @jamie2596 dude, look at this #NickiMinaj bracelet from #PinkFriday http://twitpic.com/39e15v loveeeeeee.    
    
    
    Ohhhhmyword! In&Out in Dallas, someone pinch me! Haha, thanks Kay for letting me know :D    
    
    
    I guarantee I'm going to overuse the phrase #puravida this summer.    
    
    
    We're all so thankful for everything you've done for us, come home safe. #happymemorialday    
    
    
    @tinareneee Right? Haha, I forget I'm not alone in the height department!    
    
    
    @WhatIsJoeDoing hahaha, ohyes definitely agree! Atleast someone will be taller then me when I wear those heels! haha.    
    
    
    1. Dancing (: #13thingsilove    
    
    
    2. Learning random facts #13thingsilove    
    
    
    3. prettymuch every song that plays on the radio #13thingsilove    
    
    
    4. youtube & stumbleupon #13thingsilove    
    
    
    5. Laughing and the people who make me laugh (: #13thingsilove    
    
    
    6. The bracelets from the important people in my life! #13thingsilove    
    
    
    7. My height ;D #13thingsilove    
    
    
    8. prettymuch every movie that I end up watching in theaters #13thingsilove    
    
    
    9. Meeting new people and learning about them ...not even kidding #13thingsilove    
    
    
    10. Finding a good book (: #13thingsilove    
    
    
    11. My mom's spaghetti #13thingsilove    
    
    
    12. Life and the people I share it with #13thingsilove    
    
    
    13. God, and the best family and friends a girl could ask for <3 #13thingsilove    
    
    
    alright goodnight, I apologize for attacking your newsfeed (; haha.    
    
    
    Dang @JJGetMoney44, what's good with the 500+ followers?! lol. I thought I had some celebrity following me! ;D haha.    
    
    
    @JJGetMoney44 So apparently I'm not Asian enough? lol. I'm good, enjoying summer! You?    
    
    
    ...today is gonna be a very long day,  first Dallas to see Jan Strimple (:    
    
    
    Headed back home with my fingers crossed, hope the trip was worth it.    
    
    
    Good workout. For the record, my legs feel awesome now. But tmrw I will hate my life. Haha.    
    
    
    @J_Speights I agree with @teejaria! girl, I think you helllaa fine (;    
    
    
    Guess the wait is worth it. http://twitpic.com/573esr     
    
    
    @OhSnapItsMeri Yeaaa! It's in Frisco, they're building like 3 more in Dallas (: exciting, right?!    
    
    
    20 minute wait? not bad (:    
    
    
    in Dallas three days in a row! On the way home with class in an hour, I got this (;    
    
    
    "You threw your hands up. Baby, you gave up, you gave up." - Speechless, Lady Gaga http://tumblr.com/xcp5kry3w    
    
    
    ......I swear #nbafinals    
    
    
    Jenna Castillo after the buzzer: "HAHAHAAHAHAHAHAHAHA that was anticlimactic lol" #NBAFinals    
    
    
    "we were awesome people so we thought, ‘hey, you’re awesome, i’m awesome, let’s be awesome!’ and so..." http://tumblr.com/xcp5le9l2    
    
    
    @P4ULON4V4RRO really? I watched a couple of minutes ...and eh, its okay.    
    
    
    Does this work? (: http://tumblr.com/xcp5ltdw0    
    
    
    On the way home from HPC I almost ran over a squirrel. But then after a double take I realized it was a bunny! How random is that? lol.    
    
    
    #thisweekend Fandango is selling 2 movie tickets for $9, http://tiny.cc/2fandango. spread the word (:    
    
    
    Game on, #nbafinals.    
    
    
    I hope everyone had an awesome food filled thanksgiving (:    
    
    
    so. much. laundry...    
    
    
    Headed back from Dallas, it was so awesome working with the Army and Air Force Exchange Service (:    
    
    
    Teach me how to ...south dallas swagg.    
    
    
    #nowplaying, my hearts a stereo it beats for you so listen close (:    
    
    
    @Jim_Pichon hey!!! What's up? Sorry, I haven't checked my twitter in forever!    
    
    
    hi there @Gamer_Ely, I don't think we've ever met in person? But you go to UT Tyler, right?    
    
    
    @patricknicks15 I've seen that video, lol lol. How do you like twitter?!!    
    
    
    @RanaKhalifa it's not a super awesome story, but I got to be in a catalogue called AAFES. I'm so excited to see it (:    
    
    
    reading #HPpickuplines on twitter, they're freaking hilarious.    
    
    
    my phone just deleted my text message history, and for some reason I'm kinda upset about it :P    
    
    
    "Well, it’s because, uh we are the asian. And we have, and we have the small eye sooo and we like ro-bot." http://tumblr.com/xcp6g99dj    
    
    
    It's been awhile since I've been on twitter.    
    
    
    No. No. I don't endorse that. Pause that. Abort that (; #nowplaying    
    
    
    @katrinajflores goodluck!!!    
    
    
    woke up to the sounds of Bob Marley, best. idea. ever.    
    
    
    I am freezing! I miss having an indoor campus...    
    
    
    I'm super upset. - WHY!? I liked Joe Munoz! He should of laster longer ): Man, American Idol makes me mad. http://tumblr.com/xcp6tg10c    
    
    
    meet Karen Lee! :D    
    
    
    crazystupidlove.    
    
    
    Hunger Games! shortest sneak peek everrrr...    
    
    
    @xo_vw now we can txt & tweet each other! lol.    
    
    
    @xo_vw hahahahah, that's hilarious. but I am now that school is back up! (:    
    
    
    @xo_vw why do you need that many followers? lol, just cause?    
    
    
    Being unproductive, - is something that I’ve mastered this entire week. It’s killing me and for some reason I... http://tumblr.com/xcp7sygzz    
    
    
    haha > lol    
    
    
    watching worlds strongest man with family, intense stuff.    
    
    
    is welcoming back troops, what an awesome experience!    
    
    
    Dallas bound!    
    
    
    @uroosakhalid you're fine! I didn't think you were at all :D    
    
    
    Photo: Did I mention how excited I am to see this movie? http://tumblr.com/xcp86vzwh    
    
    
    Photo: “An extraordinary 11-part event, narrated by Oprah Winfrey, sundays 8PM.” http://tumblr.com/xcp86w3c3    
    
    
    Photo: alyssaaajeann: I totally watched this movie yesterday! It gets me everytime. http://tumblr.com/xcp86w774    
    
    
    "Baby, what’s your sign - tell me yours, I’ll tell you mine." - Timbaland, If We Ever Meet Again http://tumblr.com/xcp87wja9    
    
    
    Man, I miss football.    
    
    
    Video: major props kids, props. http://tumblr.com/xcp8cflem    
    
    
    Video: If you haven’t seen this yet, do it now. HAHAHAHA… http://tumblr.com/xcp8clfgd    
    
    
    Video: Soooo…. I’m totally determined to learn how to do this. This is so flipping beast. Skillz. (: http://tumblr.com/xcp8fca0z    
    
    
    Photo: Thee cutest thing. http://tumblr.com/xcp8fnkzg    
    
    
    Video: PIXELS. Amazing visual effects. This is legit stuff, right here. http://tumblr.com/xcp8fo9wt    
    
    
    4AM, and my cell explodes. It txtbombed itself, holding back all the txts sent to my cell since 12AM. wow, definite fail.    
    
    
    "Congratulations! You’ve been selected to the 2009-2010 KTBB Scholastic All-Stars Team." http://tumblr.com/xcp8vm2uu    
    
    
    Q:when r u coming back to visit ca? A:June 6th to the 23rd! woo. I will see you then? (:... http://formspring.me/julieannluna/q/451045007    
    
    
    Q:the question was...you know...pile.. A:Hahahaha, ummm well yes I do know someone by that ... http://formspring.me/julieannluna/q/451060589    
    
    
    Q:who's pumped for prooom?! :D A:Meee(: & I'm pretty sure my friend Antley is pretty pumped... http://formspring.me/julieannluna/q/451074127    
    
    
    @uroosakhalid ahhh, I know! I feel so bad that I couldn't be there :P    
    
    
    & HAPPY BIRTHDAY (: @uroosakhalid    
    
    
    is so outofhermind bored that she has resulted to twitter as a way of escape.    
    
    
    This lack of focus is killing me.    
    
    
    @xo_vw duhhh, I always go ;D ...haha.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 hahaha. It was soo good to see yo face!    
    
    
    @jamiafbabyy sorry, I suck at this. Same goes for #dancemovement, it's been too long!    
    
    
    Video: This… is… depressing… or really funny, i’m not so sure? http://tumblr.com/xcp97qev3    
    
    
    looking at lookbook.nu    
    
    
    so I just update here?    
    
    
    RIP, mt.    
    
    
    facebooking.    
    
    
    http://ohmythatsawesome.com/    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/dgswcd    
    
    
    I've literally seen five cars pulled over in the last ten minutes, dang...    
    
    
    CHill @ the Cowboy's stadium! Let's gooooo(;    
    
    
    #NP, Patrot Singers & University Chorale.& sitting with Katlyn Willingham!(: http://twitpic.com/3ffdj7    
    
    
    I freaking love Philip DeFranco.    
    
    
    @uroosakhalid awww, yay (: "what's going on?!"    
    
    
    @Gamer_Ely thanks Ely!!!! :D but I have no idea what you were referring to in that last tweet, lol.    
    
    
    @Gamer_Ely I know! I'm really bad with twitter.    
    
    
    Audio: Eight days, until that California sun. This is unbelieveable. http://tumblr.com/xcpany9gg    
    
    
    They're finally showing summer movie trailers!!! #soexcited    
    
    
    "What do you think of when I say Wild Wild West?" "Texas" "...which is in the South."    
    
    
    has an AWESOME guy friend that bought lunch for her, how sweet (:    
    
    
    is so ready for summer vacation!    
    
    
    is trying out txt twittering?    
    
    
    likes you a lot lot - thinks you're really hot hot.    
    
    
    Getting my teeth cleaned! :D    
    
    
    Q:Where are you going in Cali?  A:The bay area! (: Visting my home town, probably stopping by San Francisco. I miss ... http://4ms.me/929yPI    
    
    
    Q:I LOVE YOU!!!!! A:& that makes you awesome, I probably love you too. Haha. http://4ms.me/aJ8MKA    
    
    
    Packing for California, I promise I didn't procrastinate! I have a legitimate reason to why I haven't yet!    
    
    
    in Dallas, four hours from now I will be in CA. How I love my parents (:    
    
    
    About to  start boarding the plane to CA! (:    
    
    
    is in El Paso, Texas.    
    
    
    I just saw a 40ish year old blonde woman with a purple stripe in her hair! BEAST! (;    
    
    
    & I just saw another 40ish blonde girl IN A ROMPER! LMAO! No lie! HAHAHAHAHA!    
    
    
    I have the cutest little boy behind me on this flight to San Jose! I like this flight already! (:    
    
    
    Guys - an appropriately sized polo, black fitted jeans, plus awesome kicks = one badask outfit (;    
    
    
    ...extremely bored    
    
    
    I'm sorry California, 102.3 is better then 94.9 (;    
    
    
    I spent way too much money at GREAT MALL!    
    
    
    tired of stress    
    
    
    @hyperblonde428:  does this work?    
    
    
    @hyperblonde428: Hmmm. I wonder, what's so cool about twitter anyways?    
    
    
    ready to get this week over with...    
    
    
    Personality Pageant, today - be there.    
    
    
    I got that Boom Boom Pow.    
    
    
    Highlighter try-outs. Wish me luck.    
    
    
    Taylor Lautner & Selena Gomez, say it ain't so :(    
    
    
    Lazy, lazy, lazy.    
    
    
    LASICK SURGERY, gives me chills...    
    
    
    chilling at Lake Tyler.    
    
    
    The early bird, gets the worm.    
    
    
    Officially a High School Aerospace Scholar (:    
    
    
    Whytheheck am I tearing up at Logan's graduation?    
    
    
    AP testing!! joy...    
    
    
    Short hair or long hair? (:    
    
    
    @hyperblonde428: ha ha ha (:    
    
    
    @hyperblonde428: I Love You!    
    
    
    & then, I fell in love with NYC.    
    
    
    @weirdnews: What IS that!?    
    
    
    "Just do it.. you’re never going to see these people again!" - Facebook likes http://tumblr.com/xcpbz13qj    
    
    
    @mikeyphillips: Hey!    
    
    
    EPIC FAIL!    
    
    
    Cute Shoes: http://tinyurl.com/awesome001    
    
    
    & just Gorilla Zoe, I'm goneeeeeeeeeeeeeeee - and you're alone in my eh-echo eh-eh-ehco.    
    
    
    My Fave Actresses: Angelina Jolie, Jennifer Connelly, Megan Fox, Jessica Stroup and Jessica Lowndes.    
    
    
    is the Queen of Justice. Cause I'm marching in a parade ;D    
    
    
    EPIC FAIL!!!!! part two!    
    
    
    Long night, fun night ;D    
    
    
    My poor shoulder is supersore...    
    
    
    My Fortune Cookie: "Accept the challenge, so that you may feel the exhilaration of victory."    
    
    
    forgot how hot Texas weather is… http://tumblr.com/xcpc5iqe2    
    
    
    is studying, a lot :(    
    
    
    10 things Ryloves understand... - Elves will capture giants. We play tag, elbow style. Okay, this tree is a... http://tumblr.com/xcpc8xpgy    
    
    
    Photo: tmrw, tmrw, tmrw, tmrw, tmrw, tmrw. http://tumblr.com/xcpccrrp5    
    
    
    has an hour before Eclipse! (: http://tumblr.com/xcpcfvfaz    
    
    
    @RealLadyGaga: The Fame / Boys, boys, boys    
    
    
    Break Bad Habits: http://tinyurl.com/awesome002    
    
    
    spring break, I need you ...now.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 Yea! I saw it the Friday it came out, got the soundtrack forsurre! lol, what didya think?    
    
    
    Bitten by an ant :(    
    
    
    "Love is what you live for." - Angelina Jolie http://tumblr.com/xcpdh5byz    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 ohmygaaa!!! I just saw this :D :D :D #bestfriends    
    
    
    Freshman orientation totally reminds me of RYLA, I’m thinking I made the right college choice (; http://tumblr.com/xcpdk472o    
    
    
    @ImStillCam & I know where you work!! haha.    
    
    
    @joesum_32 haha, thanks (:    
    
    
    @tweetlessjenna = turntopdog394    
    
    
    Research paper? Exam? Group project? done. http://pinterest.com/pin/168462842281594971/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    @God_is_real25 lies.    
    
    
    @God_is_real25 hahahahahaha.    
    
    
    @God_is_real25 traitor? what are you talking about!    
    
    
    @jjcastmoney @997now @LettyBRadio you deserve those tickets!    
    
    
    trippy... http://lights.elliegoulding.com     
    
    
    hahaha, someone do this with me! greatest workout ever <3 http://pinterest.com/pin/168462842281640043/ …    
    
    
    fyi, if you've ever written me a card/letter or made me something. I probably still have it hidden somewhere (; #reminiscing    
    
    
    internet connection is sooooooo slow #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    Sara Bareilles makes my day #NP #goodmorningsongs    
    
    
    Billie Jean is not my lover, she's just a girl that thinks I'm the one. But the kid is not my son. #throwback #wooh #heee #NP    
    
    
    @ScottKGood No! What album is that one from?    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 I miss ab workouts with ya!    
    
    
    @ScottKGood I'll definitely listen to it when I get the chance! I'll probably love it too, haha.    
    
    
    #fouledout    
    
    
    hahahahahahaha, ohmygod @ScottKGood, you made my week! you're right, hilarious!    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 gahh! ditto (: I will visit soon, promise.    
    
    
    @__Mr__Wrong tell me more! lol.    
    
    
    Using @NBA via twitter to keep up with the game #notv, this depresses me.    
    
    
    A good way to spend a saturday night #beales #streetflippers #peoplearecrazy    
    
    
    @sarah_lynn504 (: yessss! reunion.    
    
    
    New sidewalks? Look at you @UTTyler #upgrade pic.twitter.com/dISLvm0N    
    
    
    I feel like I just went back in time #nostalgia #timeline    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 hahaha, woops. #sorrybro    
    
    
    astronomical numbers with @JordanAntley1 #becareful    
    
    
    Scream, Usher #np #ohbabybaby #myjam    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 rrrrright? lol. This is why we're #friendsforevaa!    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 #sooohgoood    
    
    
    <3! Bring on more movies RT @GeekTyrant: Ryan Reynolds is Officially THE HIGHLANDER http://rant.to/MzLyGp  by @JoeyPaur at @GeekTyrant    
    
    
    Movie News - ‘Jack the Giant Killer’ Writer Tackling ‘Carmen Sandiego’... http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyOCiVi0     
    
    
    Overheard: Tim Burton: So, I was thinking of making a movie about... Johnny Depp: Yes. http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyOEr3BF     
    
    
    "@katrinajflores: #SYTYCD TOP 20 TONIGHT!!!" <3! so sxcited!    
    
    
    What do I stand for? Most nights, I don't know anymore... #np #somenights #fun #andthatsalright    
    
    
    family bonding time #dallasbound    
    
    
    Why I love IKEA :D #cutefurniture #500daysofsummer #food #furniturenames #karlsted #flurge    
    
    
    Who has a WhatsApp Messenger? #letmeknow #downloadit http://whatsapp.com/dl/     
    
    
    Thanks @tweetlessjenna for the #whatsapp recommendation ;D #thisisfun    
    
    
    @rc903holmes that's deep thinking! haha.    
    
    
    @rc903holmes haha, I feelya!!    
    
    
    Soooooo excited! (: "Where does a monster go to become a top scarer? Monsters University, of course." http://di.sn/l08     
    
    
    sunday morning (: #howsweetthesound    
    
    
    @Buntacular haha, #ifeelya. I unfriend people when their statuses make me question their sentence structure capabilities...    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1, I bet I know what your plans are for the night...    
    
    
    Watched Men in Black 3 today! #willsmith still has it :D bring on #moremovies, please. #faveactor <3    
    
    
    Baby, oh baby. My sweet baby, you're the one. #np #backintime    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 say whaaat? #shock #noway #unbelievable #idontthinkyourereallygoingtobed    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 #seeitoldyou    
    
    
    @JordanAntley1 #insomnia #biologicalclock    
    
    
    @Joz25 hahaha, I'm in that same boat :P    
    
    
    replacing old contacts with new ones #icansee #helloworld #thatsbetter    
    
    
    My phone just deleted all my texts #wellthatsjustgreat    
    
    
    @rc903holmes hahaha, I did have an ipod at one point. that counts right? ;D    
    
    
    yay! @SarahAnnBaker1 (: follow her!    
    
    
    Happy 4th of July! To celebrate, I'll watch Independence Day (; http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l31UUl5SyXk …    
    
    
    #doitforamerica    
    
    
    Why am I up? #gobacktosleep    
    
    
    Spider Man was #freakingamazing! Andrew Garfield  was brillant. #newfave    
    
    
    Got a condo on my wrist girl, I'm chasin' out #NP "@CerromeRussell: I'm cashin out? I'm outta cash I know that for sure"    
    
    
    Seriously just had the longest conversation with a complete stranger. #howisthatpossible    
    
    
    @_Jay9_ watcha reading?    
    
    
    What's so new about #NewTwitter?    
    
    
    Nevermind. Oh man, that's legit.    
    
    
    Woop, headed to Dallas! It's been awhile since I booked a shoot #work    
    
    
    @66JakeMartin I can't decide whether you're being sarcastic or not, haha.    
    
    
    Song for the Legend by Caitlin Timmins #np #youtubefind    
    
    
    gahh! representation in New York? pleasepleaseplease. #fingerscrossed    
    
    
    @JayJudeh haha, uhmm. Well, my agency is helping me (hopefully) sign a contract with a modeling agency in New York! so exciting (:    
    
    
    Thank you, Facebook for informing me when my friends get engaged. What's next... "So & so is now pregnant." Fantastic.    
    
    
    @justinmagdale (: aw, thank you! how are things?!    
    
    
    I've been up since 4AM, this is sad... #goodmorning #notreally    
    
    
    I'm dying ...@Insanity    
    
    
    @justinmagdale Same here! I'm good. With school around the corner, things better be good!    
    
    
    I like how Christopher Nolan pretty much re-casted his Inception actors for #DarkKnightRises.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 I noticed during the movie! I just wanted to make sure I wasn't the only one, haha.    
    
    
    When I feel like going on a shopping spree -- I go to the dollar store, atleast I do less damage there...    
    
    
    I've embraced the fact that I'm gonna die everyday for the next month or so @Insanity #killsme #everytime    
    
    
    Ha! @GoDJ23, you & I both know you don't really believe that statement.    
    
    
    @SCsoph I haven't had this good of a workout in a long time! & getting easier? Not soon, that's for sure. Give me your willpower!!    
    
    
    No Church in the Wild, workout jams #np @Insanity, Day 6 #iworkout #itry #idie    
    
    
    @CbeezyBaby forrealz?    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 @kneecoleM #twitterlessparker I am in August!(: Remember, I promised I'd visit.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 @kneecoleM ...a random date? But I might have given you that estimate. haha, that's a good estimated time of arrival.    
    
    
    @GoDJ23 K! Sounds like a plan @kneecoleM - can you visit later that month?!    
    
    
    @CbeezyBaby Woop! Good for you!    
    
    
    @kneecoleM @GoDJ23 Austin! :D    
    
    
    Float on, Modest Mouse #np #andwellallfloaton #anyway    
    
    
    refusing to leave the house because it's way too hot to go outside #texasprobs #summerprobs    
    
    
    Before @Insanity was cool, there was Hip Hop Abs with Shaun T! #whodhavethunkit http://tmblr.co/ZR8KRyQTH7Br     
    
    
    @Insanity #weworkout ...at 11PM @SarahAnnBaker1 @twitterlessamanda @twitterlessdevon    
    
    
    oooh Dallas radio stations, Lovers & Friends #np #oldschool #throwback    
    
    
    @rc903holmes are you here?!!    
    
    
    @rc903holmes come say hiiii!    
    
    
    @cooljunior13 I know (: let's do it again!    
    
    
    Watching Youtube videos of #sxephil and #kevjamba, I'm probably only going to get an hours worth of sleep. Ugh, no sleep fail.    
    
    
    lol, I need to start watching the amazing race #TeamJamba (:    
    
    
    This has been one crazy weekend...    
    
    
    #rushhour...    
    
    
    I'm trying to sleep but my thoughts are like, "Muahaha, NEVERRR!!" #ineednyquil    
    
    
    @tweetlessjenna I need to get you addicted to twitter, follow @EW or something for pop culture updates! #yourkryptonite    
    
    
    I hear birds chirping ...tweeting(; I guess it wouldn't hurt to get some sleep.    
    
    
    "Do you model for Victoria's Secret?" -VS Associate & random customer #whomeee? #mademyday (:    
    
    
    @Joz25 Haha, watcha talking about?    
    
    
    @NeetaJoseph what in the world are you tweeting about?! Haha.    
    
    
    @Joz25 I tweet alll the time!!    
    
    
    @NeetaJoseph ewww, hahaha. I was like, whaat is she watching?!!    
    
    
    You'd think I'd learn my lesson on waiting last minute to buy a parking permit...    
    
    
    @erickamichellee hahaha, #sosad #sotrue    
    
    
    @rc903holmes hahaha, you found another tall asian?!    
    
    
    "@mayelacat: @julieannluna Expansion facebook rage right now >>>" <3 <3 <3    
    
    
    @ChaCrazy1904 real talk tho, real talk forsuree. Haha.    
    
    
    It's all about who you know #learnit #liveit    
    
    
    last person in the library #responsiblestudentpoints    
    
    
    @ChaCrazy1904 @ToddKnowles oooh, no problem! you're welcome, you're welcome. haha.    
    
    
    So excited for my photoshoot with Edwin Watson! On my way @FordModels ;D    
    
    
    I'm texting at the gas station. Guy goes, "wanna real number to put in your phone?" #pickuplines #ohplease    
    
    
    @ImStillCam I agree, definitely #ladykilla    
    
    
    @Jared_Tucker oh man, I'm in love! Hahaha.    
    
    
    it's snowing in Dallas!    
    
    
    slowly... dwindling... away... D: @SarahAnnBaker1    
    
    
    "@GoDJ23: I have no idea why Native Americans interest me so damn much, but they do #possibleancestors" @twitterlessparker    
    
    
    @cooljunior13 once in a blue moon! #fullmoon #supaacool    
    
    
    Floating the Comal! #whyisalltherumgone    
    
    
    Breakfast at Tiffany's (:    
    
    
    Me & @ColleenMcDeezy will now proceed with giving @SarahAnnBaker1  the silent treatment...    
    
    
    Rin on the Rox (:    
    
    
    I've auditioned for Leah Clearwater.    
    
    
    #nightowl    
    
    
    VMAs (:    
    
    
    Awwww, I love #ladygaga    
    
    
    Thinks @RinontheRox are amazing! Rin looks like Kimora (:    
    
    
    Making posters with my Expansion loves for College Night at Oliveto! <3<3<3.    
    
    
    I plan to use twitter more.    
    
    
    Ellen's 8th season premiere :D    
    
    
    Get on my level @rc903holmes!    
    
    
    @rc903holmes No drink in hand!!    
    
    
    8 drunk guys vs. a flat tire. Who wins?    
    
    
    My SGA campaign websites are now open for business ;D    
    
    
    I swear, I eat like 8 meals a day #yumm #foooood #dontjudge    
    
    
    All means, if you wanna listen to My Humps in your big red truck. Cool. Blasting it out your windows while alone... #impressionswillbemade    
    
    
    Expansion is Going Greek! <3<3<3 love my girls (:    
    
    
    @SarahAnnBaker1 singleeee partayyy guurlz! #iaintnowifey #ladies&thedrinks    
    
    
    #ionlycamefortheb*tches&thedrinks    
    
    
    @Blake_Bristow thank you! (:    
    
    
    Passing out handbills is such an interesting way to spend time, haha.    
    
    
    @SweetHeart_212 (: (: (: thank you! if only my hair was as cool as yours :P    
    
    
    There was way too much contact in that flag football game tonight, haha.    
    
    
    The 4G network is ridiculously fast in Dallas.    
    
    
    @rc903holmes Hahahaha, should've been playing!    
    
    
    @ImStillCam y'all already know it ;D    
    
    
    @rc903holmes you, as in me? Why am I getting hurt?    
    
    
    @ImStillCam can't help it! Haha #allstar #mvp ...just kidding.    
    
    
    @rc903holmes lol, don't get hurt! Everyone else is like half your size.    
    
    
    "@mayelacat: @julieannluna #phonetag -_-;" we're too good at that game :P    
    
    
    A yellow camaro isn't cool unless it has its black stripes #bumbleebee    
    
    
    @MikeaHoIic are you still playing intramural football with @ImStillCam & me!?    
    
    
    Just spent an hour in Sephora <3    
    
    
    "Girl, you look exactly like Kimora Lee Simmons!" Awww, thanks (:    
    
    
    @SarahAnnBaker1 we are so opposites right now! haha.    
    
    
    #whenlifegivesyoulemonsaddvodka    
    
    
    @Ale__Sanchez haha, I wonder why!? Doesn't @ashleyaparicio3 look familiar too?    
    
    
    VOTING STARTS NOW! http://tumblr.com/xzujbhea0    
    
    
    VOTE JULIE ANN APODERADO FOR FRESHMAN/BUSINESS SENATOR >> http://tumblr.com/xzujbht97    
    
    
    @TimoCampbell & @Sainandan: Cool you have Twitter! (:    
    
    
    I need longer weekends #notexcitedformonday    
    
    
    Finally watching The Michael Jackson Memorial on the DVR.    
    
    
    ...after being inside for hours #ohmygodthisweatherisbeautiful    
    
    
    Goodbye social life, I must get my priorities in order.    
    
    
    