It’s coming…  http://qkme.me/3vbxty     
    
    
    “You’re intimidating pre-coffee. I know my place. If anything destroys our friendship, it will be something pre-coffee.” —@erikamkay    
    
    
    I just mixed tangerine Emergen-C, Orange Valencia refresher and orange Gatorade together. 

Remind me to always have these things on hand.    
    
    
    Too many permissions.    
    
    
    Now it’s even easier for your toddlers to use your iPhone! http://d.pr/i/jit7     
    
    
    You know it’s Monday* when I get engulfed in random Tumblr http://copselfies.tumblr.com 

*any day of the week    
    
    
    .@felixgallo: Innocent blinking. ME: Is that like Jamie blinking? HE: Slower and more innocent for sure. You always blink guiltily.    
    
    
    @undeux Did you see the one teefury for today? http://teefury.com  :)    
    
    
    @goodmanio I’m so glad your avatar is there to express how I feel about this.    
    
    
    @coolpowers Whoops.    
    
    
    Two hours later...

Need. Both. http://teefury.com     
    
    
    Every time I open Clock.app from Control Center (iOS 7 beta 4), it defaults to the timer. 

Really. Fucking. Irritating.    
    
    
    @macmixing Oh…it’s a beta?    
    
    
    @rv1raj Ew. Why? If I need a timer, I tell Siri to do my bidding. I only use it for Alarms.    
    
    
    @dbcel I know the icon is for the Timer now, but you can more quickly set a timer via Siri. 

I need to manage Alarms & World Clock far more    
    
    
    This is my entertaining face. @khad @HeikeBaird http://instagram.com/p/cajdJrIADO/     
    
    
    @khad @HeikeBaird Boooo    
    
    
    @goodmanio Yup.    
    
    
    @shewchuk You should totally get a mole and name him that.    
    
    
    @DearAnyone Sexist.    
    
    
    And scene.    
    
    
    @erikamkay I accidentally the entire morning    
    
    
    @mhafez Oops.    
    
    
    I just poured water, to refill the Keurig, where the K-cup goes. 

I seriously need coffee before I make my coffee.    
    
    
    @mikemeade Shit.    
    
    
    @JonnySchnittger Blasphemer!    
    
    
    That time @joshuatopolsky spelled ridiculously with an e.    
    
    
    @JonnySchnittger THAT'S TWO BLASPHEMES IN JUST FIVE MINUTES    
    
    
    @JonnySchnittger This has been a rough exchange for me.    
    
    
    @JonnySchnittger Did you say something? Do I know you?    
    
    
    So, @erikamkay is playing Emoji charades with me and I have no idea what's going on.    
    
    
    Pro tip: Don’t watch this while you have some sort of beverage in your mouth. I learned the hard way. http://memebase.cheezburger.com/share/53028353     
    
    
    Good thing this thrift shop offers free HIV testing.    
    
    
    “Real Food Daily’s Ginger Ale is like a paper cut in your mouth.” —@felixgallo    
    
    
    [HOW-TO] Over 700 Words Of Redundant Rambling Just To Piss You Off At The Last Paragraph And Make You Want Three Minutes Of Your Life Back    
    
    
    @CatDrawingGuy http://appadvice.com/review/quirky-app-of-the-day-create-a-cat-to-love-without-the-scratches … by the amazing @Book_Dork  :)    
    
    
    @Ventchat @christyxcore I haven’t gotten one, but @macmixing did review aspects of it for @AppAdvice. 

Does seem pretty neat!    
    
    
    When you text me with “OMGGGGGGG,” I read it like Popeye.    
    
    
    Good thing the quilt convention is this weekend.    
    
    
    Peter Capaldi went from WHO doctor in World War Z to Doctor Who. Win.    
    
    
    Great @thelistserve today. Simply states, “Be kind.” 

Words of wisdom.    
    
    
    @sidoneill Haha. Hwoops. @thelistserve    
    
    
    So many amazing vegan restaurants, so little time.    
    
    
    “Very reliable and secure app. Play for hours without the app crashing.” 

Best pitch ever.    
    
    
    The test results are back. Turns out I’m allergic to stupid.    
    
    
    @undeux Share you secrets!    
    
    
    The ocean breathes salty, won't you carry it in?    
    
    
    @KanePoehlman No. Here for a visit.    
    
    
    I hate myself for liking the smell of patchouli.    
    
    
    @macguitar I am.    
    
    
    I have never regretted asking what a wifi password was until today.    
    
    
    Amber Alert. Rabble rabble.    
    
    
    @macguitar All the way up north? Get outta here!    
    
    
    You assholes and your double crossing animals.    
    
    
    ME: Another amber alert. HE: Stop stealing babies, Jamie.    
    
    
    I love how in each iOS 7 beta, names in Messages lose letters. Pretty soon I will just be conversing with the alphabet, one letter at a time    
    
    
    @localcelebrity I can’t help it. I just want one so badly. 

To eat.    
    
    
    “Hey, baby. Let’s Airdrop sometime.” 
—iOS 7 pick up lines    
    
    
    ME: I think I’m just getting bitter the older I get. HE: No, you’ve always been that way.    
    
    
    “I’m eating a licorice Jelly Belly. I’m taking one for the team.”    
    
    
    @normnarvaja Buttered Popcorn is only the best flavor.    
    
    
    @corythefish20 So good.    
    
    
    “They eat reconstituted fish guts. They’re not fragile.” —my brother talking about his cats    
    
    
    I really feel the need to buy this. http://sellout.woot.com/offers/ukulele-for-dummies-pack-3 …    
    
    
    …and now I will be listening to ukelele music. Good job, @felixgallo.    
    
    
    I know I picked the right drink when it's too strong for everyone else. Hawaiian Martini FTW! @ Roy's… http://instagram.com/p/cuxnTfoAB2/     
    
    
    I just had a salad with peppercorn basil dressing and I think I am in love.    
    
    
    Go to California. Come back with a League of Legends addiction.    
    
    
    @gntrnr I’m so proud.    
    
    
    “Anyone who genuinely and constantly with both hands looks for something, will find it.”
 —  Rumi    
    
    
    Running through the forest at 9pm, alone, with a dead phone is not fun. 

I need to start going for runs earlier.    
    
    
    @goodmanio I MADE IT I AM ALIVE    
    
    
    @erikamkay Dude, I totally did.    
    
    
    ...and a Snark tuner. Like I need to tune my snark. Snort. http://instagram.com/p/c17PDsoANJ/     
    
    
    → Today’s song of the day http://vimeo.com/20414854     
    
    
    I won’t even touch that one.    
    
    
    @chasesclouds Nada!    
    
    
    “You will want to find the darkest room in your house and just play with it all night long.”

App or personal massager? You decide.    
    
    
    When we work together, @KarenSFreeman likes to make me dry heave by showing me Awkward Family Photos of pregnant women.    
    
    
    Responded to an email addressing another publication that we weren’t said publication. Response? “So….?”

…    
    
    
    I really miss @QueenKing0’s sass.    
    
    
    @mantia This is the story of my life.    
    
    
    Google Maps easter egg: It’s bigger on the inside! http://techcrunch.com/2013/08/13/google-maps-doctor-who-tardis-easter-egg/ …    
    
    
    @iKeralot Oh, hi! :) I am doing pretty well. I hope you are too!    
    
    
    Jamie, why can’t you pay your bills this month? Oh, just because I put all my money on my Starbucks card. #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    @toyaisle I know, right? It’s always like…”AHHH!!!”    
    
    
    @undeux Where'd you go on Instagram? :(    
    
    
    Found in the Starbucks bathroom. Combining tampons with fortune cookies is so genius! #wtf #no http://instagram.com/p/c-ILiZoAJU/     
    
    
    @undeux Figured. Irritating. 

Thanks! Should have known that’s what it would be. :)    
    
    
    @julipuli Do you really want me to answer that?    
    
    
    I feel really anxious when I reply to a tweet and fav it afterwards. 

Is this normal?    
    
    
    I have ukulele arm. Yep. Apparently that’s a thing.    
    
    
    @seevishal I already have a pretty sweet mustachio iPhone 5 case :D    
    
    
    @HereIsTrev Fitbit Flex!    
    
    
    I feel like cookies should leave icing to the cakes.

What the fuck are you doing, cookie? Get outta that icing! You don’t belong there!    
    
    
    @codyfink But the icing is on a CAKE. See?    
    
    
    @mathewi Gorgeous!    
    
    
    Because @felixgallo’s addiction is now my addiction is now your addiction. You’re welcome. http://onetinyhand.com     
    
    
    @matticus No. That’s just a bad player.    
    
    
    @ptgrw Speaking of, how goes the iPhone shopping?    
    
    
    I always wanted to be Commander in Chief.

Of my one woman army.    
    
    
    "What are you doing? Wouldn't you rather be petting me though?" http://instagram.com/p/dC2R4aoAOl/     
    
    
    @superpixels La la la lala    
    
    
    Great. Now my baristas are getting my name wrong AND sexually harassing me. http://d.pr/i/pIdg     
    
    
    .@felixgallo: Clearly you need 4 more shots of espresso to work up the motivation. ME: I’ve had 4, so I’m only 50% motivated right now.    
    
    
    .@KodyJGMcGee: You totally picked the best songs! ME: Of course I did. Best! *points at self* HE: And not cocky at all. So humble.    
    
    
    .@KodyJGMcGee: I don’t know this Mac shit. I’m technically retarded. ME: Yes. Technically. Retarded.    
    
    
    You know you work out of Starbucks too much when your barista gives you some of his lunch. Out of pity.    
    
    
    @AnthonyEsposito @macmixing But seriously…you should.    
    
    
    @AnthonyEsposito @macmixing Express! D’uh.    
    
    
    It’s all about the didgeridoo.    
    
    
    @AnthonyEsposito @pacman4484 @macmixing Clearly @Walmart’s social media rep is missing out on a big opportunity here.    
    
    
    I think Cleveland has weather Tourette’s.    
    
    
    @mb TEASE    
    
    
    PLEASE REMEMBER TO ALWAYS CLOSE YOUR <BLINK> TAGS http://shirt.woot.com     
    
    
    “God that’s ugly.” —@AppAdvice consensus on a gold iPhone    
    
    
    @localcelebrity “Possibly the source of all this madness.” Hah!    
    
    
    @rxcs @EvaGiselle Best troll ever!!!!!11    
    
    
    Now, if Apple turned these into Star Wars themed iPhones, that I could get behind. 

Gold=C3PO
Black=Vader
White=R2D2    
    
    
    @naimcesur @joshuaschnell YOU GUYS ARE SO RACIST    
    
    
    @codyfink Unfortunately. http://apadv.co/14Q9jbJ     
    
    
    @BrentDirks I want a green/red/yellow Boba Fett one.    
    
    
    @matthewrex I CARE WRECKS I CARE    
    
    
    @codyfink So ugly. :(    
    
    
    @codyfink This isn’t beige. It’s…so, so gold. 

I can’t imagine there is a market for this.    
    
    
    @codyfink Haha. “Fuckin’ fanboys with their gold phones! GOD!”    
    
    
    Someone should name a song “Steve Jobs Would Be Rolling In His Grave.” Then we can call it the Anthem For The Year 2013 and be done with it.    
    
    
    @christyxcore OMFG IT'S HUGE    
    
    
    @christyxcore WHERE IS THIS    
    
    
    @christyxcore Wow.    
    
    
    @christyxcore Oh, I will have that magnet.    
    
    
    @kbaxter Really? My 3rd gen battery lasts me forever. I rarely have to charge it.    
    
    
    @kbaxter Ah. I see.    
    
    
    @sdw Does it mean other places or a specific place? Wanderlust could work if it’s not specific.    
    
    
    @sdw I wish there were a word meaning to be homesick for a specific place that is not your home.    
    
    
    I’m procrastinating reading a book about not procrastinating. 

Am I doing it right?    
    
    
    @jeremypair No. Vegetarian.    
    
    
    “Do not worry that your life is turning upside down. How do you know that the side you are used to is better than the one to come?”
 — Rumi    
    
    
    @jeremypair I just love vegan food. :)    
    
    
    @jeremypair So I hear! I’ve never been to Portland either. :(    
    
    
    Oh, hello, Hearthstone beta.    
    
    
    That Dirty Frank was a bad mother…    
    
    
    @snavetrebor Hey, man, I’m just talking about dirty Frank.    
    
    
    @joshuaschnell Hey, man, I’m just talking about dirty Frank.    
    
    
    @localcelebrity Hey, man, I’m just talking about dirty Frank.    
    
    
    → Because who doesn’t <3 Mikey? Get you some Mikey Hooks action! 

74JJFRRMFYRL
YHJR94RKJMWK
N4TRXE4Y73T9
RXLLKPYW44NN
M4EHYWWLH7HH    
    
    
    @josephaleo Ooooo.    
    
    
    @chartier @localcelebrity I cook ‘em just to see the look on their face!    
    
    
    @superpixels iBeetus.    
    
    
    @MaLindaLou <3 Rumi.    
    
    
    I would kill for some Miso soup right about now. 

All the migraines.    
    
    
    Nothing like eating stale saltines to really make you feel pitiful.    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas Stop spying on me, Joel!    
    
    
    @SnorkyJr My dignity.    
    
    
    …and apparently now we post TV show spoilers on Instagram. 

Nothing is sacred. Fucking brilliant.    
    
    
    I don’t want to live in this world anymore. (See previous retweet.)    
    
    
    @localcelebrity I am fuckin' speechless.    
    
    
    @markgurman No, it was accident. It wasn’t scheduled. It was immediately pulled but our back end is all effed.    
    
    
    @MicahSingleton Wait. Just to be clear: You mean Pocket Formerly Read It Later, right?    
    
    
    Social networking platforms are great until people join and ruin them. Gosh.    
    
    
    @johnroderick Definite keeper. Because toilet paper.    
    
    
    Pro tip: Embargoes are always a mistake.    
    
    
    @XimenaTalks Because no one really knows how to handle them if they’re broken or if the time changes.    
    
    
    @XimenaTalks And trust me…someone will break them or some PR intern will forget to tell someone the embargo time has changed.    
    
    
    @XimenaTalks Plus: Your audience doesn’t give a fuck about an embargo. And they’re the important thing. Or at least they should be.    
    
    
    @XimenaTalks I hope so! Same plane? Same Stephen Chow film? :)    
    
    
    @XimenaTalks That’s awesome! Good for you! Let me know so I can attend.    
    
    
    @XimenaTalks Awesome! Up voted.    
    
    
    @joshuaschnell Oops.    
    
    
    @Ventchat That is the BEST mustache car.    
    
    
    Not much there yet, but I’m working on it. I’m plotting some new projects. http://facebook.com/itsjamieyoung     
    
    
    @mikemeade How’d you know the very reasons I quit Facebook years ago?    
    
    
    This ain’t no funky reggae party.    
    
    
    And now we LoL!    
    
    
    @jmattm Mwahahaha. I’m everywhere!    
    
    
    @toddtrann I haven’t been on Facebook in 4 years.    
    
    
    @nateboateng Meh. At least they linked to us in the body. More than I can say for a lot of other blogs today. Shameful.    
    
    
    @nateboateng Yeah, I know. Sourcing pisses me off to no extent.    
    
    
    @nateboateng Pff. I read it as “They are inconsistent in linking…” :)    
    
    
    I’m sorry. I just found the Instagram account @bunnymama. You can all go home with your damn cats now.    
    
    
    When I woke up this morning, all I could think about was League of Legends.    
    
    
    @Bonesax I tried texting you! Also: Change your Twitter password. You’re sending me spam.    
    
    
    Hey, left handers! Weird question → Any of you find it hard to use some apps as the minority in the dominate hand department?    
    
    
    It seems to be difficult for females to play male characters in games, when given the choice.    
    
    
    @julipuli I know. Me included. Makes me feel guilty though. And sexist!    
    
    
    @thebiggameover got in last week…haven’t had time to play yet. :(    
    
    
    @adammccombs This is amazing.    
    
    
    @Giggidee2157 Japan. Though Ireland is in my top 5!    
    
    
    @ZachGalifianaks I hope you really don’t run your own account. Because these are jokes people on Twitter use all the time. :(    
    
    
    @iKeralot Guy is hilarious. But his Twitter feed is a joke. :/    
    
    
    [Straw Grasping] Things We Already Knew About iOS 7 Presented As New Knowledge Because None Of Us Can Find Anything To Write About    
    
    
    Dear Press People, 

My name is not Jaime. 

Best,
Jamie (see how easy that is?)    
    
    
    So, like, what does that mean when your dog’s twitter account has more followers than yours? Doesn’t that make you feel worthless?    
    
    
    @joshuaschnell @alexeheath “Let me tell you about our new calculator app…”    
    
    
    “I have high Twitter standards.” 
—thing I actually just said in a conversation    
    
    
    @MicahSingleton The first few were epically cheesy. Loved it.    
    
    
    Everywhere @KarenSFreeman and I go to cowork, we find someone who looks like Tim Cook.    
    
    
    Never leave home without it. http://instagram.com/p/d2VjFRoAMC/     
    
    
    Is this journalism? So pathetic and exaggerated. http://goo.gl/q1C0hm     
    
    
    “NIN closed the night with a slow & smoky cover of Johnny Cash’s ‘Hurt,’ which earned nonstop cheers from the crowd.” http://d.pr/pxgw     
    
    
    Yikes.    
    
    
    @plagueis ….    
    
    
    @plagueis Point of the tweet.    
    
    
    @goodmanio Ouch. 

But reasonable on account of, well, Johnny Cash.    
    
    
    Everyone is loading LoL. Time to go make a sandwich.    
    
    
    @agentbizzle @psdesignuk What if you can’t name any of either?    
    
    
    REAL FRIENDS LEAVE LOL QUEUES FOR YOU @bonesax    
    
    
    And now for your Friday entertainment… http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jofNR_WkoCE …    
    
    
    Now, @viticci’s how-to is an iBook—for only $3! Don’t be dumb. If you want more out of the Editorial app, get it. https://itunes.apple.com/us/book/writing-on-ipad-text-automation/id697865620?ls=1 …    
    
    
    I do not regret the things I’ve done, but those I did not do.    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA You know it, hooker!    
    
    
    @jmattm No. But I recite that movie daily. :)    
    
    
    …and tonight we celebrate the birth of @ray_ob1 with lots of love and Sailor Jerry!    
    
    
    At a bar discussing English lit. 

Appropriate.    
    
    
    “I was hoping this was rufied! Thank you!” –@ray_ob1    
    
    
    @QueenKing0 You should be at Bucks! I miss you so much!    
    
    
    OH: I don’t have any friends, so I just read a lot.    
    
    
    @macguitar OR DO I    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman OH=overheard    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman haha ❤️    
    
    
    SPORTSBALL    
    
    
    Seeing @FAKEGRIMLOCK on a package that was delivered to me can only mean one thing: AWESOME.    
    
    
    @matthewrex Congrats, Wrecksy poo!    
    
    
    @gruber With a special part of the keynote titled, “How To Twerk Your iPhone.”    
    
    
    @ptgrw I want a $20 for putting pants on today!    
    
    
    @ptgrw Please make it out to Maxine Eyeroll.    
    
    
    “Now I’m going to take a cold shower and die.” —what I always say after exercising    
    
    
    @flargh I swear that is the best bread.    
    
    
    @flargh Mmm. They make their vegetarian sandwiches on that by default. I fell in love.    
    
    
    If Rick Astley doesn’t appear once the countdown is up for this “live Apple event stream”: Missed opportunity. http://www.wcpo.com/apple-live-video …    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas Good thoughts! Knock 'em dead    
    
    
    Ruh ruh. Like a dungeon dragon.    
    
    
    I hope Phil said slow-mo in slow motion. Otherwise: Another wasted opportunity today.    
    
    
    Phew. My fingerprint isn’t stored in iCloud. Dodged that bullet.    
    
    
    No 128gb? I totally need that, too.    
    
    
    No…5S preorder? Are you kidding?    
    
    
    @localcelebrity Leaks weren’t from Apple. Manufacturers.    
    
    
    @TandyQ @matthewrex I'D LOVE TO GET A 5S IN BLACK    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Any word on being able to surf + talk simultaneously with the new iPhone 5S? More LTE bands!    
    
    
    @panzer @jerols Looks so awful. :(    
    
    
    @christyxcore @panzer @jerols Must. Color. Co-ord-i-nate.    
    
    
    IS IT OKAY FOR ME TO EAT BREAKFAST NOW    
    
    
    Kthx    
    
    
    @lexfri …and it shows bits and pieces of the lettering on the back. Looks awful.    
    
    
    @SteveStreza Ugh. Hate it so much.    
    
    
    [RUMOR] The iPhone 6 Will Be Faster Than The iPhone 5S And Come In A New Color That Is Not Brown But More Of A Whiskey    
    
    
    Some people, man.    
    
    
    Apple Adds Lots Of Wallpapers And Backgrounds To iOS 7 To Match New iPhone 5C Colors http://apadv.co/17ogoxy  tip @Techmeme    
    
    
    @seevishal I say no. Unless you’re upgrade-ready. I am not upgrading. Camera and speed improvements and fingerprint sensor.    
    
    
    This how-to play Janna guide is called “Cause Your Girlfriend Can't Blow Well Enough.” #LoL    
    
    
    @ArtDish She’s beautiful!    
    
    
    Email reads, “How likely are you to recommend X to a friend?” 

Less likely now that you’re sending me stupid emails like this.    
    
    
    The culprit is always a <div> tag. 

Always.    
    
    
    @kknoer @WilliamKish @AppAdvice BUT THIS ONE IS ONLY $24.99!!!!    
    
    
    BECAUSE @FAKEGRIMLOCK http://instagram.com/p/eIswvBIAMP/     
    
    
    An ad actually worth watching. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fz5uWl_XEeA …    
    
    
    @mikemeade ….

I totally expected better from you.    
    
    
    @WilliamKish And we 💙you!    
    
    
    Preventing people from making the mistake of getting the space grey iPhone since 2013.    
    
    
    @Merkprof So ugly. Now there are no good looking iPhones. :(    
    
    
    @Merkprof It was the slate backing that was the problem. Although I LOVE the look. It scratched so easily. I assume that’s why they changed.    
    
    
    “Ahri has got to be the slave Leia of @riotgames conventions.” 
—@felixgallo
#LoL    
    
    
    @TheRealJoshuaD Every single iPhone 5s is ugly.    
    
    
    @mattmusiol Also barf.    
    
    
    @BrentDirks I DON'T EVEN KNOW

I HATE THEM ALL    
    
    
    @dbcel …but everyone is getting the gold now.    
    
    
    @dbcel Well, @macmixing for one. But a lot of people have told me they’re getting gold now.    
    
    
    I wish tech blogs would source when they clearly rip information from another tech blog. 

So gross. At least give them a via!    
    
    
    @jasonspooner Not if bloggers did their job and sourced and found the actual source.    
    
    
    I’ve decided I need some gaming therapy this weekend.    
    
    
    @jmattm Probably LoL and Hearthstone. I don’t play WoW anymore. :(    
    
    
    @localcelebrity Okay, old man.    
    
    
    Some silly Microsoft social media intern got fired today.    
    
    
    @BrentDirks So awful. :(    
    
    
    @JoeManna They just made really awful video shorts mocking the new iPhones and failed miserably.    
    
    
    @localcelebrity <3!    
    
    
    @JoeManna Yeah. I tend to like their commercials though! Those are good.    
    
    
    @JoeManna Samsung ads are usually bad I think.    
    
    
    ME: I have a really big head. @ray_ob1: I’m pretty sure my head is totally bigger than yours.    
    
    
    Next week: More drubken math tips from Aunt Jamie! cc @ray_ob1    
    
    
    “IT’S YOUR BIRTHDAY CHERRY! POP IT!!!” —me to @ray_ob1 just now about her birthday dessert    
    
    
    Thank you, 2am @woot shopping self. http://www.woot.com/offers/batgirl-hooded-dorm-shirt-with-cape-1 …    
    
    
    @greghiggins457 I use @draftsapp for note taking. Quick and simple. Then you can send your notes anywhere.    
    
    
    @greghiggins457 :)    
    
    
    @Starbucks I’ve been reporting an incorrect pin for a store for several months now with no change. Anything else I can do to get it fixed?    
    
    
    Crazy Saturday night up in here. #LoL #caffeine #watermelonmints #what http://instagram.com/p/eQ1KWtoALR/     
    
    
    I’ll just leave this here. #ios7 http://d.pr/i/dVxO 

Thanks, @goodmanio.    
    
    
    There’s a really talkative bird outside my window right now. Kind of want to throat punch it.    
    
    
    @localcelebrity @finertech @chartier But I don’t have notes!    
    
    
    “I don’t consciously use iCloud.” 
—@KarenSFreeman    
    
    
    Total hipster today. Photo bomb by my cat. #foreveralone http://instagram.com/p/eXlRI4oADT/     
    
    
    @MicahSingleton :(    
    
    
    NOW I'M NOT SUFFICIENTLY HIPSTER 

IT'S NEVER ENOUGH FOR YOU GUYS IS IT    
    
    
    So my iPhone just shuts down/dies anywhere from 18-35%. Won’t start back up. Insists the battery is dead. Didn’t happen prior to iOS 7.    
    
    
    @macmixing I thought it was directly related to iOS 7 somehow since it started happening in the first beta. Guess I need to go in.    
    
    
    @macmixing Well, it comes out tomorrow :P    
    
    
    @macmixing Really? How do they tell the difference?    
    
    
    @macmixing Wow, that’s stupid. Because I can’t be a developer? Fuck that.    
    
    
    @christyxcore @macmixing Started for me in beta 1. Meh. This sucks. Did you get yours checked out?    
    
    
    @WCHamilton @macmixing well I wasn’t going to go today. :P D’uh.    
    
    
    @christyxcore Ahh. Thought you would have if it’s been happening since 6!    
    
    
    @christyxcore Hah! Fair enough.    
    
    
    @JBTech17 @macmixing I don’t have apple care though. :/    
    
    
    @rickdjng Apparently it’s just a bad battery. Going to take it in after the public iOS 7 is released/installed.    
    
    
    @rickdjng Same here. But I’ve had numerous people just tell me the same happened to them on iOS 6. They took it in; the battery was bad.    
    
    
    @JBTech17 @macmixing Good to know. Thanks, guys!    
    
    
    @JBTech17 Yeah. I preordered, so hopefully that still works.    
    
    
    Why is this only in long sleeve? Want. But a tshirt or hoodie. :( http://shirt.woot.com/offers/at-at-long-sleeve-tee …    
    
    
    @bryterside Exactly. AT, AT.    
    
    
    @DavePolak !!!!    
    
    
    @bryterside :)    
    
    
    @horizonpr1 Hi?!    
    
    
    HEY DID ANYONE ELSE WANT TO UPDATE THEIR APP FOR IOS 7 AND EMAIL ME ABOUT IT RIGHT NOW    
    
    
    @joewhite89 No.    
    
    
    @chasesclouds Sounds like I just have a bad battery. Going to have to take it in.    
    
    
    All of my gmail servers are offline? What.    
    
    
    I really love how all of these iOS 7 app updates look. Nice work, guys!    
    
    
    → Public iOS 7 download links: http://www.icj.me/ios/     
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA Yay!    
    
    
    @toddtrann @iChris @SaskGatz @fenderf4i @saskajules @talk2tr @bigshmexy @KiltedBroker @ShahanFancy @chrispowell @melistress @iluvsmooches .    
    
    
    @sidoneill I know, right?    
    
    
    @toddtrann My work here is done.    
    
    
    @toddtrann Also: Way to be difficult by being Canadian. I hope your promo code finally worked.    
    
    
    @toddtrann No, not me. I just noticed it earlier as I was creeping on our account. - Are notifications off in AppAdvice under Settings?    
    
    
    @toddtrann How is it spamming? Should just be once in while when we push a post.    
    
    
    @toddtrann Well, shit. I thought you needed tech support because you were a dummy.

NEVER AGAIN    
    
    
    @SimonAnnable http://osxdaily.com/2012/11/15/determine-iphone-gsm-or-cdma/ …    
    
    
    Now…how to turn off email…    
    
    
    @ACES_1983 No.    
    
    
    @ACES_1983 You need to make sure you get the right download for your phone.    
    
    
    @ACES_1983 Nope.    
    
    
    My Batman pajamas with cape and mask just arrived. 

You can all go home now.    
    
    
    @seevishal Oh, no. There are still bugs. But this is Apple’s public release. It’s safe. This is not the beta.    
    
    
    @macmixing @dubbalubagis May I interject to say: What the fuck are you even doing?    
    
    
    I popped the Finer Things Podcast's guest cherry  http://atjamie.com/blog/9182013finer-things-podcast …    
    
    
    Dad calls me to say he can’t install iOS 7, keeps getting error message. 

“It’s okay. We’ll get through this,” he assures himself out loud.    
    
    
    @macmixing @dubbalubagis ONE OF US ONE OF US    
    
    
    @iChris Haha. It is. 

Legit I mean.    
    
    
    @iChris I think you mean: 2legit2quit    
    
    
    So, does anyone have a fix for the “Can not connect to the activation server, try again.” dilemma? 

Been trying for over an hour, now.    
    
    
    @JeffBenjam Triple tapping home = Voice Over ?!    
    
    
    @JeffBenjam Holding! Cheers! See if this works…    
    
    
    Is it weird that I’m still working, but I’m wearing my new Batman pajamas? ‘Cause like…that’s happening.    
    
    
    @QueenKing0 I will have to come to Rocky River wearing my Batman pajamas then. :(    
    
    
    @QueenKing0 Noooo…I can not tonight! BUT SOON DAMMIT    
    
    
    @goodmanio Can’t.    
    
    
    @QueenKing0 @kaitthegr8 Yay!    
    
    
    @JeffBenjam Worked on the fifth try over cellular. 

I love you, Jeff! Thank you!    
    
    
    The Jamie the Internet deserves... http://instagram.com/p/ebebh1IADn/     
    
    
    Told @felixgallo I have a Genius Bar appointment today. He says, “Walk up and order a scotch.”    
    
    
    @mattgemmell :(    
    
    
    New Age Girl is in the radio. Hah.    
    
    
    One lawn chaired man already outside my Apple Store.    
    
    
    GETTING A NEW PHONE WITH ONE DAY LEFT ON MY WARRANTY 

WHAT WHAT    
    
    
    @corythefish20 I like it. It’s just buggy still. Been using it a while. We’ve written a lot about it over the last couple of months!    
    
    
    @iamdereklong Just take it in! I’m not positive what they do if yo drop it though. :( Is it obvious you dropped it?    
    
    
    @iamdereklong They should just give you a new phone. I’ve never had Apple Care for the record - haha.    
    
    
    @corythefish20 http://appadvice.com/appnn/tag/ios-7-2 … may be of some help! Lots there, though.    
    
    
    ME: I think most guys wear hats because they’re douchebags. @ray_ob1: I would agree with that statement.    
    
    
    “I wonder if you can buy groceries at Chipotle.” —basically what @felixgallo just said to me    
    
    
    Why are you people still awake? Jeez.    
    
    
    @MyAppinions Best. Show. 

Also: Wow! Love your hair!    
    
    
    @manicsocratic You are not worthy.    
    
    
    .@JBTech17 That’s what I want to do. Wait in line. Then ask for an iPad 3.    
    
    
    @manicsocratic You are not worthy of trying harder.    
    
    
    @manicsocratic I know, Adan. I know.    
    
    
    @manicsocratic That is why we get along so well.    
    
    
    @manicsocratic We would never work as analog.    
    
    
    A poem: 

iPhones are white. 
iPhones are gold. 
Space gray? 
What the fuck, Apple?    
    
    
    @manicsocratic I’m GLaDOS. So like…while you’re dying, I’ll be still alive.    
    
    
    @joebrooklynn_1 Merci!    
    
    
    Well, that was easy. 

Too. Easy.    
    
    
    …and no one understands that shipping times and delivering times are different.    
    
    
    And scene.    
    
    
    @joebrooklynn_1 That’s all I got. :(    
    
    
    @matthewrex @codyfink My point is that just because something will be shipped in 3 days, doesn’t mean it is delivered in 3 days. Needs time.    
    
    
    @matthewrex @codyfink People are saying the dates don’t add up. They’re wrong.    
    
    
    If you really want to fuck with me, send me a string of random emoji. I’ll sit there trying to figure it out all day.    
    
    
    .@KarenSFreeman: Nah. You're only sarcastic PART of the time. @Book_Dork: The other part is spent sleeping. #whatmycoworkersreallythinkofme    
    
    
    @businessinsider May want to correct your grammar in that post. 

*it’s    
    
    
    @BrentDirks @KarenSFreeman I just saw the ring and was like “RUN!!!”    
    
    
    @BrentDirks @KarenSFreeman :(    
    
    
    The iPhone is doomed, and it always has been http://m.tuaw.com/2013/09/20/the-iphone-is-doomed-and-it-always-has-been/ …    
    
    
    @matthewrex What are you getting?!    
    
    
    @matthewrex Yowza.    
    
    
    @Zettt Thanks for the heads up!    
    
    
    @matthewrex :) Very nice! Good luck. Send pics!    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis I think you just gave them an idea for their next commercial.    
    
    
    @matthewrex Yes. 

You. On the car. Naked. Go!    
    
    
    @preshit @matthewrex I’m his manager. $500 for one picture. Or an iPhone 5s. Whatever you got really.    
    
    
    @kbaxter @inkedmn @merrilamb Me three.    
    
    
    @preshit @matthewrex I’m sorry, I was waiting for you to say “challenge accepted.”    
    
    
    At least until Things gets an iOS 7 update, I’m tempted to use OmniFocus 2…again.    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman Welcome to my life.    
    
    
    @ray_ob1 :(    
    
    
    “It’s okay. I can tweet it because no one follows me.” —@ray_ob1    
    
    
    Well, I’m glad Dexter’s over.    
    
    
    @seevishal The last 3 seasons or so have been pretty bad. I loved Dexter. Was just waiting for it to end so I could be done with it.    
    
    
    @SquaredApe Nice. Skip the last 3 seasons though. Not worth it.    
    
    
    @ChrisAMcKinstry My thoughts exactly.    
    
    
    @seevishal One what?    
    
    
    @ChrisAMcKinstry Haven’t seen BB yet. So I won’t read it.    
    
    
    @seevishal Carnivale. Six Feet Under. Firefly.    
    
    
    “They didn’t put whipped cream on my pumpkin spice latte. Now I know how Jesus must have felt.” —@felixgallo    
    
    
    → We wanted to believe… http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/elements/2013/09/horse-ebooks-and-pronunciation-book-revealed.html …    
    
    
    “I love French. It’s like speaking in cursive.” —@KodyJGMcGee    
    
    
    @FredChartrand @KodyJGMcGee Thank you, Tweetbot translate.    
    
    
    @FredChartrand It does look great! But the way I use the Twatter…man, I need those power user features.    
    
    
    Does Mophie make battery packs for vibrators? 

Asking for a friend. Please respond ASAP.    
    
    
    An intelligent water bottle that syncs with your phone to ensure you’re being hydrated. 

Welcome to the future. Where we can’t do math.    
    
    
    Did I mention how incredibly disappointed and shocked I am that Apple shipped this OS as is? 

Awful.    
    
    
    @RandGM It is such a buggy piece of software. So many issues. Apple is better than shipping such a flawed product.    
    
    
    @CERVEZAmasFINA So buggy.    
    
    
    @acreature Anime.    
    
    
    It’s been so long, peanut butter M&Ms.    
    
    
    @RandGM Buggiest public release they’ve had. Kind of appalling. Not like them to ship something they know has so many bugs rendering the OS    
    
    
    @RandGM …unusable in some aspects. They were aware from beta bug reports; chose to ship anyway. Disappointing.    
    
    
    @RandGM I was. That wasn’t as bad as this. And, you’re right, the updates were ready to go instantly.    
    
    
    @viticci Oh, yeah.    
    
    
    No Instagram icon update? Huh.    
    
    
    Wondering how many more nice days like today we get before it’s snowing.    
    
    
    Migraines have defeated me this week.    
    
    
    Still not sure about my iOS 7 home screen. pic.twitter.com/HFA1Hr51IG    
    
    
    @agiletortoise I’m hoping it will embarrass me into going through it all.    
    
    
    @RandGM That’s what I was saying yesterday! Not sure why they updated the app and not the icon. :/    
    
    
    @espresso @agiletortoise Get outta here!    
    
    
    @reneritchie @drance @espresso I like the way you Inbox Zero, sir.    
    
    
    @shewchuk ONIONS. Also, meat.    
    
    
    Okay. I found the standing desk I want. http://www.engadget.com/2013/09/26/stir-kinetic-desk-hands-on/ …    
    
    
    @chartier Haha. Actually thought of you when I saw this too.    
    
    
    I really don’t like ampersands.    
    
    
    @mattgemmell Don’t waste a perfectly good row! 

Also: Why is your screenshot so blurry?    
    
    
    @mattgemmell I see it now!    
    
    
    Makin’ spaghetti. No garlic bread. Livin’ on the edge.    
    
    
    → Poll: Who uses Evernote?    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA THANK YOU MATTY 

Haha, I was just thinking, “Anyone NOT use it? Fuck.”    
    
    
    [HOW-TO] Video Without Sound To Complicate Things Even More    
    
    
    @timdeville Why weird?    
    
    
    Just a stunning video to appeal to your creative side http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lX6JcybgDFo …    
    
    
    OH: There’s nothing worse than a double selfie.    
    
    
    Thank you, @AAAauto, for telling me your hours are 9am-5:30pm today and yet not answering the phone at 4pm. Good service.    
    
    
    @SteveStreza WHAT IS THAT EVEN    
    
    
    @SteveStreza EQUAL RIGHTS FOR PONIES ACTIVISTS    
    
    
    @jonfingas Just listened to that today.    
    
    
    @SteveStreza :|    
    
    
    @SteveStreza http://PONYADVICE.COM     
    
    
    I can’t stop making coffee mixed with hot cocoa. I think IMOCHAy, though.    
    
    
    WHERE ARE THESE MYSTERY EMAILS iOS 7?! 

HUH?!    
    
    
    @richburroughs This sounds like a metaphor. I like it.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Right? It bogs down my 3rd gen iPad. Like huh?    
    
    
    @Grizzly_Aaron Just walk away.    
    
    
    I should forward 40% of the emails we get to Apple. Since they all seem to need Apple tech support or need to vent about Apple anyway.    
    
    
    @timdeville I don’t think it’s weird at all! Normal to be excited about cool, new things. :D    
    
    
    @superpixels Most are all lowercase. No punctuation. 

DELETE    
    
    
    @timdeville Agreed. They’ve done a really good job.    
    
    
    Is it just me, or is it an incredible pain in the ass to figure out how to add a song or album to your collection in @rdio for iOS?    
    
    
    Getting sick from iOS 7? → Solution: http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/10/jimmy-kimmel-has-a-solution-for-those-reportedly-getting-sick-from-apples-ios-7 …    
    
    
    “My hair is a very accurate barometer. It never lies.” 
—@KarenSFreeman    
    
    
    @johnpaul And to think I deleted that…this is gold.    
    
    
    Some apps for iOS 7 being released again as new makes sense. But, at this point, it just seems like this is the trend. Kinda disappointing.    
    
    
    Please learn to source, people. You’re despicable.    
    
    
    @bst3r Technically no one can break a rumor. Because, well, rumor.    
    
    
    @inkedmn Yeah. Everyone.    
    
    
    @ablaze I have been having a god awful experience with Apple mail on all devices for the past two weeks.    
    
    
    @ablaze Bahaha. Oh no! Yeah, kept asking for my password over and over. Then wasn’t sending mail at all.    
    
    
    @macmixing LOOKS LIKE YOURE HAVING TROUBLE HOLDING THAT THING BRO    
    
    
    High five to the guy who laughed at me as I fumbled in my bag to turn my sonic screwdriver off that accidentally turned on.    
    
    
    @AnthonyEsposito @macmixing Wouldnt this be a TWHS instead?    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA YOU GOTTA TEACH IT BRO    
    
    
    @RdioHelp I always forget. Thanks!    
    
    
    @ismh By to the word.    
    
    
    @BrentDirks Jesus christ.    
    
    
    @julipuli @BrentDirks Amen.    
    
    
    Thanks, Zuck.    
    
    
    @chartier @inkedmn @1Password WHAT DO YOU MEAN    
    
    
    GO HOME MOSQUITO YOU’RE DRUNK @ray_ob1    
    
    
    “You know who you remind me of? Robin Sparkles!” 

If I had a nickle…    
    
    
    @ylnt🍭    
    
    
    How could I *not* buy this, though? http://tech.woot.com/offers/diy-at-at-cable-organizer …    
    
    
    I want to tell Chris Hansen to just have a seat.    
    
    
    After two drunks I’m tipsy.    
    
    
    OH: I’m like Jesus. I hang out with the whores and the tax collectors.    
    
    
    Multifuckintudes.    
    
    
    @greghiggins457 You know, I’m done telling people what the best one is. We all have different needs. I use Things. But also Reminders.    
    
    
    @greghiggins457 But there are a lot of great free to do apps too.    
    
    
    @greghiggins457 What are you sorry for?    
    
    
    @abrahamvegh The fuck    
    
    
    @abrahamvegh Did you yell at them to get off your lawn?    
    
    
    @abrahamvegh Then you’ve done all you can do.    
    
    
    OH: You know. Michael Jordan. The basketball player guy?    
    
    
    HE: Hang on. I have to locate my child. ME: I knew you would lose it! This is why you can’t have nice things.    
    
    
    @superpixels “Singing” machine. 

What else could it be?    
    
    
    @MicahSingleton That’s awesome.    
    
    
    @SteveStreza Missed all this earlier. Hope she’s okay! ❤️🐱    
    
    
    I’m that friend that messages you at 2am with pictures of cupcakes that look like vaginas.    
    
    
    You’re welcome.    
    
    
    @SteveStreza Good to hear! Never fun to have a sick kitty. :(    
    
    
    @AaronIsSocial Or an eyeless, super sad face. D    
    
    
    I just got my hand stuck in a K-cup box in case you wondering how eager I am when it comes to coffee.    
    
    
    @KyleSwank I shook my hand violently for a good 2 minutes.    
    
    
    @CelyneTinMar pic.twitter.com/oXfl5aYvKb    
    
    
    @CelyneTinMar No problem. :)    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA Meep meep!    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA MEEPMEEPMEEPMEEPMEEPMEEP    
    
    
    Jamie and the Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day    
    
    
    @sensibleworld This seems very NSFW.    
    
    
    “I just want to create situations where people forget time.” –Marina Abramović    
    
    
    And a perfect end to my no good day? Migraine.    
    
    
    All I care about is that @launchcenterpro finally added a very Jamie appropriate icon. :{    
    
    
    #tbt That time I gave out free hugs. http://instagram.com/p/fT8bkXIAME/     
    
    
    @Thatguyjoeymin OMG. I want this!    
    
    
    I’m not allowed to Twitter after 2am. I just start FAVING EVERYTHING BECAUSE FUNNY.    
    
    
    Oops. Capslock. Too lazy.    
    
    
    @Deathstance Real gamers don’t sleep. Amateur.    
    
    
    @100soft @Galleries1988 @lilyofspades This is awesome!    
    
    
    So at least I know what everyone’sfeet look like. #ventchatvegas #hopeyouguysarehavingfun    
    
    
    I’m totally going to start ordering Venetian Sunsets at the bar from now on.    
    
    
    ME: I think I cuss too much. But is it endearing? @ray_ob1: It’s really fucking endearing.    
    
    
    It’s pretty bad when your server comes up to your table and says, “It’s like man vs. Food over here.” @ray_ob1    
    
    
    @MyAppinions That’s such a coincidence because I’d like to think that’s my true calling too!    
    
    
    @SteveStreza That’s so awful that happened, but honestly…who would agree to a body shot with all male *coworkers*?    
    
    
    @SteveStreza Obviously not her fault. She’s a victim. And this is wretched. But..wtf?    
    
    
    @SteveStreza Nuts, man.    
    
    
    @JB_Bryant @1Password @culturedcode @iTVShowsApp hahaha. I’m waiting on those same three. :)    
    
    
    I’m allergic to email, guys. This is serious.    
    
    
    I should watch Empire Records. It’s been a while.    
    
    
    @itsnauman http://appadvice.com/appnn/appadvice-is-hiring/ … 

Then if were interested we’ll hit you up!    
    
    
    @goodmanio Back in the day, I created a two disc soundtrack with all of the songs in order of when they play in the movie. By memory.    
    
    
    @itsnauman If you send all the info we asked for and we’re interested, we’ll get back to you.    
    
    
    @itsnauman No problem!    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman @ceejayoz @SteveStreza I’m just still stuck on the body shot.    
    
    
    Garcinia really got you guys good.    
    
    
    @twinsnwhims No clue. But everyone’s tweeting about it.    
    
    
    @goodmanio gtfo    
    
    
    @goodmanio OMG. :(    
    
    
    @goodmanio I miss that house so much.    
    
    
    @goodmanio Did you go to “The Wall?”    
    
    
    @goodmanio I miss that wall. Ah, when we were young and in love…    
    
    
    @goodmanio What are you doing back?    
    
    
    @goodmanio Have fun! It’s been about 6 years since I’ve seen my old house.    
    
    
    @ccMick @JB_Bryant Wait wait wait. Where’s my beta invite?    
    
    
    @SteveStreza But Lee Sin, man.    
    
    
    New tattoo! ; @ Body Anthology Tattoo & Body Piercing http://instagram.com/p/fY4RI8IAGd/     
    
    
    My boyfriend just got Lee Sin in ARAM. Time to post some revenge porn. #LoL    
    
    
    @ray_ob1 @KodyJGMcGee Guys! We suck! Rocky Horror is tonight too! I think they do it every Sat in Oct :( @CedarLeeTheatre    
    
    
    @CedarLeeTheatre Love you! Thanks for the info. <3 @ray_ob1 @KodyJGMcGee    
    
    
    @MaLindaLou Thanks!    
    
    
    @chasesclouds😁    
    
    
    @bernardmoon This was totally an episode of Lie To Me.    
    
    
    Well then. pic.twitter.com/kz5KRwBbSn    
    
    
    @nategorby Yes. Yes they do. You have no idea how many people think that either.    
    
    
    I’m at a baby shower and vodka is being spilled on me.    
    
    
    Drunk words are sober thoughts.    
    
    
    I always end up with multiple Starbucks cups in my car. Especially after hanging out with @ray_ob1. Who knows what’s in these.    
    
    
    “We clone games also we take the original source code with full rights and we offer reskin of games as well.” 

What.    
    
    
    Do you ever feel like you can never change your avatar?    
    
    
    Seems like a fun event to attend, my SF dev friends. http://dayofthedevs.com     
    
    
    “Just realized something awesome on the iphone 5s! You don't need to even slide to unlock! Just keep your finger on the home button” 

Oh my    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA BUT I AM KNOWN MY THE STACHE    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA My mustache brings all the boys to the yard, Matty.    
    
    
    I don’t know about you, but I’m already an Instagram rockstar. Or, at least, my cat is.    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA I had heard a few reports last month of this. I can’t recreate it. I also rarely use the app.    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA Try: Exiting the app, quitting it from the multitasking bar (double tap home then swipe up on the app), and then open it again.    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA You can also access it through the Music app.    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA No problem, dude.    
    
    
    @dbcel Why does your avatar have to be self taken?    
    
    
    I really should put a ban on the use of ‘bronies’ in headlines.    
    
    
    @DavidBruno Whoops. Wrong link. http://appadvice.com/appnn/contact-info-developers/ …    
    
    
    Devs and PR folk: If you can’t send me your app’s name AND a direct link to the App Store…good luck to you!    
    
    
    Why, yes, my alarm list IS longer than my contacts list. #troublewakingup #ihatemornings #goaway    
    
    
    @mikemeade Sometimes I love you, Mr. Meade.    
    
    
    “Win the Hunger Games, Be 50 Shades healthier.”

I see what you did there.    
    
    
    @markgurman …as you invite everyone to bother you.    
    
    
    I can’t get Tenacious D out of my head.    
    
    
    @ACityInOhio They’re inward singing in my soul.    
    
    
    @ACityInOhio It’s for the ladies.    
    
    
    I always match my dinner to my outfit. http://instagram.com/p/flsloioACp/     
    
    
    @thisiscyril83 Self-titled?    
    
    
    @cmfcknw Sounds peaceful. But still sorry to hear.    
    
    
    @cmfcknw I just read back. That’s awesome!    
    
    
    @johnroderick Where’s your cigar?    
    
    
    Really frustrated with customer service today. So glad I’m done with @AAACares insurance. Now to get rid of @TWC_Ohio.    
    
    
    And I still can’t access the App Store whatsoever on my iPad since iOS 7. 

What a clusterfuck.    
    
    
    @iChris Yup. Also did a full restore. Worked for about two days, then went back to not working.    
    
    
    @gameism Reset all my settings. Powered off and on again MULTIPLE times. Did a full restore. 

Nothing.    
    
    
    I’M ALL SETTLED UP NOW    
    
    
    @shewchuk I absolutely love this photo. That look.    
    
    
    @shewchuk The photo or the look?    
    
    
    I saw the sign. It opened up my eyes. I saw the sign.    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas But but    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas :{    
    
    
    Panera Bread is out of bread. What is this I don’t even    
    
    
    @chartier @PensAndPaws Congratulations!    
    
    
    @chartier @PensAndPaws Also, thank you.    
    
    
    OH: Well, she’s pretty old. Like 30 or 40.    
    
    
    @goodmanio Yep.    
    
    
    @davidcaolo Eye Kay Arr    
    
    
    PLS TO TAG ALL SPORTSBALL TWATS WITH APPROPRIATE HASHES THX    
    
    
    I had to dig out my winter coat tonight. Fuck you, Ohio.    
    
    
    “You always tweet silently.” –@ray_ob1    
    
    
    @EvaGiselle I do the same thing. 

WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG WITH US    
    
    
    @jazzy3thousand Listen to Dawn of Midi.    
    
    
    You’re now in a queue to wait even longer for a thing which leads to unnecessary hype, causing unrealistic expectations we won’t fulfill.    
    
    
    @ahockley Worse. BBM.    
    
    
    For having a lot to cover, they’re sure wasting a lot of time zzzzzzzzz    
    
    
    Oh, Phil.    
    
    
    Phil wants to be left alone with the Mac Pro. 

Let him be, guys. Let him be.    
    
    
    iYawn    
    
    
    We decided Oprah is going to come out and give away free Retina iPad minis to everyone.    
    
    
    Here’s a video showing people taking photo and video with their iPads. 

Next week on What Not To Do.    
    
    
    “I’m not bringing my iPad when I climb Mt. Everest.” 
—@KarenSFreeman    
    
    
    @DeanPerry It’s the iPad Air, bro! 

(5th gen iPad)    
    
    
    Apple is angering me with this no preorder bullshit.    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis Nailed it. 👍    
    
    
    @QueenKing0 Okay!    
    
    
    Update all the things!    
    
    
    @gpkamath Not yet. Passed to the review staff, but we’re not really doing reviews today. :) If they decide to post it, I’ll shoot you a link    
    
    
    Well, I was hoping the App Store would be fixed in iOS 7 now.

Silly me.    
    
    
    @coolpowers Just doesn’t work most times. Doesn’t work at all on my 3rd gen iPad.    
    
    
    Whoa, @iMore.    
    
    
    Is it lunch time yet?    
    
    
    @Ventchat_Sauce Please own this. http://shirt.woot.com/offers/lets-get-sauced-apron …    
    
    
    @Ventchat_Sauce But you’d look so much douchier just wearing the apron around.    
    
    
    @Ventchat_Sauce Now we’re on the same page.    
    
    
    Obligatory migraine tweet.    
    
    
    @JeffBenjam YES! About to take the PM version now. 

Even though I think it was discontinued. 😳    
    
    
    Too. Many. Sports. Twats.    
    
    
    And someone is a little TOO obsessed with Katy Perry. 

Yikes.    
    
    
    @SiddharthGoliya As well as? We cover all iOS apps and news.    
    
    
    @SquaredApe I don’t know. I unfollowed the guy.    
    
    
    ⌃ ⌘ Space    
    
    
    @ianpatrickhines Do it in a text box in Mavericks.    
    
    
    @ianpatrickhines Haha. Whoops.    
    
    
    @ianpatrickhines How. Dare. You. Sir.    
    
    
    @ianpatrickhines I don’t think I know you well enough for you to make such comments!    
    
    
    @ianpatrickhines Not even Fillion can get you out of this mess.    
    
    
    It’s snowing. I’m so glad I’m leaving tomorrow!    
    
    
    @Thatguyjoeymin Dat Lee Sin.    
    
    
    Forget noise canceling headphones. Screaming baby directly behind me. Fml.    
    
    
    @BrentDirks Hiiiiiiiii    
    
    
    @FredChartrand Yessssss!    
    
    
    @BrentDirks A proper welcome from a real Texan!    
    
    
    And the worst part about switching from Tweetbot to Tweetbot 3… pic.twitter.com/q5H15qte5H    
    
    
    @jmattm O HAI    
    
    
    @morphorod I don’t know what to do. T.T    
    
    
    @localcelebrity I HAVE ALL OF THIS GREAT MATERIAL THOUGH    
    
    
    Mango sticky rice floats my boat. Every. Time.    
    
    
    Every time I hear @felixgallo say GUI out loud, I can’t help but giggle. 

Because: GOOEY.    
    
    
    @erikamkay East side of Cleveland actually got 7 inches! Wtf.    
    
    
    @mattcomi Does that…say…babies?    
    
    
    @m4tt what year is your current one?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @m4tt Pff. I have a 2010.    
    
    
    Holsters for iPhones shouldn’t even exist.    
    
    
    @Ragart I hope you find your imaginary, fantasy holster, dude.    
    
    
    Really, Amazon? @dayoneapp http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/30/5046248/amazon-launches-day-one-digital-literary-journal-weekly-fiction-poetry …    
    
    
    @Ventchat I love you, Fin.    
    
    
    @Mike_Stopcast Same thing happened to me. Take it to the Apple Store and get a new phone.    
    
    
    @Mike_Stopcast Something is wrong with the battery.    
    
    
    @Mike_Stopcast You don’t sign a new contract… o.O    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Mike_Stopcast Okay. Then don’t go and keep your broken phone. :P    
    
    
    @Mike_Stopcast @bryterside Then drive 5 hours or keep your broken phone and don’t bitch haha    
    
    
    @Mike_Stopcast @bryterside Yeah. It’s definitely a hardware/battery issue. Many have had it. I just got mine replaced a month or so ago.    
    
    
    How the hell do you add Top Sites in Safari now?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @unkn0wnvariable Cheers! Thank you.    
    
    
    @cgw3 Thanks!    
    
    
        
    
    
    If you can believe it, @christyxcore and I have the girliest conversations in Messages, now. 

Her bubble is pink and mine is purple. 💁    
    
    
    @chartier @unkn0wnvariable I know! It was all so obvious, too. Dammit, Apple.    
    
    
    Why are my LinkedIn connections sending me Halloween e-cards? 

I didn’t even know e-cards were still a thing. 

Stop it.    
    
    
    @abrahamvegh It seems you’re trapped in a shitty Twitter app, too!    
    
    
    @abrahamvegh :/    
    
    
    “The game is almost mostly entirely free…”    
    
    
    I keep deleting emails and they keep coming back. Anyone else experiencing this in Apple Mail (Mavericks)?    
    
    
    @SteveStreza Hmph.    
    
    
    @niclake @SteveStreza WHAT OTHER ACCOUNT IS THERE THOUGH    
    
    
    Rule #2: Double Tap! RT @BrentDirks: @atjamie It’s the new zombie email. They’re not really gone until you shoot them in the head.    
    
    
    @reneritchie @SteveStreza I just have multiple Gmails and my iCloud. Of course iCloud is working. That’s all I can speak for.    
    
    
    @reneritchie @Vanish @SteveStreza I have it enabled. Still fucked up.    
    
    
    @Vanish @reneritchie @SteveStreza It’s been enabled. Yes.    
    
    
    @Vanish Ah-ha! I didn’t have it set to show all mail on this particular email address. 

Cheers!    
    
    
    “Just don’t make a scene until we leave.” –drunken @ray_ob1    
    
    
    @ray_ob1 I don’t remember either.    
    
    
    I will take you literally if you talk using double negatives. Just not seriously.    
    
    
    @matthewrex Hug anyway!    
    
    
    So, @KarenSFreeman just discovered swedish fish. We can be friends again.    
    
    
    Proof that people would do anything for swedish fish → http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kpzs3nXjwAQ …    
    
    
    “Don’t judge me, but I have to take a photo of myself picking my nose and send it to @felixgallo.” —what I just said to @KarenSFreeman    
    
    
    [Slow News Day] How To Click An Icon In Your Menu Bar (Because That’s What It’s Called In OS X)    
    
    
    I don’t get these iPhone folio cases. Incredibly impractical, in my opinion.    
    
    
    “You don’t have to read any further: this game has a poo flinging monkey. Download it now!” 💩🙊    
    
    
    As much as I love @woot, both times I’ve contacted customer service have made me feel like, as a customer, I am a very low priority. Awful.    
    
    
    @ahockley I really value customer service. Both receiving it and giving it. So, I guess I just have high expectations of everyone.    
    
    
    @ahockley Things aren’t the same anymore. It’s shitty.    
    
    
    I find myself tapping way too much to do things in Tweetbot, now. 

What is this I don’t even    
    
    
    Some doofus is trying to get review codes by impersonating me using jamieyoung.appadvice@gmail.com 

Not doing a good job.    
    
    
    @paulbrotherston @lifehacker I love you so much right now. 

Thank you! :{    
    
    
    @paulbrotherston Hadn’t even seen it yet! 

Cheers!    
    
    
    @jessemillar @chartier Damn them.    
    
    
    I finally set up auto reload on my Starbucks card. 

Step #1: Admitting you have a problem. 

Step #2: Enabling yourself anyway.    
    
    
    @Mike_Stopcast Don’t forget the caffeine 

FUCK

Tourette’s.    
    
    
    @ericleamen Bring two pair of your most comfortable shoes. Pace yourself with those free drinks. Decide what you want to see ahead of time.    
    
    
    @ericleamen Not sure yet.    
    
    
    @ericleamen Oh, you’ll know! :)    
    
    
    @QueenKing0 No idea why I kept putting it off :( It was inevitable.    
    
    
    @superpixels Oh. My. God. Love the new avatar.    
    
    
    New retina MBP lasted just over 9 hours with 3% left yet. 

I worked it to death today too.    
    
    
    @themacinjosh 13″    
    
    
    @Ragart 13″, 16 ram, 2.8 i7, 512.    
    
    
    @johnhmeyer123 Mid 2010 15″ MBP.    
    
    
    @Ragart LoL is my current addiction. 60-72 FPS consistently with max settings. Runs it crazy well.    
    
    
    @themacinjosh https://twitter.com/atjamie/status/398279215063531522 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Ragart yup.    
    
    
    @MikeWehner You’re killing it lately.    
    
    
    @bob_ham Robert.    
    
    
    @bob_ham Robert, no.    
    
    
    @themacinjosh Yeah. That would be nice.    
    
    
    @bob_ham You’d be breaking my heart right now if I had one.    
    
    
    @parislemon I need a headphone untangler assistant.    
    
    
    @bob_ham </3    
    
    
    @themacinjosh @macmixing Dom’s your guy as far as video goes. I am super indecisive. I needed something more portable plus I don’t do video.    
    
    
    @SteveStreza Kung Fu Hustle and Shaun of the Dead.    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas STOP SUBTWEETING ABOUT ME    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas WHAT 

I’ll have you know I just found out what a lululemon was last week!    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas I hate you.    
    
    
    “Wait!” called Edward Gorey “You didn’t hear the last ingredient! Moderation!” 

But Tim Burton was already out the door…    
    
    
    @JINX Better watch that finger!    
    
    
    @ThatChrisGore Always Thor.    
    
    
    @donutjaucian @ldrin oh no! Thanks! He’s okay though, right?    
    
    
    “Usually wasabi is so hot I can feel it burning a hole in the back of my skull.” 
–@KodyJGMcGee    
    
    
    “Why would someone lie like that on Twitter, though?” 
–@ray_ob1    
    
    
    @donutjaucian @ldrin Good! Had been trying to get a hold of him to make sure. Thank you!    
    
    
    @DODOsays I assume the iPad mini custom cases will fit fine on the iPad mini Retina, yes?    
    
    
    Just saw the first Christmas lights of the year.    
    
    
    @DODOsays <3 Ordered. Thanks!    
    
    
    64gb space gray, Wi-Fi. Done. 

Goodnight.    
    
    
    Looks like I may be able to get a new mini in store today.    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman Just was told I could get mine in 30 minutes! 

Yay iPad mini work day! ;)    
    
    
    I’m ready for you, too, Apple Store.    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman Nice! Waiting for mine now!    
    
    
    @seevishal That is a loaded question. Be more specific.    
    
    
    @JBTech17 But I love you!    
    
    
    @JBTech17 HAHAHAHA hate you    
    
    
    @TheBloggess This is amazing.    
    
    
    Hello, beautiful! #retinaipadmini http://instagram.com/p/gomNnTIABZ/     
    
    
    @seevishal Every device but a nano and a touch now.    
    
    
    @luisalejandrocc Yes.    
    
    
    @seevishal I could no sooner pick a favorite star in the sky…    
    
    
    Because…why the hell not? http://holidaybullshit.com     
    
    
    Poll: Do you own an iPad *and* an iPad mini? Why are you holding onto both?    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @jonfingas I’m also a big list user.    
    
    
    @ccMick It takes way too many taps to do things now. Inefficient. And lists are a nightmare.    
    
    
    @ajorama Definitely the mini. Was hoping someone could convince me to keep my 3rd gen.    
    
    
    @KyleSwank @ccMick Tweetbot 3 is like Twitteriffic now.    
    
    
    I don’t think people know what guest posting is. Especially some PR folk.    
    
    
    @ccMick @KyleSwank I like you, Mick. 

Kyle, I shake my fist in your general direction.    
    
    
    @donwb Do you use both regularly?    
    
    
    @JohnMetta @brennannovak @icupcake I work (write/edit) using a wireless keyboard + iPad often. Worked on the mini yesterday. I was surprised    
    
    
    @JohnMetta @brennannovak @icupcake I thought the size would bother me, but it was just fine. I have no reason to keep a full size iPad.    
    
    
    @JohnMetta @brennannovak @icupcake Especially since I have a 13” rMBP. Love the mini.    
    
    
    I dislike that after I install an update on an iOS device it automatically turns Bluetooth on.    
    
    
    Hot corners don’t work for me in Mavericks. Anyone else having issues?    
    
    
    Zelda: A Link Between Worlds may be the tipping point for me. It may be time to buy a 3DS. D:    
    
    
    @Vilkata That ALMOST made me get one. I was already shamelessly addicted to AC on the Game Cube back in the day.    
    
    
    @thebuttmaster That’s what I think I’ll get. Hoping maybe I can snag a good deal for Black Friday. We’ll see.    
    
    
    @chartier @danvpeterson @1Password Yes, tell Dan all of those things! And then roll your eyes at @KyleSwank. Make him feel like I’m there.    
    
    
    @jmattm Oh, that almost made me cave. It was very difficult. But I think now I *have* to get an XL. And get both games!    
    
    
    @WCHamilton Finder *is* a disaster. Oof.    
    
    
    Sell my 3rd gen iPad…buy a 3DS XL…

Just keeping the economy alive, one gadget at a time.    
    
    
    @thebuttmaster My social life will regret it…

…but I gotta do what I gotta do. Priorities, man.    
    
    
    @iChris @lonelysandwich @coin This sounds so dirty. 

I like it.    
    
    
    @JBTech17 I love my Nintendo.    
    
    
    I’m so much better at the sarcasm than @iChris.    
    
    
    @KyleSwank I’m going to have to get one now. :(    
    
    
    @iChris I see what you did there. 

No, really. I do.    
    
    
    @RyanSumo Really? My recommendations have all been 3DS XL or bust.    
    
    
    @RyanSumo haha. Well then.    
    
    
    I may have gotten impatient and just ordered a 3DS XL. 

Fml.    
    
    
    @thebuttmaster Oh, yes. Thank you! :)    
    
    
    @thisiscyril83 Nope. No time/money. I’m more a computer gamer anyway.    
    
    
    @thisiscyril83 Nope. Got a Retina mini. Selling my 3rd gen.    
    
    
    Mint has alerted me that I’ve purchased too many electronics this month. 

Whoops.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @JeffBenjam Space Gray + black Smart Cover is for winners!    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas You know me too well, Joel.    
    
    
    We’ve received your request. You’ll be unsubscribed in 28299727513 days.    
    
    
    Has anyone ever actually not beaten them then joined them?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Got my 3DS XL today (along with New Leaf and Pokemon Y). 👾

Friend Code: 4098-3754-6409    
    
    
    Not liking the new @iTVShowsApp as much. Especially since I can no longer hide sections (i.e. ended). Too showy. I just need info, clearly.    
    
    
    @tperzl Just as showy. Not as much info. No notifications or sync. :(    
    
    
    @tperzl Hm. Guess I’ll have to check it out again then.Those features weren’t there last I saw.    
    
    
    @tperzl And what I mean is, it’s the same design (no titles) and there is no way for me to manage shows I want to keep but hide.    
    
    
    @morphorod That too is no good. :/    
    
    
    I’ll still never understand the disconnect on iOS between the iPad and iPhone. Safari buttons on top on one and bottom on the other. Awful.    
    
    
    @gameism It’s always been like that. And it’s so awkward.    
    
    
    If you invite me to your party, I’ll be the one eating all of the little brown pieces out of your party mix.    
    
    
    @HeikeBaird Bee arr tee    
    
    
    @loganowitz Wait. That actually means something? Mine’s been on for years.    
    
    
    I think it’s good day to drink some hot chai and watch The Nightmare Before Christmas.    
    
    
    I totally got pulled in by Cyber Monday. My bank account is in pain.    
    
    
    @macmixing Hahaha. Actually none! :O    
    
    
    @macmixing Video games and a portable external hard drive.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @hiBrie Never used a Nespresso, but I swear by my Keurig!    
    
    
    I may have purchased a 3.5 pound bag of Swedish Fish on Amazon. 

Don’t judge me.    
    
    
    Watching The Sound of Music live. Didn’t realize Bill Compton played the father. Too funny.    
    
    
    I still get a prize in my cereal box. http://instagram.com/p/hkF6KnIAAn/     
    
    
    Because so many asked: Cinnamon Toast Crunch. What else?    
    
    
    @RandGM Why Dialvetica (love the app though!) when you have LCP?    
    
    
    Co-working with @KarenSFreeman today. Talking about how god awful Apple’s calendar app is in iOS 7.    
    
    
    @jmattm I’m a Fantastical girl!    
    
    
    My mustache grew, you guys. http://instagram.com/p/hrq-MAoAM9/     
    
    
    @MaLindaLou Haha, yup.    
    
    
    New PR tactic seems to be to change the from name to “Hi Mom” to get the email read.

Joke’s on them. I delete my mom’s emails.    
    
    
    @joshuaschnell I’d totally read that too.    
    
    
    “Don’t you just want to cut a bitch sometimes?” —why I love @KarenSFreeman so much    
    
    
    It seems like we’ve had so many Friday the 13ths this year.    
    
    
    @sidoneill Really? Seems like we’ve had at least 3 or 4! I must be losing it.    
    
    
    I would kill for some delicious Turkish food delivery today.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jeremymeyers Huh?    
    
    
    @teefury My first scented shirt! I love you guys. #jamiehastoomanytshirts http://instagram.com/p/h9FlWTIACq/     
    
    
    “Yeah, people always want to put me in their circles. I don’t want to be in anyone’s circle!” 
–my father on G+    
    
    
    Desolation of Smaug with my Pops today.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ianpatrickhines @sidoneill I could deal with the silliness of the barrel scene. It’s Tauriel, the love story, and the entire mountain scene    
    
    
    @ianpatrickhines @sidoneill Yes. I think instead of adding the Tauriel bullshit, they could’ve just did the mountain scene correctly/longer.    
    
    
    @felixgallo POTATOS SUICIDE PACT    
    
    
    I’ve never had to return anything to Amazon until this year. And this year, I’ve had to return so many things due to defective/broken items.    
    
    
    Watch this. It’s only 7 minutes. http://vimeo.com/36470597     
    
    
    @Thatguyjoeymin Who else? ;)    
    
    
    @DeanPerry Pretty good. Busy. But good. How’re you, Mr. Perry?    
    
    
    @dbcel Not until the last 6 months. I even got a McDonalds egg sandwich without the egg a month ago. Just the bread part. Wtf.    
    
    
    You should be able to go to Target, buy a glass of wine, and shop. 

Shops with hops.    
    
    
    Thing 3 announced officially for 2014 — but *when*?! Need. http://culturedcode.com/things/blog/     
    
    
    @AyeGear Shoot me your email. I don’t seem to have it anywhere.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Double checking is iffy. Triple checking is a no.    
    
    
    @hiBrie @ItsMattRVA I’m working!    
    
    
    @hiBrie @ItsMattRVA Yes.    
    
    
    I realize today is the Airing of the Grievances, but…damn, Twitter.    
    
    
    @richburroughs Coffee regret?    
    
    
    “Mashed potatoes is kind of like frosting for vegetables.” –@HeikeBaird    
    
    
    Talking in doge meme with @HeikeBaird  all night. 

Such amuse. Much funny.    
    
    
    @HeikeBaird Dead to me.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @HeikeBaird WHAT DOES THE DOGE SAY    
    
    
    Anyone else used to play that free Chex FPS for PC in the 90s?    
    
    
    Ahh, Christmas! The day of the epic regeneration of a great time traveller.    
    
    
    @Turdhat The Beetus.    
    
    
    @HeikeBaird In case you somehow missed it: http://www.buzzfeed.com/jwherrman/millions-of-dogecoins-stolen-in-apparent-heist …    
    
    
    @TheRealJoshuaD I thought I was the only one! Yessss! 

However, never tried the Mr. Pibb one.    
    
    
    That moment when your boyfriend gives you a Christmas gift and it’s literally marked NSFW. 

#soulmate    
    
    
    @ericleamen Got the exact one recently. 👍    
    
    
    @TheRealJoshuaD👍    
    
    
    I think I’m finally going to order a Google Chromecast.    
    
    
    So, Apple gave me two gifts for day two of their 12 Days Of Gifts promotion. 

Mistake?    
    
    
    @michelledeidre @Marvel Very calender. Much mistake. Wow.    
    
    
    @Pantysnawad A show and now an app.    
    
    
    @TheRealJoshuaD I have an Apple TV. Wanted something portable. For traveling.    
    
    
    @KyleSwank Me too. Just want something portable for travel.    
    
    
    @jasonspooner Good call!    
    
    
    @gameism For now, very few. But more than those two.    
    
    
    @jim_napier No. :( We have how to ditch your PC for an iPad though. ;) We mainly only do iOS.    
    
    
    @KyleSwank Oh, he’d love that.    
    
    
    @iChris Real Life: Who uses Find My Friends?    
    
    
    @SteveStreza Oh god. Oh god no.    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas All of your tweets are now read aloud using the face you’re making in your avatar. Tone included. 

You’re welcome.    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas You’re ruining this for me.    
    
    
    @iChris Ah, that makes sense I guess.    
    
    
    Nothing says Christmas time quite like watching Lord of the Rings/The Hobbit.    
    
    
    @shoesmith81 I never read Harry Potter. And didn’t like the 2 movies I saw. :(    
    
    
    @KyleSwank I have been, yes!    
    
    
    Seeing all the entitled, whiny brats complain about the gifts Apple is giving away for free for the 12 Days Of Gifts is unbelievable.    
    
    
    @KyleSwank Yes! Did you?    
    
    
    @RayneBradley I have. A couple years ago, AppAdvice did a similar thing where we gave away a lot of awesome stuff (including some iPhones).    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @DeanPerry I did. Did you, Mr. Perry?    
    
    
    @KyleSwank Sounds like a win Christmas to me.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Probably me! :P    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Hashtag all baby photos with #MuteThisJamie, imo.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Lol!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Thank you. I am glad we worked this out in plenty of time.    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA I feel so awful old school RTing…    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA …it makes me feel dirty.    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA AND IT’S TOO LONG TOO 

FUCK YOU MATT    
    
    
    @ItsMattRVA So selfish. I mean really.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @HeyVeronica Put velcro on your clothing and on the remote. Never lose remote again.    
    
    
    @JINX o.O    
    
    
    @JINX So tempted to send forwards.    
    
    
    @MikeIsaac Like…tea bags? Loose tea? Brewed tea?    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @DeanPerry @christyxcore Or just post it all on Facebook. Where it belongs. (AKA: Why Jamie quit.) ;)    
    
    
    Oh, god. Oh, god. 

https://vine.co/v/h9PBY0Z2DIz 

Can’t. Un. See.    
    
    
    @sidoneill OH MY GOD STOP    
    
    
    @JeffBenjam I, too, have rage for me.    
    
    
    I just made a huge cup of hot cocoa and put four Hershey kisses in it—and no one can stop me!

I love being an adult.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @macmixing I just noticed your new avatar. Perfect.    
    
    
    I’m still waiting for the Tweetbot 3 update that will fix the gestures and other shit they messed up in the new release.    
    
    
        
    
    
    ME: Do I actually have to put pants on for this party tonight? @ray_ob1: I’ll be ripping them off at midnight, so don’t bother.    
    
    
    My new year’s resolution is 2048x1536.    
    
    
    Drunken politics. @KodyJGMcGee is on his soapbox. We’re just laughing.    
    
    
    Going outside now to bang pots and pans and yell drunkenly about 2014. Just to trip people out.    
    
    
    We have whiskey up the nose, folks!    
    
    
    Let’s not get too excited about steak and shake into thousand 14. 

Thanks, Siri.    
    
    
    I’m just pizza.    
    
    
    Going out in the same clothes I wore last night because yolo.    
    
    
    @nateboateng What even    
    
    
    I want to know why you ladies are so obsessed with this EOS lip balm. It’s more waxy than moisturizing; ends up drying my lips out more.    
    
    
    @hiBrie Or…I just never buy it again and stick to Burt’s Bees and C.O. Bigelow. 👍    
    
    
    If you can’t find what you’re looking for 

→ MAKE IT.    
    
    
    I got my first grid-it today. No idea why I waited so long. Anything to make my life easier and more organized.    
    
    
    @SpaceCatPics Psstt. Don’t retweet a bunch of someone else’s tweets. That’s not why we follow you.    
    
    
    I am surrounded by so many external hard drives right now.    
    
    
    