"Chance is like a picture, it'd be nice if you'd just take it."    
    
    
    I'm at The Juice Press (New York) http://4sq.com/oc64P0     
    
    
    It's been a majorly productive day at work....  thanks to the "Fountain of Youth" smoothie I drank this morning perhaps?    
    
    
    I live in the greatest city in the world. Amazing opportunities around every corner #NYC    
    
    
    #MBFW = best.week.ever.  http://twitpic.com/6kvmzc     
    
    
    Yes my dear you absolutely CAN. :) RT @aidgemcclells @allie_hunt11 omg I am so envious of you. Can I move there already ?    
    
    
    @nycprgirls how is #mbfw going for you ladies?! It's my first experience with it and I am LOVING every second. :)    
    
    
    wait. why is everything in the Missoni for Target bedding collection sold out?  everything. I NEED. #FirstWorldProblems    
    
    
    Central Park Wedding  http://instagr.am/p/NFbBu/     
    
    
    Annnnd I just got off work. #fashionweek    
    
    
    My fav bar :) RT @mollybloomsbar #Sunnyside bar takes a stand RT @mollybloomsbar Molly Blooms in The New York Times: tinyurl.com/3d3wly2    
    
    
    @AlanaMadden How much longer are you in the city? We need to brunch it or someting... #JustSayin    
    
    
    I wish they provided emergency liquor in cabs... For times like these when traffic is at a standstill.    
    
    
    Check out the article I helped write for O'Dwyer's Magazine! Page 12. http://bit.ly/qAKXSS  This is a milestone in my career :)    
    
    
    Loving that the sushi place we're eating lunch at is playing RHCP - #swag    
    
    
    A man legitimately just tried to start a conversation with me through a restaurant window.... But why? #OnlyInNY    
    
    
    @toryburch WHY do you do this to me? I want these hard. http://bit.ly/rlmMe8     
    
    
    #NowPlaying "Pumped Up Kicks" - Foster the People.    
    
    
    I'm SO doing this http://www.travelzoo.com/local-deals/deal/955 … ... Who wants to join me?? Live a little.    
    
    
    Good thing I made an appointment Because the nail salon is poppin right now #EverythingDid    
    
    
    If iced coffee is a bad idea, then everyday is one big bad decision for me RT @bdim14 That iced coffee was a bad idea #nyc cc/ @allie_hunt11    
    
    
    Sooo, if you use Instagram like all the cool kids, you should probably follow @ScottFishman #JustSayin    
    
    
    Shoutout to @Justin_M_Ochoa for being a web design BOSS    
    
    
    I cannot even put into words how DELIGHTED I am to bust out my fall wardrobe. Mother nature flipped the switch this morning and I am not mad    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/qBMidl  >>  best music video ever! #DogLover    
    
    
    #FF #PRGirls @SanaAndTheCity @nycprgirls @dkny @OscarPRGirl @WomenInPR1 @kmg_89 @JennaGlynn @ClaireMBiggs @HautePR @NYCPR @AlexLorenz23    
    
    
    @RickHunt1 Happy Friday Daddy-O! Love you!    
    
    
    My motto: Dream.Believe.Achieve. #MakeItHappen    
    
    
    I love when I get a major iced coffee buzz. It makes me feel...what's the word?...invincible. #mmwahaha    
    
    
    Just found out I'm going to L.A. for a week in October!!!! I love my job :)    
    
    
    Thanks for all the #FF love! Hope you're all having a #FF (fabulous friday, duh)    
    
    
    *blush* thanks for all the amazing experiences! RT @HautePR 
@allie_hunt11 is, like, the best pr assistant EVER.    
    
    
    normal gets you nowhere.    
    
    
    Yankees are up. Stocks are up. This makes for a lot of happy new yorkahs    
    
    
    To run a successful #PR campaign, you must truly believe in your client. #PR101    
    
    
    #FF @eric_wheeler @bdim14 @PRNews @PublicityGuru    
    
    
    @sarahnrussell Aw yay- have fun! I'm going on one tomorrow to the Brooklyn Brewery, and I'm rather excited about this one too!    
    
    
    @sarahnrussell no way! a little edginess is a good thing :)    
    
    
    Cabbin' it downtown for @LoveAddictNYC 's birthday bash!    
    
    
    Damn it. I left my apartment and forgot to put my statement ring on. #FashionGirlProblems    
    
    
    The city looks ravishing tonight! But then again, when doesn't she? #NYCLover    
    
    
    Loving life, NYC and bottle service with @mallory_ryan @LoveAddictNYC http://twitpic.com/6m1ger     
    
    
    "May the best of your days be the worst of your tomorrows" - Jay-z    
    
    
    One of the best men in this ginormous city. :) http://twitpic.com/6m3i1i     
    
    
    cc/ @Teddy_J_Penley RT @ScottFishman EPIC Plank https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=220584074667004&set=a.213713805354031.54067.213227492069329&type=1&theater … #planking #owling #horsemaning    
    
    
    taking nyquil, curling up in a ball and going to sleep... hoping i'm back to 100% tomorrow so I can enjoy sunday funday with my favorites    
    
    
    Photoset: Last Sunday, the 10th anniversary of 9/11, I spent the day downtown at the Memorial. It was an... http://tumblr.com/xbg4reywvp     
    
    
    Photo: I love Sundays… Treat yourself! http://tumblr.com/xbg4rfblcl     
    
    
    #Jets    
    
    
    Strolling around Sunnyside... Loving this absolutely perfect weather l    
    
    
    Stopped and played with these cuties... And got invited to a barbecue! #winning http://twitpic.com/6mz6ch     
    
    
    Sooo when they said they were sending a car, I was thinking a simple black sedan.. Nope. Just got picked up in an all black escalade. #Woah    
    
    
    @AlanaMadden um omg. HOW did you get all the Missoni??? EVERYTHING is sold out    
    
    
    Missoni is sold out at @Target ... so I had to make do with it as my Twitter background for now.    
    
    
    Good morning upper east siders (in gossip girl voice) #RiseandGrind    
    
    
    Acronyms all #PR girls should know... thanks @nycprgirls ! http://bit.ly/qA88Ub  #PR101    
    
    
    I die. Ordering. RT @collegefashion: New at CF: TOMS Launches College-Inspired “Campus Classics” Line http://bit.ly/qbCICV     
    
    
    @SofiaVergara definitely! She looked stunning RT @GiltCityNYC Who was best-dressed at last night's #emmys? Tell us what you think!    
    
    
    Tory & Tom.  http://instagr.am/p/Ni0jI/     
    
    
    Got pumpkin spice IN my iced coffee. Officially obsessed. (@ Starbucks) http://4sq.com/qNfPlC     
    
    
    It is to-die! I definitely recommend it :) RT @ashleysantucci @allie_hunt11 wow! That sounds amazing!!    
    
    
    "Sometimes PR is a thankless job. So do it for YOURSELF. #PR101" - (via dknyprgirl) http://tumblr.com/xbg4s3y7fd     
    
    
    Don't follow your dreams. CHASE them. #ReadySetGo    
    
    
    I love the big flower I'm wearing in my hair today.. almost as much as all the crazy looks I get for wearing it. Sorry i'm not sorry.    
    
    
    cc/ @KelceyJBaby I love the big flower I'm wearing in my hair today.. almost as much as the crazy looks I get for wearing it. sorrynotsorry    
    
    
    Today has been one for the books. #HappyGirl    
    
    
    You got this!! RT @WordlyAdvice Loosely inspired by PR maven @allie_hunt11,I'm giving this personal Twitter thing another shot.Wish me luck.    
    
    
    Whipping up an organic Mexican feast before the game. #MuyDelicioso    
    
    
    I'm on my #MidnightGrind. You can sleep when you're dead.    
    
    
    It may not be the prettiest day- but it's going to be a fan.tastic one. Excited for my meeting this afternoon!    
    
    
    Ladies- Don't rely on a man for your happiness... they should only ADD to it. You should find your own happiness first. #truth    
    
    
    Oh how I love waiting in line at the post office. LOVE it #meh    
    
    
    But on a happier note- today was an amazing day. And it's about to get better with a veggie din and $1 burrs with @mallory_ryan    
    
    
    Love jamming out with the cabbie "I just came to say hello"    
    
    
    We were bar bunnies tonight @mallory_ryan ... We hopped.    
    
    
    I'm at Haute PR (115 E 57 St., Park, New York) http://4sq.com/phNvpR     
    
    
    LOVE you. & yes, this weekend it is! RT @Bconnpsu @allie_hunt11 so good to see you last night!!!! More drinks this weekend?? xo    
    
    
    Hanging out with these little chickens (@ TRUMPistan) [pic]: http://4sq.com/qB9IM0     
    
    
    Slightly obsessed with my most recent purchase @MichaelKors #swag http://twitpic.com/6ogtcb     
    
    
    Can.not.wait. until the new Modern Family premier at 9. #BestShowEvs    
    
    
    The most epic of shows for sure!  RT @mattcarlson12 @allie_hunt11 I'm soo pumped too!    
    
    
    Ready to break out my inner #hipster tomorrow at the Williamsburg Film Festival in good ol Brooklyn. What to wear? Thick-rimmed glasses?    
    
    
    Watching the first episode of  2BrokeGirls ..love it already. "I wear knit beanies because it's cold out, YOU wear them because of coldplay"    
    
    
    @MissJennaB "Whitney" ? Like as in Port? I need details    
    
    
    Miss ya.. and so does NY...so come back soon little bro. RT @EHunt55 @allie_hunt11......miss my favorite sister     
    
    
    LAVO. RT @nycprgirls New Post: The Best New York City Clubs http://bit.ly/mX5EqL#nyc     
    
    
    If you're a rockstar #webdesign pro ... DM me!    
    
    
    I'm at Sea (114 N 6th St, at Berry St, Brooklyn) http://4sq.com/nxNby9     
    
    
    A dose of Williamsburg does the soul some good every once in awhile. Unleash your inner hipster.    
    
    
    Just had the best pad thai of my life- now on to the Williamsburg Film Festival!    
    
    
    Mark Zuckerberg: "I'm making these changes so social media 'experts' can charge more money to teach clueless people all these changes" #fb    
    
    
    This weather is miz. But my mood is quite the opposite "life isn't about waiting for the storm to pass it's learning to dance in the rain"    
    
    
    "Don't cheat the world of your contribution. Give it what you've got." -Steven Pressfield    
    
    
    New Hunters and perfume! (@ Bloomingdale's w/ 8 others) http://4sq.com/pSObIG     
    
    
    10 Things Everyone Should Know About SEO in 2011 http://bit.ly/ohIOtY  via @jornalistics #pr    
    
    
    Drinks with my lovelies @mallory_ryan @LoveAddictNYC .The rain will NOT rain on our parade... And that totes makes sense.    
    
    
    Does the fact that my cabbie is burning incense and reading the NYTimes while driving, and me being fine with it, make me a real new yorkah?    
    
    
    Getting some work and laundry done before lunch at Southern Hospitality (@jtimberlake 's restaurant) !    
    
    
    Jewelry Heaven (@ Hell's Kitchen Flea Market w/ 7 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/nNojZ2     
    
    
    Hey big baby. #presh #doglover http://instagr.am/p/ODgOt/     
    
    
    Yummy brunch with the roomie! (@ Sidetracks) [pic]: http://4sq.com/oM2DNg     
    
    
    I love Sundays, they're fun days.    
    
    
    My newest obsesh? cappuccino muffin. #nomnom    
    
    
    Great tips-thanks! RT @PRDailyNews 8 tips for writing press releases that journalists(& bloggers) read http://bit.ly/qVEffz  #PR #socialmedia    
    
    
    You know you're in the real world when you Check LinkedIn more often than Facebook. #JustSayin    
    
    
    I'm at Haute PR (115 E 57 St., Park, New York) http://4sq.com/pVU7Ae     
    
    
    Ryan Habor Collection's "Vander Pump". To die for!  http://instagr.am/p/OYlk-/     
    
    
    Photo: Ryan Habor Collection’s “Vander Pump”. To die for! (Taken with instagram) http://tumblr.com/xbg4xjd8du     
    
    
    #Yankees let's gooooo    
    
    
    faves song!xoxo RT @catierix @allie_hunt11, listening to #heysoulsister & working on stupid homework.Wish u were here to make it 1/2-way fun    
    
    
    Getting my hair chopped tomorrow. Seasons are changing, so the 'do must too.    
    
    
    A little late, but finally joining in #pr20chat.. Allie here! AE at PR firm in Manhattan    
    
    
    word. RT @kevinkimbrell never settle for less than you deserve in life    
    
    
    @ClaireMBiggs I work at Haute PR! How are you and what are you up to??    
    
    
    @ClaireMBiggs email me! adhunt89@gmail.com - we STILL need to get together missy.    
    
    
    Grande iced coffee with extra skim and 2 splenda, please and thank you. #RiseandGrind    
    
    
    Happy Rosh Hashanah and Shana Tova to all celebrating!    
    
    
    Chop chop time (@ Le Salon East) http://4sq.com/qmrKAC     
    
    
    The 3 Cs of life: Choices, chances and changes. You must make a choice, to take a chance, or your life will never change.    
    
    
    New hair: asymmetrical awesomeness. http://instagr.am/p/OfZ3f/     
    
    
    Pita burger with gorgonzola cheese, mushrooms and onions. Made by chef Allie. #delish http://twitpic.com/6s3nyd     
    
    
    New obsesh: Maybelline "Baby Lips" lip balm.    
    
    
    solid question, noey. RT @ncminitelove why do you park on a driveway but drive on a parkway?    
    
    
    Looks like I'm in the right career field. "Study: PR is the second-most-caffeinated profession" http://lnkd.in/f3XANA     
    
    
    Happy National Coffee Day, fellow coffee junkies. I will be celebrating with... coffee? iced, to be exact.    
    
    
    Dinner and drinks with my loves :) http://twitpic.com/6skyl1     
    
    
    I'm at Elmo Restaurant and Lounge (156 7th Ave, btw 19th and 20th, New York) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/ofYwrn     
    
    
    Starbucks is BLARING their music... making it imppossible for me to even hear my own thoughts and get my work done. Not okay with this.    
    
    
    High heels high hopes  http://instagr.am/p/OtF-G/     
    
    
    @catherineburd it's delish! You HAVE to try it. And Bethany was on Ellen? I die. My favorite women! #nohomo :)    
    
    
    Last night was epic. This morning was epic-er though. @mallory_ryan    
    
    
    The umbrella pic.  http://instagr.am/p/OxxLs/     
    
    
    Nail time with @mallory_ryan    
    
    
    I love the random street fairs of #NYC and the strawberry+nutella crepes that come with them.    
    
    
    Kind of obsessed with my mani #nailart http://twitpic.com/6uaqoh     
    
    
    @ashleysantucci thanks love!    
    
    
    I love fall weather! And by fall weather, I mean fall fashion..duh. #SweatersandStarbucks    
    
    
    First book club meeting! (@ Soy Cafe) http://4sq.com/potTz2     
    
    
    A glass of wine and Microsoft Excel lists at 11:30pm on a Monday... Just another day in the life of a #PRgirl    
    
    
    @SammyMalone2112 You can join mine when you move back to NYC, duh. And here's a pic, per your request  ..>> http://instagr.am/p/OfZ3f/  MISS YOU    
    
    
    Hot Heels- Hot Dogs?  http://instagr.am/p/PFju0/     
    
    
    It's a blazer+jeans+heels kinda day, ya know? oh, and throw in a statement necklace, duh. #fashion    
    
    
    Ut oh....Apple is up to something. The Apple Store is temporarily shut down . #Iphone5  eeeeek SOOOO essited    
    
    
    58 degrees is too cold for iced coffee. - sigh - chi tea latte it is. #Fall http://twitpic.com/6v44q5     
    
    
    and I, for rock stars. sigh. RT @SanaAndTheCity I am a sucker for super heroes.    
    
    
    Truth. RT @eric_wheeler Five ways #PR campaigns are like getting married http://bit.ly/o8KkoJ     
    
    
    Dear Apple, 4S is all you got for me?  #really #letstalkiphone    
    
    
    The Versace for H&M Campaign Is Out... and I die. #fashion http://shar.es/b08HA     
    
    
    @Teddy_J_Penley YOU CAN DO IT :)    
    
    
    WHAT?! RT @NewYorkPost BREAKING NYC: HELICOPTER CRASHES IN EAST RIVER... developing    
    
    
    #NowPlaying (more like jamming out to) "Nothing's Gonna Stop Us Now"- Starship,  in the office. Yup.    
    
    
    So lovely meeting up with @ClaireMBiggs today... and eating a mountain of frozen yogurt at Forty Carrots.    
    
    
    @bdim14 my obsession with him is borderline unhealthy.. I NEED to see it    
    
    
    So mad, SO MAD, that I am not watching the George Harrison doc right now. I am SO MAD omg    
    
    
    iPhone 4S= For Steve #iSad    
    
    
    #NP "she's gotta dress with class and Jean Paul Gaultier and a Hermes bag" ... yea, I WISH I had a Hermes bag #FirstWorldProblems    
    
    
    @hannah_kirkland sames.I see @ least 5 daily on park ave and want to vom. I'm glad we have such high aspirations- thresher ct would be proud    
    
    
    It's a beautiful morning in the city... Loving this fall weather!    
    
    
    Guys, take notes. #mensfashion #swag http://tmagazine.blogs.nytimes.com/2011/10/01/styled-to-a-t-cristian-zuzunaga/?ref=mens-fashion …    
    
    
    I'm at Haute PR (115 E 57 St., Park, New York) http://4sq.com/oPxgR7     
    
    
    Love this, ladies! RT @nycprgirls New Post - 10 Signs You Have PR Girl Charm http://nycprgirls.com/10-signs-your-have-pr-girl-charm/ …    
    
    
    "you need, like, a good jewish guy...or, like, a non-jewish guy that actually has, like, a good career" - yes, this was actually said to me    
    
    
    What a beautiful day it is on the #UpperEastSide :) Happy Friday!    
    
    
    @ClaireMBiggs @kmg_89 Perf- 12 on Sunday it is. Can't wait lovelies!    
    
    
    Legit just saw a mom pushing what had to be a 5 year old in a stroller. There is something so not right about that #spoiled    
    
    
    #NowPlaying "Ticket to Ride"- The Beatles my fave    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow @OohlalaNY ..Loving your site! #fashion    
    
    
    Working down the street from Bloomingdales, H&M and Sephora was fine... Until it wasn't. #shopaholic    
    
    
    My calendar just sent me this push message. Not even jew. Thanks for the reminder though? #easyfasting hahaha http://twitpic.com/6wnhyp     
    
    
    Had a delish dinner in Little Italy... Now home to work more and then, wait for it....A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP!! #winning    
    
    
    Thanks, babes! @AlexLorenz23 ... come visit soon! xoxo    
    
    
    Dropped my laundry off- now to the coffee shop to get some reading in and relax!    
    
    
    I'm at Sunnyside nail spa [pic]: http://4sq.com/nt7fVq     
    
    
    Today was supposed to be a relax and do nothing day... I just spent an hour rearranging my room. #neurotic    
    
    
    @EHunt55 what makes it so kick ass?! & did you wish our little bro a happy 15th bday? loves ya    
    
    
    @Bethenny omg that sounds DELISH! you're amaze. period. end of story.    
    
    
    Watching "Bridesmaids" for the first time (pause for reaction).. only 4 minutes in and I'm already dying! totes hilares    
    
    
    Brunching it with @Mallory_ryan duh (@ Bier International w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/oH5Yqt     
    
    
    Peaceful, Easy Living (Central Park Duh) http://instagr.am/p/PoZ6X/     
    
    
    Perf day of brunching, shopping, exploring... And more shopping. With @mallory_ryan and Veronica! #SundayFunday    
    
    
    It's a gorgeous day in the city #RiseandGrind :)    
    
    
    Was having the worst day- until I got home and checked the mail. Had a card and Starbucks giftcard from my parents :) they're the best.    
    
    
    Going to meet the girls for "A Night of Luxury" event. We fancy, huh? @LoveAddictNYC @mallory_ryan    
    
    
    New Lamborghini revealed! #sexy http://twitpic.com/6zhtks     
    
    
    Loved meeting @mccordalex and @SimonvanKempen tonight! http://twitpic.com/6zibrv     
    
    
    @aidgemcclells you CAN!    
    
    
    @laurenlonson oh no! I can relate to that though, not going to lie. Let's get together soon! PR girl happy hour??    
    
    
    Let's be honest, Hey Soul Sister is the greatest song of the decade. Period. End of story. #music    
    
    
    I did! The Lambo was HOT! RT @mccordalex @allie_hunt11 so nice to meet you as well - hope you had a great night!    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Jobs" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/oWsplq     
    
    
    New phone, say what? (@ Apple Store w/ 19 others) http://4sq.com/or5RDA     
    
    
    I spy cute nerds at the Genius Bar in the 5th ave Apple Store :)    
    
    
    Cute guy at the Apple store downloaded iOS5 on my iphone- I'm obsessed! the new notification system is AMAZE.    
    
    
    What do I walk past on my way to the train after work? a murder crime scene investigation with a million reporters    
    
    
    @ScottFishman iMessage is LEGIT #iObsessed    
    
    
    LA Oct 27-Nov 3 and Indiana Nov 18-26 soooooo excited! Will miss my boyfriend NYC though. Don't think he'd fit at the Thanksgiving table    
    
    
    This is epic. http://book.babewalker.com/  Totes pre-ordering. #WhiteGirlProblems    
    
    
    All of our pumpkins! Bet you can't guess which one is mine pic.twitter.com/zT8Y2gA    
    
    
    Miss you betches @blakeleighking @ncminitelove @carlyszabo http://instagr.am/p/QcPGV/     
    
    
    why isn't sleep happening for me?    
    
    
    Life isn't fair, but it's still good. #StayingPositive    
    
    
    I'm best reachable by email as my iphone is attached to my hand. #PRgirl    
    
    
    Does anyone know of any open positions in #PR in #NYC ?    
    
    
    Don't piss off McDonald's employees... http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2011/10/14/rayon-mcintosh-mcdonalds-_n_1011580.html?ir=Food …    
    
    
    I love @pinkberry like a love song. #justsaying    
    
    
    I'm at Hop Devil Grill (129 Saint Marks Pl, Ave A, New York) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/mZCQgK     
    
    
    It's 2011, can we please get some waterproof phones? I would like to text in the shower. #justsaying    
    
    
    @ClaireMBiggs thanks so much, love! How do I go about applying @sforman8 ?    
    
    
    Subway Stranger http://instagr.am/p/Q5kPR/     
    
    
    I need this! @mallory_ryan you know how i feel about HH RT“@FashionSnag: Haute Hippie Poncho http://bit.ly/mYnkIp ”    
    
    
    Missoni is on sale at @GiltCityNYC today! http://www.gilt.com/sale/women/missoni-409 …    
    
    
    Italian din with @ClaireMBiggs    
    
    
    Just watched "Horrible Bosses" for the first time- SO hilar!    
    
    
    Thai dinner and a comedy show tonight  #LifeisGood    
    
    
    I'm at Turtle Bay Grill & Lounge (987 2nd Ave, btw 52nd & 53rd St, New York) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/rbcSW9     
    
    
    Autumn looks splendid on Central Park http://instagr.am/p/ROPWJ/     
    
    
    Getting lost in Central Park.... And I'm not mad about it. :) http://twitpic.com/74uxk4     
    
    
    Hope it gets here fast! xo Rt @SammyMalone2112 @allie_hunt11 I cant wait to restart our Sunday afternoon Central Park tradition this summer!    
    
    
    Gives me chills every time http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tgc5l9X3Dn4 … #MusicMonday    
    
    
    This is the best and worst Tumblr of all time. Kanye'd By The Bell.. can you dig it? http://kanyedbythebell.tumblr.com/  Thank you @Bconnpsu    
    
    
    Just a quick touch up with the Yves Saint Laurent products I can't afford (@ Sephora w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/sUGCIQ     
    
    
    More Beds for the Homeless Children http://instagr.am/p/RWG69/     
    
    
    Tom Petty will be the soundtrack to my busy day today #RiseandGrind    
    
    
    Totes can't wait for exercise, homemade veggie pizza and movies with @mallory_ryan tonight...  @LoveAddictNYC PLEASE try and make it!    
    
    
    The things that get me through the day are as follows: coffee, gchat and rock n' roll.    
    
    
    @dkny reveals herself! LOVE THIS... #PR girl motivation http://ology.com/fashion-and-beauty/dkny-pr-girl-reveals-herself …    
    
    
    Madame Werz Photography is seeking a rockstar web design intern. email alliehuntpr@yahoo.com if you're interested! #internships #webdesign    
    
    
    You'll text me? No no no...The best way to reach me is via email or gchat. Please and thank you. #PRgirlproblems    
    
    
    @Official_LMD check out my little bro @EHunt55 's prof pic... reppin.    
    
    
    @arhakim oh, I totes agree!    
    
    
    one glass of pinot grigio please. on second thought, make that a bottle.    
    
    
    Just when we thought @instagram couldn't get any better... http://printstagr.am/     
    
    
    Blood orange margs, yes please. (@ La Palapa w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/tSC6rY     
    
    
    I'm at Forty Carrots w/ @loveaddictnyc http://4sq.com/vO56sk     
    
    
    @LoveAddictNYC @mallory_ryan and myself playing around with the photo booth app pic.twitter.com/aq0tpjD    
    
    
    Celebrating my birthday in the greatest city in the world with my fab friends! #LifeisGood    
    
    
    I'm at Ninja New York (25 Hudson St., btwn Duane St. & Reade St., New York) http://4sq.com/rWISrJ     
    
    
    I'm at Bistro 60 (formerly Le Taxi) (37 E 60th, at 60th St, New York) http://4sq.com/uudKor     
    
    
    Happy belated birthday to me!  http://instagr.am/p/SsA4M/     
    
    
    "Wonderful Tonight" by Pattie Boyd RT @AbbevillePress Which books are on your coffee table right now? #fridayreads #bookworm    
    
    
    Ryan Gosling vs. Puppies http://ryangoslingvspuppy.tumblr.com/  #PureComedy    
    
    
    Girls night! Best sushi I've had in NY (@ Shi w/ @loveaddictnyc) [pic]: http://4sq.com/tzHMJX     
    
    
    #NewYork #nyc #city #lights #view @mall0ryry  http://instagr.am/p/Sxr89/     
    
    
    Now that I've spent 3 hours cleaning my apartment (and it looks fab)... I'm off to brunch! Favorite part of the week :) #LoveSundays    
    
    
    I kind of NEED this fab Bvlgari Serpenti watch. DIE. http://us.bulgari.com/productDetail.jsp?prod=SPP35BGDG.2T … #fashion    
    
    
    I love my city. and this vid.  #nyc http://vimeo.com/31159101     
    
    
    you're so right! smells delish :) RT @WordlyAdvice @allie_hunt11 some chicken soup will make you feel better!!!    
    
    
    Yellow diamonds in the lighttttt    
    
    
    Possibly the cutest street in the city http://instagr.am/p/UBxiR/     
    
    
    Too presh for words http://instagr.am/p/UCjoY/     
    
    
    Today was just one of those "wow, do I really live in new york city?!" kind of days #ILoveNY    
    
    
    Pretty sure "We Found Love" has been on repeat for the last 48 hours. #obsessed    
    
    
    @nycprgirls I'm loving this! http://nycprgirls.com/how-to-look-pr-pretty/ … #PR101    
    
    
    Sweet home Indiana, here I come! RT @a_brook7 Three days until the arrival of @allie_hunt11!!!!! Bring me somethin' good!!!!!    
    
    
    I just unlocked the Level 3 "Fresh Brew" badge on @foursquare! Sweet! http://4sq.com/vVY1y2     
    
    
    Purchased. #obsessed http://www.toms.com/movember-grey-black-women-s-classics?icid=us-home-092011_49 …    
    
    
    I have a love/hate relationship with the 7 train... This morning I'm leaning more towards hate. #Slow    
    
    
    @catierix I'm so excited its cray. #SweetHomeIndiana    
    
    
    I just unlocked the Level 2 "Baker's Dozen" badge on @foursquare! In it to win it! http://4sq.com/urnvPF     
    
    
    En route to the airport. Step on it, cabbie, I'm going home!!    
    
    
    Empire in the rear view mirror, makes me kinda sad to leave the city... But can't wait to see my fam and friends!    
    
    
    The smell of bacon and the sound of wind chimes... Love being home.    
    
    
    Missed these dudes... And looks like they missed me too. :) http://twitpic.com/7gcgg2     
    
    
    @Justin_M_Ochoa we were all so proud last night. This morning? Not so much. #ouch    
    
    
    Miss you already! RT @carlyszabo The peanut butter to my jelly is a mere 30 minutes away from me @allie_hunt11 :)    
    
    
    Thank you @jwalaszek for allowing me to be front row for Coldplay's performance of Baba O'Riley. Highlight of my night.    
    
    
    Besties duh @carlyszabo http://instagr.am/p/VA_v1/     
    
    
    @snakealexiou I'll for sure see you! :)    
    
    
    Surprise gift from my parents! They're the best. http://twitpic.com/7hkyl5     
    
    
    http://Steaknshake.com  omg http://twitpic.com/7hprsr     
    
    
    SO excited!! RT @LoveAddictNYC: Lucky me next week: Rockefeller Center tree lighting w @mallory_ryan, @allie_hunt11 & @allthelooks    
    
    
    Back in the Apple http://instagr.am/p/V9pLX/     
    
    
    A bus seriously almost ran over my cab. God, I've missed New York.    
    
    
    Brunch + Bloomingdale's + mani pedi= perf ny sunday with my city biff @mallory_ryan    
    
    
    oh my gah. This is kind of amazing. http://www.gagasworkshop.com/#welcome  @BarneysNY @ladygaga    
    
    
    I'm at The Tree At Rockefeller Center w/ @loveaddictnyc [pic]: http://4sq.com/tnAZVA     
    
    
    Cee-Lo at Rockefeller Christmas Tree Lighting with @latigar @JLinney http://instagr.am/p/WsUZq/     
    
    
    All I want for Christmas is you... to buy me a Cartier Heart Bracelet.  http://instagr.am/p/XAdaC/     
    
    
    New York slice(s) + Sangria and movies with @mallory_ryan #Friday    
    
    
    Coney Island in December? I don't see why the hell not. #PhotoShoot http://twitpic.com/7ntvr2     
    
    
    I'm at Forty Carrots (1000 3rd Ave, inside Bloomingdale's, New York) http://4sq.com/sRK2lk     
    
    
    Best #Froyo of all time. #Bloomingdales #Foodporn http://instagr.am/p/XtVbS/     
    
    
    Just saw @TaylorArmstrong at @Bloomingdales on Lex... Holy lip injections!    
    
    
    Even in December, iced coffee >    
    
    
    @KaceyWeaver I want it ALL... her bags are on sale at Bloomingdale's right now and I'm struggling to hold back    
    
    
    Salted Caramel Mocha from @Starbucks ... Try it. It's holiday heaven.    
    
    
    SantaCon 2011 #NYC http://instagr.am/p/YfFZH/     
    
    
    Why is this my last YouTube search?@mallory_ryan #SmartGuy #90s http://twitpic.com/7rq1oe     
    
    
    I'm at Brooklyn Bridge (Brooklyn Bridge, New York City) w/ 13 others [pic]: http://4sq.com/sUX5Xy     
    
    
    Monday Night Mass at Saint Patrick's #Cathedral http://instagr.am/p/YzreB/     
    
    
    just spent my weekly budget on cough drops, meds, lysol disinfectant and hand sanitizer. 6 days into the worst cold I've ever had. #ThanksNY    
    
    
    I'm at Stitch Bar & Lounge (247 W 37th St, btw 7th and 8th Ave, New York) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/sb36mK     
    
    
    I just watched "The Help" for the first time and bawled my little eyes out    
    
    
    Watching the Swedish House Mafia concert live streaming online from MSG...SO wish I was there!    
    
    
    @ashleysantucci ah LOVE it!    
    
    
    I'm at Traffic (986 2nd Ave., btwn 52nd & 53rd St., New York) w/ 12 others http://4sq.com/sSDsW3     
    
    
    At IU bar with @mall0ryry  http://instagr.am/p/ZuWf7/     
    
    
    It's a beautiful day in the city :) COLD as hell... but still beautiful. #NYC    
    
    
    @ErinDorney had SO much fun with you girls! Even though I was 2 hours late! See you after the holidays! xoxo    
    
    
    Just landed an amazing job today :) Feeling so blessed    
    
    
    @bridgettryan thanks!! happy holidays love :)     
    
    
    52 degrees and sunny in #NYC today- perfect for a Central Park afternoon with my camera    
    
    
    Going home :) (@ New York Penn Station w/ 22 others) http://4sq.com/uJ1W0T     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "JetSetter" badge on @foursquare! Bon Voyage! http://4sq.com/tHgNP0     
    
    
    Mom's delish cooking and cocktails + dad and brother playing guitar + best dogs ever = Home.  #happyholidays    
    
    
    #Truth RT @a_brook7: Seriously don't know what I would do without @allie_hunt11 in my life. Best friends for 13 yrs and still going strong!    
    
    
    @emmy_leee @alexlorenz23 ah this is cray cray! Xoxo    
    
    
    @AlexLorenz23 thanks love! At Tractenberg & Co :)    
    
    
    Currently drinking an amaretto sour and bloody Mary at the same time. #MerryChristmas pic.twitter.com/SSusQNU    
    
    
    Back in the early morning hustle and bustle of the City... Love it :)    
    
    
    A Note From The Universe http://instagr.am/p/cXHQm/     
    
    
    55 and sunny in January? In NY? Yea, I'll take it.    
    
    
    I was actually supposed to live in the 60s.    
    
    
    Studio54 themed party tonight... shit is about to get so real it's unreal.    
    
    
    #Studio54 #70s party  http://instagr.am/p/fdBbD/     
    
    
    Arm Party. @manrepeller http://instagr.am/p/gyM8v/     
    
    
    I'm at Museum of the Moving Image (3601 35th Ave., at 36th St., Astoria) w/ 11 others http://4sq.com/Aiyny8     
    
    
    Shit Nobody says http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f-x8t0JOnVw … #hilarious    
    
    
    Loving Sarah Burton's "Victorian Gypsy" look #fashion #wwd http://instagr.am/p/iuGp0/     
    
    
    Good Morning and #TGIF , New York.  http://instagr.am/p/i16kc/     
    
    
    I'm at The Australian (20 W 38th St, 5th Av, New York) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/xlQvWn     
    
    
    ah I do that too! "see ya in 24 hours gang" “@AlexLorenz23: Just did 8 minute abs thanks to the suggestion of @SamanthaBankey NICE JOB GANG”    
    
    
    Royal Blue Skinnies, duh. http://instagr.am/p/kDLZd/     
    
    
    Good morning, #hipster . #brooklyn http://instagr.am/p/kf13B/     
    
    
    Shit Fashion Girls Say Part 2.... Almost better than the first. #iDie http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ojnnSZcQEpc …    
    
    
    @a_brook7 haha... sadly, it really is. ps- get to nyc betch!    
    
    
    http://SweetShirt.com  http://instagr.am/p/mCAtp/     
    
    
    Being chic, and brunching...duh RT @LoveAddictNYC - @erindorney, @allie_hunt11 @mallory_ryan, @allthelooks -WHAT are we doing this weekend?    
    
    
    Xoxo RT @NYFashionisette #FF Lovely Dolls @voguehoney @vogueandcoffee @kmg_89 @lollieshopping http://tl.gd/fll58r     
    
    
    And I'm so I'm so i'm so proud of you, too! RT @ncminitelove Love catching up with my little new yorker @allie_hunt11. So proud of her!    
    
    
    Go Green. #PhotoADay #Words #Recycle http://instagr.am/p/nJ7Dz/     
    
    
    These #hands aren't moving fast enough. #FebPhotoADay #day2 #hands http://instagr.am/p/nimW7/     
    
    
    I just ousted Kathleen M. as the mayor of Dave's Bagels & Grill on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/byYZFO     
    
    
    Holy Madonna. #WorldPeace #HotBetch    
    
    
    "It was a great day to arrive in New York. No one expected me. Everything awaited me" #books #read #bookworm http://instagr.am/p/G6lTpruR2B/     
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Herbivore” badge on @foursquare! Vegan cupcakes for everyone! http://4sq.com/wA74gR     
    
    
    #LuckyGirl http://instagr.am/p/HAtOnKORy_/     
    
    
    Can't wait for a night on the town with @allthelooks tomorrow night! This week has been INSANE.    
    
    
    The most delicious Sunday treat, Mocha, from little French cafe in my neighborhood  http://instagr.am/p/HMheY4uR7y/     
    
    
    Like, I'm really diggin' neon right now. #Fashion    
    
    
    Live jazz with the kittens @mall0ryry and @allthelooksh http://instagr.am/p/HP6qhnuR9h/     
    
    
    Beyond excited to be working with a great friend and mentor @Bconnpsu ... But my liver? Not so excited.    
    
    
    @isavenok SO loving the new site! Look at you    
    
    
    Always! RT @catierix @allie_hunt11, I cannot thank you enough for supporting me. #lovesyou.    
    
    
    I'm at Union Square Greenmarket (1 Union Square West, btwn 15th & 17th St., New York) w/ 11 others http://4sq.com/AzSrEw     
    
    
    I have a conference call with http://BroBible.com  at noon. My job rocks today. #PR #BroOut    
    
    
    @_fabuloscity Ah, my account director was in Vegas last week-- so jeal! Sounds like things are going well, love :) xoxo    
    
    
    @_fabuloscity yes, let's! Sooner rather than later :)    
    
    
    #FF My new blog obsesh: @FBombedGirls --  Cocktails + Clothes = a fashionable blackout(fit)    
    
    
    I am BEYOND excite RT @jtaybaybay : So excited that I get to visit @allie_hunt11 this week!    
    
    
    I'm at Bowery Ballroom for O.A.R. (New York, NY) w/ 26 others [pic]: http://4sq.com/A1LFNA     
    
    
    Sunshine, smoothies and record stores... Perfect Sunday afternoon.    
    
    
    I'm at Rebel Rebel Records (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/z66OjM     
    
    
    Annnnd this is what is missing in my #Monday (or everyday) morning routine... RT @FBombedGirls Good morning sunshine! http://bit.ly/yYs5Vt     
    
    
    I'm at Starbucks - OBP (NY) http://4sq.com/GCYFHh     
    
    
    @k_white87 step up your twitter game, homie. #Its2012 #JustSayin    
    
    
    Amazing #PR tips for planning events-- from the fab @nycprgirls http://bit.ly/GDXTFr  ... Thanks, ladies!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Excited to be posted up in a suite at MSG with @k_white87 for #Knicks vs Pistons tonight!  #NYC    
    
    
    It would be great if all the clothes on #pinterest would magically appear in my closet.    
    
    
    Christian Kogstad of @HouseSpirits came in and gave us a tasting! I kinda, sorta love my job. #Spirits #PR http://instagr.am/p/IsLqdNOR3x/     
    
    
    Pshh, It's not like I have the new J Biebs song on repeat or anything.... @Bconnpsu http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RoFXbt2tfbU …    
    
    
    And I, 39 #RiseAndGrind . RT @Justin_M_Ochoa Woke up to 24 emails...    
    
    
    checkkkuh checkkkuh check it >> http://about.me/AllieHunt     
    
    
    Ah thanks!! Hope to see you in The Apple soon!  RT @AlexLorenz23  @allie_hunt11 love your page! supa cute.    
    
    
    #FirstWorldProblems @FirstWorldLife RT @blakeleighking Pinterest is running EXTRA slow today.    
    
    
    Interesting: How to Make Images Stand Out on #Pinterest http://on.mash.to/GRjzmL  via @mashable    
    
    
    I drink like it's my job...because it is. #Spirits #Wine #PR    
    
    
    It really was amazing RT @EverythingNYC Tonight's beautiful sunset in #NYC. http://twitpic.com/92ls81  via @isardasorensen    
    
    
    Looking for THE BEST #healthy and delicious recipes? You should def be following @driscollsberry #foodie    
    
    
    Italian dinner downtown with the fab @allthelooks - and that means wine. Lots and lots of wine. #tgif #nyc    
    
    
    Bellissimo! (@ 'inoteca e liquori w/ 7 others) http://4sq.com/HqFFr1     
    
    
    Sometimes I find myself wondering if @AntDavis is going to shave that #unibrow after they win the championship. #JustSaying    
    
    
    This is amazing -- and inspiring! Kids in a village wanted to play soccer, but there was no place to practice... http://www.omg-facts.com/view/Facts/50137 …    
    
    
    #Truth RT @WomenInPR1 Being in any field of #PR is often a high-stress job, and one which requires a thick skin.    
    
    
    I was Britney Spears' publicist in my dream last night. Wait... dream or nightmare? Could go both ways... Let's decode this @sarahnrussell    
    
    
    I could pretend I don't enjoy the fact that "Crazy For This Girl"- Evan and Jaron -just came up on Pandora....but truth is, I do.    
    
    
    In honor of #MeatlessMonday ... I'm thinking this looks delish for din: http://www.howsweeteats.com/2010/04/crab-avocado-quesadillas/ … @howsweetblog    
    
    
    @dkny Happy Twitter-Anniversary! In my opinion, you OWN the twitter-sphere. Thanks for encouraging :)    
    
    
    NOM. Is it too early for ice cream?  RT @NewYorkology Today is @benandjerrys Free Cone Day http://bit.ly/HMYvwJ  (via @MurphGuide)    
    
    
    Making it. http://www.howsweeteats.com/2011/08/crispy-honey-lime-tilapia/ … #Delish #Foodie #TastyTuesday    
    
    
    Can't even deal. SO presh. RT @FBombedGirls How cute are these guys??? http://yfrog.com/hskuhcij     
    
    
    So inspiring @vafashiongirl http://faithfullyfabulous.tumblr.com/post/20421749031/a-year-with-twitter … Featuring @dkny @OscarPRGirl @Bergdorfs    
    
    
    @Kj_babyyy RT @InternsNtheCity Send bio & pic to nycinternshow@gmail.com if ur interested in being on reality show about #NYC summer interns    
    
    
    Ryan Gosling was perfect...and then he was more perfect: http://todayentertainment.today.msnbc.msn.com/_news/2012/04/04/11017342-ryan-gosling-saves-writers-life …    
    
    
    I mean, you just can't go wrong with a bowl of @driscollsberry for a mid-day #sweet #healthy #organic snack http://twitpic.com/95lzdb     
    
    
        
    
    
    Why thank ya :) Loving yours, too! RT @KJPrry @allie_hunt11 your About Me page is so cute! #goodwork    
    
    
    Call me, maybe. #GuiltyPleasure , maybe    
    
    
    Recycle. Lights off. Vegetarian. RT @WholeFoods Q4: And at home… what steps do you take to have a green house? #WFMdish    
    
    
    @WholeFoods My roommate @mallory_ryan and I recycle and help support each other in our new vegetarian experience (as of January)! #WFMdish    
    
    
    Dear 7 Train, get your shit together. And, thanks to you, my boss is probably going to tell me the same thing this morning. #late #tgif    
    
    
    Roomie @mallory_ryan and I making Easter brunch for our favs! We're so domesticated -- thank you, Pinterest!    
    
    
    Anytime, love! Enjoy :) RT @winobee: My girl @allie_hunt11 from thebaddishgroup hooked me up w/ yummy cocktails you should be sipping on...    
    
    
    @FBombedGirls That all looks so nom-tastic (aside from the seaweed)! And I mean, Tuesday cals don't count....right?    
    
    
    Public transportation teaches.... http://nycprgirls.com/random-life-lessons-from-the-nyc-subway-system/ … -- thanks @nycprgirls :) #PR #NYC    
    
    
    What? EVERY day is a day for iced coffee, Em! RT @emmy_leee Definitely not a day for that iced coffee.    
    
    
    Ob.sessed. RT @usweekly: Miley Cyrus is mad for neon! http://bit.ly/HvikVO  What do you think of her bright yellow leather jacket?    
    
    
    S is for #Starbucks Iced #coffee addict http://instagr.am/p/JSmye1OR_H/     
    
    
    Love this! Yum RT @sfgirlbybay which one? http://instagr.am/p/JVP60QEbMX/     
    
    
    Eeek, sorry about this @ericmmacdonald -Dave's is my jam >> I just ousted @ericmmacdonald as mayor of Dave's Bagels & Grill on @foursquare!    
    
    
    Do not, I repeat do NOT, sit next to me on the train if you plan to eat your lox bagel loudly and messy. #NYCProblems    
    
    
    Love being early enough to sit in Bryant Park and relax before going into the office. #thelittlethings http://twitpic.com/99866n     
    
    
    Pale With A Pop: http://www.polyvore.com/cgi/set?id=47135252 … #fashion    
    
    
    Getting the day started right with Three Dog Night #MusicMonday http://instagr.am/p/Jes8cjuR0S/     
    
    
    holy adorable-ness RT “@HuffPostStyle: Beyonce & Jay-Z reach new levels of cuteness (PHOTOS) http://huff.to/IRdp2N ”    
    
    
    It's summer in the city today -- 87 degrees and sunny. I may or may not sunbathe in Bryant Park on my lunch break. #HappyMonday    
    
    
    Perfect after work relaxation spot. #CentralPark (@ Central Park Duck Pond) [pic]: http://4sq.com/HO8q6y     
    
    
    "Well I've never been to heaven, but I've been to Oklahoma" - name those lyrics... #musicmonday #classics    
    
    
    Another sunny one in the neighborhood. I'm feeling a mullet dress today... #fashion    
    
    
    Great minds should also drink champagne togetherASAP RT @ErinDorney @allie_hunt11 I'm wearing a mullet blouse today! Great minds think alike    
    
    
    Excited to be at @MTV studios in Times Square for a comedy show filming tonight with @mallory_ryan and @nailthatstyle :) #nyc    
    
    
    Truer than true. RT @womeninpr1: A4: At the end of the day you must live,love + breathe PR!  It becomes your lifestyle + your life. #prcafe    
    
    
    @DriscollsBerry #DriscollsEarthDay chat starts in 20 minutes!    
    
    
    Q4: @DriscollsBerry Spicy Summer Fruit Salad is delish! http://ow.ly/andjM  #DriscollsEarthDay    
    
    
    Mimosas for breakfast in @thebaddishgroup office #ThirstyThursday #champagne #breakfast http://instagr.am/p/JmwA0pOR1W/     
    
    
    F.Stokes #new#music#hiphop#rap#nyc @k_white87 http://instagr.am/p/JoH8IVOR3e/     
    
    
    @FdotStokes putting his charm on: http://instagr.am/p/JoO8wGuR6E/  amazing show! Loving the energy. #swaggy #music #nyc    
    
    
    Perfect mani/pedi + margs + grocery night with the roomie @mallory_ryan #TGIF now bring on the Saturday activities and @ncminitelove arrival    
    
    
    I'm at Bryant Park - The Southwest Porch (New York, NY) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/Jnt2mP     
    
    
    Sometimes a rainy Sunday is just what I need to MAKE myself relax. #nycproblems    
    
    
    I just ousted @araisengirl as the mayor of The Baddish Group on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bbZAsc     
    
    
    @driscollsberry Blueberry Pie in A Jar! #cute#food#pie#berry http://instagr.am/p/J47iiuORyx/     
    
    
    @sendthetrend Great pic! Hope you enjoyed :)    
    
    
    I just unlocked the Level 2 "Herbivore" badge on @foursquare! In it to win it! http://4sq.com/KaFSVF     
    
    
    Rangers game with @k_white87 #bro    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Warhol" badge on @foursquare! Gallerific! http://4sq.com/Jg5nni     
    
    
    Keith Haring exhibit  http://instagr.am/p/KTZKZWOR7d/     
    
    
    Love that there is an #IcedCoffee Twitter Party taking place right now! Iced coffee is my life support. Large, extra skim and 2 splenda. :)    
    
    
    Stop, hey what's that sound? Everybody look what's goin' down. #amendmentone #music#classic# http://instagr.am/p/KcjWcdORzN/     
    
    
    A day that starts with Rebolution is bound to be a good one RT @drew_shafran: @allie_hunt11 really appreciated that Rebolution tip this...    
    
    
    It's finally #thirstythursday - - But now that I think about it, Monday, Tuesday and Wednesday were rather thirsty as well. @mallory_ryan    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Trainspotter" badge on @foursquare for checking in at trains and subway stations! http://4sq.com/ISrdtj     
    
    
    Central Park bike ride and sheep meadow nap sesh on this beautiful #nyc day with @mallory_ryan    
    
    
    Hi everyone! So excited for the convo tonight! #HERchat #driscolls    
    
    
    I empowher my health by going to the gym after work and healthy snacking #Driscolls #herchat    
    
    
    @driscollsberry Yum- Those look SO delish! #HERchat #driscolls    
    
    
    @DriscollsBerry Hmmm, tough one. I'd say a tie between blueberries and strawberries!  #herchat #driscolls    
    
    
    I'm almost certain my cab driver is trying to kill us. I've never experienced a crazier driver.. #Scared #nycgrlproblems    
    
    
    Record sale with @k_white87 #winning (@ Smorgasburg w/ 113 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/MvyV2x     
    
    
    #MusicMonday "Winter Winds" - Mumford & Sons #music    
    
    
    SO real. meh. RT @Justin_M_Ochoa The 2:30 feeling is real.    
    
    
    Made my morning! RT “@HuffPostGreen: Here are some cute baby animals in honor of the UK's National Vegetarian Week http://huff.to/LmATwt ”    
    
    
    Having the best weekend with my mom... Trying to convince her to move to the city!    
    
    
    Kevin White is alright @k_white87 http://instagr.am/p/LL6yijORyM/     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Brooklyn 4 Life" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/L9tbY2     
    
    
    Is it bad that the first thing I think about in the morning is Iced Coffee? Buckets of it. #goodmorning    
    
    
    Female go-getters: http://ow.ly/bfkAv  via @usweekly    
    
    
    Getting ready to experience #Manhattanhenge @katiecat & @NYCphotos pic.twitter.com/q7qO7d7j    
    
    
    #Manhattanhenge gets an A effort @NBCNewYork http://instagr.am/p/LRUDaluR_N/     
    
    
    I'm at Sunnyside Arch (Sunnyside, NY) http://4sq.com/JZMJhI     
    
    
    En route to the Burlington, Vermont jazz festival with @k_white87    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Swimmies" badge on @foursquare for checking in at water spots! Splish splash! http://4sq.com/L4vQ4Q     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Great Outdoors" badge on @foursquare for checking in at outdoor spots! Freedom! http://4sq.com/L4vPOC     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Vinyl" badge on @foursquare for checking in at record stores! 7" heaven! http://4sq.com/LXuwA1     
    
    
    Lake Champlain from The Green Mountain State. #Vermont#scenic#lake http://instagr.am/p/LbDYlkuR7u/     
    
    
    Hi #pr20chat -- Junior acct. exec in NYC-- Excited for the chat tonight!    
    
    
    A1: Social media is the perfect tool for gaining new customers, but also for engaging w/existing customers. It's all about balancing the...    
    
    
    A2: @driscollsberry engages with their current customers on a daily basis- always providing the best info & recipes! #pr20chat    
    
    
    @JGoldsborough social media def. plays a strong role- the brand hosts frequent twitter chats, updates FB with health tips and answers...    
    
    
    @JGoldsborough also using Pinterest for new, healthy recipes that appeal to their current customers as well as new #pr20chat    
    
    
    @jspepper @JGoldsborough Of course, that too! Newsletters are EVERYTHING to loyal customers :) #pr20chat    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jspepper @alsmartina @JGoldsborough I don't think it has to do with entry-level ignoring-- for me, it has to do with how the agency runs...    
    
    
    @NYCGirlinPearls welcome back!! We must get together!    
    
    
    Happy birthday to the talented, inspirational and twittersphere rockstar @dkny !! Xoxo    
    
    
    Bring on the trends! RT @sendthetrend: "One of our favorite days here in the STT office! #Trendsday http://su.pr/3gSU4h ”    
    
    
    Morning relaxation sesh in #bryantpark #nyc #morning http://instagr.am/p/LiG1-iuR3v/     
    
    
    HA! RT @stevegogreen: Call Me Maybe by Carly Rae Jepsen, from #SoundHound - I just Tweeted, this is crazy, here's my handle, so Tweet me...    
    
    
    Is my life about to be changed forever? Page one in Bryant Park. #fiftyshadesofgrey #book pic.twitter.com/GJ9iHeqf    
    
    
    And you're so #traveled- running and #drinking in Italy & shit @MelissaTavss: @allie_hunt11 you're so #laid-back #chill and #intouchwnature”    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "(RED)Rush to Zero" badge on @foursquare, triggering a $1 donation to help fight AIDS. #REDRush http://4sq.com/KPZRsA     
    
    
    Xoxo RT @NYCGirlinPearls: #FF #NYC favorites: @FSUfashiongirl @KJPrry  @jackiebaybe @_fabuloscity @amercogliano @allie_hunt11 ....    
    
    
    Ah so exciting! RT @KJPrry: #NYC bound! So close. (@ Philadelphia International Airport (PHL) w/ 67 others) http://4sq.com/KlNxf6 ”    
    
    
    No filter on this city sunset. #nofilter #city #beautiful #blessed http://instagr.am/p/LofXosuRyh/     
    
    
    A night of boozing, dancing and loving life is ahead of us @katiecat #nyc #party    
    
    
    Yes, I am watching the #bachelorette ...and yes, Arie is still my favorite.    
    
    
    Finally got the energy to get up and go on a morning run-- felt good! Ready to take on another day in this crazy city. #riseandgrind #run    
    
    
    @MelissaTavss #countingcats in Italy > #countingcalories in NYC    
    
    
    Strawberry shortcake snacks in the office! @driscollsberry Happy National Strawberry Shortcake Day!  http://instagr.am/p/L3b6ryuR5j/     
    
    
    Meet u there! RT @gracepotter Headed over to @BestBuy now for another signing! I need a burger & a slap in the face from a handsome man ASAP    
    
    
    I just died and went to rock n roll heaven @gracepotter is perfection and the nocs are dope. #live#music#nyc http://instagr.am/p/L3wgrcuR1D/     
    
    
    So nice to have a night with the girls @LoveAddictNYC @katiecat @mallory_ryan    
    
    
    Boozing & Brooklyn Bridge. Perfect #Friday night. #tgif#nyc  http://instagr.am/p/L6qyTuuR5j/     
    
    
    Happy birthday to my roomie and lovely friend @mallory_ryan !! This pic was taken on the very first day we m http://instagr.am/p/MGF9aCOR9m/     
    
    
    I don't see him enough @jlinney . #love#nyc http://instagr.am/p/MHvYeGOR20/     
    
    
    @bridgettryan I'm proud of you midge! Fun trumps everything. But I have a feeling "fun" is an understatement for #gball :)    
    
    
    WHERE are you? xo RT @sammymalone2112: @allie_hunt11 @bridgettryan I miss you both! Wish I was thereeee #longdistancebesties    
    
    
    I'm SO busy -- but we have to try this time! RT @ncminitelove: Already started packing for new York. Can't wait to the girls @Kj_babyyy...    
    
    
    Governor's Ball! #music#festival#nyc#summer http://instagr.am/p/MOfGBQuR7H/     
    
    
    Governor's Ball music festy was way too amazing. Why did it have to end? #summer    
    
    
    Healthy mexi lunch with @MelissaTavss -- at our desks, of course.    
    
    
    I just want to be Made in the Shade all day. #music#classic#rollingstones#vinyl#art http://instagr.am/p/MVlWPtORzi/     
    
    
    Guys- the liquor brands need to know- is #YOLO cool or annoying?!?! Please - I need 10 responses.    
    
    
    Ok @nancyein - I'm going to be creepy... would love to talk to you about YumSugar post you did on Four Roses cocktail. DM me! :) Thanks!    
    
    
    Amateur Night at The Apollo. With @k_white87 http://instagr.am/p/MZY21eOR5X/     
    
    
    The Jacksons just stepped on stage at The @ApolloTheater !! #nyc #music http://yfrog.us/dyw7nz     
    
    
    chic! RT @kathrynelise: neon + neutral #ootd http://instagr.am/p/Ma0UTyvG61/     
    
    
    At Prospect Park to see @TromboneShorty ... Gotta love @CelebrateBklyn #music #nyc pic.twitter.com/yEZWNyhD    
    
    
    @TromboneShorty is mind blowing at @CelebrateBklyn #music#concert#nyc#brooklyn#trombone http://instagr.am/p/MevEgOOR2R/     
    
    
    "WAIT there are some serious Phil Collins fans out there." @k_white87 #5AM #PBR #qualityconvo    
    
    
    Had to happen. (@ Astoria Park Pool w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/N7eRQO     
    
    
    Hey @CrystlMeatballs ! -- I would love to get in touch with you... could you shoot me a DM? Thanks so much! #StalkerStatus    
    
    
    Waiting for #manhattanhenge in LIC #nyc#photogtaphy http://instagr.am/p/M9bosAuR6y/     
    
    
    Tonight's #Manhattanhenge view from LIC @NYCphotos pic.twitter.com/2Li2IU9u    
    
    
    Snacks on snacks on snacks for @melissatavss bday. #birthday#work#cheese#wine  http://instagr.am/p/M_wstmuR2U/     
    
    
    Outdoor Viewing of Fantastic Mr. Fox #nyc#movie#date#night http://instagr.am/p/NAGGztOR2V/     
    
    
    I just reached Level 4 of the "Mall Rat" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 15 different malls! http://4sq.com/LVYdDU     
    
    
    @k_white87 trying to win me a roasta banana at the Brooklyn Italian carnival. #LikeABoss pic.twitter.com/d1iK6ffA    
    
    
    Bday baby @melissatavss #birthday#girl#saturday#pretty http://instagr.am/p/NFfC9vOR5E/     
    
    
    @Pepsi 's PR campaign in #BryantPark is impressive, I must say.    
    
    
    Pandora shuffle: Grace Potter, Passion Pit,Tim McGraw,The Lumineers, Trombone Shorty, 90s hits. Life's too short not to be eclectic? #music    
    
    
    Smorgasburg nom time with ze boy! #Brooklyn    
    
    
    Sandcastle sculpture contest with a dork (@ Coney Island Beach & Boardwalk w/ 57 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/Mz7L8A     
    
    
    Urgent! @KJPrry we need to have our PR pow-wow this week-- Thursday?    
    
    
    If you're cool and hip, you will go to http://nyc.thedelimagazine.com/  and vote @SwearAndShake for Artist of the Month #Brooklyn #Music    
    
    
    @WholeFoodsNYC 's Matzo-crusted salmon... I NOM-inate this for our upcoming fam din @mallory_ryan #foodie    
    
    
    My grandma celebrated #TequilaTuesday w/a tequlia rose special shake & of course @driscollsberry for garnish. #Cheers pic.twitter.com/aVGnSGCZ    
    
    
    @SwearAndShake -- great show! (@ Arlene's Grocery) http://4sq.com/LMjrHu     
    
    
    Not mad about a little CCR to start the day. #vinyl#music#wednesday http://instagr.am/p/NgQ-UguR2l/     
    
    
    Dirty Dancing outdoor flick in McCarren Park with @mallory_ryan ... Oh and Mike('s hard lemonade) #summer #Brooklyn pic.twitter.com/5vvi9Pwf    
    
    
    Annnnd a round of applause just occurred... For Patrick Swayze. The orig hipster.    
    
    
    Definitely jamming out to @theblackkeys all day -- Beyond excite to see them & @umphreysmcgee at @CatalpaNYC tomorrow! #music #nyc    
    
    
    Oh I'll def be there! RT @MyPetDragon @allie_hunt11 come early to catch our set at 2:15pm on the #JeepStage tomorrow! #music #nyc    
    
    
    No words for Umphrey's McGee. #amazing#music#jam#nyc#catalpa  http://instagr.am/p/NpTlZfOR_F/     
    
    
    I decided I was going to go to bed early... and then Pinterest happened.    
    
    
    Just ran a mile with @mallory_ryan ... Guess I can go ahead and thank Team USA @jordyn_wieber @aly_raisman for the inspiration. #olympics    
    
    
    So yea, I just drank an XL iced coffee in less than 5 minutes. Today is going to be a good one...    
    
    
    Ye Old Boston. #weekend#travel  http://instagr.am/p/N6vLS3uR3E/     
    
    
    I'm at Yankee Stadium for Texas Rangers vs. New York Yankees (Bronx, NY) w/ 369 others [pic]: http://4sq.com/TDdRrK     
    
    
    Great cocktails and convo last night @MelissaTavss @dnclin -- Needs to happen more often!    
    
    
    I'm at Williamsburg Park for Antibalas and Sharon Jones & The Dap-Kings (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 55 others [pic]: http://4sq.com/PmN5nu     
    
    
    Antibalas rocking it out in #brooklyn #music#concert#nyc http://instagr.am/p/OfNfQnOR67/     
    
    
    NYC on a Thursday night. Big Gigantic.  #nyc#city#concert#music http://instagr.am/p/OszIWLuR_J/     
    
    
    @ncminitelove SO ready to see you.    
    
    
    EZoo Boo @k_white87 . #ezoo#electric#music#festival  http://instagr.am/p/PFj0N1OR7u/     
    
    
    What's better for #NYWF than an old-school snapshot of me & fashion rockstar @ajmukamal ? #nyc#fashion#celeb http://instagr.am/p/PSCvb8OR60/     
    
    
    Vermont bound for a weekend of hilling, kayaking and music festival-ing with @k_white87    
    
    
    Kayaking on Lake Champlain. #lake#weekend#sports#nature http://instagr.am/p/Po8VeAuR3_/     
    
    
    Kayaking with @k_white87 on Lake Champlain in Burlington, Vermont. Perfect #Sunday morning! pic.twitter.com/OafK8wxk    
    
    
    Such a pretty Friday in the city! Meeting @NYCphotos @Katiecat for lunch in Bryant Park #TGIF #NYC    
    
    
    Look what I stumbled upon during lunch...The Today Show. #nyc#city#onset#tv#todayshow http://instagr.am/p/QAcD-yuR4Y/     
    
    
    My boyfriend is the silliest... Found this gem in the fridge this AM on top of my lunch #funny#october#hallo http://instagr.am/p/QPfSZAOR84/     
    
    
    So phenomenal working with @Ann_Caruso @GraceHuang @nashellymessina and many more amazing ppl on the #LorealParis #WomenOfWorth video/shoot!    
    
    
    Looks like Milo is siding with Obama... He is a loyal demoCAT #debates #cat http://instagr.am/p/QV7thIuR1E/     
    
    
    So excited for my dad's visit to NY this weekend! Looking for THEE best Little Italy restaurant... suggestions? #nyc #food    
    
    
        
    
    
    I just unlocked the "PEOPLE Hot Spot" badge on @foursquare for checking in to 3 hot spots from People magazine! http://4sq.com/QDQ2OJ     
    
    
    Just some of the magic that @mrbillyb is creating on the @LorealParisUSA set today #makeup #beauty #behindth http://instagr.am/p/Q7lPW3ORw8/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Romney has nothing on us-- we literally have binders full of women on the L'Oreal photo set. @jacmo  pure #c http://instagr.am/p/Q97-VluR1i/     
    
    
    Lobsta Dinna with the Kevster (@ Pearl Oyster Bar w/ 4 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/RLA1GF     
    
    
    I mean...everyone loves @Essie http://ow.ly/eHtxs  #beauty    
    
    
    Thanks to the lovely @rachparcell , I am now obsessed with @shoemint ! Enter this giveaway to win a free pair of shoes! http://ow.ly/eNEar     
    
    
    @Kouchiest thanks for the well wishes! I'm safe and alive :)    
    
    
    Watching Nightmare Before Christmas and eating Chinese food. #HappyHalloween #Sandy    
    
    
    Seeing "Once" with @k_white87 :) (@ Bernard B. Jacobs Theatre) http://4sq.com/QXGWNV     
    
    
    I'm at On-Stage Bar @ Once: A New Musical http://4sq.com/RxpCh4     
    
    
    Baby bottle poppin' for my birthday! (@ The Dog And Duck w/ 4 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/RwZcPG     
    
    
    Help @EverythingNYC and all NYCers-- What's a good brunch spot on the UES? Think fun/delish/laid back #nyc #brunch    
    
    
    Sunday stroll in Central Park  #nyc#sunday#park#cute#couple http://instagr.am/p/RnKbIqORxb/     
    
    
    @Brunchinee thanks for the suggestion! We went, we boozed, we nommed and we loved!!    
    
    
    @JohnnyLavoy in action on set at @LorealParisUSA haircare video shoot #beauty #behindthescenes http://instagr.am/p/RxuFE0uRzK/     
    
    
    Behind The Scenes @LorealParisUSA #beauty #photoshoot #hair http://instagr.am/p/R0Yh-0OR1k/     
    
    
    Sushi & wine Saturday, always a good time-with @mallory_ryan @kristingwhiz @Katiecat @lalev @LoveAddictNYC @katewinick pic.twitter.com/ZQL7C1q1    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Vinyl" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different record stores! http://4sq.com/QyZxDd     
    
    
    A Ray BANDS pov in Wash Square. #music #nyc #band #art #park #jazz #artsy #fall http://instagr.am/p/R5hooNORwL/     
    
    
    Making balsamic glazed salmon and twice baked potatoes for Sunday night dinner. I wish I had the time to cook like this more often! #sunday    
    
    
    Coldplay + JayZ is completely happenening for New Years.  @bridgettryan @mallory_ryan @k_white87 @KristinGWhiz #wordup    
    
    
    "I feel like murdering someone and I also want soft pretzels!!" - Jess and her feelings of PMS @NewGirlonFOX @ZooeyDeschanel #comedy    
    
    
    @k_white87 is 25 & alive. Happy birthday, peanut! http://instagr.am/p/SDWOIpuR-V/     
    
    
    @k_white87 so mad we missed The Who last night! I was living vicariously through @NashellyMessina who was there rocking out #rocknroll    
    
    
    So my office cafe was definitely serving thanksgiving dinner for lunch today. Like we need a second turkey-day feast? #carbs    
    
    
    Can't wait for my first trip to the new Barclays Center tonight to see the @BrooklynNets beat the Boston Celtics! #NYC    
    
    
    Make a difference and vote for one of these incredible women in the 2012 @LOrealParisUSA Women of Worth program! http://ow.ly/fkin7  #WOW12    
    
    
    Rooting for our @BrooklynNets -- and also frantically trying to spot Jay-Z, Beyonce and Solange [pic]: http://4sq.com/PXuZdj     
    
    
    Beer & basketball is best in Brooklyn! Goooo @BrooklynNets #HelloBrooklyn pic.twitter.com/FXCMrjak    
    
    
    Get excited #beauty buffs, @LOrealParisUSA is launching a seriously hot new Advanced Haircare line! http://ow.ly/flto8  @womensweardaily    
    
    
    @_deepinder_ It's pretty major. I'm seeing IU play there next week, DMB in December & Coldplay/Jay-Z for new years! Indy bros need to vist    
    
    
    @TylerJacobP I'm seeing @davematthewsbnd at the new Barclays Center in Brooklyn on Dec 21.Tix sold out in seconds because dave is THE man.    
    
    
    2013 is your year @Justin_M_Ochoa @Official_LMD #fashion http://www.wwd.com/eye/fashion/spring-2013-web-trend-say-the-word-6489394?module=hp-hero-topstories …    
    
    
    Tonight? I'll def be strolling to Madison Ave to see the brilliant @BarneysNY x #Disney #ElectricHoliday window display http://ow.ly/flzJ0     
    
    
    @gracepotter I just found out I'll be seeing you in DC next month! Hope you will have a "seriously dirty setlist" for that too :) #rocknroll    
    
    
    @rachparcell always has the best giveaways! http://ow.ly/fm3NO  You can't go wrong with a classic personalized monogram necklace! #fashion    
    
    
    Any recos for a nice/chill bar in the Flatiron/Chelsea? #nyc #bars @EverythingNYC    
    
    
    Congratulations to this year’s #WOW12! Help your favorite win an additional $25k grant. @LOrealParisUSA http://bit.ly/O47DB     
    
    
    En route to Maryland for the weekend with @k_white87 - There is life beyond NYC! I think...    
    
    
    Baltimore is great, but we look better in New York City. #baltimore#city#harbor#federalhill http://instagr.am/p/SLzlIiORxs/     
    
    
    #socialmedia RT “@mashable: SkinnyScoop Brings the Conversation Into Pinterest-Style Recommendations - http://on.mash.to/UaaMBp ”    
    
    
    You need this @k_white87 RT “@JonathanCheban: This modern day man cave is something every man needs to have- 
http://elitedaily.com/elite/2012/modern-man-cave/ …”    
    
    
    Not a shabby view from today's meeting at Hearst tower. @LorealParisUSA #scenic #nyc http://instagr.am/p/SOhyyDOR-2/     
    
    
    Indiana vs. Georgetown at Barclays. Hoohoohoohoosiers!! #college #basketball http://instagr.am/p/SRsAjAOR_v/     
    
    
    Maybe the fact that I've taken public transportation for almost 2 years justifies the fact that I just ran over a curb & popped the tire.    
    
    
    Decorated this bad boy last night. Finally getting in the #holiday spirit @mallory_ryan @k_white87 http://instagr.am/p/SnvzxGuR6L/     
    
    
    Can't even deal with @BritneySpears fierceness in "Scream & Shout" @mrbillyb is that your makeup magic? #obsessed http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WDZxnawFph4 …    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Great Outdoors" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different outdoor spots! http://4sq.com/TzmaE6     
    
    
    Top o' the mornin' #nyc #view #monday http://instagr.am/p/SxtZ0euR_a/     
    
    
    Cheers to what matter, thanks @KristinGWhiz #happy#life#wiwt#cheers http://instagr.am/p/S7KvF0OR4L/     
    
    
    Amazing @LorealParisUSA Women of Worth #WOW2012 http://instagr.am/p/S7LJM4OR4b/     
    
    
    I just ousted @notsincetimmy as the mayor of Blue Chips on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/4vvYJX     
    
    
    Can't wait, dear! RT @sarahnrussell :One week til I get to see the lovely @alliehunt_!    
    
    
    En route to DC from NYC to see @gracepotter jam out hard with the nocs tonight! #rocknroll    
    
    
    So, @gracepotter , you retweeted me so I'm assuming we're besties now & you'll play Medicine and Timekeeper again tonight? #rocknroll    
    
    
    No words to describe how electric your guys' energy was last night gracepotter #rocknroll #musi @ 9:30 Club http://instagr.am/p/TBXpdpORw5/     
    
    
    My boss is cooler than your boss. @nashellymessina  @ Hearst Tower http://instagr.am/p/TEfMwLuR0c/     
    
    
    Celebrating one year and an upcoming Christmas with the best. #love #happy #chris @ Rolf's German Restaurant http://instagr.am/p/TFNZtnOR1n/     
    
    
    Tis' the season. @cas_ramos #holiday#gifts#hermes  @ L'Oreal USA HQ http://instagr.am/p/TMIVl-OR2k/     
    
    
    @lorealparisusa Holiday Party #becauseyouareworthit #holiday #party @ 3 West Club http://instagr.am/p/TOpQkPuRxq/     
    
    
    Bowling, Brooklyn style. #brooklyn#holiday#party @brooklynbowl @bookingagency @k_white87 @ Brooklyn Bowl http://instagr.am/p/TZjJKiORx4/     
    
    
    In love with my @cwonderstore Christmas gift from the best boss in town, @nashellymessina # @ L'Oreal USA HQ http://instagr.am/p/TbNV79uR0a/     
    
    
    Subway conductor's announcement when we arrive at Queensboro Plaza: "this is Queensboro Plazer" #newyork #accent    
    
    
    I'm at Barclays Center for Dave Matthews Band and The Lumineers (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 242 others http://4sq.com/12FfTMz     
    
    
    About to shred some major pow pow with @k_white87 and family #letsgo    
    
    
    With Kevin & fam (@ Song Mountain Resort) http://4sq.com/10bcNBb     
    
    
    My dreams came true-- a white Christmas with @k_white87 #snow #christmas @ City of Syracuse http://instagr.am/p/TqsJvSuR6D/     
    
    
    Homebrew kit, Babel on vinyl, tix to Mumford & Sons, 101 Rock Records, music note necklace. We swear we're n http://instagr.am/p/Ttqt_3uRx0/     
    
    
    So like can we do haps hour asap @bridgettryan ? #nyc#driiink    
    
    
    Reunited and it feels so good {the booze help too} bridgettryan @sammymalone2112  @ Vapiano http://instagr.am/p/T2C0uyuRyo/     
    
    
    Dear fantasy #football gods: Please let @k_white87 win his league's #superbowl tonight. Big bucks {and a lobsta' dinna'} are on the line.    
    
    
    Bathtub in the kitchen. Tres New York. @k_white87 #newyork#vintage#home http://instagr.am/p/T4iQ4qOR4J/     
    
    
    Getting pampered with @mallory_ryan - we must end 2012 looking HAWT #duh    
    
    
    I'll be tuning in and rocking out RT“ @gracepotter: Last minute late night! I'll be performing with The Roots tomorrow night on @JimmyFallon    
    
    
    "We're from New York so we're like naturally interesting" @lenadunham @KristinGWhiz  @ East Village http://instagr.am/p/UIOoiWOR9P/     
    
    
    Los Pantalones. #ootd  @ L'Oreal USA HQ http://instagr.am/p/UPPJAquR78/     
    
    
    On set today, showing off this hot new product @lorealparisusa #ombre#hair#beauty#fashion  @ Location 05 http://instagr.am/p/URIpUhuRw0/     
    
    
    In case one of the models doesn't show, we have jacmo #photoshoot#model @ Location 05 http://instagr.am/p/URJYvaORxP/     
    
    
    No way, really? @ClaireMBiggs I must admit, it IS a great job and I love it :) We really need to chat and catch up soon. XO    
    
    
    Oh hey Friday, what took you so long? Ready to rock out at @brooklynbowl tonight @theresapoborsky @k_white87 #TGIF    
    
    
    I just witnessed the best @FdotStokes show ever. @adamtdeen told me so.. #music    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Schmear" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different bagel shops! http://4sq.com/V5958F     
    
    
    Leg air guitar. Typical. @k_white87 #goofy #kidsforlife #love http://instagr.am/p/UbyVIluR5b/     
    
    
    @Katiecat I'm watching @CarrieDiariesCW too-- We should have watched together! Next week...    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'll be in Murray Hill tonight @cas_ramos -- meet up?! Ok good, see you then. xo #nycgirls    
    
    
    Listening to Crave You (Adventure Remix) by Flight Facilities  http://grooveshark.com/s/Crave+You+Adventure+Club+Dubstep+Remix/4fisdz?src=5 … via @grooveshark    
    
    
    I sincerely hate the smell of cocoa butter. Simply repulsive.    
    
    
    Winter wedding with my love  @k_white87 #love  @ Arrowhead Lodge http://instagr.am/p/UroN8LuR8f/     
    
    
    Camo skinnies + jutton up. Fashion inspired by @nashellymessina #ootd#wiwt#fashion http://instagr.am/p/UwV210uR30/     
    
    
    Watching the show k_white booked. Anthony David is legit #music#nyc#broadway @ B.B. King Blues Club & Grill http://instagr.am/p/UxJ1FfuR4E/     
    
    
    Naturally IU stomped all over Purdue. 😊#iubb #0ismyhero    
    
    
    Check out the new & improved http://LorealParis.com  @lorealparisusa #beauty  @ L'Oreal USA HQ http://instagr.am/p/VKIkqpuR8x/     
    
    
    Yep! All 3 days. Why?? #festi “@_deepinder_: @alliehunt_ are you going to the governors ball by chance?”    
    
    
    Indiana vs. Michigan. Hoosier pow wow in NYC. Go IU!! 🏀#iubb #ncaa http://instagr.am/p/VQF4YeORyO/     
    
    
    Eff. Yes. Hoosiers. #1 #iubb #ncaa    
    
    
    No lights? Ain't nobody got time fo' that. Let's go! #ihatefootball    
    
    
    @KristinGWhiz omgah you are my favorite person    
    
    
    You would have done the same! #GPN “@gracepotter: Queen B just knocked the power out in 1/2 the stadium. She was that good:)”    
    
    
    How 'bout that Puppy Bowl?! #superbowl2013 #lightsout    
    
    
    If you're cool, you follow @fabulatina -- 2013's top #fashion blog!  http://instagram.com/p/VZjdPMuR-8/     
    
    
    @nashellymessina & ddinour rocking the karaoke like champs #fabulous#party#superstar#pretty#love @ Radio… http://instagr.am/p/Vc429OOR55/     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Fashion Week 2013" badge for checking in at events and boutiques. Everyone is wearing emerald... http://4sq.com/11uCmiO     
    
    
    Seeing some major looks at the @ProjectRunway #NYFW show. Oxblood. Leather. Sheer. B&W. pic.twitter.com/SlOQ6Zph    
    
    
    Having my moment with @iambenlyons #nyfw#fashion#love @ Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week http://instagr.am/p/VeqiI3OR-R/     
    
    
    Spotted: @michaelkors heidiklum ninagarcia @zac_posen looking fierce at the #NYFW projectrunway show. http://instagr.am/p/Vep7BUOR9h/     
    
    
    Way to go Hoosiers! #SighOfRelief #IUBB    
    
    
    @MumfordAndSons you guys put on one mind-blowing show at the @barclayscenter last night!! I still can't stop dancing. #music    
    
    
    Hoo hoo hoo hoosiers! Kevin (@ Traffic w/ 5 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/11MXdhf     
    
    
    Oladipo for the 3-po 🏀ps: nice haircut, Hulls. # iubb    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Bonnaroo why is your ticket page not working for me??!    
    
    
    It really is though.  RT @Katiecat "It's so hard being a hipster. Sometimes I just want to listen to Top 40" - @alliehunt_    
    
    
    Tickets bought -- @Bonnaroo here we come! #summer13 @k_white87    
    
    
    Croque Madame, très délicieux. #french#brunch#nyc @ Le Moulin A Cafe http://instagr.am/p/WZ2XMMuRx3/     
    
    
    Sunday run along the East River {one block from our new apartment!} #pretty @ East River Running Path http://instagr.am/p/Waee1HOR_R/     
    
    
    Game time noms: Australian feta, pâté, cornichons, baguette. All @Bedfordcheese http://instagr.am/p/WsWJUwOR4V/     
    
    
    @sbell021 guess who won the game buddy? #notyou #youoff    
    
    
    I am crying tears of pure joy for this major #iubb win #hoosiernation    
    
    
    My skin is craving the #Clarisonic Mia 2 and I just entered to win one! #fabuclarisonic @nashellymessina… http://instagr.am/p/WuZeGRuRyb/     
    
    
    Elnett errrryday. @lorealparisusa #beauty#hair#pretty @ L'Oreal USA HQ http://instagr.am/p/W17tAjOR5V/     
    
    
    Nothing would make me happier 🍸RT @_fabuloscity: "@alliehunt_ UES cocktails next week pleasee ?”    
    
    
    Ready to rock out at @007bookingagent 's first show in #NYC tonight! If you want to listen to some good #music, stop by Parkside Lounge at 8    
    
    
    @Kayleigh_H @hendricksalex @bridgettryan HOLY yes! Bagelsmith is all you ever really need in life.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Don't tell my boss, but I contimplated calling in sick today so I could watch the #IUBB vs. Illinois game.    
    
    
    Dinner across from Meryl Strepp.... This just happened. #celeb pic.twitter.com/1UqBp88gop    
    
    
    Obsessing over the new @lorealparisusa Nail Lingerie. I'm wearing "Elite Chic" in silver.… http://instagr.am/p/XAFZafOR8Z/     
    
    
    Si señorita!! “@_fabuloscity: Looking oh-so forward to a little UES mexican happy hour with @alliehunt_ tonight #fiestafiesta”    
    
    
    The ultimate sunshine essentials, recommended by the lovely @_fabuloscity -can't wait to try them all! @HamptonSun http://instagram.com/p/XX8FFzOR-f/     
    
    
    I die. RT @Bergdorfs BG + @essie : inspired by 5F hues. hand-picked by the BG team. get it exclusively here: http://bit.ly/WWMDA8     
    
    
        
    
    
    REALLY good!! Thanks for the reco, love RT @a_brook7 @alliehunt_ listen to Jake Bugg. He's 17 and the new Bob Dylan. You won't be sorryyyyy    
    
    
    Request approved. Let's make this happen asap please :) @brisaperstein @_fabuloscity    
    
    
    Looking forward to @GlamourTopTen tonight! glamourmag @LorealParisUSA #dreamjob @ L'Oreal USA HQ http://instagram.com/p/XpVRWHOR0l/     
    
    
    A cuppa joe {hipster joe, that is} @GregorysCoffee #wakeup @ L'Oreal USA HQ http://instagram.com/p/XsCpiFOR2V/     
    
    
    I wonder what @007bookingagent would say if he knew I've been listening to Top 40 all day? #oops    
    
    
    Finally reunited with my sassy bestie @KristinGWhiz #nyc #girlsnight    
    
    
    with @katiecat, Kristin, Mallory, Kevin (@ Smorgasburg Williamsburg - @bkflea w/ 243 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/Z09UBW     
    
    
    Listening to Zac Brown Band all day... pretty sure no one else in my office even knows who they are.   #musicmonday    
    
    
    That terrified moment when your cab driver starts reading the @nytimes while he's driving....    
    
    
    As a matter of fact, we do. ddinour glamourmag @lorealparisusa #GlamourHangout @ L'Oreal USA HQ http://instagram.com/p/X7Ww3DOR1v/     
    
    
    On my way! RT @CEW_NY: Connect with beauty insiders from L’Oreal, Estée Lauder and LVMH at our Young Executives event on 4/10 #CEWEvents    
    
    
    Ah! @007bookingagent  sent me this today! Ja'die RT @_fabuloscity: I'm covering my future child in puppies. http://www.buzzfeed.com/mjs538/the-most-important-pictures-of-a-baby-covered-in-french-bull?s=mobile …”    
    
    
    Successful & fun day working on set for glamourmag x @lorealparisusa #GoogleHangout @ Condé Nast Building http://instagram.com/p/YA-6DvuR0E/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Loving the spring & summer makeup looks @BGDMakeupArtist is creating today on set of @LOrealParisUSA + @ENews shoot pic.twitter.com/N8RyFxfeXb    
    
    
    Getting the royal hair & makeup treatment on set today. Who do I think I am? @ The London NYC http://instagram.com/p/Yf9L-ZuR8f/     
    
    
    Who has listened to Kopecky Family Band? @007bookingagent introduced me this week and I can't stop listening. #music    
    
    
    Lovely margarita meet & greet night with @KJPuncorked #thirstythursday    
    
    
    Working off-site today #tgif pic.twitter.com/sKrXBRHZQI    
    
    
    And I'm loving the liner! #xmasinapril “@KJPuncorked: Loving the coral lipstick @alliehunt_. Kisses!”    
    
    
    I'm at Earwax Records (218 Bedford Avenue, N 5th St, Brooklyn) http://4sq.com/15Q7sCA     
    
    
    Some of the looks from today's lorealparisusa #GetNoticed shoot. #fashion @ Demarchelier Studio http://instagram.com/p/YsrKSNuR5H/     
    
    
    Ditto. We need to do drinks, like, yesterday. RT @_fabuloscity "Dear @alliehunt_, I miss your face"    
    
    
    That moment when you drop your handbag and 8+ lipsticks spill out. #beautyjunkie    
    
    
    Funny, I was thinking the same thing.@vogueandcoffee    
    
    
    It's that time of year again peeps: Nominate a brave & inspirational woman to be a @LOrealParisUSA  WomanOfWorth  http://bit.ly/O47DB     
    
    
    A walk in @jcrew  creative director,Jenna Lyons {300 pairs of} shoes. @harpersbazaarus http://bit.ly/ZHmRhm     
    
    
    "I love the snooze button—it's really a drug." - Jenna Lyons @jcrew #heardthat    
    
    
    Mid-week #mani featuring @essie "Saturday Disco Fever" & a touch of "Where's My Chauffeur?" pic.twitter.com/lccAOas9yf    
    
    
    Just realized that today marks 2 years since I moved from little ol' Indiana to New York City. #bigdreams    
    
    
    Can’t wait to wrap myself in this #theodoracallum must-have scarf! #fabugiveaway @fabulatina    
    
    
    Listening to the new @sheandhim album & it just makes me want to be on a blanket in the park on a summer day.And then I look outside. #rain    
    
    
    #Gatsby tickets bought. Look like it's going to be a classic Saturday night "dinner & a movie" date night for me and @007bookingagent    
    
    
    Just thought you should know, @gracepotter  . Oh and "peanut" is my boyfriend... #justsaying http://instagram.com/p/ZV_9douR2-/#     
    
    
    I'm at @MercuryLoungeNy for Kopecky Family Band (New York, NY) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/17C7sGU     
    
    
    Amazing show last night @KopeckyFamily ! I'm still dancing. Hope you guys will be back in NYC soon!  #goodmusic    
    
    
    Not surprised that @LOrealParisUSA Colour Riche Nail won "Best New Product" at #CEWAwards !    
    
    
    Walked through a film set of "Anchorman The Legend Continues" on my way to work this morning. #NYC http://instagram.com/p/Zk26SZOR2w/     
    
    
    Behind the scenes with @lorealparisusa #work #pr (@ Parlay Studios) [pic]: http://4sq.com/10sYsws     
    
    
    My @WarbyParker 'home try-on' sunnies just arrived. How in the world am I supposed to choose JUST ONE?! This is difficult.    
    
    
    Good :) RT @WarbyParkerHelp '@alliehunt_ Decisions are the worst. In the event you can't pick just one, we completely support you picking 2!    
    
    
    Summer Friday at the office obviously calls for an early afternoon cocktail hour with @fabulatina & @ddinour    
    
    
    It's a great evening for peanuts & crackerjacks. @007bookingagent #yankees @ Yankee Stadium http://instagram.com/p/aJ5mmKuRz5/     
    
    
    Can't believe I'm enjoying a cold brew in NYC with my long lost friend @JWalaszek right now. #reunited    
    
    
    Currently jamming to Alanis' "Ironic" and swapping 'wedding day' for 'GovBall day' #itslikeraaaaaaaaeeeeain    
    
    
    I'm at Governors Ball Music Festival (New York, NY) w/ 467 others http://4sq.com/14qlCrM     
    
    
    Dinner with @LoveAddictNYC & then a bit of Bachelorette guilty pleasure with @KJPuncorked  = perfect evening plans on a rainy, dull Monday    
    
    
    @a_brook7 that is absolutely epic. please tell me that my father did not bring "fratty light" to the party..? Also,will I see you next week?    
    
    
    Perfection. RT @HuffPostStyle 'Lauren Conrad's new bangs take over the cover of @marieclaire http://huff.to/19m9VGd  '    
    
    
    I'm at Nashville International Airport (BNA) (Nashville, TN) w/ 17 others http://4sq.com/18zGLnE     
    
    
        
    
    
    Sir Paul McCartney. You guys... No words. #music#beatles @ Bonnaroo Music & Arts Festival http://instagram.com/p/alka1NuRzB/     
    
    
    Summer adventures are crucial. #bonnaroo http://instagram.com/p/ar6rauORyH/     
    
    
    manicplanet rocking the house at SpikeHill in Williamsburg #brooklyn @ Spike Hill http://instagram.com/p/bAkoRUOR1L/     
    
    
    A positive step forward & defining moment for America #marriageequality #DOMA    
    
    
    Jamming to @JavelinJamz at celebratebrooklyn #music @ Celebrate Brooklyn!/Prospect Park Bandshell http://instagram.com/p/bKc0kPOR1W/     
    
    
    Photo: Sassy little sneaks these are.  http://tmblr.co/ZgHQuxofTJh1     
    
    
    That awkward moment when you're painting your nails at your desk & your boss walks by...& doesn't care because you work at @LOrealParisUSA    
    
    
    Spirited? Indeed. Socially savvy? You betcha'. SO stoked to discuss further? Absolutely. @BFGCom #ContentManagerMaterial    
    
    
    Sometimes I feel life would go much smoother if I weren't the 'snooze-hitting' type... ya know? #5moreminutes    
    
    
    I'm at The Penrose (New York, NY) w/ 7 others http://4sq.com/136pZUf     
    
    
    Director of digital for @LOrealParisUSA , miss @aptluxe , and I being digital darlings #digitaltownhall pic.twitter.com/b5c0uVV0CL    
    
    
    "We're often taught that everything's good in moderation,but we're also pretty sure that street style is the exception" @ManRepeller #Truth    
    
    
    Relaxation (@ Greenwich, CT w/ 3 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/17c7Bh8     
    
    
    The only thing that would make Monday not suck is a Cronut    
    
    
    I didn't think it was possible to love @BettyMWhite more than I already did, but... http://huff.to/10YboxK  via @Huffington #insidelook    
    
    
        
    
    
    @KristinGWhiz @mallory_ryan your feelings were right... I love it. #RockOn    
    
    
    Sometimes I get flashbacks of @PaulMcCartney 's 3.5 hour performance at @Bonnaroo , but only like once or five times a day    
    
    
    amazing @manicplanetband performance at The #BitterEnd last night. @ The Bitter End http://instagram.com/p/b6RYFiuR1u/     
    
    
    L'Oreal USA #DigitalTownhall (@ New York Times Center - @nytimes w/ 15 others) http://4sq.com/152dugU     
    
    
    ladies who lunch @nashellymessina ddinour #tgif#nyc @ Fig & Olive http://instagram.com/p/b9Yn3NuRxw/     
    
    
    "I'm like closer in age to an infant than to you"  @hendricksalex @bridgettryan @mg_conway @enbrock #brunchdialog    
    
    
    If you happen to wear red lipstick while wearing a red dress/top, I will assume you do not have a mirror. Same goes for kitten heels.    
    
    
    Much needed catch up lunch with @johndtrybus (@ Marlin Bar at Tommy Bahama) http://4sq.com/18xGtut     
    
    
        
    
    
    Can it be next month already? Love. RT @ELLEmagazine Kate Spade makes summer Keds cuter than ever: http://on.elle.com/1aHhaqt  @katespadeny    
    
    
    Samsies, no joke. RT @mg_conway When "calm meditation" is your most played pandora radio, it may be time to chill outski.    
    
    
    mañana? RT @_fabuloscity : Dear @alliehunt_ , it's apparently National Tequila Day. Happy hour at our favorite locale?    
    
    
    Is it odd that when @Refinery29 asked if this cuticle nail art was "rad or bad?" I totally went with RAD? I mean...  http://www.refinery29.com/nail-art-fingers-trend?utm_source=facebook.com&utm_medium=post …    
    
    
    Apparently there's a switch on my office's AC that reads "Arctic Blast"    
    
    
    No words for the kick ass performance from @mymorningjacket at #Americanarama in Hoboken #summerofmusic pic.twitter.com/7AFGpTceQO    
    
    
    @007bookingagent just referred to me as a "rapscallion" #truelove    
    
    
    chix n wafflez (at @SweetChickBk w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/13lzj89     
    
    
        
    
    
    My lorealparisusa PR dream team gave me the most appropriate going-away gift ever: Kate Spade "Crazy… http://instagram.com/p/cZjdZquR9C/     
    
    
    To work or to @BuzzFeed , that is the question. #procrastination    
    
    
    “If you think you are too small to make a difference, try sleeping with a mosquito.”  - @DalaiLama    
    
    
    Woah. RT @eric_wheeler 'The history of social networks in 6 seconds http://bit.ly/15ftQp9  '    
    
    
    It's Thursday, and I'm thirsty. Time for wine with the ladies (obvi we're the ladies) @bridgettryan @hendricksalex  cc: @girlsHBO    
    
    
        
    
    
    The simple pleasure that is seeing a yellow taxi light come on. #cabbingit    
    
    
    Loved ending Thursday night @rockwoodNYC listening to some major jams with @annaschilawski @007bookingagent #musictime    
    
    
    XO right back at ya! RT “@_fabuloscity: Congrats to my girl @alliehunt_ on her fabulous new venture! XO”    
    
    
    "Yes, you are basically required by law to post brunch pictures on Instagram" says @Refinery29 #ItsTrue    
    
    
    I've come to the conclusion that listening to @Tromboneshorty at work is great for your soul. #MusicTherapy    
    
    
    So I'm officially obsessed with @1iota ... and would probably be even more obsessed if I got tix to #VMAs    
    
    
    It should probably be Friday already.    
    
    
    I'm at Beekman Beer Garden for George Clinton & Parliament Funkadelic and George Clinton Parliament Funkadelic [pic]: http://4sq.com/15eQDzF     
    
    
    I'll be seeing you  for my 4th time at Grand Point North in Vermont!  RT @Tromboneshorty: @alliehunt_ thank u very much. I Appreciate ya    
    
    
    Oops! Don't blame me, blame @Keds RT @melissdelong: So it's @alliehunt_'s fault that I'm listening to @taylorswift13 right now #Spotifyprobs    
    
    
    XO! Next time, brunch. “@annaschilawski: @KariFriedlander @alliehunt_ Lovely night dining and wining with you ladies! xo”    
    
    
    I'm at Thayers Beach (Colchester, VT) w/ 2 others [pic]: http://4sq.com/15Murgy     
    
    
    At least it's already Tuesday.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Possibly taking a spontaneous trip to Boston this weekend for @Boston_Calling festi with @007bookingagent #YesPlease    
    
    
    I'm at Little Branch (New York, NY) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/19rppG8     
    
    
    I'm at Fig & Olive - @figadnolivenyc (New York, NY) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/1b2PiAg     
    
    
    I am {wisdom} teething. Ibuprofen is candy right now. #ouch    
    
    
    Couldn't be a more beautiful day for the festi @gracepotter! Would love to hear you sing "Low Road" #GPNSetlist #GPNTravelstories    
    
    
    The energy of @gracepotter & the Nocs is on a whole other level. #GPNTravelStory @GrandPointNorth pic.twitter.com/7yHkePISa2    
    
    
    The new Chipotle ad is heartbreaking/beautiful/confusing all at the same time. Thoughts #marketing pros? http://bit.ly/ChipotleAd  via @Gawker    
    
    
    So I'm thinking a brunch needs to happen sooner rather than later @annaschilawski @KariFriedlander. #Holler.    
    
    
    Love that @LuckyMagazine featured the most bad-ass #rockstar fashionista, @gracepotter -- so fierce. http://bit.ly/GraceRocks     
    
    
    Best dressed at the @PrimetimeEmmys:  @SofiaVergara. Best, in general: @itsWillyFerrell.    
    
    
    Saw a dope @portugaltheman set, thanks to my girl @alexlorenz #tgif (at @AceHotel New York w/ 15 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/16xvHY5     
    
    
    The fact that @APieceOfToast is doing a @katespadeny Beau Bag giveaway just made my day a lot better {& more fashionable, obvi} #wishmeluck    
    
    
    @Drew_Shafran what an inconvenient #firstworldproblem. You've shown me the data, and I can now fully forgive you.    
    
    
    Drinks with a view at @WytheHotel followed by @funkyMETERS dance fest at @brooklynbowl - perfect #saturday night. @007bookingagent    
    
    
    Loving this fierce @LOrealParisUSA smoky eye how-to video http://bit.ly/LorealParisSmokey … -  Miss you @MrbillyB! XO    
    
    
    Kim, they're waiting for us. #organic RT @KJPuncorked: "@alliehunt_ Kevin and Jason say hurry.”    
    
    
    Slightly {incredibly} jealous that my boyfriend has a @CMJ badge and I don't. So many amazing shows this year! #CMJ2013    
    
    
    My favorite @CMJ band so far? Definitely @DEandTGL #cmj2013    
    
    
    I'm at Hill Country Barbecue Market - @hillcountryny for Daniel Ellsworth and the Great Lakes (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/1gW7DzU     
    
    
        
    
    
    Watching @deertickmusic rock out at @WebsterHall #nyc pic.twitter.com/DYJ6mpF7cp    
    
    
    Bawk bawk RT @bridgettryan: Chicken Pot Pie twins hollaaaaa🐓🐓🐓🐓@alliehunt_    
    
    
    @annaschilawski lady! I lost your number but I'm in the L'Oreal building for meetings until 5ish- would Iove to see you! Txt me :)    
    
    
    Pretty sure I just had the best meal of my life at @buttermilkbklyn #foodie    
    
    
    Heading to Billyburg to see @Rubblebucket tonight & contemplating going to @SantosAnneBK for din. Is 3 times in 1 month excessive? #itsmyfav    
    
    
    I'm thinking @gracepotter should sing "Oh Darling" by The Beatles...you'd rock it, Grace.    
    
    
    Back in the city means bagels.    
    
    
    Hannah is a drunk Cinderella w both shoes gone. RT @glamourmag The #GIRLS dressed as their Disney-princess alter-egos http://glmr.me/1k6odMk     
    
    
        
    
    
    Oh the things I would do... RT @AlizaLicht: I would kill for some sun.    
    
    
    I'm at The Supply House w/ @kjpuncorked http://4sq.com/1gUh2Hn     
    
    
    "I can't preach hate & warfare when I'm a disciple of peace"-WonderWoman #1000whistle @gracepotter @FallingWhistles http://instagram.com/p/gZItpyuRzj/     
    
    
    My #style icon (& friend, & previous boss) @fabulatina partnered w @Target to show us how to rock winter accessories! http://bit.ly/18U70kf     
    
    
    I've come to the conclusion that listening to Christmas music in the morning makes a remarkable impact on your day.    
    
    
    Nice to be home with mom, even nicer to be home with her homemade biscuits and gravy @007bookingagent #midwestchristmas    
    
    
    @a_brook7 yup. RT @007bookingagent: If you think you're a hipster, you're a yuppie #hipster#yuppie#millennials    
    
    
    I'm at @BrooklynBowl for The Felice Brothers w/ @a_brook7 http://4sq.com/1cRPzqU     
    
    
    I just beat @007bookingagent in Madden...2014 is going to be a lucky one apparently.    
    
    
    