Thanks @WARRIOR_FTBL for designing my fantasy football kit......... pic.twitter.com/ncbJS6baWa    
    
    
    @siancjones is everyone foreign aswell.........    
    
    
    @iLikeGirlsDaily Jada Stevens    
    
    
    @KopMatt well Suarez wont will he................    
    
    
    @KopMatt come on mate hes on a BAN!!!!!    
    
    
    @KopMatt if he stays how is he going too start against stoke regardless???? you cant include him in the options at all!    
    
    
    @KopMatt yes i know he might not be a liverpool player, but if he is he is unavailable for selection so why not just leave his name out?    
    
    
    @KopMatt what you are doing is speculating an impossible situation and assuming we will sign a striker    
    
    
    @KopMatt that one isnt coming up in this convo lol    
    
    
    @KopMatt im reading the convo not your profile    
    
    
    @AnfieldAkiba @RealOviedoWFC arigatoooooo    
    
    
    @AnfieldAkiba @RealOviedoWFC just emailed, thanks    
    
    
    @KopMatt if Sturridge is fit he will be in prob, I reckon Aspas will start on the bench, maybe Sterling and Downing/Borini as wide men    
    
    
    @AnfieldAkiba yeah had too do it, maybe one day thay will win the CL :D    
    
    
    @MickGraham187 @CoachingFamily 2 touch, keep ball, dont give them time too get close, they will run themselves into the ground in the 1st 45    
    
    
    @lfcindex spanish press saying hes going Spurs next week    
    
    
    @Brodinho id sell, he is well overrated imo    
    
    
    @PaulBigpaulie I dont think FSG really want too spend! Big signings should be made early on depth added later once you have what you need    
    
    
    @WARRIOR_FTBL @LFC awful kit    
    
    
    Lovely Coutinho! #tooeasy    
    
    
    @NairMitesh @LiverpoolWays @espn its not ESPNs camera man it will be a thai camera man and editor    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca the UN is a cold war relic they will never solve anything    
    
    
    Great effort from Terasil!    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca lol, either way when Syria is "fixed" another North African country will go into chaos! Tunisia next    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca cant wait for us too have one! This country is more backwards than any other, capitolism is all about growth and growth is finite    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca while Assad is alive/in Syria they will live under it! If we arm the rebels it will be far worse! Just assasinate him    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca all UK is a bigger grain harvest and banking! We all still get taken for mugs by the Gov! UK will selfdestruct eventually    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca theres people at food banks in the UK, that shows how poorly run this nation is    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca america is the reason for most problems, they monopolise the world with thier 400m tonne grain harvest and their oil companies    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca good thing with Russia and china is that they are vast and if you want you can bugger off and live off the land! UK is tiny lol    
    
    
    people need to stop blaming ESPN for the camermen, they are almost certainly Thai along with the director!    
    
    
    @Bloodzeed you not doing the F1 anymore?    
    
    
    OH look @ESPNUK have just proved me right! As i have said the cameramen are THAI they arent ESPNs!    
    
    
    Borini and Allen are clear examples of the fact that Brendan shouldnt sign players he has worked with at Swansea    
    
    
    friendly off F1 on! ill watch the rest later    
    
    
    @Delveyboy your channel crashed my sopcast at the 1st corner and now it just crashes straight away if i reload the stream    
    
    
    @Delveyboy sweet mate    
    
    
    Tony Evans reckons it will take £55m too get Luis! GOOD!    
    
    
    I cant believe Borini dived in the friendly! he is so poor, so overrated, looks out of his depth just like Allen    
    
    
    Christian Benitez has died at 27???? Unbelievable! #RIP    
    
    
    is this Benitez death true? already seen conflicting stories!?    
    
    
    some sources say car crash others say appendicitis complications!? Whats going on? #Benitez #RIP    
    
    
    this Reina loan is looking a shocker from LFC, its all about money, FSG looking worse by the day!    
    
    
    @no1confused the problem is that they loaned Reina behind his back and signed a replacement based on assumptions that Barca want him    
    
    
    @no1confused had they not rushed out and signed Mignolet they wouldnt need too loan Reina and he may have been willing to negotiate contract    
    
    
    @no1confused form was sloppy and we were still 5th lowest conceded in the league, cant believe Brendan got rid based on form    
    
    
    @no1confused why was he not put up for sale then? cut losses style?    
    
    
    As if Juve would take Borini for Matri! Haha #dreaming    
    
    
    7m is way too low for Skrtek! Ok he wasnt great last season but player of season 1 before! Dont believe the Papa rumours!    
    
    
    @beni_henney i bet the majority of this offer is in instalments too    
    
    
    Skrtel on loan??? Have a word, what is the club up too, hes not a 21 year old!    
    
    
    whats this new "if you cant sell 'em, loan 'em" policy?? #LFC    
    
    
    Fair play if Real Madrid really are going to donate £85m too the Spurs Chimpanzee fund, we need too do more for endangered animals #Bale    
    
    
    @beni_henney Real always find a way too fork out millions    
    
    
    How much does Downing earn, hes got too be next out.... #superscrimpers #FSG    
    
    
    im sure some people will find a way to defend FSG for this money saving policy,    
    
    
    FSG say they are not selling but it damn sure looks like they are trying too balance the books and make the finances look good....    
    
    
    @7Tune just looks like an Astra VXR thats been squashed by an R8...........    
    
    
    i reckon our next 2 signings will be quite obscure under 24 year olds that cost under £7.5m.......... #LFC    
    
    
    HAHAAHAHA RAMOS DID LOOK LIKE BEAVIS NOW HE LOOKS LIKE BUTTHEAD HAHAHAHAHAH!    
    
    
    Oh look ive just seen a Konoplyanka too LFC link..... as i said obscure and under 24!    
    
    
    @timbolton1 waaaaaaaaaaaaaahhheyyyy    
    
    
    just imagine no CB comes in and Skrtel goes.... Agger, Kolo, Wisdom, Coates (he will probably be gone too)......    
    
    
    Yarmolenko now.... next we will be linked with Olegzander Chaepwazgyes    
    
    
    @greaney_michael @bruisedarcade we are nowhere near as small a club as Rangers, we actually have an international fan base.....    
    
    
    so according too LFC "Half-caste" is offensive??? have a word!    
    
    
    all MPs should live in Council Houses... we pay tax for them too have a nice gaff in a nice place so they take the piss and tax more!    
    
    
    @StupidFootball HAHAAA    
    
    
    @beni_henney obscure Steuea Bucharest player    
    
    
    @beni_henney no idea if he is any good, i missed most of the romanian league last season :| ... 6 foot, Centre Back, 23, was a Benfica youth    
    
    
    @niceguylfc joke mate! correct terminology? i always tick "other" on those "equality" forms, im not "mixed" anything im not fucking paint...    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca the press twists everything too suit their own agenda, that is what the press is, a manipulation tool    
    
    
    @timbolton1 WHAT??? "MAN UP" is banned? Im half tempted too walk into Anfield and shout all the words on the list..    
    
    
    John Barnes appears too be as deluded as the fans that think we can sign a Luis replacement with no european football and low wages....    
    
    
    @Pepsi2353 its french there will always be something wrong with it... lol    
    
    
    love too hear who this world class striker Barnes has got lined up...........    
    
    
    @lee_parnell @PaddyTaylor_ please dont tell me you are talking about Noahs Arc....    
    
    
    surely this Sterling loan rumour isnt true!    
    
    
    "Sterling has looked great in pre-season"......"Loan him we need to save money on wages"........"great idea"...... #LFCconvos    
    
    
    WHY DONT WE JUST PLAY STERLING AND SELL DOWNING???    
    
    
    @Corballyred loan too West Ham    
    
    
    i know what will make us consistent.... get rid of all the mature players and replace them with as many young players as possible.....#LFC    
    
    
    free till 13.00 @TonyBarretTimes on fans transfer influence http://blogs.thetimes.co.uk/section/the-game/104424/transfers-dont-get-caught-up-in-the-blame-game/?shareToken=8391b795f7f9fc527680ab8bf1e04c21 …    
    
    
    @SJview problem is that he has been repeatedly banned through his career and he will probably get banned again at some point    
    
    
    @beni_henney what u think about Caulker going? Is there a buy back deal?    
    
    
    Why cant they hurry up and imbed @Instagram into @twitter so I dont have to open a link to see the pic!!!    
    
    
    OMG does Ayew really want too join us? would definitely have him    
    
    
    whats happened at Doncaster??    
    
    
    oh some cock from 1D has joined Doncaster.... this is worse than when Wimbledon signed that guy from So Solid....    
    
    
    so SSN says Schalke have recieved no bids for Papa, no surprises there, i have always been confident its just another twitter signing..    
    
    
    Brendan has really covered his arse with this "money to spend on getting quality in, but if it's (quality) not available I won't waste it"    
    
    
    how many people have actually seen this guy from 1D play?? Id go with Sergio Pizzorno or that guy from JLS, both decent on #Socceraid......    
    
    
    theres on 1 DRS!!! Drag Reduction System! #F1 #AshesBoreOff    
    
    
    Roy Keane needs too come out of retirement NOW! #Doncaster #CareerEnder    
    
    
    @AdamDo_DaDay @SkySportsNews its his wife hahaha    
    
    
    @Green_Scouser i think he is shit, hope we dont go near him    
    
    
    £20m for Diego Costa?.................    
    
    
    The english media are going too love Diego Costa........................    
    
    
    Join my league http://fantasy.premierleague.com/my-leagues/207418/join/?autojoin-code=582083-207418 …    
    
    
    @BassTunedToRed @LFCTS should show games too! Hes played loads hardly scores    
    
    
    @BassTunedToRed @LFCTS no an assist isnt a goal... 31 appearances (2055 mins playing time) 10 goals last season = 205.5 mins per goal    
    
    
    @BassTunedToRed @LFCTS he was actually far better at Vallecano on loan    
    
    
    People seem too think if Suarez puts a transfer request in we will sell him too Arsenal    
    
    
    Selling Suarez too Arsenal would just put us even further away from CL than selling to Real as Arsenal are the 4th place team!    
    
    
    @no1confused I think 2 or 3 signings at least are needed! Not sure on Melaguero as a LB apparently he is more of a winger!    
    
    
    @no1confused cant see us finishing above 6th without Luis, still dont think we will get 4th with him! Need some shrewd deals with no euro    
    
    
    @no1confused strange we havent signed him! Clearly the logical move! Think Enrique would have a tough time aswell! Would improve him too    
    
    
    @BecciBoopLFC hopefully WHU will take him! He doesnt fit, the new signings just make him look more out of place    
    
    
    #TheSupportersClub    
    
    
    @JackSear its only 2 weeks away, whens he back in full training?    
    
    
    @JackSear yeah but when games are "winnable" thats when half the team doesnt show up and we draw or lose 1-0!    
    
    
    @okSuse that is an awful recommendation lol    
    
    
    @LFCFansCorner as if he would get a train...    
    
    
    @LFCamiArias2 has surprised me, hopefully he can continue it in the prem! A lot tougher    
    
    
    @stanic007 im watching, nothing at all has happened yet    
    
    
    Diego Costa has had about 2 touches, this game is nowhere near interesting enough too continue watching..........    
    
    
    Doctor Who? #BoreOff    
    
    
    more rumours Skrtels going, i still dont think Papa is going too be signed either, hes going too have too sign someone!    
    
    
    are they having that crazy 3 team match in Italy again this season?    
    
    
    Media's favourite word...........source! Which is basically, im going too quote you but not give you any credit or my story any credibility    
    
    
    The Echo says Suarez DID wave too the fans, now we are going too have too say he was waving bye instead of hes going cause he didnt wave....    
    
    
    @LFCNewsRumours1 @ConnorwilsonLFC Hes not smiling as much as you....hes going..... #TwitterLogic    
    
    
    @FitzgeraldNO5 @stanic007 we have blatantly been rejected by a few players    
    
    
    not too sure about Reina on Suarez saga! Hes been offloaded and he isnt happy so he is sticking his oar in!    
    
    
    @CoreyLH that pic was posted about 3 hours ago, it means absolutely nothing    
    
    
    @TrueKopites96 i dont see how Sturridge is going too start against Stoke if he is only going too play in the friendly against Celtic    
    
    
    @JoeScouse_LFC im literally on it now taking Sturridge out, hes not going too get any game time till Celtic, i wouldnt start him at Stoke    
    
    
    @CoreyLH im not but some tobys have been going on about it for hours, surprised you havent already seen it    
    
    
    @JoeScouse_LFC i can see Sturridge being injured on and off all season, never seems too be fit for more than a month    
    
    
    @CoreyLH people going on like he wouldnt do that much shopping if he was going.....like he cant afford too throw £100 worth of food away....    
    
    
    @AnfieldMatt WOWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW    
    
    
    how do people dig up these tweets from 2 years ago about footballers that have turned out shit    
    
    
    @LiverpoolFF @FootyHumour ive seen that tweet from a few others aswell!    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca thats more than weird... lol    
    
    
    i think we can get at least £7-8m for Downing, he was a lot better last season than in his first, total square peg at @LFC though    
    
    
    @RobVaughanYNWA far too uch of a traditional english winger, almost obsolete at top level nowadays, like Navas too City makes no sense    
    
    
    @lfcmaestro23 even if he is willing, i cant see anyone wanting to pay him more than 1/3 of what he is on now, that will cause probs    
    
    
    We should do a Downing and Assaidi double sale event! Get them both for £8m.........    
    
    
    @JoeyBurns87 Bo Selecta..........    
    
    
    Surely we should have said Downing is available for sale at the end of last season when his decent 2nd half was fresh in peoples minds    
    
    
    i think its well a low fee for Downing, but realistically it will probably be hard too sell him, Stoke might have him.....    
    
    
    ive downloaded and listened too so much of Marty on @WHYY im now listening too shows from 2009....    
    
    
    These "breaking (insert stupid transfer here)" tweets are already boring......    
    
    
    Id give NUFC 8-10m + Downing for Ben Arfa!    
    
    
    How can Suarez take LFC too court if he hasnt even handed in a transfer request? Judge would surely throw it out    
    
    
    @Corballyred you would have said that about Messi when he joined Barca, always pull hamstring, changed training now rarely injured..    
    
    
    @Corballyred i think recurring muscle injuries can be dealt with, with a higher quality of physio and training, something we have over NUFC    
    
    
    @Corballyred they would never let a frenchman leave the revolution anyway lol    
    
    
    @Zizouology people seem too forget the UK is a major hub too european nations? Loads of indirect flights go thru Heather    
    
    
    @dom_campbell he needs to learn when too pass, he gives the ball away far too often! When he plays shit its really bad!    
    
    
    Suarez needs too stop being immature and hand in a transfer request! Interviews just looks desperate! Hasnt got a leg too stand on!    
    
    
    @emmamcdonnellll @CiaraGissane what a shout! "They are so chocolaty that they turn the milk.........white!!" lol    
    
    
    @LFC @LFCNorwegian what a shed!!!    
    
    
    I wonder what Suarez is doing right now..... probably sulking    
    
    
    @stanic007 he cant possibly go too court until he has handed in a transfer request, no way would his lawyer advice these interviews either    
    
    
    @Sennesation yeah if only it was him that was trying to engineer a move lol    
    
    
    credit @Adam_Holland_ where i got my idea for my name    
    
    
    @FitzgeraldNO5 well said, Torres left with far more dignity than Suarez will, at least it was relatively low key when Torres jumped    
    
    
    @BazLFC19 @Robbie9Fowler no way    
    
    
    id definitely leave Suarez in the reserves over selling him too Arsenal #NoBrainer    
    
    
    @aaaprilLFC we will struggle too sign them is the real problem    
    
    
    AHAAAAAA Spearing at RB HAHAHHAHA    
    
    
    BT Sport, Sky Sports and ESPN..... yeah because im going too pay for 3 channels so i cant watch football............NOT #stream    
    
    
    acestream is twaff though... ive got disgustingly fast Virgin internet and it still lags, sopcast fine as usual, think ill watch in spanish    
    
    
    sopcast time, acestream still manages too lag even with ridiculous Virgin internet, cant bare it    
    
    
    Coates is nowhere near as bad as people make out, dont know what people expect from a young CB that plays 12 games a season....    
    
    
    Valerengas goalkeeper playing with a smile! got too love that!    
    
    
    Loving this Valerenga keeper!    
    
    
    @LFCFansCorner this is the only 25 mins ive ever seen him play and i love him lol    
    
    
    @KopMatt 37,000 fans in Norway is a bloody good turnout!    
    
    
    THIS FUCKING KEEPER IS EPIC!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    albertooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo    
    
    
    FUCK YOU SUAREZ!    
    
    
    Alberto has come too life, he looked really lethargic in the 1st friendly!    
    
    
    went too get my dinner out the over now its 1-1.............................................    
    
    
    You can literally see the relief on Aspas face when he scored that!    
    
    
    @KopMatt i think its 27k, the commentator said 37 but the stadium record is 35k apparently    
    
    
    @KaneD101 decent but thier goalkeeper has had a stormer it could be 4 or 5-1 if it wasnt for him in goal!    
    
    
    ill reserve my judgement on Allen for when he plays in the prem!    
    
    
    id rather we had a game or two against bigger european sides too, just playing these sort of game lulls players into false sence of ability    
    
    
    @CoreyLH lol whaaaat haha! im good!    
    
    
    Ive just realised who Valerengas keeper is..... STIFFLER #AmericanPie    
    
    
    cant stand Owens commentary, clinging onto his career mentioning himself and the scum all the time!    
    
    
    @AzzurriLFC lol the whole game ive been going whos this guy ive seen him before    
    
    
    i truly dont believe Borini will ever score more than 10 goals in all competitions for LFC in a season, just doesnt impress me!    
    
    
    @LFCFansCorner @Robish13 AHAA is that Papa    
    
    
    @LFCFansCorner what??? thats not what it said earlier, it said it was a kid and he said "sell him, hes like a vampire he bites people"    
    
    
    all i hear about Borini is "hes got great movement"... what great movement too nowehere? if his movement was that good he would get goals!    
    
    
    i love you Barca but JOG ON #Agger    
    
    
    @NewsTweetsLFC @Anfield_Road96 bided?? #english    
    
    
    @LFC_KopArt actually a transfer could earn them more money thru signing on fee and possible sale %    
    
    
    @KopMatt europa is better than nothing and they are clearly in a better position than we are    
    
    
    Im not sure how I will react if Suarez somehow ends up still at LFC    
    
    
    @Anton_button someone said his wife is heavily pregnant so he was with her    
    
    
    lol has Suarez just tried a U-turn???    
    
    
    any links too this Marca piece?    
    
    
    I just dont think i have any support left for Suarez... i cant fathom how i will react if he does play for us this season    
    
    
    Suarez will still blatantly try too engineer a move again in January, and he will keep trying until he gets the move he actually wants    
    
    
    just waiting for @John_W_Henry too tweet "what is Luis smoking over there"................    
    
    
    Has Suarez not read The Boy Who Cried Wolf........    
    
    
    Suarez has literally read BR's comments post-Valerenga and thought "SHITTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT"    
    
    
    Suarez needs too kneel in from of a full Kop and make one heck of an apology if he is ever to relinquish the slightest bit of respect    
    
    
    i said too my mate Luis doesnt want too join AFC he just will have too settle for it if he wants CL that bad, would appear he doesnt now....    
    
    
    @henney946 @DarrenOzW12 yeah hes tricky runs at people but couldnt get a look in over Downing.... Hardly got too see him Rodgers didnt like    
    
    
    @henney946 @DarrenOzW12 has looked ok preseason! Similar too Ait Fana and Belhanda not as good as Belhanda though    
    
    
    @henney946 @DarrenOzW12 yeah hopefully he stays with QPR, cant see him playing for us he barely got a look in after a few Europa Legue games    
    
    
    @henney946 @DarrenOzW12 apparently he has told Dutch media he hasnt heard anything about QPR move and wants too join Feyenoord    
    
    
    @LFCTransferNRS yes! Id rather start him than Sturridge who is going too be will behind on fitness    
    
    
    @PeeGeeJayEm now Fergie is gone all the Mancs average players will show! He got shit players playing good!    
    
    
    Offer Borini in a Muriel deal is what id be doing, we will be waiting till he is 30 for Borini too come good    
    
    
    @Rhiannon_Heap James May    
    
    
    @SexyFootyWAGs @indykaila piss off! Hes proper ugly, jammy bugger!    
    
    
    Good news too hear Cissokho deal is making headway! Enrique needs some pressure and Cissokho is a steamtrain    
    
    
    @Brodinho @SkyBet we should try too move Borini on this window, we will get nothing for him next summer    
    
    
    @NathanEccleston new Total Recall! Grear film    
    
    
    so we arent going too get Cissokho now?    
    
    
    Quality that Carra got a signed shirt from Messi!    
    
    
    Watford won 6-1! Fair play!    
    
    
    Liverpool are like a game of Fifa! Got too score first or your in for a tough game!    
    
    
    Milan are interested in Sakho too? is that going too be another player we miss because of our lack of EU football and poor league position    
    
    
    @stanic007 you have too wonder if we can.... Just cant see us spending much money    
    
    
    When we have played 2-3 league games Luis will realise he cant keep this up and will be well in the mood for football and its world cup year    
    
    
    @Sotty_LFC people who spam things like "get this LFC fan too 3000 followers" I find people with less followers are much more respectable...    
    
    
    @thisisanfield I can read it    
    
    
    Downing was poor.....BUT you cant fault the effort he put in too make up for it    
    
    
    hoping Borini isnt playing and its because he is off.... #overrated    
    
    
    @BradBearne Blinding! i got that Barca shirt.... but for some reason i got Maxi on the back #flop    
    
    
    damn Borini is there.....    
    
    
    N'Gog > Borini........ on paper and in my opinion! and N'Gog was shit..........    
    
    
    @beni_henney like our lot talking about 4th when we still need 3-4 signings!    
    
    
    @BradBearne mine pic.twitter.com/eG7mX6whtW    
    
    
    @BradBearne mine pic.twitter.com/ssOkZbe7ev    
    
    
    according too the bellends at @talkSPORTDrive we "ruined" Downing... jog on, he played and tried loads but wasnt good enough, not LFCs fault    
    
    
    @AzzurriLFC nah because BR will put Coutinho wide if that is the case and i dont think he is anywhere near as effective out wide    
    
    
    bugger starting Sturridge against Stoke too reinjure himself, rather he came off the bench    
    
    
    cant we do some sort of Borini swap deal for someone in Italy??? PLEASE!    
    
    
    damn i am going too be at dog training for the game on Saturday    
    
    
    @LiverpoolWays I would bring him on rushing him back is no good    
    
    
    @LiverpoolWays yeah that was not against stoke though was it! There will be far more commited challenges and far tougher opponents    
    
    
    @LiverpoolWays not saying he shouldnt play! Just had a few injuries been a bit stop start, maybe im being cautious    
    
    
    saying we are going too get Siq because Cissokho could join Sunderland, what makes you so confident, last week Cissokho had "agreed terms"    
    
    
    All Norwich bench #fantasyfootball    
    
    
    Dont believe that FSG would put the cash up for Willian, can see us stuck outside top 5 for being too frugal at this rate    
    
    
    @beni_henney barclays proper 1, u got a league?    
    
    
    @beni_henney dont know, cant be bothered with more than 1 and definitely not the scum!    
    
    
    @_aim93 cant stand it when you ask for an orange one and someone brings you a dirty original one!    
    
    
    Who just got stretchered off! Jusy loaded stream please not Sterling!!!    
    
    
    #datamined again! This time via my twitter on my mates laptop at his, now im home and theres ads for the obscure product i was looking at    
    
    
    Will be truly shocked if we actually sign Willian, just sounds like another twitter dream    
    
    
    These Suarez quotes cant be real    
    
    
    What Suarez will turn up next month???? Crazy Suarez, Happy Suarez, Stroppy Suarez or Wild Suarez? Who knows    
    
    
    Suarez still has a lot too do to convince us he really does give 2 shits! We need a player of his ability but can we cope with mentality    
    
    
    #LocoSuarez get it trending!!!!    
    
    
    We all all pissed off but I tell you now, 30 goals is a lot too lose! He will score goals and he will make a difference! A massive one!    
    
    
    You know there is a release clause if Suarez gets a new contract! Better be £55m #LocoSuarez    
    
    
    We have to appreciate Suarez but thats all! He wont be getting any love unless he is still here next season    
    
    
    @LfcDan well said    
    
    
    Suarez told one of the most reliable sources available while in Japan (@MartinCharquero) and now people are trying too discredit it...?    
    
    
    @BBC not satisfied with Suarez quotes so they spin up thier own story too keep the saga going on #shoddy    
    
    
    Meanwhile, im quite happy Diego Costa isnt coming!    
    
    
    @AzzurriLFC errr hes decent young DM on #FM13 lol.........!    
    
    
    @beni_henney england will show up tonight! Typical! Then when it matters we will revert to desperate performances    
    
    
    @CooolBeer Arsenal's transfer window:
Rooney ✖
Julio Cesar ✖
Fellaini ✖
Fabregas ✖
Jovetic ✖
Higuain ✖
Bernard ✖
Suarez ✖
Gustavo ✖"    
    
    
    @deanosmigsmith UNREAL!!!    
    
    
    Welbeck is twaff #Gerald #HeyArnold    
    
    
    Oh dear!!!    
    
    
    Get Wellbeck off! How does he get in the team!    
    
    
    @beni_henney well this isnt going how I expected...    
    
    
    INSERT WALCOTT IN DREAM TEAM.........    
    
    
    @BoringMilner is on........    
    
    
    Fair play Lambert!!!    
    
    
    WHAT ZAHA??? Gets signed by Utd = auto call up! Have a word #FA    
    
    
    Zaha = stepover stepover stepover stepover stepover stepover    
    
    
    Oh god Gurnhead is coming on    
    
    
    @LFCFansCorner u got a league mate??    
    
    
    #TypeR    
    
    
    HAHA Suarez saga on FM13, trying too sign regen, told him he needs to join us, hes put in a transfer request, they want 51m, im trying 40m!    
    
    
    I can see us having 2 sponsors on the top soon, another way too earn more money! Teams abroad have loads    
    
    
    Brendan theres this FALCAO rumour going about.............. #SignHimUp    
    
    
    Gerrard, Hendo, Lucas AND ALLEN???? WTF loads of people are tweeting Allen and not Aspas, please tell me its a mistake???    
    
    
    @steveG_pool good!    
    
    
    This is already looking like last season! All over them! 1 chance and they nearly score! Sort it out!    
    
    
    Hate Etherington with a passion!    
    
    
    AHHHHH KOLO    
    
    
    Whats this Halsey bit everytime the ref makes a decision? #BTSport    
    
    
    Stoke getting some of thier own medicine!    
    
    
    Lucas is having a great game    
    
    
    @LiamJackAndrews yeah id move Coutinho more central and bring Sterling on he was great for u21    
    
    
    Betting advert! Betting advert! Betting advert!    
    
    
    David James appears too have had an altercation with an electrical device......    
    
    
    Enrique so wasteful today    
    
    
    LOL Arsenal!    
    
    
    @RSDeeMan_LFC thats well nice, they started selling it in watford about 2 years ago!    
    
    
    Today is the day of amazing away keepers! #Begovic #Guzan    
    
    
    Hope your watching this Arsenal game @luis16suarez    
    
    
    OWWW SANGA!!! That did not look good!    
    
    
    @Brodinho he was good at first! But then 1 day he got nowhere near any again....    
    
    
    @BBCMOTD #NO    
    
    
    be great if we get Willian but i am not going too get too into it based on random twitter follows    
    
    
    I just started following Willian...........everyone go mad!    
    
    
    Whats this Cissokho back on now??? No Siquiera then?    
    
    
    @Phil_Coutinho @LucasLeiva87 RING WILLIAN NOW...........    
    
    
    is the U21s on LFCTV?    
    
    
    they are having a proper argument on this Russia stream....    
    
    
    OMG this Acestream 2.1 download is soo slow, what is it with their mirror, always had too wait 20 mins too download 55mb!    
    
    
    oh, just see the download via torrent link.......    
    
    
    What a goal Aguero!!!!    
    
    
    Yanga-Mbiwa looked like he was about too kill Dzeko    
    
    
    City look so much better under Pellegrini, NUFC playing poor though, cant keep the ball for 2 seconds    
    
    
    Jonas looks like hes just picked up a hamstring injury    
    
    
    Newcastle are so poor, havent really looked at all the part today, cant see Pardew lasting much longer, honeymoon period ended ages ago!    
    
    
    Stephen Taylor red card!    
    
    
    Taylor is such a thug!    
    
    
    i reckon 5-0 now, it looked like it was going to be 4-0 as it was    
    
    
    Am i the only one that has noticed FIFA music popping up on loads of betting and loads of football shows    
    
    
    "If your gonna get booked or sent off...tackle someone...." - Jamie Carragher    
    
    
    YYAAAYYYAAAYYYAAAYYAAAAAA    
    
    
    Craig Davids effort blocked...... #Clichy    
    
    
    OMG Zabaleta you are in my dream team should have scored!    
    
    
    Whats up with @virginmedia broadband tonight! Mines running like dialup..... Cant even load images!    
    
    
    We have no capability too sign any big money players......!    
    
    
    I still think letting Ayre negotiate is awful, he is a nobody, cant we get someone with footballing rep in too convince players too sign????    
    
    
    @JNorthcroft @JimBoardman going for good targets and not getting hardly inspires confindence or any rep among the next big target....    
    
    
    @LiverpoolinfoFc i havent said anthing about Willian if thats what you mean, i mean in general id rather have a reputable person in his role    
    
    
    @LiverpoolinfoFc i fully believe Ayre is part of the problem, i know FSG are stubborn and our league finish was poor doesnt help    
    
    
    Surely you would want Lamela OR Willian....?    
    
    
    The only thing worse than LFC negotiations is.......................Arsenal negotiations......    
    
    
    @M_Sweeting London is a shithole nowadays, the real advantage is that just outside London its quite nice...    
    
    
    Oh all of a sudden we want Lamela now that we appear too have lost Willian, who Spurs also want, so we wont get either now???    
    
    
    @PopItUpSnowman @DD4LFC @LiverpoolFF arsenal can barely field a starting 11 without picking up 2 injuries and playing someone unfit    
    
    
    @Brodinho hopefully he will see the hell hole that north London is and think bugger that!    
    
    
    Still though people talking top 4 is outrageous! Willian or not!    
    
    
    Great Scott Sinclair..............cant wait for that signing.......................    
    
    
    @stanic007 some european football is better than none, and Spurs also looking from outside England are far closer too CL!    
    
    
    so we didnt really want Willian, we were just interested for the sake of it??..............    
    
    
    @Waynehue @Cullstar problem being that we didnt get them 2 until Jan. we need too do our business now not play catchup in Jan    
    
    
    @jorge_decastro i was just thinking, he looked decent when he was in Turkey, personally i wouldnt sign him now either    
    
    
    almost like FSG are thinking, if we dont sign anyone big we will make a profit so we wont go in that hard for them.....    
    
    
    If we do for some reason sign Eriksson does that mean Coutinho will end up playing from wide? if thats the case dont bother!    
    
    
    @hondaculture when is it havent been for ages    
    
    
    @kevtorpey yeah they were total idiots, never wanted him anyway, was well happy we didnt get him, cant stand him!    
    
    
    @PopItUpSnowman @DD4LFC @LiverpoolFF no trophies does...............    
    
    
    how can Wenger say that the transfer strategy is on track? lol    
    
    
    @kevtorpey well i thought he was interested in playing for us? wasnt it us that didnt want too pay? he has too leave Anzhi no matter what!    
    
    
    @kevtorpey im not saying he is, but if we offered that much someone at the club obv believes he is, it was clearly an opportunist bid anyway    
    
    
    @Brodinho what go on holiday too Hungary....? Lol    
    
    
    @ckenchington @nickyclyde more like because we didnt get Dempsey and Sigu we ended up with Sturridge and Coutinho.......THANK GOD!    
    
    
    didnt someone say we was after Yarmo at the start of the window?    
    
    
    Coates has torn his knee ligament????    
    
    
    going too watch a vid of Yarmolenko and try and find errors in a vid of only good bits! Thats the only way you can assess a player via YT!    
    
    
    MY GOD the defending in Ukrainian league football is poor!    
    
    
    good think about Yarmo, hes quite big and hes Ukrainian so there shouldnt be any physicality issues there    
    
    
    Yarmo looks like a Ukrainian Zaha......... STEPOVER STEPOVER STEPOVER STEPOVER STEPOVER STEPOVER STEPOVER STEPOVER    
    
    
    id go as far as saying that he does too many tricks and he will get caught out by prem defenders, has a good touch though    
    
    
    @Robish13 im watching a vid now, he scored with his left but he seem too be quite comfy to take and move the ball on either    
    
    
    Yarmo loves a backheel aswell!    
    
    
    @lfc2652 @_aim93 LOL, only thing i noticed is it say Everton 2, Liverpool 1. which i read as Liverpool NUMBER 1, Everton number 2........    
    
    
    This Papa excitement (if you can call it that) hasnt he been injured for months??? Is he fit too play yet?    
    
    
    Did i just read that Yarmolenko is the "Ukrainian Messi"???...................#facepalm    
    
    
    @jamiewoodall7 Yarmolenko    
    
    
    @jamiewoodall7 i just cant be bothered too write his whole name    
    
    
    @KaneD101 i thought he was getting 130 years??    
    
    
    @jamiewoodall7 oh, he is a Ukrainian winger that we are supposedly interested in, tall, tricky, only see him at EURO2012 and youtube tho....    
    
    
    @KaneD101 ahhh i dunno about shoot a random kid for no reason, something dodgy was going on there, that zimmerman did have some injuries    
    
    
    @KaneD101 the more you read into that case the less Trayvon looks a victim of profiling    
    
    
    @jamiewoodall7 i dont think hes going to set the prem on fire, but if he is around £10m (no idea what his price is) id say maybe    
    
    
    @no1confused just looked, he played 10 times last season, assuming he was a reg at S04 hes been out for a LONG time!    
    
    
    @jft96 @Cullstar thats going a bit far aint it mate?    
    
    
    @no1confused no Coates is out apparently with a ligament injury and Kelly on the recovery i cant see any logic whatsoever in signing Papa    
    
    
    @no1confused now**    
    
    
    @no1confused i dont mind gambling on forwards/attacking mids/wingers but not on the defence, it absolutely MUST be reliable all season!    
    
    
    safe too say 95% of LFC fans cant say anything about Yarmolenko, he looks decent on YT, did look ok at EURO2012 i cant say more than that    
    
    
    @mrjakehumphrey HAHA good luck getting any sensible questions! How did he find out about the supposed clause in Suarez contract??? #TAPPEDUP    
    
    
    Kelly recovering, Coates injured, Wisdom inexperienced.. i know lets get Papa who hasnt played for 10 months........ #FanLogic    
    
    
    @beni_henney AVB has said there have been "conversations" is he actually in for a medical now?    
    
    
    @wilsoncov @LfcAnfieldNews i bet all those people have been watching Youtube... only time ive seen him was Euro's, decent/average    
    
    
    @timbolton1 AHAAAAAAAAAAAAA    
    
    
    @Karlton81 hes proper average, loads of hype around him, seems like we will be waiting a couple of seasons too see it!    
    
    
    @beni_henney oh, you mean Sky sports as reliable as using mayonnaise for superglue sources    
    
    
    @wilsoncov @LfcAnfieldNews has a price been flung about? from the limited amount ive seen him + Youtube i still wouldnt pay over £8-10m    
    
    
    @thomgough1 @JackSear took the words out my mouth Thom!    
    
    
    @markrogers_ @LFCforever19 why would we need a central player, we need too play Coutinho central, buy a wide man!    
    
    
    @JackSear @thomgough1 no logic whatsover in signing a player too prevent someone else, no1 would have signed him if Anzhi werent flogging    
    
    
    Although Willian looks decent and would IMO be a good addition NOT ONE PERSON SAID I HOPE LFC SIGN WILLIAN UNTIL ANZHI STARTED FLOGGING!    
    
    
    @markrogers_ @LFCforever19 YES no.10 in the middle, not talking about CM, why would we need another CM, Eriksson is hardly phyiscal himself!    
    
    
    according too Sky Italia................yeah ok i believe that......... #sauces    
    
    
    @lfcindex @JackSear when is he even back? hes been out 10 months, we need a fit CB, Kelly recovering Coates out Wisdom inexperienced    
    
    
    @henney946  No1 had a danny or gave 2 shits about him till last week, if they really rated him they would have said when at Shaktar    
    
    
    @henney946 it should have been clear that Anzhi was going too be a flop anyway lol, total madness what went on there!    
    
    
    i seriously doubt, UNLIKE SPURS who were linked too Willian a while ago, that LFC had even sent a scout too look at Willian before last week    
    
    
    @dom_campbell yeah and ive read that he "will not join according too his agent!" sky italia is shocking!    
    
    
    ive got too walk the dog too much craziness on here!    
    
    
    So Spurs didnt "outbid" us for Willian, they just paid Joorbachians fee, which apparently we wouldnt, bet that will change a lot of opinions    
    
    
    Meireles looks quite mad...... Kuyt looks more like Sloth.....    
    
    
    Feners passing is embarrassing!    
    
    
    Meireles painfull too watch! Didnt realise he was this bad!    
    
    
    @R_Fredriksson @Nina_LFC Papa has been injured for 10 months he cant come in as 3rd or 2nd choice CB!    
    
    
    People going on and on about Papa! Been out 10 months still recovering, he cannot be 2nd or 3rd choice CB, hes a long way from his best    
    
    
    NOOOOO VILLA!!!    
    
    
    One game and Gerry is creaming himself about Atletico    
    
    
    Atletico havent created a single clear chance themselves! Villas goal was amazing apart from that they have just fouled and pressed    
    
    
    Has anyone noticed that loads of betting adverts have the same music as FIFA13!? #subliminalMessaging    
    
    
    @LiamJackAndrews yeah papas well capable of beibg 3rd choice premiership CB after 10 months out....    
    
    
    Tata just walking up and down stroking his face! Cant stand it when you see a manager not dictating when a team is losing!    
    
    
    VAMOSSSSSS NEYMARRRRRRRR QUE GOLAZZZZZOOOOOOO    
    
    
    Watch Atletico melt now    
    
    
    This "New Robben" we are interested in!? Is he like "Messi fron Madrid" Gerardo Bruna....... Who is now clubless!    
    
    
    Arsenal in for a couple more players they wont get....................    
    
    
    quite a bit of blame being placed at the feet of Dalglish.... in realism he shouldnt have been appointed after caretaker spell    
    
    
    whats actually happened today?? ive got in from work and its kicking off on here....    
    
    
    @timbolton1 are you just trying too get our hopes up??    
    
    
    SOMEONE GIVE ME SOME UPDATE ON WHAT YOU LOT ARE HAVING FITS ABOUT! #LFC    
    
    
    BR talking about how Coates is out like he had plans too play him, yeah right, FSG probably gutted they are missing out on money from sale    
    
    
    @LFCImpulse @LFCFansCorner isnt he left footed?    
    
    
    AVB willbe gutted if he misses out on Willian, he needs a massive cotton bud for those nostrils............    
    
    
    Oh look Papa fans, he couldnt even get thru his first training session without attention too his knee, cant think of a worse deal right now    
    
    
    he needs too be left at S04 for a season too prove his fitness, he might never recover!    
    
    
    @LFCImpulse @LFCFansCorner hes definitely a talent, and for me a far better signing than Papa who couldnt even make it thru training today    
    
    
    @SkySportsPeteO apparently his brother/agent has died, your "sauce" is twaf!    
    
    
    @SkySportsNews dragging Anelka through the mud with their appauling sources!    
    
    
    @liverbabygirl apparently his agent/brother has died so he has left training not "walked out"    
    
    
    @LFCImpulse @LFCFansCorner i know, im not a fan of all this Papa talk, he is noway capable of being a 3rd choice CB till he is proven fit    
    
    
    O'Rourkes story soon changed #SSN    
    
    
    Is there some BR presser that i have missed or something?    
    
    
    @ConnorwilsonLFC Kriz Walsh @KrizWalsh 2m @tancredipalmeri His brother isn't his agent. It (was) Doug Pingisi http://www1.skysports.com/football/news/11854/8599652/ … (EDIT)    
    
    
    Anelkas brother IS not his agent    
    
    
    "But his agent, Doug Pingisi, says the Frenchman is capable of playing on for at least three more years" #SSN on Anelka 26/03/2013    
    
    
    @LFCFansCorner its not his brother his agent was Doug Pingisi    
    
    
    @liverbabygirl its wrong, his agent was Doug Pingisi, SSN had an interview in March with him    
    
    
    WHAT Manning is now a woman? i had heard about him crossdressing but this is extreme, solitary confinement clearly been detrimental!    
    
    
    @dom_campbell NO HE WASNT! It was Doug Pingisi!    
    
    
    bit harsh too retweet peoples Anelka comments prior too the whole story coming out! Even major media had it wrong!    
    
    
    @edflinkinp @DamianConnor as long as we dont sign him im happy, been saying for days hes not fit and look today he breaks down in training..    
    
    
    Ok so apparently Anelkas agent isnt his brother or this Doug geezer that was in #SSN article in March this year!...    
    
    
    @SkyFootball @AndrewWebbLFC why is this being reported like BR had any intention too use Coates this season? he was clearly getting shipped!    
    
    
    not impressing me the way that Coates injury is being used as an excuse too sign a CB like BR was going to actually play him    
    
    
    @liverbabygirl i dont get why he doesnt get sold, he is never going too make it, i think littirally no1 wants too buy him    
    
    
    Squad player or not if Lamela doesnt sign for LFC im getting Alberto on me shirt, not ordering one until window is closed!    
    
    
    @liverbabygirl if the teams loaning him are paying his wages that makes sense, think we are hoping one of them will sign him at end of loan    
    
    
    YES Sinclair has signed for WBA on loan, we arent getting him even if it was just a passing rumour i wasnt impressed!    
    
    
    @liverbabygirl neither can i but surely this is his last season under contract, im sure he has been on loan 3 seasons in a row already    
    
    
    @ErinNYC75 we havent signed anyone since this time yesterday.......lol    
    
    
    @UKBanter @beni_henney genius!    
    
    
    If this Madrid back in for Suarez deal has any truth and he is sold........meltdown, JWH cant make statements like he did then sell him!    
    
    
    Sahko is "desperate" too move too LFC, according too Metro... yeah thats until Spurs realise and put a bid in......    
    
    
        
    
    
    @edflinkinp “We are not going to sell Luis. It’s a football reason. It’s not finances. So for football reasons we can’t, especially to Ars"    
    
    
    @stanic007 hes been here years and barely got a look in at CB, with no RB cover id be surprised if recovering Kelly played CB over Wisdom    
    
    
    is this rodgers presser on youtube??    
    
    
    Quite surprised we havent brought in a CB quicker considering that the plan appears too have been too loan Wisdom and Coates    
    
    
    How pathetic is all this "Suarez news at...." come off it, why delay, surely the point of  media is too be the first too break a story...???    
    
    
    @martellshields oh dear    
    
    
    JWH was pretty stong worded about Suarez going nowhere "especially Arsenal", cant see him going back on that, he will look a pratt    
    
    
    Oh.. "The impending purchase for $70m in cash marks (JW) Henry’s first foray into the financially unsettled world of the news media." 3/8/13    
    
    
    JWH is spending 70m dollars on the Boston Globe..........    
    
    
    FSG didnt have a danny about football when they took over and let Kenny spend, now they have no confidence in spending money    
    
    
    @_aim93 WHAT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    i dont know how many more CBB tweets i can take before i start unfollowing people.....most of them probably arent following me anyway.....    
    
    
    @ashlazy1991 it appears too be assumptions based on his facial expressions in the presser...... clutching!    
    
    
    has anyone bothered too check tomorrows headlines RE Suarez??    
    
    
    @_aim93 90s kids tv comedy, proper cheesy! Classic though    
    
    
    thats not even news........ i said earlier JWH said he wouldnt sell Luis too ANYONE, especially Arsenal, that was 2 weeks ago!    
    
    
    pathetic really how the media has cooked up a storm tonight regarding completely un-sensational Suarez "news"    
    
    
    i could of made that suarez news up whilst i was on the toilet.......    
    
    
    has too be said this is clearly the media trying too instigate some form of speculatable situation so they can write more stories    
    
    
    You could have said Juve "may" bid for Suarez anyone "may" bid for anyone whenever, they just picked the team that most suited the "news"    
    
    
    People need to learn too read what is written, Real Madrid "may" means could IF they decided they want to bid, not Real WILL bid!    
    
    
    Definition of "May" - Used to indicate a certain measure of likelihood or possibility, NOT a COMPLETE POSSIBILITY    
    
    
    @empireofthekop of course they "might" so "might" Galatasary, they are just generalising to make some form of story, its painfull    
    
    
    isnt Benzema one of Florentinos lovechildren? Cant see him going Arsenal!    
    
    
    SO, Willian is worth £30m too Chelsea who have Mata, Hazard and Oscar and are in the top 3 but hes not worth it for LFC..........?    
    
    
    @Sara_156 he didnt even get too make the choice lol    
    
    
    wheres the people who were trying too justify not spending £30-35m on Willian now that hes set too join Mata, Oscar, Hazard, Schurrle? #LFC    
    
    
    @GraemeBandeira PLEASE DRAW JULIO CESAR FALCIONI! HE WOULD BE AN AMAZING CARICATURE #angryface    
    
    
    @GraemeBandeira pic.twitter.com/XqvSsd1ycO    
    
    
    @dom_campbell at least £30m and teams in CL would be interested, can rule us out!    
    
    
    @AlexGumery piss off!    
    
    
    OMG already fans saying we should get Mata... as if no one in the CL will be after him IF hes even available! #dream    
    
    
    @TrueKopites96 its massive, but its not a signing, we still need the other positions strengthened,    
    
    
    @timbolton1 WOW    
    
    
    Wish that BR presser was today, after it was confirmed Chelsea value Willian higher than LFC do despite the lack of need for him!    
    
    
    "@Bloodzeed I'm off to Stamford bridge to blow that fucking place up Liverpool fans can join me We can set fire to Willian's  barnet" LOL    
    
    
    @bossy12 they have....... do they really need him, Mou is saying someone will have too make way for him    
    
    
    SEE I SAID GET TER STEGEN! LFC have good relationship with Gladbach and no he has stalled on contract offer apparently    
    
    
    @Kop305 @guardian what terrible journalism, it reads like Real have no control over the sale of Benzema!    
    
    
    ANYONE who is seriously wanting Moses at LFC.......come off it!    
    
    
    @Corballyred its madness, but JWH did a deal in march to buy Boston Globe for $70m! Hes here for profit hes an investor wants a  return    
    
    
    @ImNotArsedLad what was he on lol    
    
    
    Michael Owen has praised LFC for the way they handled Suarez....? 2 weeks ago he said LFC should sell him.......    
    
    
    Can see it now Turan signing for Spurs and Ljajic going AC #LFC    
    
    
    @AnfieldIndex ukrainian winger! Only see him at Euro2012, was hyped up but I wasnt that amazed! Dzageov was better than him at Euro2012    
    
    
    @R_Fredriksson @Nina_LFC still too steep @YaroLFC watches reg and says €15m max    
    
    
    @PeteKopite @Nina_LFC more like €15m    
    
    
    Ayew available for €13m! Cheap gamble???    
    
    
    @YaroLFC too be fair Coutinho was totally out if favour at Inter    
    
    
    @BornOffside9 id be surprised if we was the only club too make an offer!    
    
    
    great strategy from the back marker teams!    
    
    
    Hamilton way too close too going out in Q2 there for my liking    
    
    
    Joe Allen better not get rinsed by Delph today if he starts! Lot of people have overlooked the need too get in decent cover for Lucas!    
    
    
    DI RESTA IS GOING TOO GET POLE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! #F1    
    
    
    THAT WAS AN EPIC QUALI!!!!!!    
    
    
    @LFCamiArias2 @kLFCreds Ahahhahaa that pic is great hahahha    
    
    
    @Corballyred im dreading watching Allen in competitive football too be honest!    
    
    
    nice Everton draw!    
    
    
    Allen not starting has calmed me!    
    
    
    Yes Jamie! #Dalglish    
    
    
    @Kop305 what a joke! Its always my worst nightmare too end up stuck with a pillar in the way!    
    
    
    AHHHHHH i forgot we would be wearing the away kit!!!    
    
    
    Hopefully the digital blur will mess with Villas vision........ #lfckit    
    
    
    OMG how are they squeezing these adverts in all the time!    
    
    
    That Bacuna is poor! Tough game for him though!    
    
    
    was hoping Mignolet would look more solid with aerial balls/corners today.....    
    
    
    awful defending!    
    
    
    last 5 mins has been poor, whats happened....    
    
    
    Aspas has been non existent in this game! Id bring Sterling on for him, the games gone a bit quiet need a pace injection    
    
    
    we have totally flopped! Enrique evidence, had a decent 1st half now nothing!    
    
    
    this is a really poor 2nd half from LFC    
    
    
    ALYYYYYYY!!!    
    
    
    the stats for this half are going too be terrible from us! We still lack the ability too kill games off it appears!    
    
    
    Theres no way we can get 4th if we cant put a game we dominated the 1st half too bed!    
    
    
    this should be a big reality check too the 4th place commenters! Madness, we havent even shown up in this half, lucky we have a goal!    
    
    
    Disappointing really, cant see us keeping a clean sheet against bigger sides! No potency whatsoever!    
    
    
    people are talking like Villa are a top 6 team, that was poor after first 40 mins, good result plenty too do in my opionion    
    
    
    @JWSlfc its a point but the vast difference in performance in the 2 halfs is poor, we played really well and then really poor    
    
    
    OMG are the Ashes still on? What a joke, seems like its been on a month already    
    
    
    @ashlazy5 still think we need another DM too, people were criticizing Lucas yesterday (for some reason) imagine we didnt have him....    
    
    
    @henney946 i swear someone was mugging off an aussie on tv the other day about us winning it, i genuinely thought it had finished    
    
    
    @mrjakehumphrey skip Church its all superstition....    
    
    
    seriously excited about this 2014/15 Civic Type R plan, the FN2 was a joke! Really hope im in a good situation when its on sale!    
    
    
    Golazo Adriano!!!    
    
    
    @empireofthekop NOOOO NOOOO NOOO NOOOO NOOOO    
    
    
    @LFCTS dont sit on the ball you will egg it haha    
    
    
    no acestream or sopcast for the game...... and its on SS1..... #letdown    
    
    
    dont look like im watching the game tonight then..    
    
    
    @Delveyboy what do you have too do put the channel on and click a button on the pc or something....    
    
    
    @Delveyboy ah i suppose! you need a streaming rig... ive found a bareable flash one    
    
    
    Hope Alberto gets a bit more involved in the 2nd half, very tidy on the ball    
    
    
    @LFCTransferNRS thats some crazy celebration haha    
    
    
    @stanic007 madness, he was keeping it a bit simple, should come out more confident in 2nd half    
    
    
    @AttackoftheKop totally agree, i never envisioned this! My mate (Arsenal) was saying hes going too be big for LFC when we signed him!    
    
    
    theres no need for Sturrdige too be on    
    
    
    Notts County will win in injury time.....    
    
    
    We have been poor in the 2nd half of all our games! Brebdan must be saying the wrong things    
    
    
    Brendan blatantly overpraises the players at half time!    
    
    
    This would have been totally different had Cissokho not gone off! Jono has been poor!    
    
    
    This is a strong team too get the job done???    
    
    
    @MrFredGuest if i was id have put "Brendan overpraises", the way we come out in the 2nd half like the games over is realy poor!    
    
    
    @TheFamousKop id love a seat in the Kop but im a wool...., some people dont know how lucky they are    
    
    
    why take a short corner when you havent been able too play through them all game?    
    
    
    i think most of the Atletico players have made 3 fouls, refs done well too keep the cards away!    
    
    
    Atleti playing in true Simeone fashion.....    
    
    
    Thank god we didnt get Costa, hes a proper twat, wouldnt last 2 mins in the Prem without getting sent off! so petulant    
    
    
    how can they say thats not a pen??? he clattered Pedro, he took a touch and got smashed    
    
    
    Messis pen hits the bar"!!!!    
    
    
    Ref looked ok until about 80 mins..... Turan sent off from the bench.. who knows!    
    
    
    Can see this being another poorly done summer transfer window... Catch up in Feb as usuall when FSG have seen 4 months of problems    
    
    
    Wasnt that into Erikson.... But now reports Spurs have got him im screwing! How we going to challenge for top 4 in next few years with FSG??    
    
    
    Can see us signing Given.... Hes cheap, cant see anyone else coming in! FSG spending 1st season was just showing off and it failed miserably    
    
    
    What seemed was going too be a good transfer window appears too have cumulated in multiple failures leaving LFC well behind competition    
    
    
    i hate Moses!    
    
    
    not even remotely convinced that someone else in a better position wont come in and sign Sakho    
    
    
    @liverbabygirl Go too Liverpool, London is awful!    
    
    
    @joehayesireland its not even realistic, can see him getting quite a bit of gametime under Tata, he likes wingers    
    
    
    @joehayesireland yeah seasons hardly underway is it... they have played 2 legs of Super cup, he will get more gametime in season    
    
    
    @joehayesireland either way, we was linked too him before and he has been linked with loan moves and they have never materialised    
    
    
    @joehayesireland didnt he sign a contract today?    
    
    
    @Howorth71 haha its well weird!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Bayern are making David Luiz look good at football.....    
    
    
    @_DarrenLFC_ @GeniusFootball have a word lol    
    
    
    No Gus! Neuer is in goal he wouldnt have scored if he hit the target there    
    
    
    @kLFCreds @YaroLFC watches him regularly    
    
    
    @fraythered @kLFCreds he wasnt that impressive at Euros! Definitly not £20m impressive    
    
    
    Love Kroos!!!    
    
    
    RED HAJAHAHHAHHABABABBABABHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAH    
    
    
    Okm actually amazed Gotze isnt injured after that!    
    
    
    YYYYYYUEEEEEEESAASASSSSSSSSSSS!!!' YYYYEEEEEEEAAHHHHHHH    
    
    
    Hahhahahahahhaaaaaaa thats what happena when you try and be cocky Lukaku! Wish it was Terry though haha    
    
    
    has anyone photoshopped John Terry into the Bayern celebrations yet???    
    
    
    ahhhhh last night was so good haha #UEFASuperCup    
    
    
    @timbolton1 hes a turncoat! TURNCOAT I TELL YOU!!!!!!!    
    
    
    imagine all the games end 0-0! MOTD will be dogshit    
    
    
    wwwwwwwaaaaaaaaaaaawwwwwwwwwwwwww    
    
    
    The US WILL go into Syria because there is OIL there and thats what the US wants! Control of the resources = control of the world    
    
    
    We seriously need too perform in this 2nd half! Havent been impressed with our 2nd halves this season!    
    
    
    Get off Evra    
    
    
    What a goal Postiga!!!!    
    
    
    Illori is leaning on stuff at Melwood... Done deal lol    
    
    
    Lol quite a few tweets saying Ozil has rejected Arsenal    
    
    
    Why on earth have Chelsea signed Atsu!???    
    
    
    Borini lovers going too pipe down now? He wont do anything at Sunderland, cant see him playing for us again personally!    
    
    
    as if we are going too get Di Maria!    
    
    
    Purslow is a killer! get off the screen mug!    
    
    
    @Blame_Suarez HOW FUNNY WAS THAT LOLOL    
    
    
    Bales spanish is shit................ lol    
    
    
    @TransferNewsCen quicker than SSN! nice!    
    
    
    OMG please dont let United get Ander! Always liked him!    
    
    
    @Corballyred he seems too get injured every other month, its something the physios and coaching staff need too work on! BIG TIME!    
    
    
    @RedMerlin1892 veryy unimpressive since pre season ended, just seems non existant, touch was poor v United, seems overwhelmed like Joe Allen    
    
    
    OMG @SkySportsNews are going too repeat these Bale clips all day! Worse than @marca    
    
    
    Bales spanish is better than Beckhams.........    
    
    
    @Bloodzeed Purslow hasnt got a danny! He was the twat who done deals like Konchesky and Poulsen! #wanker!    
    
    
    its optimistic too think we could get Mata! can see him stuck at Chelsea till January, might be able too get him then!    
    
    
    @LiamJackAndrews he did the medical CHACK lol    
    
    
    @Tooley92 @LFC we need another one regardless, Borini is useless!    
    
    
    @Karlton81 i cant see us missing Borini much...    
    
    
    @StephenJKnight @Karlton81 Assiadi isnt exactly a player we used, Ibe replaces him and will probably get more games!    
    
    
    @edflinkinp still think we need some natural cover for Lucas    
    
    
    @edflinkinp we have done well    
    
    
    Over half A BILLION pounds has change hands for........ Men in shorts that kick a sphere full of air........    
    
    
    ONE HUNDRED AND TWENTY THOUSAND POUNDS A WEEK.......... GARETH BARRY!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Arsenal fans are mad! They still have no cover at all anywhere    
    
    
    @AKARuairiG what Momo???? #snaphimup    
    
    
    @AnnOdong @Kate_LFC_SFC wheres "Railed"    
    
    
    @hthr182 hes totally mad! always has been!    
    
    
    @TheRealEbouee not as good as that goalie from cup of nations!    
    
    
    Its the Grinch.... #EducatingYorkshire    
    
    
    @Channel4News WOW! Great exclusive! #grilled    
    
    
    General McCaffrey had some good things too say about the UK!    
    
    
    @LiamLFCooch1990 THAT IS QUALITY!!!!    
    
    
    Yeah Moses scored.............against Malawi #overreaction    
    
    
    @Brodinho im well happy! Cant stand Borini, people go on about him like hes a world class forward    
    
    
    follow back mugs! Imagine having 10-20k peoples tweets coming up on your TL... Your no-one and no I dont follow back and you get blocked    
    
    
    Get too see how average Yarmolenko is tonight    
    
    
    We should have got Konoplyanka.........    
    
    
    Loving the onesie..... @DuncanBannatyne    
    
    
    we better bash Swansea! not been overly impressed with our 2nd half performances, really need too get a cushion rather than playing on edge    
    
    
    @DaveHendrickTLW so enjoyable you can take your eyes off it too tweet whilst thinking about the the film you watched earlier? lol    
    
    
    @StanCollymore @talkSPORT no way would any club give up 50% of its shirt revenue unless they were guaranteed they would get double the sales    
    
    
    @AnfieldOracle mate theres nothing more epic than playing GTA (1) now! Its such a classic! Even though its budget!    
    
    
    Quite a disappointing half really! Barely creating anything! Id give Alberto a chance he has good vision! Aspas better than previous games    
    
    
    @Rednigerian its more a lack of supply    
    
    
    Still think Alberto needs at least 20 mins today too show he can create!    
    
    
    Didnt think Aspas was that good a signing, then he had  decent preseason and i thought maybe now he looks how i thought he would! Early days    
    
    
    Should have played Agger at LB    
    
    
    Woeful performance!    
    
    
    Was hoping Brendans woeful team selections were over.... That inexperience is showing again! 4 CBs and no no.10 what could possibly go right    
    
    
    Everytime the opposition scores 1st we go into some sort of total lack of creativity mode! THATS WHY SUAREZ IS SO IMPORTANT DOES IT HIMSELF    
    
    
    @Corballyred he was a waste of £9m! Never liked him hope he goes! Was well average at Roma dont know what some fans see in him    
    
    
    We need too score because the chances of us actually playing football in the 2nd half are slim    
    
    
    Thats game over for us most likely    
    
    
    @hthr182 hes shit at everything else...    
    
    
    Oh look we have become awful at football again    
    
    
    Havent had the ball hardly in this half.... No suprise its the 2nd one...    
    
    
    Those fans saying we dont need Suarez couple of months ago! Haha what pillocks    
    
    
    Cant see us scoring, can see them putting it too bed though! Fed up    
    
    
    Sturridges touch left him 2 games ago!    
    
    
    Sturridge needs too come off!    
    
    
    Worse thing is the mancs will think they are amazing...    
    
    
    This match is infuriating i dont know how people are making positive comments! Totally dogshit 2nd half yet again!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Unbareable too watch LFC! Thought we were lucky too win games this season scraping 1-0s seems too satisfy! Havent once looked comfy after 45    
    
    
    @pjnolan28 the bench is shit....    
    
    
    Whats that? Brendan talking about January already...... Wow    
    
    
    Brendan MUST start Alberto in an AM role against Sunderland!    
    
    
    Bojan just pulled his hamstring #FCB #Ajax    
    
    
    @Jay_78_ @Robbie9Fowler Moyes lol    
    
    
    2 things MUST be achieved tomorrow! Score in the 2nd half (and actually play football) and capitalise on others dropped points!!! #LFC    
    
    
    Thank god Borini is ineligible....................NOT    
    
    
    Omg what was that Suarez Jaws clip from Sky Sports    
    
    
    Sunderland have been crap, Howard Webb is ref, other results went in our favour.......    
    
    
    We look awful! Again!!!    
    
    
    Haha half the players have the socks on opposite feet! lol    
    
    
    This ref is AWFUL! How was that a yellow for Cesc??    
    
    
    that was embarrasing from Neymar!    
    
    
    seriously how is this guy reffing in the CL?? #FCB    
    
    
    FABREGASSSSSSSS    
    
    
    im a rat and i love men. got to love a good old sausage    
    
    
    FUT is a joke! They score 1 goal and your whole team turns into a bunch of wankers    
    
    
    @benthedimond unreal! I knew there was major morale swings but handicap is a joke! Walcott getting caught by Mertesaker with red fitness..    
    
    
    @benthedimond haha the FIFA09 guide tells you that momentum can "swing" after conceding and the control, pace, passing and strength all drop    
    
    
    Palace cannot defend! Should get 5 today!    
    
    
    Sahko is a MONSTER!    
    
    
    Better get Alberto on! Total waste so far from Brendan so far, closest thing we have to a Coutinho backup!    
    
    
    Take Sturridge off for a rest! Move Moses forward and GIVE ALBERTO SOME GAME TIME    
    
    
    Sterling in this WB/RM role is pretty poor! Another poor 2nd half!    
    
    
    Cant wait for us too start playing good in 2nd half! Top of the league even with some pretty average football after half time    
    
    
    @EASPORTSFIFA robbing scum! Charge people for points and make your millions but cant run servers properly another crash too menu and DNF!    
    
    
    @EASPORTSFIFA you need too reset everyones DNF multiplier! Its YOUR fault for most of the DNFs! Buy a decent server you can afford it!    
    
    
    @SonyUK how do you control your music from the Smartwatch 2!? Everywhere its advertised it says you can but theres no extension or app....?    
    
    
    @SonyUK what is it and where do i get it? Is it a 3rd party app? I dont want too have to have another app for all my music Walkman is good    
    
    
    @SonyUK ok ive found it but you have too google for smartwatch 1 music player! It doesnt come up in the app store!    
    
    
    Been watching the game 5 mins looks awful!    
    
    
    This is awful! Cant keep the ball for 10 seconds!    
    
    
    We had more had more luck so far this season than i think we have had in the last 3 combined!    
    
    
    HOW IS THE BALL ALLOWED TOO GET BELOW HEAD HEIGHT IN THE BOX WHEN WE ARE DEFENDING SET PIECES!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    This is a joke really even a win now needs more luck! Dont Believe BR has the nouse too lift the players    
    
    
    Why are we trying too shoot from anywhere! What happened too "SAS"???    
    
    
    This better end 4-2 or we are a joke riding the luck waves    
    
    
    Trying too force the ball against 10 man NUFC......    
    
    
    Omg i leave the room and we scored...... Back in 5 ;)    
    
    
    Its unbelievable that we are currently in the top 3 if you ask me! Cant wait for us too start playing good for 90 mins!    
    
    
    Great challenge Cissokho    
    
    
    Might aswell give us a goal kick when the ball goes out for a corner    
    
    
    OMG WE ARE GONNA LOSE!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Cant believe there is people tweeting about a draw away to Newcastle being a good result! What are these tossers reading the match online?    
    
    
    @Skyhelpteam my pals had no broadband all day, is there a problem with the service? TV is working fine, restarted everything, no smiley face    
    
    
    Shows how far off we are from top 4!    
    
    
    @joerogan "Himalayan" salt isnt from the Himalayas..... well disappointed!    
    
    
    Need too get a @wagamama_uk tomorrow!    
    
    
    Great header from Amorebieta...........    
    
    
    SKRTEL THE TURTLE    
    
    
    We actually scored from a corner..    
    
    
    WHAT A GOAL!!!    
    
    
    Rather see Luis Alberto....    
    
    
    Coutinho.... All but!!!    
    
    
    @joerogan hey Joe you may have seen this its an artists self portraits while on drugs (inc. DMT) http://bryanlewissaunders.org/drugs/ugs     
    
    
    Joe Allen is a waste!    
    
    
    GOT TOO BE RED    
    
    
    YELLOW??????????? Fucking joke    
    
    
    @DaveHendrickTLW clutching at straws trying too defend the ref!    
    
    
    WHATS THE POINT IN MARK HALSEY HE JUST AGREES WITH EVERYTHING THE REF DOES    
    
    
    Uh oh Delofeau!    
    
    
    Flanagan dealing with Barca players #Solid hahaha    
    
    
    @beni_henney oh dear...... How did he miss    
    
    
    Flanagan has done really well, beaten a couple of times but has kept his chin up!    
    
    
    JOE ALLEN    
    
    
    I keep hating Allen and he keeps helping me do it! Hes just too weak and doesnt seem too have the focus under pressure    
    
    
    How Mirrallas is still on is a joke    
    
    
    He cant kick though.....    
    
    
    YES JOE ALLEN OFF    
    
    
    Disgusting!    
    
    
    Got too blame Joe Allen! That really killed it!    
    
    
    Weve fucking lost it! Havent had a hold at any point! Woeful ref woeful defending woeful Joe Allen    
    
    
    YYYYYEEAAHJHJ YOU TRAMP SCUM.BLUESHITE MUG PHIL DOWD JOE ALLEN PRICKS!    
    
    
    Scoooore now!!!!!    
    
    
    MICHAEL OWEN CLOSET BLUE    
    
    
    Ohhhh Moses    
    
    
    NO NO NO NOT A CORNER    
    
    
    Fuck it ill take a draw......    
    
    
    Funnily enough the only thing that game didnt have was A RED CARD REF!    
    
    
    Looking pretty poor! Cant keep the ball, what is going on?    
    
    
    Final ball is poor! Hull just giving us the ball twice as often as we give it too them...    
    
    
    Look how deep Luis is having too come! Need Coutinho desperately! Just trying too force long balls!    
    
    
    @Nina_LFC exactly the sort of fixture we do though...    
    
    
    Why is Suarez constantly having too come so deep? Hendo has been totally ineffective!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Come on Brendan something needs too change! Can see this going on till 75th min!    
    
    
    Laughing stock!    
    
    
    Prems the best league? Where the team in 2nd plays poor every week and cant defend...... Yeah ok    
    
    
    Cocky team selection from Rodgers! Well done! He really needs too sort it out! He needed a reality check!    
    
    
    saying Rodgers out is silly! but he needs to sort out his decisions! Toure looked well off the pace! no excuse for not playing Sakho    
    
    
    "@Corballyred: Who is this Ings lad, fuck off with these Championship players." How is a cship striker gonna cover international forwards??    
    
    
    Where is Sakho???    
    
    
    WHam havent been conceding a lot of goals! Got goalkeeper man of the match 0-0 written all over it! Hope Luis bags another hattrick    
    
    
    Can see why West Ham havent conceded many goals this season!    
    
    
    Sakho needs too be playing every week!    
    
    
    How is that an OG?? Surely if its not Skrtels its Sakhos looked like it was going in!?    
    
    
    Noo bring on Alberto!!!!!    
    
    
    Turned completely shit!    
    
    
    3 CBs on Caulker and he still wins the header....    
    
    
    @henney946 its poor! Id rather play Agger and Sakho! Skrtel is a liability! Especially when he is playing bad he gets in a right mess    
    
    
    @FringeOnToast its much more fun being a wool mate lol!    
    
    
    Skrtel is proper poor everygame he is all over people pulling and never winning headers!    
    
    
    Howard Webb appauling today!    
    
    
    Moment of truth for Aspas as far as im concerned, terrible so far looked good preseason under no pressure, performed as expected in league!    
    
    
    Aspas doesnt close down enough, he doesnt seem too be able too think for himself!    
    
    
    this is a joke Hull have created more than us all we are doing is passing around at the  back!    
    
    
    Why do we keep playing long balls too Suarez and Aspas???    
    
    
    this game and the weather have a lot in common.....    
    
    
    Aspas needs too come off its like playing 10 v 12    
    
    
    Might aswell have signed real Quasimodo #Aspas    
    
    
    Game needed that big time!    
    
    
    Aspas has too come at half time he is a joke! Awful, total waste, hes done probably 1 thing all half and the rest has been terrible    
    
    
    @theenkay it wasnt even form, it was preseason he was under no pressure    
    
    
    Thats it Aspas hang your head, poor again!    
    
    
    Coutinho has tried too hard today!    
    
    
    @joerogan OOOHH TSA! http://vitaminl.tv/video/1953     
    
    
    Never trust a CB that wears gloves! #Chirices #FACup    
    
    
    infuritates me that a 50 year old rule set up because 1 chairman thought that televised 3pm games affected his attendance still applies    
    
    
    @henney946 theres nothing worse than listening too QPR fans!    
    
    
    FA SCAM! Theres no reason not too show the game based on some Burnley chairman from the 60s claim that TV games at 3pm lower attendances    
    
    
    shocking tackle from De Rossi!    
    
    
    AHAHA 2 reds in a minute!    
    
    
    if Navas just crossed it straight away instead of waiting till the last second City would probably be 2 up, he delays so much!    
    
    
    oh no the 3rd kit! i forgot about it!    
    
    
    YES @LucasLeiva87 wearing the odd socks the opposite way too everyone else!    
    
    
    Cant trust a centre back that wears gloves! #Kolo    
    
    
    this is pretty poor really!    
    
    
    HAHA LUIS!    
    
    
    uh oh Lucas us limping a bit!    
    
    
    Get Lucas off! clearly a problem!    
    
    
    We should be all over this team, poor, keep punting the ball up the pitch, cant see how its 60% possession!    
    
    
    talk of Champions League, not with this defence!    
    
    
    got too be one of the softest penalties ever!    
    
    
    @beni_henney that was a terrible decision!    
    
    
    Sturridge will get injured if he comes on in this game! #Rugby    
    
    
    Mignolet honeymoon period appears too be coming too an end, that was soft unsighted or not!"    
    
    
    No Lucas! say what you want about him but when he isnt playing we have no protection! Never confident in midfield without him!    
    
    
    Gerrard is really struggling! This is a horrible start from him!    
    
    
    You CANNOT play Suarez, Sturridge, Coutinho and Sterling! Move Coutinho central and move Luis/Sturridge wide swapping    
    
    
        
    
    
    Are we playing a 4-2-4 with 2 attacking CMs or something! Going too get done on the counter very soon!    
    
    
    FOR FUCK SAKE BRENDAN HAVE YOU GOT NO BOLLOCKS! Do something!    
    
    
    WE HAVENT HAD THE FUCKING BALL BRENDAN MAKE A SUB!    
    
    
    Did i just say we are going too get done on the counter!!????    
    
    
    Need too see that a few times! Looked a dive...... #eeek    
    
    
    People forget that Cissokho is a loan!    
    
    
    @MrFredGuest yeah he does struggle on the decision front! Also i think he is incredibly slow chasing back!    
    
    
    @MrFredGuest exactly mate! I can hear him sighing when we lose the ball from here haha    
    
    
    anyone who thinks top 4 is on is mad! its too tight too be making silly tactical errors at home against bottom half teams    
    
    
    all down too poor tactics, we hardly had a problem after the formation change! If we had changed it at 1-0 might have won    
    
    
    BR wanted too show off today and it proved too be another cocky team selection from him that backfired!    
    
    
    @kop_that missed Sahko, he is considerably more reliable than Kolo for me    
    
    
    @RobHarris @StanCollymore LETS BRING UP STANS PAST WHILE WE ARE AT IT    
    
    
    So Yesils career is looking a bit on the rocks, ACL 2 times in a year, can you recover from that?    
    
    
    apparently the Yankees have spent $530m dollars this offseason, so if you want too know where LFCs moneys going its probablt into Redsox....    
    
    
    another horrendous watch this Barca game    
    
    
    OMG DID SUNDERLAND SCORE?????!!!!! GET IN! AHAHAH!    
    
    
    DEVASTATING PASS FROM MESSI!    
    
    
    @LFC_DAN_RCCV the pass!!!!!    
    
    
    come on stream load i wanna see Utd lose on pens!    
    
    
    ahhh man im minutes behind no twitter for 5 mins!    
    
    
    omg this stream must be 10 mins behind, still havent even taken the 1st pen!    
    
    
    STREAM WAS WELL BEHIND! YYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEESSSSSSSSSS    
    
    
    So Lucas has said he will only be out for a few weeks! Nice, where did this out for 2 months crap come from???    
    
    
    ahhh what a killer @FALCAO will miss the world cup!    
    
    
    soooo, we are signing no one this window then??    
    
    
    Thanks @WARRIOR_FTBL for designing my fantasy football kit......... pic.twitter.com/ncbJS6baWa    
    
    
    @siancjones is everyone foreign aswell.........    
    
    
    @iLikeGirlsDaily Jada Stevens    
    
    
    @KopMatt well Suarez wont will he................    
    
    
    @KopMatt come on mate hes on a BAN!!!!!    
    
    
    @KopMatt if he stays how is he going too start against stoke regardless???? you cant include him in the options at all!    
    
    
    @KopMatt yes i know he might not be a liverpool player, but if he is he is unavailable for selection so why not just leave his name out?    
    
    
    @KopMatt what you are doing is speculating an impossible situation and assuming we will sign a striker    
    
    
    @KopMatt that one isnt coming up in this convo lol    
    
    
    @KopMatt im reading the convo not your profile    
    
    
    @AnfieldAkiba @RealOviedoWFC arigatoooooo    
    
    
    @AnfieldAkiba @RealOviedoWFC just emailed, thanks    
    
    
    @KopMatt if Sturridge is fit he will be in prob, I reckon Aspas will start on the bench, maybe Sterling and Downing/Borini as wide men    
    
    
    @AnfieldAkiba yeah had too do it, maybe one day thay will win the CL :D    
    
    
    @MickGraham187 @CoachingFamily 2 touch, keep ball, dont give them time too get close, they will run themselves into the ground in the 1st 45    
    
    
    @lfcindex spanish press saying hes going Spurs next week    
    
    
    @Brodinho id sell, he is well overrated imo    
    
    
    @PaulBigpaulie I dont think FSG really want too spend! Big signings should be made early on depth added later once you have what you need    
    
    
    @WARRIOR_FTBL @LFC awful kit    
    
    
    Lovely Coutinho! #tooeasy    
    
    
    @NairMitesh @LiverpoolWays @espn its not ESPNs camera man it will be a thai camera man and editor    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca the UN is a cold war relic they will never solve anything    
    
    
    Great effort from Terasil!    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca lol, either way when Syria is "fixed" another North African country will go into chaos! Tunisia next    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca cant wait for us too have one! This country is more backwards than any other, capitolism is all about growth and growth is finite    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca while Assad is alive/in Syria they will live under it! If we arm the rebels it will be far worse! Just assasinate him    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca all UK is a bigger grain harvest and banking! We all still get taken for mugs by the Gov! UK will selfdestruct eventually    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca theres people at food banks in the UK, that shows how poorly run this nation is    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca america is the reason for most problems, they monopolise the world with thier 400m tonne grain harvest and their oil companies    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca good thing with Russia and china is that they are vast and if you want you can bugger off and live off the land! UK is tiny lol    
    
    
    people need to stop blaming ESPN for the camermen, they are almost certainly Thai along with the director!    
    
    
    @Bloodzeed you not doing the F1 anymore?    
    
    
    OH look @ESPNUK have just proved me right! As i have said the cameramen are THAI they arent ESPNs!    
    
    
    Borini and Allen are clear examples of the fact that Brendan shouldnt sign players he has worked with at Swansea    
    
    
    friendly off F1 on! ill watch the rest later    
    
    
    @Delveyboy your channel crashed my sopcast at the 1st corner and now it just crashes straight away if i reload the stream    
    
    
    @Delveyboy sweet mate    
    
    
    Tony Evans reckons it will take £55m too get Luis! GOOD!    
    
    
    I cant believe Borini dived in the friendly! he is so poor, so overrated, looks out of his depth just like Allen    
    
    
    Christian Benitez has died at 27???? Unbelievable! #RIP    
    
    
    is this Benitez death true? already seen conflicting stories!?    
    
    
    some sources say car crash others say appendicitis complications!? Whats going on? #Benitez #RIP    
    
    
    this Reina loan is looking a shocker from LFC, its all about money, FSG looking worse by the day!    
    
    
    @no1confused the problem is that they loaned Reina behind his back and signed a replacement based on assumptions that Barca want him    
    
    
    @no1confused had they not rushed out and signed Mignolet they wouldnt need too loan Reina and he may have been willing to negotiate contract    
    
    
    @no1confused form was sloppy and we were still 5th lowest conceded in the league, cant believe Brendan got rid based on form    
    
    
    @no1confused why was he not put up for sale then? cut losses style?    
    
    
    As if Juve would take Borini for Matri! Haha #dreaming    
    
    
    7m is way too low for Skrtek! Ok he wasnt great last season but player of season 1 before! Dont believe the Papa rumours!    
    
    
    @beni_henney i bet the majority of this offer is in instalments too    
    
    
    Skrtel on loan??? Have a word, what is the club up too, hes not a 21 year old!    
    
    
    whats this new "if you cant sell 'em, loan 'em" policy?? #LFC    
    
    
    Fair play if Real Madrid really are going to donate £85m too the Spurs Chimpanzee fund, we need too do more for endangered animals #Bale    
    
    
    @beni_henney Real always find a way too fork out millions    
    
    
    How much does Downing earn, hes got too be next out.... #superscrimpers #FSG    
    
    
    im sure some people will find a way to defend FSG for this money saving policy,    
    
    
    FSG say they are not selling but it damn sure looks like they are trying too balance the books and make the finances look good....    
    
    
    @7Tune just looks like an Astra VXR thats been squashed by an R8...........    
    
    
    i reckon our next 2 signings will be quite obscure under 24 year olds that cost under £7.5m.......... #LFC    
    
    
    HAHAAHAHA RAMOS DID LOOK LIKE BEAVIS NOW HE LOOKS LIKE BUTTHEAD HAHAHAHAHAH!    
    
    
    Oh look ive just seen a Konoplyanka too LFC link..... as i said obscure and under 24!    
    
    
    @timbolton1 waaaaaaaaaaaaaahhheyyyy    
    
    
    just imagine no CB comes in and Skrtel goes.... Agger, Kolo, Wisdom, Coates (he will probably be gone too)......    
    
    
    Yarmolenko now.... next we will be linked with Olegzander Chaepwazgyes    
    
    
    @greaney_michael @bruisedarcade we are nowhere near as small a club as Rangers, we actually have an international fan base.....    
    
    
    so according too LFC "Half-caste" is offensive??? have a word!    
    
    
    all MPs should live in Council Houses... we pay tax for them too have a nice gaff in a nice place so they take the piss and tax more!    
    
    
    @StupidFootball HAHAAA    
    
    
    @beni_henney obscure Steuea Bucharest player    
    
    
    @beni_henney no idea if he is any good, i missed most of the romanian league last season :| ... 6 foot, Centre Back, 23, was a Benfica youth    
    
    
    @niceguylfc joke mate! correct terminology? i always tick "other" on those "equality" forms, im not "mixed" anything im not fucking paint...    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca the press twists everything too suit their own agenda, that is what the press is, a manipulation tool    
    
    
    @timbolton1 WHAT??? "MAN UP" is banned? Im half tempted too walk into Anfield and shout all the words on the list..    
    
    
    John Barnes appears too be as deluded as the fans that think we can sign a Luis replacement with no european football and low wages....    
    
    
    @Pepsi2353 its french there will always be something wrong with it... lol    
    
    
    love too hear who this world class striker Barnes has got lined up...........    
    
    
    @lee_parnell @PaddyTaylor_ please dont tell me you are talking about Noahs Arc....    
    
    
    surely this Sterling loan rumour isnt true!    
    
    
    "Sterling has looked great in pre-season"......"Loan him we need to save money on wages"........"great idea"...... #LFCconvos    
    
    
    WHY DONT WE JUST PLAY STERLING AND SELL DOWNING???    
    
    
    @Corballyred loan too West Ham    
    
    
    i know what will make us consistent.... get rid of all the mature players and replace them with as many young players as possible.....#LFC    
    
    
    free till 13.00 @TonyBarretTimes on fans transfer influence http://blogs.thetimes.co.uk/section/the-game/104424/transfers-dont-get-caught-up-in-the-blame-game/?shareToken=8391b795f7f9fc527680ab8bf1e04c21 …    
    
    
    @SJview problem is that he has been repeatedly banned through his career and he will probably get banned again at some point    
    
    
    @beni_henney what u think about Caulker going? Is there a buy back deal?    
    
    
    Why cant they hurry up and imbed @Instagram into @twitter so I dont have to open a link to see the pic!!!    
    
    
    OMG does Ayew really want too join us? would definitely have him    
    
    
    whats happened at Doncaster??    
    
    
    oh some cock from 1D has joined Doncaster.... this is worse than when Wimbledon signed that guy from So Solid....    
    
    
    so SSN says Schalke have recieved no bids for Papa, no surprises there, i have always been confident its just another twitter signing..    
    
    
    Brendan has really covered his arse with this "money to spend on getting quality in, but if it's (quality) not available I won't waste it"    
    
    
    how many people have actually seen this guy from 1D play?? Id go with Sergio Pizzorno or that guy from JLS, both decent on #Socceraid......    
    
    
    theres on 1 DRS!!! Drag Reduction System! #F1 #AshesBoreOff    
    
    
    Roy Keane needs too come out of retirement NOW! #Doncaster #CareerEnder    
    
    
    @AdamDo_DaDay @SkySportsNews its his wife hahaha    
    
    
    @Green_Scouser i think he is shit, hope we dont go near him    
    
    
    £20m for Diego Costa?.................    
    
    
    The english media are going too love Diego Costa........................    
    
    
    Join my league http://fantasy.premierleague.com/my-leagues/207418/join/?autojoin-code=582083-207418 …    
    
    
    @BassTunedToRed @LFCTS should show games too! Hes played loads hardly scores    
    
    
    @BassTunedToRed @LFCTS no an assist isnt a goal... 31 appearances (2055 mins playing time) 10 goals last season = 205.5 mins per goal    
    
    
    @BassTunedToRed @LFCTS he was actually far better at Vallecano on loan    
    
    
    People seem too think if Suarez puts a transfer request in we will sell him too Arsenal    
    
    
    Selling Suarez too Arsenal would just put us even further away from CL than selling to Real as Arsenal are the 4th place team!    
    
    
    @no1confused I think 2 or 3 signings at least are needed! Not sure on Melaguero as a LB apparently he is more of a winger!    
    
    
    @no1confused cant see us finishing above 6th without Luis, still dont think we will get 4th with him! Need some shrewd deals with no euro    
    
    
    @no1confused strange we havent signed him! Clearly the logical move! Think Enrique would have a tough time aswell! Would improve him too    
    
    
    @BecciBoopLFC hopefully WHU will take him! He doesnt fit, the new signings just make him look more out of place    
    
    
    #TheSupportersClub    
    
    
    @JackSear its only 2 weeks away, whens he back in full training?    
    
    
    @JackSear yeah but when games are "winnable" thats when half the team doesnt show up and we draw or lose 1-0!    
    
    
    @okSuse that is an awful recommendation lol    
    
    
    @LFCFansCorner as if he would get a train...    
    
    
    @LFCamiArias2 has surprised me, hopefully he can continue it in the prem! A lot tougher    
    
    
    @stanic007 im watching, nothing at all has happened yet    
    
    
    Diego Costa has had about 2 touches, this game is nowhere near interesting enough too continue watching..........    
    
    
    Doctor Who? #BoreOff    
    
    
    more rumours Skrtels going, i still dont think Papa is going too be signed either, hes going too have too sign someone!    
    
    
    are they having that crazy 3 team match in Italy again this season?    
    
    
    Media's favourite word...........source! Which is basically, im going too quote you but not give you any credit or my story any credibility    
    
    
    The Echo says Suarez DID wave too the fans, now we are going too have too say he was waving bye instead of hes going cause he didnt wave....    
    
    
    @LFCNewsRumours1 @ConnorwilsonLFC Hes not smiling as much as you....hes going..... #TwitterLogic    
    
    
    @FitzgeraldNO5 @stanic007 we have blatantly been rejected by a few players    
    
    
    not too sure about Reina on Suarez saga! Hes been offloaded and he isnt happy so he is sticking his oar in!    
    
    
    @CoreyLH that pic was posted about 3 hours ago, it means absolutely nothing    
    
    
    @TrueKopites96 i dont see how Sturridge is going too start against Stoke if he is only going too play in the friendly against Celtic    
    
    
    @JoeScouse_LFC im literally on it now taking Sturridge out, hes not going too get any game time till Celtic, i wouldnt start him at Stoke    
    
    
    @CoreyLH im not but some tobys have been going on about it for hours, surprised you havent already seen it    
    
    
    @JoeScouse_LFC i can see Sturridge being injured on and off all season, never seems too be fit for more than a month    
    
    
    @CoreyLH people going on like he wouldnt do that much shopping if he was going.....like he cant afford too throw £100 worth of food away....    
    
    
    @AnfieldMatt WOWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW    
    
    
    how do people dig up these tweets from 2 years ago about footballers that have turned out shit    
    
    
    @LiverpoolFF @FootyHumour ive seen that tweet from a few others aswell!    
    
    
    @LJ_Barca thats more than weird... lol    
    
    
    i think we can get at least £7-8m for Downing, he was a lot better last season than in his first, total square peg at @LFC though    
    
    
    @RobVaughanYNWA far too uch of a traditional english winger, almost obsolete at top level nowadays, like Navas too City makes no sense    
    
    
    @lfcmaestro23 even if he is willing, i cant see anyone wanting to pay him more than 1/3 of what he is on now, that will cause probs    
    
    
    We should do a Downing and Assaidi double sale event! Get them both for £8m.........    
    
    
    @JoeyBurns87 Bo Selecta..........    
    
    
    Surely we should have said Downing is available for sale at the end of last season when his decent 2nd half was fresh in peoples minds    
    
    
    i think its well a low fee for Downing, but realistically it will probably be hard too sell him, Stoke might have him.....    
    
    
    ive downloaded and listened too so much of Marty on @WHYY im now listening too shows from 2009....    
    
    
    These "breaking (insert stupid transfer here)" tweets are already boring......    
    
    
    Id give NUFC 8-10m + Downing for Ben Arfa!    
    
    
    How can Suarez take LFC too court if he hasnt even handed in a transfer request? Judge would surely throw it out    
    
    
    @Corballyred you would have said that about Messi when he joined Barca, always pull hamstring, changed training now rarely injured..    
    
    
    @Corballyred i think recurring muscle injuries can be dealt with, with a higher quality of physio and training, something we have over NUFC    
    
    
    @Corballyred they would never let a frenchman leave the revolution anyway lol    
    
    
    @Zizouology people seem too forget the UK is a major hub too european nations? Loads of indirect flights go thru Heather    
    
    
    @dom_campbell he needs to learn when too pass, he gives the ball away far too often! When he plays shit its really bad!    
    
    
    Suarez needs too stop being immature and hand in a transfer request! Interviews just looks desperate! Hasnt got a leg too stand on!    
    
    
    @emmamcdonnellll @CiaraGissane what a shout! "They are so chocolaty that they turn the milk.........white!!" lol    
    
    
    @LFC @LFCNorwegian what a shed!!!    
    
    
    I wonder what Suarez is doing right now..... probably sulking    
    
    
    @stanic007 he cant possibly go too court until he has handed in a transfer request, no way would his lawyer advice these interviews either    
    
    
    @Sennesation yeah if only it was him that was trying to engineer a move lol    
    
    
    credit @Adam_Holland_ where i got my idea for my name    
    
    
    @FitzgeraldNO5 well said, Torres left with far more dignity than Suarez will, at least it was relatively low key when Torres jumped    
    
    
    @BazLFC19 @Robbie9Fowler no way    
    
    
    id definitely leave Suarez in the reserves over selling him too Arsenal #NoBrainer    
    
    
    @aaaprilLFC we will struggle too sign them is the real problem    
    
    
    AHAAAAAA Spearing at RB HAHAHHAHA    
    
    
    BT Sport, Sky Sports and ESPN..... yeah because im going too pay for 3 channels so i cant watch football............NOT #stream    
    
    
    acestream is twaff though... ive got disgustingly fast Virgin internet and it still lags, sopcast fine as usual, think ill watch in spanish    
    
    
    sopcast time, acestream still manages too lag even with ridiculous Virgin internet, cant bare it    
    
    
    Coates is nowhere near as bad as people make out, dont know what people expect from a young CB that plays 12 games a season....    
    
    
    Valerengas goalkeeper playing with a smile! got too love that!    
    
    
    Loving this Valerenga keeper!    
    
    
    @LFCFansCorner this is the only 25 mins ive ever seen him play and i love him lol    
    
    
    @KopMatt 37,000 fans in Norway is a bloody good turnout!    
    
    
    THIS FUCKING KEEPER IS EPIC!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    albertooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo    
    
    
    FUCK YOU SUAREZ!    
    
    
    Alberto has come too life, he looked really lethargic in the 1st friendly!    
    
    
    went too get my dinner out the over now its 1-1.............................................    
    
    
    You can literally see the relief on Aspas face when he scored that!    
    
    
    @KopMatt i think its 27k, the commentator said 37 but the stadium record is 35k apparently    
    
    
    @KaneD101 decent but thier goalkeeper has had a stormer it could be 4 or 5-1 if it wasnt for him in goal!    
    
    
    ill reserve my judgement on Allen for when he plays in the prem!    
    
    
    id rather we had a game or two against bigger european sides too, just playing these sort of game lulls players into false sence of ability    
    
    
    @CoreyLH lol whaaaat haha! im good!    
    
    
    