Watched "little miss sunshine" again - always good...    
    
    
    Everybody who writes code in #java should read "Concurrency in practice" by Brian Goetz e.a.    
    
    
    @aneeshs @shilpa_26 How cute! Congratulations!! :)    
    
    
    Toooooooooooooooooooooor!!! #BVB 1-0    
    
    
    @gomikael @miguelrios @monicaquiroz @lija OMG, Lina didn't win the beer competition? With all the German training?    
    
    
    @lija vermutlich haben die ganzen prozesskosten weit mehr als 510 Euro gekostet. #sinnlosebürokratie    
    
    
    @flo did you win?    
    
    
    @flo I agree. it's been like this for a long time, can't believe they don't fix it    
    
    
    @BVBDortmund09 Love your media gallery! #bvb http://twitter.com/#!/BVBDortmund09/media/grid …  Thanks @caramev and team!    
    
    
    Weiss noch nicht Sind grad im hq    
    
    
    Just sent out the #ZURBwired application for #literacybridge in the last minute! YAY! Everyone has to cross their fingers now!    
    
    
    Spektakuläre Notlandung: Flugzeug kracht in deutsche Kleinstadt - SPIEGEL ONLINE - http://spon.de/adrQO     
    
    
    OH: IntelliJ is slow. Really slow. Sometimes it cannot keep up with my typing.    
    
    
    12:45 in the office: OH it's not too bad - there's just one chair that has beer on it. #augtoberfest #justanotherdayatwork    
    
    
    After desperately watching the rain going by for 45 mins, knowing I forgot the umbrella: sunshine in san francisco! thanks, universe :)    
    
    
    NB Caltrain broke down at California ave.  No estimate how long it's gonna take to fix it.    
    
    
    We're moving again!  (why do I always tweet about the caltrain???)    
    
    
    On top of Mt. Etna ... http://yfrog.com/kj41yhonj     
    
    
    Today I got bitten by a grumpy horse in front of the Pantheon. #rome #meanhorse    
    
    
    @jennadawn where are you going?    
    
    
    Immigration officer at SFO when he noticed twitter in my visa: "you're like a god to people, everyone loves you!" @jointheflock    
    
    
    Excited to see @nutmegthedog after two weeks soon! :)    
    
    
    I can't believe I have 49,988 miles @UnitedAirlines. I need 50,000 for the next membership level! Why is there no flight SJC->SFO? :(    
    
    
    @BVBDortmund09 Herzlichen Glückwunsch zu 15.000 Followers! Das nächste Ziel sollte 80.720 sein :) #bvb    
    
    
    @gsingers @ingorenner Thanks, guys! United distinguishes between status miles and bonus miles and unfortunately you can only buy bonus miles    
    
    
    @ingorenner Yeah I think I'll really call them and ask. I'll start with 0 status miles 1/1/11 again, so I really want to get that upgrade :)    
    
    
    Still awake and coding at #zurbwired...    
    
    
    @ej Happy Birthday!!!    
    
    
    #HowToTrainYourDragon was really awesome! Just watched it in 3D. Such a cute dragon!    
    
    
    Goodbye, Steve. We will miss and never forget you.    
    
    
    #java6: DataOutputStream#size() returns a 32 bit int. javadoc: "If the counter overflows, it will be wrapped to Integer.MAX_VALUE." #2011    
    
    
    If I hadn't know before already, the napkins at the #chirp party would have convinced me that Twitter is the coolest company out there!    
    
    
    @omrvp I love the memory model changes! C++ 11    
    
    
    my two most recent emails #icloud pic.twitter.com/80gJKx8s    
    
    
    Munich airport welcomes me. pic.twitter.com/gn6UC4YG    
    
    
    Cute plane. Now back to Amsterdam. Looking at a map, this is a quite inefficient trip so far :) pic.twitter.com/psixUPhO    
    
    
    Never had to assemble a fork in a plane before. Also, still working on my slides for my #lucene talk in a few hours. :) pic.twitter.com/IHF0ZBQh    
    
    
    @mwessendorf yep, will be there tomorrow. Just arrived at schiphol    
    
    
    First food I saw in Munich: weisswurst and beer. schiphol: a gigantic chocolate globe! pic.twitter.com/z5ESDgLF    
    
    
    @mwessendorf bummer :( come to the #lucene conf in Barcelona next week?    
    
    
    You come to the office and there's bacon waiting for you!  Can a day start better?!    
    
    
    @mdo but... then I would probably eat less BACON - that wouldn't be a better day! :)    
    
    
    @abdur you were in amsterdam? So was I, left yesterday evening. Bummer we didn't hang out!    
    
    
    Next part of my trip: from Nottuln to Barcelona! pic.twitter.com/f9eKSS00    
    
    
    seriously @germanwings ? One checkin person for this many people? #lame pic.twitter.com/2DRUg6VN    
    
    
    Cool, looks like the referees of the barca game tonight are checked into the same hotel and having breakfast right now too!    
    
    
    Camp nou. 25 mins till the champions league game starts! #barca pic.twitter.com/LqRtu18g    
    
    
    Ich werde aber natürlich dem BVB die daumen drücken, auch wenn ich ausnahmsweise mal in Camp Nou bin! @BVBDortmund09 Auf geht's Dortmund!    
    
    
    @adrianocrestani yes, it sucks (TM)  :)    
    
    
    @adrianocrestani awesome that you'll finally read that book!  Maybe you'll become a good programmer after all ;)    
    
    
    Just came back from a nice run with @nutmegthedog, and now we're very hungry and waiting for @maybefriday to bring us some Indian food!    
    
    
    Twitter search guys with @ConanOBrien!  He was awesome! http://yfrog.com/joyadj    
    
    
    I have never seen such a long line of people waiting for busses at 3.45am! #bigsurmarathon    
    
    
    We're taking you now to the start line of the best marathon on the planet. -- bus announcement    
    
    
    Oh my gosh, I don't remember any race hurting as much as the #bigsurmarathon. Not even the ironman 08. I guess that was in a different life    
    
    
    C'mon caltrain move faster! Only a few hours till @BVBDortmund09 plays against the vfb. Thank you @lija for organizing such a great evening!    
    
    
    @lija yeah the weather was perfect! It was really fun!    
    
    
    @nurisahin05 Congrats, Nuri! Now you can finally show them how good you are! Best wishes from a BVB fan! :)    
    
    
    Man the new gmail interface is really terrible. How can I go back to the old one?    
    
    
    @crunch09 thanks! I always clicked on the wrong gears symbol. There are two now on the right upper side. Even those are not user friendly :)    
    
    
    @mikeyk Hey Mike, would be happy to drop by to talk about lucene. I'm working on Twitter's realtime index that's based on lucene.    
    
    
    @monicaquiroz @lija you should invite other international tweeps to your offsites :) #hint    
    
    
    @nutmegthedog has a sophisticated understanding of probability.  -- @maybefriday    
    
    
    @skf well if you could you would probably like what you would be seeing    
    
    
    @sm we all would be nothing without you.    
    
    
    Just found out that US $ bills survive the washer and dryer pretty well actually. I'm impressed.    
    
    
    @jreichhold "working from home" today    
    
    
    Beer is the best medicine.    
    
    
    Thanks @UnitedAirlines for upgrading me even though I was a few miles short!!  And I didn't even have to call :)    
    
    
    @BVBDortmund09 Unglaublich wie um jeden einzelnen Ball gekämpft wird! Ich bin stolz auf euch, egal wie das Spiel ausgeht!    
    
    
    TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOR!!!! @GoetzeOfficial @BVBDortmund09    
    
    
    @mwessendorf das kannst du laut sagen! :)    
    
    
    Heavy rain and a storm seems to be coming in. Should be an interesting flight lesson! :) pic.twitter.com/BMscdyMB    
    
    
    @sm no worries, my instructor used to be bush pilot in Alaska. He thinks this was easy weather :)    
    
    
    @monicaquiroz thanks! It was actually an awesome day for flying. Rain and gusts in the beginning, sunshine and rainbows in the end!    
    
    
    Had a great run. Fresh, crisp air after a rain in the fall - doesn't get much better than that for running. pic.twitter.com/5juTEJki    
    
    
    OH: Now I have to go give an autograph to the guy I spanked.    
    
    
    @thomasarend wow! did you bake them all yourself?    
    
    
    Finally, after 10 hours of driving and countless coffees, arrived in San Diego!  #happythanksgiving    
    
    
    Happy birthday @nutmegthedog!! Cutest dog in the world!    
    
    
    @isasun @katies @lija @thomasarend wow really? It has the autographs?! Super awesome :) thank you!! #bvb    
    
    
    @thomasarend @isasun @katies @lija yes you did!! Doing my bvb-happy-dance now :) thanks so much! Are you still in Dortmund? Game tomorrow?    
    
    
    Legoland! pic.twitter.com/AJ7edawD    
    
    
    Didn't think I'd get to play in the snow today in sunny San diego! #happykids pic.twitter.com/hW1mUU9n    
    
    
    @lija ja es war ein toller tag! Haben sogar San Francisco gesehen ... aus Lego :) pic.twitter.com/9D0Fyg84    
    
    
    Next project after legoland: build a Lego truck! pic.twitter.com/znJPtYS2    
    
    
    @lija you saw dolphins?    
    
    
    Mission accomplished. pic.twitter.com/JKSQCSbV    
    
    
    @KatieS @isasun @lija if you need someone to verify that it tastes authentic, I'd volunteer! :)    
    
    
    The new #literacybridge website is live! Thank you @maybefriday, @jebritton, @smileyj68, @mdo!  http://www.literacybridge.org    
    
    
    @mabb0tt @kpcb congrats Mike! Sounds exciting!    
    
    
    Waiting for my Kassler with Sauerkraut, while drinking a Köstritzer.    
    
    
    Just looked out of the launch room's window and saw a huge swarm of birds. Coincidence? #LetsFly    
    
    
    @Ellen_Friedman Thanks, Ellen! Hope you like it! :)    
    
    
    Cool plane we saw the other day during a flight lesson lunch break in hollister. pic.twitter.com/9QTvah4T    
    
    
    Happy birthday @maybefriday!  :)    
    
    
    From "What's new?" in IntelliJ 11: "lag-less typing even in huge documents" 2011: the year my computer started to keep up with my typing.    
    
    
    YES! I'm at the peak of my twitter career! Klout says I'm influential about one topic: Beer! #proud #germany    
    
    
    @lija so mean! #dontjudgepeoplebytheirtypos    
    
    
    @nutmegthedog is an excellent guard dog! She professionally protects the apartment from fire alarm inspectors.    
    
    
    @sunghu @thomasarend Yes, I'm a huge @bvb fan! Mats and Mario are very awesome players. :) Do you like them too?    
    
    
    @flo why was I not your date again? Are you cheating on me?    
    
    
    Fire alarm at 2:45am. Yay. #needsleep @nutmegthedog is enjoying the extra walk though :) pic.twitter.com/b9V89dRy    
    
    
    Himmel-Safari per Cessna - Namibias Skelettküste von oben http://spon.de/adxba     
    
    
    @isasun @katies @lija @thomasarend @jolanta aww so much snow! I miss winters in Germany!    
    
    
    Ein neues Wort heute gelernt: Ultraschall-Flatrate! :)    
    
    
    A happy dog riding and sniffing along on highway no 1. /cc @nutmegthedog pic.twitter.com/Dw6o1Guq    
    
    
    Javadoc of Java's Calendar class: "The first month of the year is JANUARY which is 0; the last depends on the number of months in a year."    
    
    
    @jebritton @selina_w happy birthday!! Sounds like you had a great weekend!    
    
    
    NyQuil cold medicine definitely tastes better than root beer.    
    
    
    Brille, Bier, Borussia: Dortmunds Titeljahr - Bundesliga - Bildergalerie - kicker online http://www.kicker.de/news/fussball/bundesliga/startseite/562511/2/slideshow_brille-bier-borussia_dortmunds-titeljahr.html …    
    
    
    In the plane on my way to Germany...    
    
    
    Arrived in Stuttgart and am watching Germany vs. Bosnia now!  0-1 so far, but just 35 mins played so far.  GO GERMANY!!    
    
    
    Germany-Bosnia 1-1!  What a nice goal from Lahm!    
    
    
    Germany-Bosnia 2-1!  Penalty shot, Schweinsteiger    
    
    
    Another penalty. Schweinsteiger again, 3-1!    
    
    
    Just got Rocksmith and connected my dusty guitar to the PS3 - it's pretty awesome! Remember this day when you see me on stage someday! :)    
    
    
    .@nutmegthedog just farted so loudly that she startled herself and ran to the other side of the room. #TMI    
    
    
    Arrived today in Berlin for #berlinbuzzwords.  Looking forward to good talks at an awesome looking venue!    
    
    
    @Ellen_Friedman Cool, I have my first groupie! Well, maybe @nutmegthedog  is one too :)    
    
    
    C'mon #checkstyle! "Boolean expression complexity is 14 (max allowed is 4)." Let me express myself the way I want to!    
    
    
    Have to quickly tweet from 35309 feet before I eat my "Lemon & Pepper Seasoned Tuna Medley". First flight with @VirginAmerica. AWESOME!    
    
    
    Wagemutige Weltumrundung: Abenteurer fliegt alleine einmal um die Erde - SPIEGEL ONLINE - Nachrichten - Reise http://spon.de/adyj3     
    
    
    I'm less than an hour in NYC, and less than 10 mins in a cab, but already in a traffic jam. :)    
    
    
    @chrisrueger #berlinbuzzwords IP is now whitelisted, there should be no rate limit problem anymore.    
    
    
    @techno @gakuueda Yes it is! Very fun to go to work these days! :)    
    
    
    Back in california on my way to work after a great trip to #berlinbuzzwords with lots of super nice people! Thanks all who made this happen!    
    
    
    Watching espn!  So excited that the worldcup is finally starting.  7am games aren't so bad if you have a jetlag :)    
    
    
    Go #RSA!  What a great goal! 1-0    
    
    
    @mwessendorf hey sorry ich bin in NYC. Trotzdem: HEJA BVB! :)    
    
    
    @sm @rymatic @emblem__ thank god the wheel of shots was broken. And that everyone was wearing pants.    
    
    
    @mwessendorf twitter hat hier jetzt ein office und ich hab zwei Wochen lang da gearbeitet.    
    
    
    Watching the #GER game from Santa Rosa, ca. Of course with beer, not wine! 2-0. Go Germany, my tipp was 4-0!    
    
    
    Standing in front of the ruins of Jack london's wolf house. 10 years ago I wrote a biography about him. Interesting to finally see it now.    
    
    
    @thetaph1 yes! Great game!    
    
    
    Oh man, I need the #bundesliga winterbreak to recover too! 6.30am is too early.  Anyway, GO #BVB!!    
    
    
    OH: Not sure why this isn't working... hmmm... ooh, I know why! I haven't finished implementing the backend yet! /cc @sam    
    
    
    I just voted for Literacy Bridge to win 25k on Chase Community Giving! #chasegiving http://bit.ly/9Ipaqi    
    
    
    In Germany at a Autobahn rest stop, drinking coffee and watching the snow falling. Cold but nice here. #welcomehome    
    
    
    Cool TV in my hotel room! Objects in this picture may appear bigger than they are. pic.twitter.com/m5uCS9dP    
    
    
    Nicht traurig sein #BVB. Ihr habt eine unglaubliche Hinrunde gespielt und alle Fans sind stolz auf euch!    
    
    
    @lija I hope you didn't encounter any Stinktiere.    
    
    
    The end of a crazy week with @isasun! I think we spent more hours on trains/planes than in hotel rooms. :) It was a lot of fun!    
    
    
    "interesting" morning that started at with a fire alarm and continued with an earthquake in #mountainview. Also, @nutmegthedog had diarrhea.    
    
    
    And I also spilled coffee on my laptop - ironically before, not during the earthquake    
    
    
    @krishnagade was at about 9:30am. Yeah it was quite scary, the walls were shaking twice!    
    
    
    My little niece is in there! I felt her kicking for the first time! Feels like she's already a very strong girl :) pic.twitter.com/D1aUOy3m    
    
    
    My little niece is in there! I felt her kicking for the first time! Feels like she's already a very strong girl :) pic.twitter.com/DeuKUNaG    
    
    
    Retweet this & @Bing will donate $10 to @CNN's Gulf Telethon up to $100K. More at http://bit.ly/howtodonate. #BingforGulf    
    
    
    @isasun es war super! 1-0 gewonnen! #bvbb04 #echteliebe @BVB    
    
    
    Secret service agents really do have those curly things in their ears and wear suits.    
    
    
    Great to see the president of Russia tweeting at Twitter HQ today. Have a nice stay in the Silicon Valley, Mr. Medvedev! @KremlinRussia    
    
    
    1-0 for #ger! Just came back from Pete's Tavern where several Germans were watching the game and celebrated! England, we're coming...    
    
    
    @LiteracyBridge Well, luckily both #GER and #GHA are both in the next round! :)    
    
    
    Building the #lego #mindstorms alpha rex robot together with @maybefriday.  @nutmegthedog is not very impressed...    
    
    
    Until yesterday I believed the mac made every aspect of my digital life better. Then I made a 230k svn patch without tortoise merge...    
    
    
    Not 230k bytes, but 230k lines.    
    
    
    @smileyj68 I think I'll modify twitter to reject any tweets that contain the terrible word "prolly".  @maybefriday will thank me too.    
    
    
    This is were I used to go every other week: http://bit.ly/c1chPj #BVB. Now I have to get up at 6 to watch soccer! #soccerunfriendlytimezone    
    
    
    What a day    
    
    
    @KatieS @fass4 @isasun Well, too bad that no matter how that game ends FCB will still be behind the BEST GERMAN TEAM @BVB !! :)    
    
    
    @DJanecek Hi Dieter, auf dieser Liste sind einige Spieler zu finden: https://twitter.com/#!/twitter_de/bundesliga/members …    
    
    
    @EinAugenschmaus good news - hoffentlich zieht Deutschland nach: http://techcrunch.com/2012/03/01/netflix-gets-serious-about-closed-captioning/ …    
    
    
    I paid $180 for a monthly pass and today got a citation because your system doesn't work @BayAreaClipper and @caltrain. #customerservice    
    
    
    @mikesonn @mccv @Caltrain_News The wasted time is really what I'm angry about. I wonder what can be done to fix that broken system.    
    
    
    @mikesonn @mccv @Caltrain_News Didn't kick me off, but gave citation. No I have more than $1.25. The March ticket didn't show up at all.    
    
    
    #gha you played great and should be proud!    
    
    
    @KatieS @bvb @1fsvmainz05 thanks Katie :) yes I'm still celebrating here! :)    
    
    
    Finally arrived in San Diego after 9 hour drive. Now two hours of sleep before we're heading to a German Biergarten to watch #worldcup!!    
    
    
    @DFB_Team Wir druecken euch von San Diego aus die Daumen. Schiesst Argentinien die Bude voll! Wir sind stolz auf euch, egal wie's ausgeht!    
    
    
    People waiting in line at 6.20 at #kaiserhof in San Diego to watch the Germany game! http://yfrog.com/3mq3nzj    
    
    
    This is so awesome! #ger http://yfrog.com/eau6eaj    
    
    
    @Caltrain_News @mccv @mikesonn Hi, I emailed details to the provided email address. Thanks.    
    
    
    @lija @isasun @techno @KatieS I didn't feel it either. But I was probably too far away anyway.    
    
    
    @monica @bvb they are! 7 points ahead of the 2nd! :) #echteliebe    
    
    
    Today I found out that @nutmegthedog does not like shrimp, even though she likes fish.    
    
    
    Today I landed a Citabria at San Jose International!  They told us to watch out for wake turbulences of Boings and Airbuses! #awesome    
    
    
    @asonneck @isasun Ist behoben! Zeitzonen können kompliziert sein: http://www.differencebetween.com/difference-between-pdt-and-vs-pst/ … Vielen Dank! Wir wünschen einen guten Spieltag! :)    
    
    
    The adventure begins... pic.twitter.com/NedX5fUu    
    
    
    Highway no 1 from 5500 feet. It's a beautiful day! First stop: Oceano pic.twitter.com/z8vzruPd    
    
    
    Kingman, Arizona, 9500ft. Grand canyon in the background. pic.twitter.com/OhOflPe1    
    
    
    Lots of DHL planes parked here pic.twitter.com/x89ECoeu    
    
    
    Final destination for today: Seligman, on route 66. Enjoying the first beers in the downtown bar :) pic.twitter.com/zMcq3t51    
    
    
    There's even a Stammtisch in Seligman at Lilo's :) pic.twitter.com/6ut5vtDu    
    
    
    Too windy for flying, driving trucks on dirt roads instead! :) pic.twitter.com/UGvJSZsE    
    
    
    On our way home. pic.twitter.com/cuk3GJuA    
    
    
    @lija Wow, did you draw that?    
    
    
    Das Spiel ist aus! Deutscher Meister wird nur der @BVB!!!    
    
    
    Thank you!!!!! What a day :)  #bvbfcb @maybefriday    
    
    
    Das wars fcb :)  #echteliebe #bvbfcb @BVB pic.twitter.com/c8aLeuX8    
    
    
    If the stewardess encourages the passengers to give a SECOND round of applause you've been in a pretty rough landing :) welcome to JFK!    
    
    
    Also, people around me are calling their families and telling them that they were convinced they'd die.    
    
    
    @marius yeah pretty gusty and very rainy here    
    
    
    Wow the #Lucene meetup is in a very cool location!  http://yfrog.com/5ngj2lj    
    
    
    @gsingers awesome, looking forward to seeing you there, Grant!    
    
    
    Yay!  8GB RAM upgrade.    
    
    
    Viele Grüße zurück aus Mountain View! @isasun #BVBFCB #Pokalfinale Drücke @BVB die Daumen!! :)    
    
    
    Tooooooooooooooooor!!! @BVB #BVBFCB    
    
    
    @ZDF Kommentator: "Dortmund führt den FC Bayern vor!!" 4-1 #BVBFCB @BVB    
    
    
    #Pokalsieger! @BVB #BVBFCB pic.twitter.com/ohNaxafb    
    
    
    @techno @rowbar @BVB Ja ich bin am feiern! Unglaubliches Spiel!! :)    
    
    
    Happy birthday @nutmegthedog!! pic.twitter.com/RenBeZly    
    
    
    That was one of the most undeserved goals I have ever seen in my life by Drogba. #ChampionsLeague    
    
    
    Sorry #FCB. Today even I admit that you would have deserved to win. At least you didn't play destructively and unattractively like Chelsea.    
    
    
    Respekt #Sky Kommentator! Chelsea's Trainer geht einfach weg nach der Frage: "Ihr Fußball ist effizient, aber finden sie ihn auch schön?" :)    
    
    
    Move to SF: check    
    
    
    Now it's officially confirmed: I moved into a good neighborhood! pic.twitter.com/zUhHKnii    
    
    
    OH: I downloaded the wrong cowsay cc @larsonite    
    
    
    @MarcManiez thanks, Marc. Yes was a fun evening! Have a good trip too!    
    
    
    Impressive how many people were necessary to direct me to my seat! :) The A380 is indeed a big plane.    
    
    
    Germany here I come! Looking forward to meeting a very special person soon...    
    
    
    This is the newest A380 that Lufthansa has. Just 3 weeks old. Good, makes it more likely that the wings don't have the infamous cracks yet.    
    
    
    3 live outside cameras. That is pretty cool! pic.twitter.com/5ppmUcUU    
    
    
    @Ellen_Friedman oh cool! Yeah that's where I'm headed. See you in Berlin!    
    
    
    Wow a go-around in a 380 on VERY short final. Cool, but also a little scary how late they realized that another plane was on the runway!    
    
    
    @rusashka @marcmaniez we just didn't mention it explicitly since it goes without saying that you're responsible for all the awesomeness! :)    
    
    
    @laura @MarcManiez @nsallembien @miguelrios yep I'm awake too :) very bright outside already in berlin. #iloveearlymornings    
    
    
    @hypertable 16.7M docs is the max. size for one Lucene index segment, not the size of the entire index. #pleasequotecorrectly    
    
    
    My favorite part about #bbuzz? The people. Looking forward to seeing all of you next time!    
    
    
    Just an hour left, but 2010 could still become the first year ever in which I do karaoke... drink, michael, drink faster!    
    
    
    2010, this is the last piece of "art" you make me look at? Really?    
    
    
    @michibusch  http://yfrog.com/gy5o4uj    
    
    
    @larsonite hey you can't go to bed 30 mins before midnight! Be brave!    
    
    
    Piano man did it. And Bacardi-coke    
    
    
    Endlich geht es los! #Euro2012    
    
    
    Bisher waren nur Spieler des @BVB an 100% aller Tore der #Euro2012 beteiligt! :)    
    
    
    @Konni Ja, die rote Karte war wirklich überflüssig.    
    
    
    @mwessendorf Gerne! Für ein Bier bin ich immer zu haben :)    
    
    
    Russia played really impressively. I wouldn't be surprised if they got pretty far in the tournament this time. #Euro2012 /cc @rusashka    
    
    
    My new years wish: I want to see a polar bear in the wild.    
    
    
    I left Germany 7 years ago. Today I met my two best friends. It feels like not a single day has passed. Life is good. :)    
    
    
    I think the Italians are already champions in singing their national anthem most passionately! :) #Euro2012    
    
    
    TOOOOOOOOOOOORRRR!!! 1-0 Germany!    
    
    
    @lija Awwwwwwwww :)    
    
    
    Erkenntnis des Tages: Deutscher Tütencappuccino hat tatsächlich Koffein, nicht nur extra viel Löffelschaum. #sleeplessImSauerland /cc @lija    
    
    
    @mwessendorf Auf jeden Fall!! Hab schon meine Karte fuer den 14. Mai :)    
    
    
    @monica congrats, Monica! :) Well deserved, it was a really impressive match!    
    
    
    Thanks for letting me solo today and the impressive artwork @CFI_Erik! :) /cc @goodflying #N9091L pic.twitter.com/lR8gVhq4    
    
    
    @n8agrin you should see me playing tennis.    
    
    
    $ man yes: 
NAME
     yes -- be repetitively affirmative
/cc @zhenghuali @wangtian    
    
    
    Please! Someone has to help @SelfAwareROOMBA!    
    
    
    @deliprao great time! Why did your doctor tell you not to run?    
    
    
    @hannaschaer @schaer yep I saw his SMS! The anticipation is killing me! :)    
    
    
    If they were on the same planet I think @marscuriosity and @selfawareroomba may hook up...    
    
    
    Awesome meeting @rainnwilson today!  Looking forward to enjoying the questions in #soulpancake!  http://yfrog.com/h5tbxxj    
    
    
    .@Popcorn_Indiana On the kettlecorn bag you're saying: "Our plan is to make people really, really happy." #success! :)    
    
    
    Watch "Cliff Schmidt: On-demand access to knowledge for the poor" Video at TED2013 #TEDTalentSearch http://talentsearch.ted.com/video/Cliff-Schmidt-On-demand-access#.UEAsdDc9buc.twitter …    
    
    
    @isasun @twitter_de @rowbar @lija @dhensen @katies @techno Congrats, Isa!! A good day for twitter! :) see you soon in Berlin    
    
    
    I guess that's what they do at an airport when the major airline goes on a strike. #FRA pic.twitter.com/qNhzqXIE    
    
    
    If you like your feet don't get seat 75H on lufthansa's A380    
    
    
    My little 3 months old nephew Lias! :) #proud and #happy pic.twitter.com/05Rw9jgt    
    
    
    @s1m0nw yep, gut gelandet und schon fast auf dem Weg nach Berlin. :)    
    
    
    @miguelrios yes! Can't wait for it to start. Go @BVB!!    
    
    
    @EinAugenschmaus @techno @lija @isasun @katies @dhensen It was great having you here! Keep your fingers crossed for @BVB tonight! :)    
    
    
    hello @thetaph1 - nice hanging out yesterday!    
    
    
    This was a very very good week so far - for multiple reasons.    
    
    
    It finally happened: I dreamed about code deploys last night.  At the same time a mosquito tried to kill me - unfortunately a real one.    
    
    
    Wenn bei der #Stadtwette das @BVB Logo nachgestellt würde, wäre ich schon längst auf dem Weg. #Wettendass    
    
    
    OH: I wasn't playing chess in the meeting, it was in the bathroom!    
    
    
    @lija Gute Hutwahl, Hut ab!    
    
    
    @_hossman Wow 15 months. Time flies, doesn't it?! :)    
    
    
    @smiley really?! 10/11/12 13:14? Congrats!! Very very cute :)    
    
    
    Greencard: check.    
    
    
    #TheBlackSwan was really good and Natalie Portman was absolutely incredible. I don't often leave the theater that exhausted - in a good way!    
    
    
    Dance! http://youtu.be/ERbvKrH-GC4     
    
    
    Propellor confused the panorama thing a bit, but clouds still look really cool. pic.twitter.com/AHwrjDN8    
    
    
    Wer wird Deutscher Meister? BVB BORUSSIA! Wer wird Deutscher Meister? BORUSSIA BVB!!! #bvb    
    
    
    Just got $3 change: one $2 bill, and a $1 coin. #unusual    
    
    
    OMG Tooooooooooooooooor!!! @BVB 1-0    
    
    
    Spitzenreiter der Gruppe D: @BVB! #todesgruppe #echteliebe    
    
    
    This is gonna be interesting... :) pic.twitter.com/9frlPgtF    
    
    
    A few loopings later, I'm still alive pic.twitter.com/rRJPrH1P    
    
    
    @zhenghuali luckily, unlike while driving, they don't ticket you for that :)    
    
    
    @LiteracyBridge Exciting!  Would be cool if you tweeted some pictures of the new office!!    
    
    
    Foggiest place on earth! :) #pointreyes #lucky pic.twitter.com/h6ASpNhr    
    
    
    Enjoying the view @nutmegthedog pic.twitter.com/BdUhnhMl    
    
    
    Back in #sf pic.twitter.com/E6agdHrh    
    
    
    @fgcallari Just an iphone actually. Pretty cool how good its new camera is!    
    
    
    @ablegrape @nutmegthedog Well, I think it's time for you to come back to California! :)    
    
    
    @lija Ne, noch nicht. War mein erster Acrobatic-Flug. Hat Spaß gemacht!    
    
    
    @sportschau #1 wird der @BVB, und wo der FCB landet ist dann eigentlich auch egal. :)    
    
    
    You know that you're doing something truly boring, if the laundry, that you're doing in parallel, is the much more interesting activity.    
    
    
    Unbelievable @BVB! You guys are already heros!    
    
    
    Und immer noch: Spitzenreiter @BVB! :)    
    
    
    First pain free run in over two months. Muscles seem to finally be healing. Only 20 mins, but makes me very happy. #thelittlethings    
    
    
    @ablegrape Looks like I pulled my adductor muscles and ignored it for a bit too long. How about you?    
    
    
    @ablegrape ouch! Glad it's getting better!    
    
    
    Watching Rachel @maddow video: Time for the right to leave the bubble -   http://video.msnbc.msn.com/the-rachel-maddow-show/49736294 … via @msnbc    
    
    
    @oelmo http://www.great-wall-marathon.com  ? :)    
    
    
    @isasun Hmm :) mal schauen... am liebsten mal ganz woanders laufen: http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2012/01/23/top-10-marathons-worth-traveling-for/ …    
    
    
    Look what gem I found in the mission! Worth buying a record player? :) /cc @lija @isasun @techno pic.twitter.com/iXRnNyOu    
    
    
    @EinAugenschmaus hahaha! :)    
    
    
    When the same person manages to almost run me over twice within 2 mins, at 2 intersections I question the effectiveness of CA driving tests.    
    
    
    @jelder @bdarfler Sorry for the delay.  It's online now: https://www.box.net/shared/hivdg1hge9    
    
    
    @huettermann most surprising here is that this class has >230 lines :)    
    
    
    So exciting to finally see the MIT!   http://yfrog.com/6uthetj    
    
    
    @ablegrape thank you for the fantastic pizzas and wines.  I really enjoyed the nice evening!    
    
    
    Good morning San Francisco. pic.twitter.com/oNbZoTa4    
    
    
    Sensationeller Fallrückzieher: Die große Vier-Tore-Show des Zlatan Ibrahimovic http://spon.de/vflqU  via @SPIEGELONLINE    
    
    
    Very very proud that a coworker just rated me on her "favorite coworker" scale higher than 10!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EbVKWCpNFhY …    
    
    
    YAY! So happy for @LiteracyBridge right now, winner of #thetechawards!!    
    
    
    @jewelia oh man, are the pictures embarrassing? :)    
    
    
    Really? The guy who pushes for the very sad anti-nudity law in SF is called Weiner? http://www.cnn.com/2012/11/21/us/california-san-francisco-nudity/index.html … #undressEveryone!    
    
    
    Heute spielt @MarioGoetze absolute Weltklasse! 2-0 für @BVB!!    
    
    
    Gruppensieg! Sehr, sehr stolz auf meinen @BVB!! :)    
    
    
    @plok @suppenkuche @twittersearch you're welcome! one of my major skills is to setup beer-focused events :)    
    
    
    So excited that #BVB tops the #bundesliga for the first time since 2002!  go dortmund!!    
    
    
    @kevinweil me too!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @ablegrape !! Hope you had a great day!    
    
    
    @gsingers congrats, Grant! Really happy for you!! You'll have to sign my copy when we see each other next time. :)    
    
    
    @lucasjosh you can find the slides on my linkedin profile.    
    
    
    @aam @colinkirkhodge happy to hear you enjoyed it :)    
    
    
    Doku: Dortmund-Süd, die schwarz-gelbe Wand: http://youtu.be/VuGm90VzIXc  /cc @BVB    
    
    
    @sam That's just because I didn't participate.    
    
    
    @lija Coconut filling? Sieht lecker aus :)    
    
    
    @Gotthilf_Otto I especially like that you spelled ALF, my childhood hero, in all caps. I'm a dog person though.    
    
    
    Mission accomplished! /cc @s1m0nw pic.twitter.com/9yKiRvYq    
    
    
    Dinnertime! pic.twitter.com/5130k04S    
    
    
    @s1m0nw wow, that must be a new record? :)    
    
    
    @pottblog da wohnt meine Schwester mittlerweile. Bin grade zu Besuch aus sf. Komme aber eigentlich aus dem Sauerland    
    
    
    Merry first Christmas, little Lias! :) pic.twitter.com/vpnJAf0n    
    
    
    @pottblog Danke, dir auch frohe Weihnachten!    
    
    
    @mwessendorf hi, nur über Weihnachten. Bist du auch in der nähe? Frohe Weihnachten!    
    
    
    Happy 94th birthday, grandpa! My recommendation to everyone: drink wine every day. And ride your bike until you're >94 pic.twitter.com/FombQHkx    
    
    
    Bin sehr beeindruckt wie cool Du bei Deinem Auftritt geblieben bist, 
@EinAugenschmaus! :) War echt klasse!    
    
    
    4 generations talking.  #facetime pic.twitter.com/X5irFgDV    
    
    
    @mwessendorf my little nephew, who btw is a very awesome kid!    
    
    
    What's your new year's resolution, @nutmegthedog? Subtle hint: http://youtu.be/BWAK0J8Uhzk     
    
    
    http://youtu.be/WZIY5c0CsPY     
    
    
    Almost there... pic.twitter.com/nowLZwtO    
    
    
    The new year is 10 hours old here in Germany. I really hope the pilot isn't drunk. pic.twitter.com/wP21ldwp    
    
    
    @irnnr happy new year!    
    
    
    #protip: never start a major nerf gun battle if there is a glass full of water on your desk.    
    
    
    Grass is greener in Dortmund http://www.bundesliga.com/en/liga/news/2012/0000236435.php …    
    
    
    @techno I'm very happy that we met Thomas! Also that I turned you into a @BVB fan :) Looking forward to hearing about your new adventures!    
    
    
    @HendricRuesch @flo @techno @bvb am besten für Block 14, da hab ich ne Dauerkarte! :) #echteliebe    
    
    
    @nurisahin05 Welcome home, Nuri! Und viele Grüße aus Kalifornien, wo ein treuer @BVB Fan jedes eurer Spiele guckt! :) #echteliebe    
    
    
    @CFI_Erik @goodflying thank you, Erik, for your patience and so much fun! :) #bestCFIever    
    
    
    @isasun @lija @cfi_erik @goodflying anytime! :)    
    
    
    @monica Yeah it's cool that the Bundesliga now also has the 2nd best coach in the world :) (that Jürgen Klopp is #1 goes with saying) @BVB    
    
    
    @michibusch @monica @BVB Ha, I meant 'goes without saying' :)    
    
    
    @kenbsd thank you! the shirt definitely brought me good luck :) when are you going to fly with me?    
    
    
    My first passenger! :) #brave /cc @maybefriday pic.twitter.com/be5xQua9    
    
    
    @kenbsd @maybefriday @nutmegthedog she was waiting very patiently in the flight school where various people threatened to kidnap her. :)    
    
    
    @larsonite how can you be sure it's spam? Maybe it's true? You should follow up!    
    
    
    Killing it in the game room! @yz #jointheflock http://vine.co/v/b5dpQWMFxzg     
    
    
    Sooo hungry! @nutmegthedog /cc @maybefriday http://vine.co/v/b50XaDx7W5T     
    
    
    @isasun Du hättest deine Zeit auf am/pm stellen und eine Minute warten sollen!    
    
    
    Always happy when @nutmegthedog is happy. I think right now she is :) pic.twitter.com/XjbLXCt4    
    
    
    @Ostwestf4le @stillstandpunkt HEJA BVB! :) Viel Spass im Stadion und bring drei Punkte mit!    
    
    
    @ErnieRacer glad you like it! Looking forward to lots of tweets from you! :)    
    
    
    Amazing, this pudding is good for more than 3 years! pic.twitter.com/TuEl1J3Eth    
    
    
    Good night San Francisco. pic.twitter.com/U9oeUdIFOL    
    
    
    Good job calling shotgun @nutmegthedog! :) pic.twitter.com/SEUMVLIVaI    
    
    
    I think my little nephew is very lucky and happy to have such awesome parents :) pic.twitter.com/wJ5FixQqgq    
    
    
    Guilty looking @nutmegthedog. pic.twitter.com/615ywprRg3    
    
    
    Lias can already drink by himself! pic.twitter.com/lD2XXKdh38    
    
    
    @krishnagade yes, cute, isn't he?! :)    
    
    
    Lunch time! pic.twitter.com/Iub5xIpB50    
    
    
    ... and soooo hungry pic.twitter.com/7MdzqZR6n3    
    
    
    Home. pic.twitter.com/eKNdAarQKr    
    
    
    . @KathiBusch baking pic.twitter.com/qg3WxKJFbb    
    
    
    Lias got his first own plate :) pic.twitter.com/LhAvaovFT5    
    
    
    @Ellen_Friedman thank you! It's easy because Lias is so cute :)    
    
    
    Dogs in Germany look much sadder when they can't go into places! /cc @nutmegthedog pic.twitter.com/YZCVIgX0sN    
    
    
    Three guys working very hard. #lego pic.twitter.com/vRFkJWtGUi    
    
    
    On the road to Wembley @BVB! #echteliebe #bvbmcf pic.twitter.com/BYxoa5p1O3    
    
    
    @sunghu yep, still in the stadium. Unbelievable and unforgettable.    
    
    
    Aquarium. pic.twitter.com/3YS57SmIDi    
    
    
    @pflore ja echt unglaublich! Den Tag werden wir wohl alle nie vergessen. Hat mich auch sehr gefreut - bis bald (Vielleicht Halbfinale! :) )    
    
    
    I think Lias will be a dog person! Just as his uncle :) pic.twitter.com/z80gwjHGDF    
    
    
    YAY - I did my taxes!  For the first time not on or after 4/15!  I feel like an overachiever :)    
    
    
    Rainbows. pic.twitter.com/xVznyYKpAq    
    
    
    Sauerland. pic.twitter.com/fMnq3JGphD    
    
    
    @mwessendorf @s1m0nw nice! That sounds fun. Trinkt ein Bier für mich mit! :)    
    
    
    Well, the popcorn bags are definitely smaller in Germany. pic.twitter.com/dBehgbVykI    
    
    
    @marius I wished!    
    
    
    Family time pic.twitter.com/vsH5V1q6o2    
    
    
    @pflore ja ich komme morgen! Wollen wir uns treffen?    
    
    
    Surfing with a @bvb shirt in Munich. #brave #cold #fairytale #uclfinal #echteliebe pic.twitter.com/U61gWT9txc    
    
    
    Via Dortmund to London. #uclfinal pic.twitter.com/rgwmqGEkzU    
    
    
    Dortmund Airport. pic.twitter.com/19CepgaHXD    
    
    
    Here ends the road to Wembley. We made it. Let's win this! @bvb #uclfinal #fairytale pic.twitter.com/PIM9gYeXC3    
    
    
    The sun is shining only on @bvb's side! #uclfinal pic.twitter.com/Fd9O7R7Hr1    
    
    
    Well, I guess sometimes you lose. But we'll get back up on our feet. As always. Ich bin stolz auf euch Jungs! Heja @BVB! Congrats @FCBayern    
    
    
    @ablegrape yeah that's true. I hope everything is ok with you guys?    
    
    
    This is pretty cool: @Everest1953 #everest53    
    
    
    Ich bin dann mal weg. pic.twitter.com/1WHLSy6i7l    
    
    
    The little girl next to me on the plane just took my book to play with it. I'm reading "The book thief". :)    
    
    
    How to walk on water. http://www.marcandangel.com/2009/01/31/how-to-walk-on-water/ …    
    
    
    I like how three-legged dogs are always just as cheerful as their friends with four legs. pic.twitter.com/EWHj4FpTO5    
    
    
    @trammell reminds me of monkey island 2    
    
    
    Tomorrow: Grand Canyon Rim to Rim. Guy in my hostel room: "That will be a hike of a lifetime!" #MonsoonHaveMercy pic.twitter.com/JDNvAQ07YH    
    
    
    Supposedly this soap is good for skin, hair, clothes, laundry, ...AND... brushing teeth! #magic pic.twitter.com/TL8CTmU8x3    
    
    
    Up! pic.twitter.com/hLmc6TnJbh    
    
    
    South Rim. pic.twitter.com/pA6ktxdfmH    
    
    
    Stuck in a traffic jam on I-40W in the middle of a thunderstorm. Flash flood warnings. #monsoon pic.twitter.com/kWhemGhgJf    
    
    
    @andres @marius yes, iPhone shot while driving, and before it looked like this from my windshield pic.twitter.com/gk09iaTn3t    
    
    
    Well, this could take a while. I-40W. #flooding pic.twitter.com/L95lvyDr3X    
    
    
    @javasoze between Ashfork and Seligman, AZ, on I-40 West.    
    
    
    Wheel down. pic.twitter.com/pAGXNTWsTq    
    
    
    Enjoying Arizona's countryside. pic.twitter.com/3IN6Homyh4    
    
    
    @nebbiolata I tasted it :) the peppermint flavor isn't that bad, but I still opted for a travel size tooth paste :)    
    
    
    @ablegrape yeah, the sacrifices you make in life...    
    
    
    Sunset in Seligman. pic.twitter.com/574wA59qGI    
    
    
    TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOR!!! #BVB    
    
    
    Schade #bvb.  Ein Sieg waere heute verdient gewesen.    
    
    
    @lija @Luisa @schumandammit @PhilzCoffee Awesome! Please bring Philharmonic! :)    
    
    
    Will miss you @KatieS /cc @KatieaParis pic.twitter.com/7TzNAdidHR    
    
    
    Tracks. https://vine.co/v/hh3uAUH6DQx     
    
    
    My favorite error message! It's been too long, I missed you! #internalerror #eclipse pic.twitter.com/0kXp6gtIHW    
    
    
    Spitzenreiter. @bvb    
    
    
    @elizabethwadeth we need to go back to Ponferrada and get you some new ones!    
    
    
    Lake Tahoe hiking and kayaking trip ending with cooking and guitar lessons by @oelmo. Life is good :)    
    
    
    Niemals aufgeben. Vom Fussball kann man viel lernen. http://youtu.be/uGUABtAL7_A  @BVB    
    
    
    @BVB Good, that you always meet twice in life. #Revenge /cc @Arsenal @OM_Officiel    
    
    
    New running group with @anew68 and @oelmo. Day 1: Looks like we succeeded in consuming more calories than the run burned. #ftw    
    
    
    Awww! <3 http://youtu.be/L64c5vT3NBw     
    
    
    Dear barre chords, I'm looking forward to the day when it feels surprising that you ever seemed hard.    
    
    
    Playing soccer with a flat ball we found near the cliff house last week with @oelmo, @anew68 and @mkoehnke. pic.twitter.com/ZCyHF89JCL    
    
    
    #beer #paradise pic.twitter.com/pu94QKIiwH    
    
    
    @honten @beerhallsf    
    
    
    @marius cool, I have to try it    
    
    
    @marius @Mi_Mo at @beerhallsf with the search team. Really liked tank 7. We should go sometime, seems like you know good beers! :)    
    
    
    Get out of the way @KarlTheFog! I'm trying to show the bay to my friends. pic.twitter.com/byBEunmf2l    
    
    
    @ShilohNoelle :) hair ok?    
    
    
    #bruchpilot @mkoehnke pic.twitter.com/uSTjNmx6pM    
    
    
    Just like home. Lehr's German Specialities. //cc @oelmo @anew68 pic.twitter.com/Jh6AO7dl7n    
    
    
    German chocolate. Lots of it. //cc @ShilohNoelle pic.twitter.com/5kXv31hybP    
    
    
    @ShilohNoelle well, *maybe* I bought some... pic.twitter.com/w3zOZLUq2E    
    
    
    Sail pic.twitter.com/JM4ScycVoO    
    
    
    My beloved guitar in so much better hands right now. @oelmo pic.twitter.com/WHCPmyqk92    
    
    
    @oelmo Yes, finally I know how good it can sound :)    
    
    
    @lija I think your photo is not sharp enough.    
    
    
    Thank you @CA_DMV. Very happy about how efficient this appointment was!    
    
    
    .@BVB Netradio: "Mitch Langerak könnte auch zum Oktoberfest gehen oder eine Picknickdecke in sein Tor legen und würde nichts verpassen."    
    
    
    And suddenly my finger is hundreds of dollars more expensive.    
    
    
    @oelmo wonder medicine! Get better!    
    
    
    @ShilohNoelle Sorry to hear. Hugs from California!    
    
    
    Camping at Manresa Beach. pic.twitter.com/a82VoWkjyP    
    
    
    Maybe I shouldn't have watched breaking bad so late. I guess I could have expected to be sleepless now. #GoodbyeBreakingBad I'll miss you.    
    
    
    Da ist es!! 1-0 @BVB    
    
    
    @javasoze @pasha407 reinforced with nerf guns.    
    
    
    Saturday afternoon run. Such a beautiful day. <3 sf pic.twitter.com/fv1ywkW9Dq    
    
    
    First time flying a plane with retractable gears. pic.twitter.com/hkD8tqFbE4    
    
    
    @ShilohNoelle how strong was it? I didn't feel anything. Also, how big is your cat??    
    
    
    @ShilohNoelle Too many treats? :)    
    
    
    OH: "This tea tastes like dirt, doesn't it? But clean and sweet dirt." - I can confirm it does.    
    
    
    @andres @lija for whom?    
    
    
    @zhenghuali @johnsirois Progress, not perfection. (Lucene's Mike McCandless likes to say that)    
    
    
    Es gibt nur eine Person mit der ich übers Leben sprechen kann u. Begriffe wie "Frau Holle" und "Sensemann" fallen. #bestpartofmyday cc @lija    
    
    
    Witnessed a pitch for kale at a venture capital round table. Really THE trending veggie. As a kid I was eating it every week in Germany. :)    
    
    
    Arab Film Festival. #aff2013 pic.twitter.com/KJg1M7MWBJ    
    
    
    I love you @nutmegthedog. pic.twitter.com/U9XXTOPuYc    
    
    
    Benjamin Franklin was a wise man. pic.twitter.com/xD2yNg1Oq5    
    
    
    Yay my flight school aerodynamic aviation is on twitter now!  Welcome @goodflying    
    
    
    @ShilohNoelle is this what I think it is?    
    
    
    @ShilohNoelle impressive how precisely you captured my thoughts! :)    
    
    
    @KatieS Happy Birthday Katie! :)    
    
    
    @bvb can you please send me a tweet in 4 hours so that I'll wake up for the game? This will be a short night...    
    
    
    @BVB thank you! :) 6.30am in California: Breakfast and Borussia with @anew68! #echteliebe pic.twitter.com/8XThbuAQ8J    
    
    
    @adrianocrestani Yes!  It's a lot of fun.  I'm training in a tailwheel plane: Citabria 7ECA.    
    
    
    Sandy. pic.twitter.com/PfO6wb5j1U    
    
    
    @lija which beach is that?    
    
    
    @lija you replied to yourself. Are you schizophrenic?    
    
    
    @lija yes, just because I'm stalking you all the time! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Current status: walking through SF, facetime with my nephew in Germany. <3 pic.twitter.com/3VOeuGkAYS    
    
    
    @sunghu @omid Dortmund was better in the first half and we'll win! cc @BVB    
    
    
    Was für ein Hammertor!!!! @BVB    
    
    
    @omid @sunghu :)    
    
    
    Beautiful night at the Shoreline Theater. #bridgeschool pic.twitter.com/86YTPSq90F    
    
    
    Just signed up for the @AIDSLifeCycle bike ride from SF to LA next year. Please help! http://www.tofighthiv.org/site/TR/AIDSLIFECYCLE2014/AIDSLifeCycleCenter?px=3034254&pg=personal&fr_id=1630 …    
    
    
    @lija love this    
    
    
    Back in Germany. Another 30 mins flying before seeing @Maja1805 and my nephew :) pic.twitter.com/6TnMwyxw2j    
    
    
    @mwessendorf danke! Gehst du Freitag ins Stadion?    
    
    
    Dutch dike. pic.twitter.com/1OEVpW3syN    
    
    
    @pflore haha :) bis bald! Freu mich schon    
    
    
    @anew68 thank you!! It made me happy to see this :) Das Spiel war echt klasse!    
    
    
    #selfie with Lias. He pushed the button :) pic.twitter.com/dEYq8ujCBi    
    
    
    Trinity College. pic.twitter.com/nr1V9QSaSx    
    
    
    Bye bye Dublin. This stay was awesome but too short - I'll come back! But now back to SF.    
    
    
    @verena @lija leider schon wieder auf dem Rückflug. War nur ganz kurz hier, aber komme bestimmt wieder. Dublin ist echt super schön!    
    
    
    The Long Room in the Old Library. Just like the Jedi archives. pic.twitter.com/0Rc0JCubXM    
    
    
    @anew68 ne schaffe ich nicht. Hoffe ich kann Netradio in Chicago beim Umsteigen hören.    
    
    
    Last flight for today: Chicago -> SFO. pic.twitter.com/9l5OY91Gly    
    
    
    #IPO pic.twitter.com/cwysK6ePgx    
    
    
    I may not have believed someone telling me as a kid watching Star Trek that Captain Picard would ring the bell of a company I'd work for.    
    
    
    #up pic.twitter.com/bGeQnLMFvu    
    
    
    Last week I got my copy of Newton's Principia, this week I saw his statue at the Trinity College. #coincidence pic.twitter.com/MmHYRVidCo    
    
    
    Surfers. pic.twitter.com/NIQajhqqIr    
    
    
    @kmonkeyjam it's a quite hidden nameless beach near San Gregorio. You get there by following a small river. Can show you on a map :)    
    
    
    My new friend. pic.twitter.com/K9z8U9MIx8    
    
    
    @jreichhold 14 weeks. But my friends dog, not mine. I guess that tweet may have been misleading :)    
    
    
    Sun rise from the Golden Gate Bridge. #morningrun pic.twitter.com/QrUVW3lJHa    
    
    
    Clipper card empty and no dollar bills, but super nice bus driver lady let me ride for free. <3    
    
    
    Well, now I'm really motivated to finish this race fast. #beer pic.twitter.com/SK9QeLsIs9    
    
    
        
    
    
    Exploring waterfalls in Oregon. pic.twitter.com/Na2kGQ3P5t    
    
    
    Exploring beer in Oregon. pic.twitter.com/AfbzntLnyy    
    
    
    @lija somewhere in SF pic.twitter.com/7IBK13nyQ2    
    
    
    @bvb Wir drücken die Daumen von Kalifornien aus! #bvbfcb #jetzterstrecht    
    
    
    Proud to run in black and yellow today. #jetzterstrecht @bvb pic.twitter.com/1HjQL8fxNk    
    
    
    Thank you @Mi_Mo for baking a cake for the search team :) #HappyMonday pic.twitter.com/QIgw1n8dXD    
    
    
    @lija @CheckerZulu Nackig find ich besser als beige.    
    
    
    Jetzt gewinnen wir! @BVB #jetzterstrecht #echteliebe    
    
    
    @lija SAIL /cc @oelmo    
    
    
    @lija nice rack!    
    
    
    Island Park. pic.twitter.com/dPWCenDYTB    
    
    
    Wolves playing. pic.twitter.com/IdLaSVIv5h    
    
    
    Gorgeous roadtrip in Yellowstone Park. pic.twitter.com/vhvqiFA9uE    
    
    
    @lija da war ein Zaun dazwischen. Sonst hätten sie wohl mit uns "gespielt" :)    
    
    
    Boiling river, Yellowstone. pic.twitter.com/ttYEQcFMrO    
    
    
    @larsonite yes, only the north entrance near Gardiner is open    
    
    
    @lija it IS freezing HERE. And we're waiting for the bus :) pic.twitter.com/hQl09q4IWk    
    
    
    @lija we have to make it over the snowy Grand Teton Pass today. They closed it for cars without chains or all wheel drive. #fingerscrossed    
    
    
    Love this. pic.twitter.com/0VxU0FTNvp    
    
    
    @lija 4WD yes, chains no. But supposedly you only need one of the two :)    
    
    
    Crossing the Grand Teton Pass. #snowstorm pic.twitter.com/NtusRb9SPW    
    
    
    Grand Teton Brewing Co. /cc @anew68 pic.twitter.com/lXB23W8m7t    
    
    
    @lija feiern. Das schlimmste ist überstanden :)    
    
    
    @larsonite welcome to Germany!    
    
    
    @larsonite the only appropriate action right now is to order another beer (I see yours is empty) - that'll help    
    
    
    5.10a is the new 5.8 /cc @jmh    
    
    
    @lija so pushy    
    
    
    @elizabethwadeth yes!! :)    
    
    
    @elizabethwadeth ok I signed up and am working on convincing some friends to join. #exciting    
    
    
    Current status: brrrrr! Waiting for #runcim to start. It's below freezing.    
    
    
    Hero of the day: @yz    
    
    
    @lija @Isa #proud    
    
    
    Current status: watching Micky Mouse :) pic.twitter.com/lUUKUhO85v    
    
    
    I'm so proud of my team! http://nyti.ms/hNFZlW  #bvb    
    
    
    The only way to activate an online verizon account is to receive the password by sms? But they sell data devices without sms support?! #lame    
    
    
    Great!  Will ask them as soon as I find them!    
    
    
    Man I hate IntelliJ.    
    
    
    Every day that dortmund wins a soccer game I'm very very happy!  #bvb    
    
    
    @kmonkeyjam hey hating a few things in my life passionately doesn't make me a negative person :)    
    
    
    Changing Bits: Hack on Lucene this summer! http://blog.mikemccandless.com/2011/03/hack-on-lucene-this-summer.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Bummer #bvb lost yesterday. It was unlucky I think - we're still going to become german champion!!    
    
    
    Want to work on one of the world's most frequently queried #lucene indexes? On exciting realtime search? @jointheflock!  http://twitter.com/job.html?jvi=oE2EVfwZ …    
    
    
    OH: doing it that way would be the cleanest solution. The only problem is that it may not work.  -- @omrvp    
    
    
    @smileyj68 dankeschoen! :)    
    
    
    @nicolebartelt thank you!! We should hang out again soon!    
    
    
    @ablegrape thank you Doug!    
    
    
    @mwessendorf was fun to watch that awesome match with you!    
    
    
    Cool that they have wifi now in german ICE trains! On my way from Munich to Stuttgart after a very nice lufthansa flight. Cold in Germany...    
    
    
    Heja BVB!!! 4-0 gegen Nuernberg - hoechster Sieg der Saison!    
    
    
    @pbrane the DWPT is a prereq for lock-free indexing. That's why we worked so hard on it and I'm super excited it's almost done! #lucene    
    
    
    Borussia Dortmund ist deutscher Meister! #BVB geniesst es alle - diesen Tag werden wir niemals vergessen!    
    
    
    @nutmegthedog is celebrating Dortmund's victory too! #BVB http://yfrog.com/hstqnwbj     
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/h89rq2j   My dad is preparing our house in Brunskappel, Germany #bvb    
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/gz8sp9j  And is celebrating! #bvb    
    
    
    This is my first tweet sent from my iPhone! :)    
    
    
    @mkoehnke just downloaded tweetie2! It looks good so far... Thanks for the tip!    
    
    
    Beautiful day in California! Crossing over from 101 to I5 right now... 7 hours or so to go to San Diego...    
    
    
    working with Tanya on a 5000 pieces puzzle... this is gonna take a while :)    
    
    
    @mkoehnke danke, das wuenschen wir dir auch! Bald sehen wir uns in hamburg! Btw: den Rand des puzzles haben wir schon fast fertig... :)    
    
    
    On our way to the San Diego wild animal park...    
    
    
    Eine unglaubliche Meisterfeier. Der BVB macht eine ganze Region stolz! Danke Jungs für ein tolles Jahr. Es hat sehr viel Spaß gemacht! #bvb    
    
    
    @maja1805 Happy birthday Marion!  http://yfrog.com/hsea0jlj     
    
    
    Deutscher meister ist nur der BVB! #bvb http://yfrog.com/h3d28vmj     
    
    
    I'm in Stuttgart now!    
    
    
    Very awesome @nutmegthedog picture! Miss you Nutmeg! http://www.flickr.com/photos/maybefriday/5739188218/ …    
    
    
    OH NO!! My parents discovered twitter - from now on I have to be careful about the tweets I send :)    
    
    
    Meeting with Sven to design the audio content management application for #literacybridge...    
    
    
    I'm in Hamburg now. Took the train yesterday from Stuttgart; all Germany is white!    
    
    
    Excited that our new #search is live now! I hope you will like and enjoy it. Tell us what you think! http://twitter.com/search-home     
    
    
    @jennadawn where in Alaska are you?    
    
    
    @jennadawn yes, a pretty long time ago, I think in 1993 :) I loved Alaska. Want to go back someday.    
    
    
    @jennadawn seeing the northern lights would be cool. Also polar bears would be    
    
    
    @supercooc we recently committed http://bit.ly/mhepaT  to #Lucene trunk, which is a necessary refactoring for RT search. More RT patches soon!    
    
    
    Waiting in Frankfurt for my plane to SF and watching the snow falling down faster and faster onto the runway...    
    
    
    Flug über Achttausender: Gipfelsturm per Düsenjet - SPIEGEL ONLINE - http://spon.de/adnHT     
    
    
    Deutscher Meister 2011! #bvb pic.twitter.com/b7R1d0x    
    
    
    Heja #bvb!! pic.twitter.com/Jo0sf6e    
    
    
    Trying more twitter photos! pic.twitter.com/czaDT1J Cute puppy :)    
    
    
    A lot of people listening to @wfarner's talk at twitter's first eng open house! #twitterhq http://yfrog.com/keam6tj     
    
    
    @manand hack?!? I don't know what you're talking about ;)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Polar Bears - Video: Behind the Photo - Pictures, More From National Geographic Magazine: http://on.natgeo.com/mdWNWR  via @NatGeoSociety    
    
    
    Nice article on @BVBDortmund09 and twitter: http://bit.ly/isIrbh  Thank you @lija for finding it! #bvb    
    
    
    Leaving my IBM office for the last time now. It feels sad to go after 6 years IBM. But at the same time I'm excited to start a new job soon    
    
    
    and am ready for new adventures! Bye bye IBM - you've been good to me.    
    
    
    It's impressive to watch how my almost 92 years old grandpa is using my ipad to check soccer results! :)    
    
    
    There must be a competition going on between @BayAreaClipper and @Caltrain about whose service is worse. Both screw up so remarkably often.    
    
    
    B street and vine in San Mateo was awesome as always tonight! :)    
    
    
    @nicolebartelt yes let's do that!    
    
    
    @ablegrape me too! Can't wait to finally start :)    
    
    
    On the express caltrain, commuting for the first time to my new job. Exciting!    
    
    
    Even though the #caltrain iPhone site says you can't take bikes on this train (leaves mv at 7:57) I noticed you can! Yay!    
    
    
    Coding on the caltrain is actually productive. Worked on DAISY metadata validation for #literacybridge.    
    
    
    @herrtodd ah thank you! That's good to know...    
    
    
    @javasoze you're using it right now ;)    
    
    
    The first few days working at twitter were really fun! I'm excited :)    
    
    
    Borussia Dortmund won today 4-1!! http://bit.ly/aqCDvq    
    
    
    #protip: if your dog poops right next to sprinklers just before they turn on, put your foot on the sprinkler before you're soaking wet.    
    
    
    thank you @nutmegthedog for a fun walk :)    
    
    
    @krishnagade i did! After two unsuccessful attempts to find the poop in the dark while being rained on :) #tmi    
    
    
    Tomorrow when I come home heavy rain will be awaiting me!    
    
    
    @joshelman that's what she said    
    
    
    @lija Zwiebelkuchen?! I'm jealous! :)    
    
    
    I now have a digital, wireless picture frame on my desk with.... wait for it.... Twitter search integration!! :) Thanks @maybefriday    
    
    
    @ej beeping comes from awesome picture frame... I could try to turn it off now, but it would beep while trying to find the setting. #catch22    
    
    
    On my way to the airport to say goodbye to my good friends. This is a sad day.    
    
    
    @smileyj68 so far I like #heavyrain, graphics are impressive, especially faces and emotions. The story seems good, but we only played 2hrs..    
    
    
    Caltrain is running again. Next nb train in mountain view leaves in 5-10 mins    
    
    
    In the caltrain this announcement was just made: "It is highly recommended to not leave abandonned cars on the caltrain tracks!"    
    
    
    Riding north on the southbound track, overtaking the other trains, expressing to sf. Looks like I picked the right train! :)    
    
    
    Using my new verizon #mifi2200 for the first time today in the #caltrain. It works really well! Basically no drops so far. #knockonwood    
    
    
    Schalke vs. Dortmund today! Still 0-0. Go BVB!!    
    
    
    Halftime. Schalke-BVB 0-0    
    
    
    Schalke won 2-1. :(    
    
    
    On my way to the woodside half marathon. Man, I feel so out of shape!    
    
    
    @adrianocrestani me = out of shape: officially confirmed :) but in my defense the hm had 1800 feet elevation    
    
    
    Endlich geht's wieder los! @BVBDortmund09 Heja BVB!    
    
    
    2-0 Götze! Marcel Reif: "Die sind ja noch besser geworden als letzte Saison!" #happiness #bvb    
    
    
    Watched "little miss sunshine" again - always good...    
    
    
    Everybody who writes code in #java should read "Concurrency in practice" by Brian Goetz e.a.    
    
    
    @aneeshs @shilpa_26 How cute! Congratulations!! :)    
    
    
    Toooooooooooooooooooooor!!! #BVB 1-0    
    
    
    @gomikael @miguelrios @monicaquiroz @lija OMG, Lina didn't win the beer competition? With all the German training?    
    
    
    @lija vermutlich haben die ganzen prozesskosten weit mehr als 510 Euro gekostet. #sinnlosebürokratie    
    
    
    @flo did you win?    
    
    
    @flo I agree. it's been like this for a long time, can't believe they don't fix it    
    
    
    @BVBDortmund09 Love your media gallery! #bvb http://twitter.com/#!/BVBDortmund09/media/grid …  Thanks @caramev and team!    
    
    
    Weiss noch nicht Sind grad im hq    
    
    
    Just sent out the #ZURBwired application for #literacybridge in the last minute! YAY! Everyone has to cross their fingers now!    
    
    
    Spektakuläre Notlandung: Flugzeug kracht in deutsche Kleinstadt - SPIEGEL ONLINE - http://spon.de/adrQO     
    
    
    OH: IntelliJ is slow. Really slow. Sometimes it cannot keep up with my typing.    
    
    
    12:45 in the office: OH it's not too bad - there's just one chair that has beer on it. #augtoberfest #justanotherdayatwork    
    
    
    After desperately watching the rain going by for 45 mins, knowing I forgot the umbrella: sunshine in san francisco! thanks, universe :)    
    
    
    NB Caltrain broke down at California ave.  No estimate how long it's gonna take to fix it.    
    
    
    We're moving again!  (why do I always tweet about the caltrain???)    
    
    
    On top of Mt. Etna ... http://yfrog.com/kj41yhonj     
    
    
    Today I got bitten by a grumpy horse in front of the Pantheon. #rome #meanhorse    
    
    
    @jennadawn where are you going?    
    
    
    Immigration officer at SFO when he noticed twitter in my visa: "you're like a god to people, everyone loves you!" @jointheflock    
    
    
    Excited to see @nutmegthedog after two weeks soon! :)    
    
    
    I can't believe I have 49,988 miles @UnitedAirlines. I need 50,000 for the next membership level! Why is there no flight SJC->SFO? :(    
    
    
    @BVBDortmund09 Herzlichen Glückwunsch zu 15.000 Followers! Das nächste Ziel sollte 80.720 sein :) #bvb    
    
    
    @gsingers @ingorenner Thanks, guys! United distinguishes between status miles and bonus miles and unfortunately you can only buy bonus miles    
    
    
    @ingorenner Yeah I think I'll really call them and ask. I'll start with 0 status miles 1/1/11 again, so I really want to get that upgrade :)    
    
    
    Still awake and coding at #zurbwired...    
    
    
    @ej Happy Birthday!!!    
    
    
    #HowToTrainYourDragon was really awesome! Just watched it in 3D. Such a cute dragon!    
    
    
    Goodbye, Steve. We will miss and never forget you.    
    
    
    #java6: DataOutputStream#size() returns a 32 bit int. javadoc: "If the counter overflows, it will be wrapped to Integer.MAX_VALUE." #2011    
    
    
    If I hadn't know before already, the napkins at the #chirp party would have convinced me that Twitter is the coolest company out there!    
    
    
    @omrvp I love the memory model changes! C++ 11    
    
    
    my two most recent emails #icloud pic.twitter.com/80gJKx8s    
    
    
    Munich airport welcomes me. pic.twitter.com/gn6UC4YG    
    
    
    Cute plane. Now back to Amsterdam. Looking at a map, this is a quite inefficient trip so far :) pic.twitter.com/psixUPhO    
    
    
    Never had to assemble a fork in a plane before. Also, still working on my slides for my #lucene talk in a few hours. :) pic.twitter.com/IHF0ZBQh    
    
    
    @mwessendorf yep, will be there tomorrow. Just arrived at schiphol    
    
    
    First food I saw in Munich: weisswurst and beer. schiphol: a gigantic chocolate globe! pic.twitter.com/z5ESDgLF    
    
    
    @mwessendorf bummer :( come to the #lucene conf in Barcelona next week?    
    
    
    You come to the office and there's bacon waiting for you!  Can a day start better?!    
    
    
    @mdo but... then I would probably eat less BACON - that wouldn't be a better day! :)    
    
    
    @abdur you were in amsterdam? So was I, left yesterday evening. Bummer we didn't hang out!    
    
    
    Next part of my trip: from Nottuln to Barcelona! pic.twitter.com/f9eKSS00    
    
    
    seriously @germanwings ? One checkin person for this many people? #lame pic.twitter.com/2DRUg6VN    
    
    
    Cool, looks like the referees of the barca game tonight are checked into the same hotel and having breakfast right now too!    
    
    
    Camp nou. 25 mins till the champions league game starts! #barca pic.twitter.com/LqRtu18g    
    
    
    Ich werde aber natürlich dem BVB die daumen drücken, auch wenn ich ausnahmsweise mal in Camp Nou bin! @BVBDortmund09 Auf geht's Dortmund!    
    
    
    @adrianocrestani yes, it sucks (TM)  :)    
    
    
    @adrianocrestani awesome that you'll finally read that book!  Maybe you'll become a good programmer after all ;)    
    
    
    Just came back from a nice run with @nutmegthedog, and now we're very hungry and waiting for @maybefriday to bring us some Indian food!    
    
    
    Twitter search guys with @ConanOBrien!  He was awesome! http://yfrog.com/joyadj    
    
    
    I have never seen such a long line of people waiting for busses at 3.45am! #bigsurmarathon    
    
    
    We're taking you now to the start line of the best marathon on the planet. -- bus announcement    
    
    
    Oh my gosh, I don't remember any race hurting as much as the #bigsurmarathon. Not even the ironman 08. I guess that was in a different life    
    
    
    C'mon caltrain move faster! Only a few hours till @BVBDortmund09 plays against the vfb. Thank you @lija for organizing such a great evening!    
    
    
    @lija yeah the weather was perfect! It was really fun!    
    
    
    @nurisahin05 Congrats, Nuri! Now you can finally show them how good you are! Best wishes from a BVB fan! :)    
    
    
    Man the new gmail interface is really terrible. How can I go back to the old one?    
    
    
    @crunch09 thanks! I always clicked on the wrong gears symbol. There are two now on the right upper side. Even those are not user friendly :)    
    
    
    @mikeyk Hey Mike, would be happy to drop by to talk about lucene. I'm working on Twitter's realtime index that's based on lucene.    
    
    
    @monicaquiroz @lija you should invite other international tweeps to your offsites :) #hint    
    
    
    @nutmegthedog has a sophisticated understanding of probability.  -- @maybefriday    
    
    
    @skf well if you could you would probably like what you would be seeing    
    
    
    @sm we all would be nothing without you.    
    
    
    Just found out that US $ bills survive the washer and dryer pretty well actually. I'm impressed.    
    
    
    @jreichhold "working from home" today    
    
    
    Beer is the best medicine.    
    
    
    Thanks @UnitedAirlines for upgrading me even though I was a few miles short!!  And I didn't even have to call :)    
    
    
    @BVBDortmund09 Unglaublich wie um jeden einzelnen Ball gekämpft wird! Ich bin stolz auf euch, egal wie das Spiel ausgeht!    
    
    
    TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOR!!!! @GoetzeOfficial @BVBDortmund09    
    
    
    @mwessendorf das kannst du laut sagen! :)    
    
    
    Heavy rain and a storm seems to be coming in. Should be an interesting flight lesson! :) pic.twitter.com/BMscdyMB    
    
    
    @sm no worries, my instructor used to be bush pilot in Alaska. He thinks this was easy weather :)    
    
    
    @monicaquiroz thanks! It was actually an awesome day for flying. Rain and gusts in the beginning, sunshine and rainbows in the end!    
    
    
    Had a great run. Fresh, crisp air after a rain in the fall - doesn't get much better than that for running. pic.twitter.com/5juTEJki    
    
    
    OH: Now I have to go give an autograph to the guy I spanked.    
    
    
    @thomasarend wow! did you bake them all yourself?    
    
    
    Finally, after 10 hours of driving and countless coffees, arrived in San Diego!  #happythanksgiving    
    
    
    Happy birthday @nutmegthedog!! Cutest dog in the world!    
    
    
    @isasun @katies @lija @thomasarend wow really? It has the autographs?! Super awesome :) thank you!! #bvb    
    
    
    @thomasarend @isasun @katies @lija yes you did!! Doing my bvb-happy-dance now :) thanks so much! Are you still in Dortmund? Game tomorrow?    
    
    
    Legoland! pic.twitter.com/AJ7edawD    
    
    
    Didn't think I'd get to play in the snow today in sunny San diego! #happykids pic.twitter.com/hW1mUU9n    
    
    
    @lija ja es war ein toller tag! Haben sogar San Francisco gesehen ... aus Lego :) pic.twitter.com/9D0Fyg84    
    
    
    Next project after legoland: build a Lego truck! pic.twitter.com/znJPtYS2    
    
    
    @lija you saw dolphins?    
    
    
    Mission accomplished. pic.twitter.com/JKSQCSbV    
    
    
    @KatieS @isasun @lija if you need someone to verify that it tastes authentic, I'd volunteer! :)    
    
    
    The new #literacybridge website is live! Thank you @maybefriday, @jebritton, @smileyj68, @mdo!  http://www.literacybridge.org    
    
    
    @mabb0tt @kpcb congrats Mike! Sounds exciting!    
    
    
    Waiting for my Kassler with Sauerkraut, while drinking a Köstritzer.    
    
    
    Just looked out of the launch room's window and saw a huge swarm of birds. Coincidence? #LetsFly    
    
    
    @Ellen_Friedman Thanks, Ellen! Hope you like it! :)    
    
    
    Cool plane we saw the other day during a flight lesson lunch break in hollister. pic.twitter.com/9QTvah4T    
    
    
    Happy birthday @maybefriday!  :)    
    
    
    From "What's new?" in IntelliJ 11: "lag-less typing even in huge documents" 2011: the year my computer started to keep up with my typing.    
    
    
    YES! I'm at the peak of my twitter career! Klout says I'm influential about one topic: Beer! #proud #germany    
    
    
    @lija so mean! #dontjudgepeoplebytheirtypos    
    
    
    @nutmegthedog is an excellent guard dog! She professionally protects the apartment from fire alarm inspectors.    
    
    
    @sunghu @thomasarend Yes, I'm a huge @bvb fan! Mats and Mario are very awesome players. :) Do you like them too?    
    
    
    @flo why was I not your date again? Are you cheating on me?    
    
    
    Fire alarm at 2:45am. Yay. #needsleep @nutmegthedog is enjoying the extra walk though :) pic.twitter.com/b9V89dRy    
    
    
    Himmel-Safari per Cessna - Namibias Skelettküste von oben http://spon.de/adxba     
    
    
    @isasun @katies @lija @thomasarend @jolanta aww so much snow! I miss winters in Germany!    
    
    
    Ein neues Wort heute gelernt: Ultraschall-Flatrate! :)    
    
    
    A happy dog riding and sniffing along on highway no 1. /cc @nutmegthedog pic.twitter.com/Dw6o1Guq    
    
    
    Javadoc of Java's Calendar class: "The first month of the year is JANUARY which is 0; the last depends on the number of months in a year."    
    
    
    @jebritton @selina_w happy birthday!! Sounds like you had a great weekend!    
    
    
    NyQuil cold medicine definitely tastes better than root beer.    
    
    
    Brille, Bier, Borussia: Dortmunds Titeljahr - Bundesliga - Bildergalerie - kicker online http://www.kicker.de/news/fussball/bundesliga/startseite/562511/2/slideshow_brille-bier-borussia_dortmunds-titeljahr.html …    
    
    
    In the plane on my way to Germany...    
    
    
    Arrived in Stuttgart and am watching Germany vs. Bosnia now!  0-1 so far, but just 35 mins played so far.  GO GERMANY!!    
    
    
    Germany-Bosnia 1-1!  What a nice goal from Lahm!    
    
    
    Germany-Bosnia 2-1!  Penalty shot, Schweinsteiger    
    
    
    Another penalty. Schweinsteiger again, 3-1!    
    
    
    Just got Rocksmith and connected my dusty guitar to the PS3 - it's pretty awesome! Remember this day when you see me on stage someday! :)    
    
    
    .@nutmegthedog just farted so loudly that she startled herself and ran to the other side of the room. #TMI    
    
    
    Arrived today in Berlin for #berlinbuzzwords.  Looking forward to good talks at an awesome looking venue!    
    
    
    @Ellen_Friedman Cool, I have my first groupie! Well, maybe @nutmegthedog  is one too :)    
    
    
    C'mon #checkstyle! "Boolean expression complexity is 14 (max allowed is 4)." Let me express myself the way I want to!    
    
    
    Have to quickly tweet from 35309 feet before I eat my "Lemon & Pepper Seasoned Tuna Medley". First flight with @VirginAmerica. AWESOME!    
    
    
    Wagemutige Weltumrundung: Abenteurer fliegt alleine einmal um die Erde - SPIEGEL ONLINE - Nachrichten - Reise http://spon.de/adyj3     
    
    
    I'm less than an hour in NYC, and less than 10 mins in a cab, but already in a traffic jam. :)    
    
    
    @chrisrueger #berlinbuzzwords IP is now whitelisted, there should be no rate limit problem anymore.    
    
    
    @techno @gakuueda Yes it is! Very fun to go to work these days! :)    
    
    
    Back in california on my way to work after a great trip to #berlinbuzzwords with lots of super nice people! Thanks all who made this happen!    
    
    
    Watching espn!  So excited that the worldcup is finally starting.  7am games aren't so bad if you have a jetlag :)    
    
    
    Go #RSA!  What a great goal! 1-0    
    
    
    @mwessendorf hey sorry ich bin in NYC. Trotzdem: HEJA BVB! :)    
    
    
    @sm @rymatic @emblem__ thank god the wheel of shots was broken. And that everyone was wearing pants.    
    
    
    @mwessendorf twitter hat hier jetzt ein office und ich hab zwei Wochen lang da gearbeitet.    
    
    
    Watching the #GER game from Santa Rosa, ca. Of course with beer, not wine! 2-0. Go Germany, my tipp was 4-0!    
    
    
    Standing in front of the ruins of Jack london's wolf house. 10 years ago I wrote a biography about him. Interesting to finally see it now.    
    
    
    @thetaph1 yes! Great game!    
    
    
    Oh man, I need the #bundesliga winterbreak to recover too! 6.30am is too early.  Anyway, GO #BVB!!    
    
    
    OH: Not sure why this isn't working... hmmm... ooh, I know why! I haven't finished implementing the backend yet! /cc @sam    
    
    
    I just voted for Literacy Bridge to win 25k on Chase Community Giving! #chasegiving http://bit.ly/9Ipaqi    
    
    
    In Germany at a Autobahn rest stop, drinking coffee and watching the snow falling. Cold but nice here. #welcomehome    
    
    
    Cool TV in my hotel room! Objects in this picture may appear bigger than they are. pic.twitter.com/m5uCS9dP    
    
    
    Nicht traurig sein #BVB. Ihr habt eine unglaubliche Hinrunde gespielt und alle Fans sind stolz auf euch!    
    
    
    @lija I hope you didn't encounter any Stinktiere.    
    
    
    The end of a crazy week with @isasun! I think we spent more hours on trains/planes than in hotel rooms. :) It was a lot of fun!    
    
    
    "interesting" morning that started at with a fire alarm and continued with an earthquake in #mountainview. Also, @nutmegthedog had diarrhea.    
    
    
    And I also spilled coffee on my laptop - ironically before, not during the earthquake    
    
    
    @krishnagade was at about 9:30am. Yeah it was quite scary, the walls were shaking twice!    
    
    
    My little niece is in there! I felt her kicking for the first time! Feels like she's already a very strong girl :) pic.twitter.com/D1aUOy3m    
    
    
    My little niece is in there! I felt her kicking for the first time! Feels like she's already a very strong girl :) pic.twitter.com/DeuKUNaG    
    
    
    Retweet this & @Bing will donate $10 to @CNN's Gulf Telethon up to $100K. More at http://bit.ly/howtodonate. #BingforGulf    
    
    
    @isasun es war super! 1-0 gewonnen! #bvbb04 #echteliebe @BVB    
    
    
    Secret service agents really do have those curly things in their ears and wear suits.    
    
    
    Great to see the president of Russia tweeting at Twitter HQ today. Have a nice stay in the Silicon Valley, Mr. Medvedev! @KremlinRussia    
    
    
    1-0 for #ger! Just came back from Pete's Tavern where several Germans were watching the game and celebrated! England, we're coming...    
    
    
    @LiteracyBridge Well, luckily both #GER and #GHA are both in the next round! :)    
    
    
    Building the #lego #mindstorms alpha rex robot together with @maybefriday.  @nutmegthedog is not very impressed...    
    
    
    Until yesterday I believed the mac made every aspect of my digital life better. Then I made a 230k svn patch without tortoise merge...    
    
    
    Not 230k bytes, but 230k lines.    
    
    
    @smileyj68 I think I'll modify twitter to reject any tweets that contain the terrible word "prolly".  @maybefriday will thank me too.    
    
    
    This is were I used to go every other week: http://bit.ly/c1chPj #BVB. Now I have to get up at 6 to watch soccer! #soccerunfriendlytimezone    
    
    
    What a day    
    
    
    @KatieS @fass4 @isasun Well, too bad that no matter how that game ends FCB will still be behind the BEST GERMAN TEAM @BVB !! :)    
    
    
    @DJanecek Hi Dieter, auf dieser Liste sind einige Spieler zu finden: https://twitter.com/#!/twitter_de/bundesliga/members …    
    
    
    @EinAugenschmaus good news - hoffentlich zieht Deutschland nach: http://techcrunch.com/2012/03/01/netflix-gets-serious-about-closed-captioning/ …    
    
    
    I paid $180 for a monthly pass and today got a citation because your system doesn't work @BayAreaClipper and @caltrain. #customerservice    
    
    
    @mikesonn @mccv @Caltrain_News The wasted time is really what I'm angry about. I wonder what can be done to fix that broken system.    
    
    
    @mikesonn @mccv @Caltrain_News Didn't kick me off, but gave citation. No I have more than $1.25. The March ticket didn't show up at all.    
    
    
    #gha you played great and should be proud!    
    
    
    @KatieS @bvb @1fsvmainz05 thanks Katie :) yes I'm still celebrating here! :)    
    
    
    Finally arrived in San Diego after 9 hour drive. Now two hours of sleep before we're heading to a German Biergarten to watch #worldcup!!    
    
    
    @DFB_Team Wir druecken euch von San Diego aus die Daumen. Schiesst Argentinien die Bude voll! Wir sind stolz auf euch, egal wie's ausgeht!    
    
    
    People waiting in line at 6.20 at #kaiserhof in San Diego to watch the Germany game! http://yfrog.com/3mq3nzj    
    
    
    This is so awesome! #ger http://yfrog.com/eau6eaj    
    
    
    @Caltrain_News @mccv @mikesonn Hi, I emailed details to the provided email address. Thanks.    
    
    
    @lija @isasun @techno @KatieS I didn't feel it either. But I was probably too far away anyway.    
    
    
    @monica @bvb they are! 7 points ahead of the 2nd! :) #echteliebe    
    
    
    Today I found out that @nutmegthedog does not like shrimp, even though she likes fish.    
    
    
    Today I landed a Citabria at San Jose International!  They told us to watch out for wake turbulences of Boings and Airbuses! #awesome    
    
    
    @asonneck @isasun Ist behoben! Zeitzonen können kompliziert sein: http://www.differencebetween.com/difference-between-pdt-and-vs-pst/ … Vielen Dank! Wir wünschen einen guten Spieltag! :)    
    
    
    The adventure begins... pic.twitter.com/NedX5fUu    
    
    
    Highway no 1 from 5500 feet. It's a beautiful day! First stop: Oceano pic.twitter.com/z8vzruPd    
    
    
    Kingman, Arizona, 9500ft. Grand canyon in the background. pic.twitter.com/OhOflPe1    
    
    
    Lots of DHL planes parked here pic.twitter.com/x89ECoeu    
    
    
    Final destination for today: Seligman, on route 66. Enjoying the first beers in the downtown bar :) pic.twitter.com/zMcq3t51    
    
    
    There's even a Stammtisch in Seligman at Lilo's :) pic.twitter.com/6ut5vtDu    
    
    
    Too windy for flying, driving trucks on dirt roads instead! :) pic.twitter.com/UGvJSZsE    
    
    
    On our way home. pic.twitter.com/cuk3GJuA    
    
    
    @lija Wow, did you draw that?    
    
    
    Das Spiel ist aus! Deutscher Meister wird nur der @BVB!!!    
    
    
    Thank you!!!!! What a day :)  #bvbfcb @maybefriday    
    
    
    Das wars fcb :)  #echteliebe #bvbfcb @BVB pic.twitter.com/c8aLeuX8    
    
    
    If the stewardess encourages the passengers to give a SECOND round of applause you've been in a pretty rough landing :) welcome to JFK!    
    
    
    Also, people around me are calling their families and telling them that they were convinced they'd die.    
    
    
    @marius yeah pretty gusty and very rainy here    
    
    
    Wow the #Lucene meetup is in a very cool location!  http://yfrog.com/5ngj2lj    
    
    
    @gsingers awesome, looking forward to seeing you there, Grant!    
    
    
    Yay!  8GB RAM upgrade.    
    
    
    Viele Grüße zurück aus Mountain View! @isasun #BVBFCB #Pokalfinale Drücke @BVB die Daumen!! :)    
    
    
    Tooooooooooooooooor!!! @BVB #BVBFCB    
    
    
    @ZDF Kommentator: "Dortmund führt den FC Bayern vor!!" 4-1 #BVBFCB @BVB    
    
    
    #Pokalsieger! @BVB #BVBFCB pic.twitter.com/ohNaxafb    
    
    
    @techno @rowbar @BVB Ja ich bin am feiern! Unglaubliches Spiel!! :)    
    
    
    Happy birthday @nutmegthedog!! pic.twitter.com/RenBeZly    
    
    
    That was one of the most undeserved goals I have ever seen in my life by Drogba. #ChampionsLeague    
    
    
    Sorry #FCB. Today even I admit that you would have deserved to win. At least you didn't play destructively and unattractively like Chelsea.    
    
    
    Respekt #Sky Kommentator! Chelsea's Trainer geht einfach weg nach der Frage: "Ihr Fußball ist effizient, aber finden sie ihn auch schön?" :)    
    
    
    Move to SF: check    
    
    
    Now it's officially confirmed: I moved into a good neighborhood! pic.twitter.com/zUhHKnii    
    
    
    OH: I downloaded the wrong cowsay cc @larsonite    
    
    
    @MarcManiez thanks, Marc. Yes was a fun evening! Have a good trip too!    
    
    
    Impressive how many people were necessary to direct me to my seat! :) The A380 is indeed a big plane.    
    
    
    Germany here I come! Looking forward to meeting a very special person soon...    
    
    
    This is the newest A380 that Lufthansa has. Just 3 weeks old. Good, makes it more likely that the wings don't have the infamous cracks yet.    
    
    
    3 live outside cameras. That is pretty cool! pic.twitter.com/5ppmUcUU    
    
    
    @Ellen_Friedman oh cool! Yeah that's where I'm headed. See you in Berlin!    
    
    
    Wow a go-around in a 380 on VERY short final. Cool, but also a little scary how late they realized that another plane was on the runway!    
    
    
    @rusashka @marcmaniez we just didn't mention it explicitly since it goes without saying that you're responsible for all the awesomeness! :)    
    
    
    @laura @MarcManiez @nsallembien @miguelrios yep I'm awake too :) very bright outside already in berlin. #iloveearlymornings    
    
    
    @hypertable 16.7M docs is the max. size for one Lucene index segment, not the size of the entire index. #pleasequotecorrectly    
    
    
    My favorite part about #bbuzz? The people. Looking forward to seeing all of you next time!    
    
    
    Just an hour left, but 2010 could still become the first year ever in which I do karaoke... drink, michael, drink faster!    
    
    
    2010, this is the last piece of "art" you make me look at? Really?    
    
    
    @michibusch  http://yfrog.com/gy5o4uj    
    
    
    @larsonite hey you can't go to bed 30 mins before midnight! Be brave!    
    
    
    Piano man did it. And Bacardi-coke    
    
    
    Endlich geht es los! #Euro2012    
    
    
    Bisher waren nur Spieler des @BVB an 100% aller Tore der #Euro2012 beteiligt! :)    
    
    
    @Konni Ja, die rote Karte war wirklich überflüssig.    
    
    
    @mwessendorf Gerne! Für ein Bier bin ich immer zu haben :)    
    
    
    Russia played really impressively. I wouldn't be surprised if they got pretty far in the tournament this time. #Euro2012 /cc @rusashka    
    
    
    My new years wish: I want to see a polar bear in the wild.    
    
    
    I left Germany 7 years ago. Today I met my two best friends. It feels like not a single day has passed. Life is good. :)    
    
    
    I think the Italians are already champions in singing their national anthem most passionately! :) #Euro2012    
    
    
    TOOOOOOOOOOOORRRR!!! 1-0 Germany!    
    
    
    @lija Awwwwwwwww :)    
    
    
    Erkenntnis des Tages: Deutscher Tütencappuccino hat tatsächlich Koffein, nicht nur extra viel Löffelschaum. #sleeplessImSauerland /cc @lija    
    
    
    @mwessendorf Auf jeden Fall!! Hab schon meine Karte fuer den 14. Mai :)    
    
    
    @monica congrats, Monica! :) Well deserved, it was a really impressive match!    
    
    
    Thanks for letting me solo today and the impressive artwork @CFI_Erik! :) /cc @goodflying #N9091L pic.twitter.com/lR8gVhq4    
    
    
    @n8agrin you should see me playing tennis.    
    
    
    $ man yes: 
NAME
     yes -- be repetitively affirmative
/cc @zhenghuali @wangtian    
    
    
    Please! Someone has to help @SelfAwareROOMBA!    
    
    
    @deliprao great time! Why did your doctor tell you not to run?    
    
    
    @hannaschaer @schaer yep I saw his SMS! The anticipation is killing me! :)    
    
    
    If they were on the same planet I think @marscuriosity and @selfawareroomba may hook up...    
    
    
    Awesome meeting @rainnwilson today!  Looking forward to enjoying the questions in #soulpancake!  http://yfrog.com/h5tbxxj    
    
    
    .@Popcorn_Indiana On the kettlecorn bag you're saying: "Our plan is to make people really, really happy." #success! :)    
    
    
    Watch "Cliff Schmidt: On-demand access to knowledge for the poor" Video at TED2013 #TEDTalentSearch http://talentsearch.ted.com/video/Cliff-Schmidt-On-demand-access#.UEAsdDc9buc.twitter …    
    
    
    @isasun @twitter_de @rowbar @lija @dhensen @katies @techno Congrats, Isa!! A good day for twitter! :) see you soon in Berlin    
    
    
    I guess that's what they do at an airport when the major airline goes on a strike. #FRA pic.twitter.com/qNhzqXIE    
    
    
    If you like your feet don't get seat 75H on lufthansa's A380    
    
    
    My little 3 months old nephew Lias! :) #proud and #happy pic.twitter.com/05Rw9jgt    
    
    
    @s1m0nw yep, gut gelandet und schon fast auf dem Weg nach Berlin. :)    
    
    
    @miguelrios yes! Can't wait for it to start. Go @BVB!!    
    
    
    @EinAugenschmaus @techno @lija @isasun @katies @dhensen It was great having you here! Keep your fingers crossed for @BVB tonight! :)    
    
    
    hello @thetaph1 - nice hanging out yesterday!    
    
    
    This was a very very good week so far - for multiple reasons.    
    
    
    It finally happened: I dreamed about code deploys last night.  At the same time a mosquito tried to kill me - unfortunately a real one.    
    
    
    Wenn bei der #Stadtwette das @BVB Logo nachgestellt würde, wäre ich schon längst auf dem Weg. #Wettendass    
    
    
    OH: I wasn't playing chess in the meeting, it was in the bathroom!    
    
    
    @lija Gute Hutwahl, Hut ab!    
    
    
    @_hossman Wow 15 months. Time flies, doesn't it?! :)    
    
    
    @smiley really?! 10/11/12 13:14? Congrats!! Very very cute :)    
    
    
    Greencard: check.    
    
    
    #TheBlackSwan was really good and Natalie Portman was absolutely incredible. I don't often leave the theater that exhausted - in a good way!    
    
    
    Dance! http://youtu.be/ERbvKrH-GC4     
    
    
    Propellor confused the panorama thing a bit, but clouds still look really cool. pic.twitter.com/AHwrjDN8    
    
    
    Wer wird Deutscher Meister? BVB BORUSSIA! Wer wird Deutscher Meister? BORUSSIA BVB!!! #bvb    
    
    
    Just got $3 change: one $2 bill, and a $1 coin. #unusual    
    
    
    OMG Tooooooooooooooooor!!! @BVB 1-0    
    
    
    Spitzenreiter der Gruppe D: @BVB! #todesgruppe #echteliebe    
    
    
    This is gonna be interesting... :) pic.twitter.com/9frlPgtF    
    
    
    A few loopings later, I'm still alive pic.twitter.com/rRJPrH1P    
    
    
    @zhenghuali luckily, unlike while driving, they don't ticket you for that :)    
    
    
    @LiteracyBridge Exciting!  Would be cool if you tweeted some pictures of the new office!!    
    
    
    Foggiest place on earth! :) #pointreyes #lucky pic.twitter.com/h6ASpNhr    
    
    
    Enjoying the view @nutmegthedog pic.twitter.com/BdUhnhMl    
    
    
    Back in #sf pic.twitter.com/E6agdHrh    
    
    
    @fgcallari Just an iphone actually. Pretty cool how good its new camera is!    
    
    
    @ablegrape @nutmegthedog Well, I think it's time for you to come back to California! :)    
    
    
    @lija Ne, noch nicht. War mein erster Acrobatic-Flug. Hat Spaß gemacht!    
    
    
    @sportschau #1 wird der @BVB, und wo der FCB landet ist dann eigentlich auch egal. :)    
    
    
    You know that you're doing something truly boring, if the laundry, that you're doing in parallel, is the much more interesting activity.    
    
    
    Unbelievable @BVB! You guys are already heros!    
    
    
    Und immer noch: Spitzenreiter @BVB! :)    
    
    
    First pain free run in over two months. Muscles seem to finally be healing. Only 20 mins, but makes me very happy. #thelittlethings    
    
    
    @ablegrape Looks like I pulled my adductor muscles and ignored it for a bit too long. How about you?    
    
    
    @ablegrape ouch! Glad it's getting better!    
    
    
    Watching Rachel @maddow video: Time for the right to leave the bubble -   http://video.msnbc.msn.com/the-rachel-maddow-show/49736294 … via @msnbc    
    
    
    @oelmo http://www.great-wall-marathon.com  ? :)    
    
    
    @isasun Hmm :) mal schauen... am liebsten mal ganz woanders laufen: http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2012/01/23/top-10-marathons-worth-traveling-for/ …    
    
    
    Look what gem I found in the mission! Worth buying a record player? :) /cc @lija @isasun @techno pic.twitter.com/iXRnNyOu    
    
    
    @EinAugenschmaus hahaha! :)    
    
    
    When the same person manages to almost run me over twice within 2 mins, at 2 intersections I question the effectiveness of CA driving tests.    
    
    
    @jelder @bdarfler Sorry for the delay.  It's online now: https://www.box.net/shared/hivdg1hge9    
    
    
    @huettermann most surprising here is that this class has >230 lines :)    
    
    
    So exciting to finally see the MIT!   http://yfrog.com/6uthetj    
    
    
    @ablegrape thank you for the fantastic pizzas and wines.  I really enjoyed the nice evening!    
    
    
    Good morning San Francisco. pic.twitter.com/oNbZoTa4    
    
    
    Sensationeller Fallrückzieher: Die große Vier-Tore-Show des Zlatan Ibrahimovic http://spon.de/vflqU  via @SPIEGELONLINE    
    
    
    Very very proud that a coworker just rated me on her "favorite coworker" scale higher than 10!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EbVKWCpNFhY …    
    
    
    YAY! So happy for @LiteracyBridge right now, winner of #thetechawards!!    
    
    
    @jewelia oh man, are the pictures embarrassing? :)    
    
    
    Really? The guy who pushes for the very sad anti-nudity law in SF is called Weiner? http://www.cnn.com/2012/11/21/us/california-san-francisco-nudity/index.html … #undressEveryone!    
    
    
    Heute spielt @MarioGoetze absolute Weltklasse! 2-0 für @BVB!!    
    
    
    Gruppensieg! Sehr, sehr stolz auf meinen @BVB!! :)    
    
    
    @plok @suppenkuche @twittersearch you're welcome! one of my major skills is to setup beer-focused events :)    
    
    
    So excited that #BVB tops the #bundesliga for the first time since 2002!  go dortmund!!    
    
    
    @kevinweil me too!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @ablegrape !! Hope you had a great day!    
    
    
    @gsingers congrats, Grant! Really happy for you!! You'll have to sign my copy when we see each other next time. :)    
    
    
    @lucasjosh you can find the slides on my linkedin profile.    
    
    
    @aam @colinkirkhodge happy to hear you enjoyed it :)    
    
    
    Doku: Dortmund-Süd, die schwarz-gelbe Wand: http://youtu.be/VuGm90VzIXc  /cc @BVB    
    
    
    @sam That's just because I didn't participate.    
    
    
    @lija Coconut filling? Sieht lecker aus :)    
    
    
    @Gotthilf_Otto I especially like that you spelled ALF, my childhood hero, in all caps. I'm a dog person though.    
    
    
    Mission accomplished! /cc @s1m0nw pic.twitter.com/9yKiRvYq    
    
    
    Dinnertime! pic.twitter.com/5130k04S    
    
    
    @s1m0nw wow, that must be a new record? :)    
    
    
    @pottblog da wohnt meine Schwester mittlerweile. Bin grade zu Besuch aus sf. Komme aber eigentlich aus dem Sauerland    
    
    
    Merry first Christmas, little Lias! :) pic.twitter.com/vpnJAf0n    
    
    
    @pottblog Danke, dir auch frohe Weihnachten!    
    
    
    @mwessendorf hi, nur über Weihnachten. Bist du auch in der nähe? Frohe Weihnachten!    
    
    
    Happy 94th birthday, grandpa! My recommendation to everyone: drink wine every day. And ride your bike until you're >94 pic.twitter.com/FombQHkx    
    
    
    Bin sehr beeindruckt wie cool Du bei Deinem Auftritt geblieben bist, 
@EinAugenschmaus! :) War echt klasse!    
    
    
    4 generations talking.  #facetime pic.twitter.com/X5irFgDV    
    
    
    @mwessendorf my little nephew, who btw is a very awesome kid!    
    
    
    What's your new year's resolution, @nutmegthedog? Subtle hint: http://youtu.be/BWAK0J8Uhzk     
    
    
    http://youtu.be/WZIY5c0CsPY     
    
    
    Almost there... pic.twitter.com/nowLZwtO    
    
    
    The new year is 10 hours old here in Germany. I really hope the pilot isn't drunk. pic.twitter.com/wP21ldwp    
    
    
    @irnnr happy new year!    
    
    
    #protip: never start a major nerf gun battle if there is a glass full of water on your desk.    
    
    
    Grass is greener in Dortmund http://www.bundesliga.com/en/liga/news/2012/0000236435.php …    
    
    
    @techno I'm very happy that we met Thomas! Also that I turned you into a @BVB fan :) Looking forward to hearing about your new adventures!    
    
    
    @HendricRuesch @flo @techno @bvb am besten für Block 14, da hab ich ne Dauerkarte! :) #echteliebe    
    
    
    @nurisahin05 Welcome home, Nuri! Und viele Grüße aus Kalifornien, wo ein treuer @BVB Fan jedes eurer Spiele guckt! :) #echteliebe    
    
    
    @CFI_Erik @goodflying thank you, Erik, for your patience and so much fun! :) #bestCFIever    
    
    
    @isasun @lija @cfi_erik @goodflying anytime! :)    
    
    
    @monica Yeah it's cool that the Bundesliga now also has the 2nd best coach in the world :) (that Jürgen Klopp is #1 goes with saying) @BVB    
    
    
    @michibusch @monica @BVB Ha, I meant 'goes without saying' :)    
    
    
    @kenbsd thank you! the shirt definitely brought me good luck :) when are you going to fly with me?    
    
    
    My first passenger! :) #brave /cc @maybefriday pic.twitter.com/be5xQua9    
    
    
    @kenbsd @maybefriday @nutmegthedog she was waiting very patiently in the flight school where various people threatened to kidnap her. :)    
    
    
    @larsonite how can you be sure it's spam? Maybe it's true? You should follow up!    
    
    
    Killing it in the game room! @yz #jointheflock http://vine.co/v/b5dpQWMFxzg     
    
    
    Sooo hungry! @nutmegthedog /cc @maybefriday http://vine.co/v/b50XaDx7W5T     
    
    
    @isasun Du hättest deine Zeit auf am/pm stellen und eine Minute warten sollen!    
    
    
    Always happy when @nutmegthedog is happy. I think right now she is :) pic.twitter.com/XjbLXCt4    
    
    
    @Ostwestf4le @stillstandpunkt HEJA BVB! :) Viel Spass im Stadion und bring drei Punkte mit!    
    
    
    @ErnieRacer glad you like it! Looking forward to lots of tweets from you! :)    
    
    
    Amazing, this pudding is good for more than 3 years! pic.twitter.com/TuEl1J3Eth    
    
    
    Good night San Francisco. pic.twitter.com/U9oeUdIFOL    
    
    
    Good job calling shotgun @nutmegthedog! :) pic.twitter.com/SEUMVLIVaI    
    
    
    I think my little nephew is very lucky and happy to have such awesome parents :) pic.twitter.com/wJ5FixQqgq    
    
    
    Guilty looking @nutmegthedog. pic.twitter.com/615ywprRg3    
    
    
    Lias can already drink by himself! pic.twitter.com/lD2XXKdh38    
    
    
    @krishnagade yes, cute, isn't he?! :)    
    
    
    Lunch time! pic.twitter.com/Iub5xIpB50    
    
    
    ... and soooo hungry pic.twitter.com/7MdzqZR6n3    
    
    
    Home. pic.twitter.com/eKNdAarQKr    
    
    
    . @KathiBusch baking pic.twitter.com/qg3WxKJFbb    
    
    
    Lias got his first own plate :) pic.twitter.com/LhAvaovFT5    
    
    
    @Ellen_Friedman thank you! It's easy because Lias is so cute :)    
    
    
    Dogs in Germany look much sadder when they can't go into places! /cc @nutmegthedog pic.twitter.com/YZCVIgX0sN    
    
    
    Three guys working very hard. #lego pic.twitter.com/vRFkJWtGUi    
    
    
    On the road to Wembley @BVB! #echteliebe #bvbmcf pic.twitter.com/BYxoa5p1O3    
    
    
    @sunghu yep, still in the stadium. Unbelievable and unforgettable.    
    
    
    Aquarium. pic.twitter.com/3YS57SmIDi    
    
    
    @pflore ja echt unglaublich! Den Tag werden wir wohl alle nie vergessen. Hat mich auch sehr gefreut - bis bald (Vielleicht Halbfinale! :) )    
    
    
    I think Lias will be a dog person! Just as his uncle :) pic.twitter.com/z80gwjHGDF    
    
    
    YAY - I did my taxes!  For the first time not on or after 4/15!  I feel like an overachiever :)    
    
    
    Rainbows. pic.twitter.com/xVznyYKpAq    
    
    
    Sauerland. pic.twitter.com/fMnq3JGphD    
    
    
    @mwessendorf @s1m0nw nice! That sounds fun. Trinkt ein Bier für mich mit! :)    
    
    
    Well, the popcorn bags are definitely smaller in Germany. pic.twitter.com/dBehgbVykI    
    
    
    @marius I wished!    
    
    
    Family time pic.twitter.com/vsH5V1q6o2    
    
    
    @pflore ja ich komme morgen! Wollen wir uns treffen?    
    
    
    Surfing with a @bvb shirt in Munich. #brave #cold #fairytale #uclfinal #echteliebe pic.twitter.com/U61gWT9txc    
    
    
    Via Dortmund to London. #uclfinal pic.twitter.com/rgwmqGEkzU    
    
    
    Dortmund Airport. pic.twitter.com/19CepgaHXD    
    
    
    Here ends the road to Wembley. We made it. Let's win this! @bvb #uclfinal #fairytale pic.twitter.com/PIM9gYeXC3    
    
    
    The sun is shining only on @bvb's side! #uclfinal pic.twitter.com/Fd9O7R7Hr1    
    
    
    