Awesome idea -> Coin » Use One Coin for All of Your Cards http://ow.ly/qPu6h     
    
    
    Battle Hack showdown in Barcelona Video: http://ow.ly/qRgwL  It was a pleasure to contribute to this awesome event as judges    
    
    
    Animated Opening Type. Really nice CSS effect by @DiegoCayenna http://ow.ly/qTkRh     
    
    
    What are the best tools to create a developers portal? We've been using wordpress but we need a more powerful solution. Thanks!    
    
    
    Sony sells over 1 million PlayStation 4 consoles in just 24 hours http://zite.to/1dHKcHI     
    
    
    Pixar's 22 Rules to Phenomenal Storytelling http://zite.to/1cBd8zU     
    
    
    @puffybsd Thanks! I've been evaluating Apigee, Mashery and 3Scale but wanted to hear recommendations like yours :)    
    
    
    @virtualCableTV Thanks! Didn't know @orchardcms Seems nice but I'd like something more specific to a developers portal to lower the workload    
    
    
    Gamification — should start-ups be interested? http://ow.ly/qU9Tu     
    
    
    The Retailers Guide to Big Data #infographic http://is.gd/RAdXXW     
    
    
    The Complete Guide to Launching a New Website http://zite.to/1gYviBr     
    
    
    When Selling Digital Content, Let the Customer Set the Price http://zite.to/19zlt4h     
    
    
    @almostvoid I find it relevant as they are selling PS4 at a higher rate than the previous generation #psFan :P    
    
    
    5 Advanced Javascript and Web Debugging Techniques You Should Know About http://zite.to/17FkapZ     
    
    
    Steve Case’s Revolution Makes Big Bets on E-Commerce http://zite.to/1gY95Dn     
    
    
    5 Ways to Increase Revenue During the Holidays http://zite.to/1dLxFDe     
    
    
    How Unbounce Uses Landing Pages for Content Marketing http://zite.to/I2ktzX 
#mustRead    
    
    
    Why the Father of the Consumer Internet Invests in Ecommerce http://zite.to/1cEuAn9     
    
    
    Without Meaningful User Experiences there is no Gamification Success http://is.gd/EDvpXm     
    
    
    Techniques for Responsive Typography http://ow.ly/qYbSx     
    
    
    Stop Thinking Keywords, Think Topics http://ow.ly/qYdTa     
    
    
    Headlines That Work: Has Science Finally Settled the Geek/Nerd Debate? http://ow.ly/qYelR     
    
    
    The Beginner’s Guide to Gamification (15 of 90): Scarcity & Impatience http://ow.ly/qYepO  /v @yukaichou    
    
    
    From the Trenches: 23 Entrepreneurs Share Their Most Valuable Lessons Learned http://zite.to/1aPvcDO     
    
    
    B2B Buyers Prefer Short Content; Rely Heavily on Google Searches http://zite.to/1bARVnX     
    
    
    2 important agile marketing insights from HubSpot's CMO http://zite.to/1aPvt9G     
    
    
    Emotion Beats Promotion By 2X http://zite.to/17J4It3     
    
    
    Top 5 Myths of Starting a Business http://is.gd/aNey2U     
    
    
    How to calculate the equity split between co-founders in a startup http://zite.to/188tT8M     
    
    
    30 Tips For Creating Content that Gets Read, Shared, and Talked About at Parties http://zite.to/188hy4k     
    
    
    Massive UK study finds video games have no negative impact on 11,000 kids http://zite.to/18pwtVS     
    
    
    Tech Is Hiring More Women Than Men For The First Time In 10 Years http://zite.to/17O2B1I     
    
    
    SEO Tips for Prestashop Stores http://j.mp/1dnEoqO  via @inboundorg    
    
    
    Top 5 Reasons why Customer-Centric Efforts Fail http://zite.to/1jrjvsb     
    
    
    BigDoor moves beyond gamification to focus on loyalty programs  http://ow.ly/r52Qr  Fear of BadgeVille or #gamification is not enough    
    
    
    Why FourSquare's Decision of Phasing Out Gamification is a Great Mistake http://is.gd/sAc8c6     
    
    
    Gamification: Merchants of Meth or Merchants of Faith http://ow.ly/r52Uu     
    
    
    To Improve SEO, Focus on the Page http://ow.ly/r5EXE  /v @PracticalEcomm    
    
    
    Content Marketing Playbook: 24 Epic Ideas for Connecting with Your Customers [Deck] http://ow.ly/r5Fnh     
    
    
    Applying App Design Concepts to Website Design http://ow.ly/r5FsW     
    
    
    Embracing Paradoxes and Narratives in Education http://ow.ly/r5FF0  #gamification    
    
    
    17 SEO Best Practices That Could Double Your E-Commerce Sales http://ow.ly/r5GjU     
    
    
    Interesting Infographics: How B2B Sales Has Changed http://zite.to/Il58cR     
    
    
    6 Proven Ways to Boost the Conversion Rates of Your Call-to-Action Buttons http://ow.ly/r5GlW     
    
    
    How Google Plus Profiles & Pages Gain Search Authority http://ow.ly/r5Grj     
    
    
    David Ogilvy’s Prophetic “Secret Weapon” of Selling http://ow.ly/r5Gtx     
    
    
    2014 SEO Roadmap: Adopting Semantic Markup http://ow.ly/r5GEE     
    
    
    The New Rules Of Disruption http://zite.to/IbtTZy     
    
    
    Motorola Will Use 3D Printing For Its Customizable Smartphones http://zite.to/I5ifz1     
    
    
    @wernerkeil XDDDD    
    
    
    Signs point up for B2B e-commerce http://zite.to/I4LaU4     
    
    
    I'm at Republic Space (Boadilla del Monte, Madrid) http://4sq.com/18z854i     
    
    
    A merendar http://instagram.com/p/hGv4TRALF_/     
    
    
    Analytics Don’t Lie: Product Content is Content Marketing http://zite.to/1e9m2WQ     
    
    
    #Ecommerce, en clave retail http://ow.ly/r813J  /v @aliciadavara @daretail    
    
    
    Focusing on the top 20 percent of your customers http://ow.ly/r81ju     
    
    
    Want to be a successful founder? Not without these qualities http://zite.to/1fztpdT     
    
    
    Betabeers Madrid. Especial Failshow, 3 diciembre 2013 - Betabeers http://ow.ly/r9e4l     
    
    
    How Design And User Experience Translates To The Bottom Line http://zite.to/17YXwnh     
    
    
    The Golden Age of Watching Other People Play Video Games http://zite.to/1jxhjiU     
    
    
    @juansandesv Así me gusta ;)    
    
    
    Should companies be making more of gamification? http://zite.to/IdcmQK     
    
    
    3 Ways Twitter Is Changing TV Forever http://zite.to/1aGvL76     
    
    
    B2B Content Marketing in 2013 [Infographic] http://is.gd/Bb6lSO     
    
    
    Customer Acquisition http://zite.to/19Vb8Q7  and why you should focus on loyalty and customer service    
    
    
    Arm yourself: The API wars are coming http://zite.to/1aZ4NUb     
    
    
    The Search Engine Market in Russia http://ow.ly/rbSYc  #infographic #search    
    
    
    Here's why 2014 will be the year of the 'Internet of things' http://zite.to/17ORZ5R     
    
    
    Data is the new sexy http://is.gd/YxBPc4     
    
    
    Okay, Google, you officially beat Siri http://zite.to/1c3koGJ     
    
    
    80% of teens shop online, and their favorite web retailer is Amazon http://zite.to/IpDeg1     
    
    
    Python Displacing R As The Programming Language For Data Science http://zite.to/1aTKbA2     
    
    
    Conversion Rate Optimization Infographic http://ow.ly/re4Mc     
    
    
    Six ways to drive conversions using geo-personalisation http://ow.ly/rcEUJ  /v @patriciohunt    
    
    
    Boost Your CTR for the Holidays by Picking Your Best Creative http://zite.to/1blUdg7     
    
    
    Suzana Herculano-Houzel: What is so special about the human brain? http://zite.to/1jGIiIW     
    
    
    A Warning to Ecommerce Startups: The Future of Online is Offline http://zite.to/1b2twab     
    
    
    E-commerce: 10 case studies to help you excel in content marketing, social media and website optimization http://zite.to/1jEOdyb     
    
    
    Email Marketing Trends of 2014 http://ow.ly/rgmDW  #emailMarketing    
    
    
    The Real Future of Social is Search http://zite.to/1dBEACP     
    
    
    Data is the new sexy http://is.gd/YxBPc4     
    
    
    Email Marketing Trends of 2014 http://ow.ly/rgmHr     
    
    
    In defense of the fat startup http://zite.to/17Zp15r     
    
    
    @VictorJuarezP XDDD @jorgegonzalezm9 @ramonvmr @javiercuervo    
    
    
    Mark Zuckerberg Inside Facebook http://is.gd/CrZHkd     
    
    
    To pivot or not to pivot http://is.gd/69H9GH     
    
    
    America's Fastest Growing Enterprise Software Companies of 2013 http://zite.to/1ioyAzp     
    
    
    TV evolution: The war for the start screen http://zite.to/18ekxmi     
    
    
    15 Rocking Content Marketing Tools with Advice from Experts http://zite.to/1inKCJs     
    
    
    Replacing (most of) d3.js with pure SVG + AngularJS http://zite.to/1iqeeWK     
    
    
    How Game Based Learning is Making Training Better http://zite.to/199y130     
    
    
    Consumer drones are coming, and they will change everything http://zite.to/18St3uY     
    
    
    A Company Without APIs Is Like A Computer Without Internet http://zite.to/Imhxhq     
    
    
    Stores Use New Technology To Obsessively Track You http://zite.to/ImqsPN     
    
    
    Sight, a Short Futuristic Film that Shows A Gamified Future http://is.gd/5V0OPB     
    
    
    Onboarding New Users Is Harder Than You Think http://zite.to/1bbdTRd     
    
    
    How to Grow Your Blog to 100,000 Visits a Month Within 1.5 Years http://zite.to/1bdoEz6     
    
    
    Eventazo organizado por @Intelectium Next Generation #ecommerce @WEAREKNITTERS @brokerfashion @brainsins_es @moodyo http://ht.ly/rmnjL     
    
    
    Gym Time http://instagram.com/p/heMXzOgLJ7/     
    
    
    http://DIY.org : Gamification for Makers http://is.gd/QUcrsM     
    
    
    Apple Acquires Twitter Analytics Platform Topsy For $200 Million http://zite.to/IEO2Y1     
    
    
    10 Tops to Make the Most of Pinterest in Your Online Store http://zite.to/18kdett     
    
    
    27 Ways to Reduce Shopping Fears on your Ecommerce Website http://zite.to/1jiFRyU     
    
    
    5 data scientists who became CEOs — and are leading thriving companies http://zite.to/1cTIaDP     
    
    
    20 Beautiful Examples Of Persuasive Ecommerce Design http://zite.to/IMQrk3     
    
    
    Efficiently Simplifying Navigation, Part 1: Information Architecture http://zite.to/1cWNUw5     
    
    
    Why FourSquare's Decision of Phasing Out Gamification is a Great Mistake http://is.gd/sAc8c6     
    
    
    11 SEO Changes That Will Give You Big Results http://zite.to/1kbcNqD     
    
    
    Why Is Google Buying So Many Robot Startups? http://zite.to/1bi5FTY     
    
    
    5 Ways Retailers Benefit from ‘Internet of Things’ http://zite.to/1gE674i     
    
    
    ASOS nails Pinterest this Christmas http://zite.to/1d0nqtS     
    
    
    @NoeliaRuiz81 XDDDDD @aCodigoAbierto    
    
    
    4 Reasons Why B2B Content Marketing is Hard to Get Right http://zite.to/18cPKMa     
    
    
    Without Meaningful User Experiences there is no Gamification Success http://is.gd/EDvpXm     
    
    
    5 experiences commerce websites should replicate from the Apple Store http://zite.to/IPEzgG     
    
    
    US startup valuations reach ten year highs http://zite.to/1f2myqR     
    
    
    7 Black Friday and Cyber Monday Landing Page Examples [with critiques] http://zite.to/1cftQ6A     
    
    
    Cratejoy is a website builder and eCommerce backend for subscription eCommerce stores http://zite.to/1hEyzWQ     
    
    
    10 reasons everyone at your startup should blog http://is.gd/Ei5JKO     
    
    
    Luxury Consumers Respond to Exclusive Access, Not Promotion
http://www.emarketer.com/Article/Luxury-Consumers-Respond-Exclusive-Access-Not-Promotion/1010419#mSvhurCRDzDWkhUd.99 …    
    
    
    Use Hashtags More Effectively in Your Social Media Content: 4 Tactics http://ow.ly/ryMj7     
    
    
    SEO: Leveraging Bing’s Pinterest Integration http://ow.ly/ryMjN     
    
    
    20 beautiful examples of persuasive ecommerce design http://ow.ly/ryMlq     
    
    
    6 of the Most Amazing Mobile eCommerce Experiences of 2013 http://ow.ly/ryMmM     
    
    
    Northern European ecommerce to grow to €31bln http://ow.ly/ryMny     
    
    
    Graphene Is Going to Change the World, specially when Moore's Law doesn't longer apply http://zite.to/IKktE3     
    
    
    Glasses vs Watch: A Battle for the Future Internet http://is.gd/7FYXP5     
    
    
    5 Secrets of High-Converting Email Newsletters http://ow.ly/ryMob     
    
    
    2014 Cheat Sheet: New Methods For Finding B2B Customers [Infographic] http://ow.ly/ryMp9     
    
    
    Damn Son, Update Your Off-Page SEO for 2014 http://ow.ly/ryMrg     
    
    
    Google rumored to launch its own TV set-top box under the Nexus brand next year http://ow.ly/ryPeB     
    
    
    12 Content Marketing Books to Add to Your Holiday Gift List http://ow.ly/ryPyk  Just bought many of them :)    
    
    
    Will gamification stay relevant? http://ow.ly/rySfn  Lots of people screwing it up, but also more relevant example, so it will survive    
    
    
    Hospital fights employee obesity with social sharing and gamification http://ow.ly/rySio     
    
    
    So bad RT @hmason: Creativity is rejected: Teachers and bosses don’t value out-of-the-box thinking. http://slate.me/1gPLu5k     
    
    
    #mustRead for B2B marketers RT @iRhodes 10 Phrases I Want You To Remove From Your B2B Website, Right Now! http://www.rhodesconsultancy.com/planning/10-terms-i-want-you-to-remove-from-your-b2b-website-right-now/ …    
    
    
    Adapt to each user's needs RT @peeplaja Long Form or Short Form? Why Not Both? http://conversionxl.com/long-form-or-short-form-why-not-both/ … guest post by @DholakiyaPratik    
    
    
    The Retailers Guide to Big Data #infographic http://is.gd/RAdXXW     
    
    
    Shopping Cart Page Recommendation Strategy http://ow.ly/rByM4  How to get more from product recommendations in your cart page #ecommerce    
    
    
    @megova Jajaja, falo galego na intimidade :P    
    
    
    Henkel Ibérica abre el primer ShopperLab http://ow.ly/rzMVr  /v @revistaARAL    
    
    
    More important than testing itself RT @peeplaja: My (condensed) answer to how to determine what to test: http://www.growthhackers.com/ask-gh-how-do-you-determine-which-tests-to-run-on-a-site-when-looking-to-optimize-conversion-rates/#comment-1971 …    
    
    
    Google a seguir dando por culo... RT @jordiobdotcom: Cambios en el tracking de emailings desde gMail http://goo.gl/fb/2XPO2  #ecommerce    
    
    
    The Collaborative Economy Is Real (And It's Here) http://zite.to/18QJBG1     
    
    
    Target Tests An Online Store Powered By Pinterest, Called The 'Awesome Shop' http://zite.to/1ffjtDJ     
    
    
    Netflix open sources its data traffic cop, Suro http://zite.to/1dj81Fe     
    
    
    The Future of Content: Upcoming Trends in 2014 http://zite.to/18hY25o     
    
    
    The 13 Best Science and Technology Books of 2013; just buying one of those :) http://zite.to/18z8jrF     
    
    
    Online sales were worth £164bn in 2012, equal to 6% of business turnover http://zite.to/1cmxXxT     
    
    
    1 in 2 Consumers Say That YouTube Videos Have Influenced A Purchase Decision http://zite.to/J2o54G     
    
    
    Stop Tweeting Your Blog Posts Only Once: The Case for Re-sharing on Social Media http://zite.to/1e3CUlQ     
    
    
    The Habits of Successful People: Be Inconsistent http://zite.to/1gmk2yQ  it makes sense    
    
    
    Why Your Offline Business Doesn’t Convert Well to an Ecommerce Business http://zite.to/18ABAm3     
    
    
    @FkieCarrero What happens?    
    
    
    E-Commerce Sites Need 2 Types of Breadcrumbs (68% Get it Wrong) http://zite.to/1dla7Ew     
    
    
    Three key rules of gamification of the workplace http://zite.to/18xh6dJ     
    
    
    How To Know You’ve Hit First Traction In SaaS. The Moment When You’ve Got A Real Company http://ow.ly/rEXSp  /v @RogerPiqueP    
    
    
    10 Ways to Speed Up Your Website – and Improve Conversion by 7% http://zite.to/18UsPWp     
    
    
    Die, Flash, Die http://is.gd/8EgHhz     
    
    
    Tablets Are Becoming A Favorite Shopping Tool, And They're Used Totally Differently From Smartphones http://zite.to/IFE5tE     
    
    
    Survey: Majority Use Smartphones In Stores, Not For E-Commerce http://zite.to/1aVcScE     
    
    
    Shopify Raises $100M To Drop The ‘E’ And Become The Commerce Company That Spans On- And Offline http://zite.to/1jQXHJm     
    
    
    5 Ways to Utilize Thank You Pages for Reconversions http://zite.to/1gZX8e7     
    
    
    @RSaltor Cracks! Enhorabuena! @SelfPackaging    
    
    
    +1000 RT @anitarm: Esta vez querido compi @Joseluisferrero te has superado. Enhorabuena!! Ole, ole,  ole.  #desayunosPhilips    
    
    
    Increased productivity, the real business case for gamification http://ow.ly/rFYbX     
    
    
    Content Marketing in 2014: Are You Prepared? http://zite.to/1bxA5Sd     
    
    
    #mustRead RT @PerryMarshall: What Conversion Tactics Will Make the Biggest Difference in 2014? http://buff.ly/198lJM0     
    
    
    15 Pinterest Users Every Designer Should Follow http://zite.to/1f9p3a9     
    
    
    Real-Life Conversion Lessons: Features vs. Benefits http://zite.to/1jRaMTe     
    
    
    Nokia & deadmau5 'This is Lumia' light show in London http://ow.ly/rJfo5  http://ow.ly/rJfv3  Bad I missed that! /v @PrincesaSEO    
    
    
    #FF to my top 3 followers of the week @brainsins_es @patriciohunt @YouPaparazz   Check it out at:  http://www.gamisfaction.com/josek_net?utm_source=timeline&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=followfriday …    
    
    
    Amigo invisible en @brainsins_es :D http://ow.ly/i/40PfI     
    
    
    SM is part of Content Marketing - > 5 Reasons Social media is Just as Important as Content in Marketing Today http://zite.to/1flXonc     
    
    
    If you are angry with everybody, then the real problem is that you are angry with yourself    
    
    
    Back to school http://instagram.com/p/h3iyUmALK9/     
    
    
    Conversion rate optimisation: eight case studies that show the benefit of UX testing http://zite.to/18WrP48     
    
    
    Tablets in Education Brings Everything to a New Level http://zite.to/IT8WCx     
    
    
    XD RT @aldamiz: Interruption marketing http://www.pinterest.com/pin/46936021090670618/ …    
    
    
    So damn right! RT @jmgomez: The key word in “Data Science” is not Data, it is Science | @leekgroup http://ow.ly/rJ3WD  #datamining    
    
    
    How Retailers Using Facebook’s Custom Audiences Can Track Offline Sales http://zite.to/1kH9Dv8     
    
    
    Absolut con Sprite http://instagram.com/p/h6yZBmgLAi/     
    
    
    The first trailer for Christopher Nolan's next project 'Interstellar' is here http://zite.to/1ddEXyA     
    
    
    Six common conversion killers from ecommerce sites http://zite.to/1jYsFzB     
    
    
    Lessons Learned: Fashionable Maternity Wear Sells http://zite.to/18HqsRd  /v @practicalecomm    
    
    
    Gartner Sticks to its Failing Gamification Prediction http://zite.to/18Zdxje     
    
    
    Tanagustico... http://instagram.com/p/h8QunigLCT/     
    
    
    Taking DynamoDB beyond Key-Value: Now with Faster, More Flexible, More Powerful Query Capabilities http://zite.to/1hPCDni     
    
    
    @jordiobdotcom XDDDDDD    
    
    
    Want Conversions? Start with User-Friendly, Useful Landing Pages http://zite.to/1bINsn0     
    
    
    Why Do Companies Choose Node? Performance, Scalability and Productivity http://zite.to/1bME6GU     
    
    
    Healing the Disconnect Between Ecommerce and Customer Experience http://zite.to/1dxxOK2     
    
    
    About PayPal's Node vs Java “fight” http://zite.to/1eaYepI  great analysis but still would be interesting to have more info from inside PP    
    
    
    B2B Content Marketing in 2013 [Infographic] http://is.gd/Bb6lSO     
    
    
    Big data and analytics trends for 2014 http://zite.to/1ja9moR     
    
    
    5 Predictions On The Future Of Databases (From A Guy Who Knows Databases) http://zite.to/1bFvqRH     
    
    
    As Software Eats The World, Non-Tech Corporations Are Eating Startups http://zite.to/JkAhOB     
    
    
    Why is a shopping mall in Thailand Instagram’s most photographed place in 2013? http://zite.to/1bITiR9     
    
    
    5 Content Marketing Trends & Predictions for 2014 http://zite.to/1dE70rC     
    
    
    Expanding options for mining streaming data http://zite.to/1k5bITW     
    
    
    I'm at Brainsins Headquarters http://4sq.com/198xLad     
    
    
    This will be bigger for Amazon than drones http://zite.to/1cLEZ2H     
    
    
    The Full Stack Marketer http://is.gd/V2ruTy     
    
    
    How One SaaS Startup Reduced Churn 71% Using “Red Flag” Metrics http://zite.to/1jcq2w0     
    
    
    20 Beautiful Examples Of Persuasive Ecommerce Design http://zite.to/JA2cLa     
    
    
    16 Tips for Balancing Website Design and Conversion http://zite.to/IZPAM0     
    
    
    Ecommerce Merchants Should Not Ignore Older Shoppers http://zite.to/18REBhG     
    
    
    Absolutely! RT @ContentVerve: Is Emotion Necessary To Make More Sales? http://conversionxl.com/is-emotion-necessary-to-make-more-sales/ … via @peeplaja    
    
    
    Top 5 Myths of Starting a Business http://is.gd/aNey2U     
    
    
    Hot Ass http://instagram.com/p/iCfktNgLCJ/     
    
    
    @jordiobdotcom :P    
    
    
    #Gamification of reading RT @evgenymorozov Kindle has a new feature called FreeTime that allows kids to earn badges and awards for reading    
    
    
    The LG Chromebase is an all-in-one PC powered by Google’s Chrome OS http://zite.to/1cayKah     
    
    
    IBM: In 5 Years, Buying Local Will Beat Buying Online http://zite.to/1fCGdxD     
    
    
    Gato Cósmico http://instagram.com/p/iEMHUygLFR/     
    
    
    The Top UX Trends of 2013 http://zite.to/JEzGIk     
    
    
    The future of API design: The orchestration layer http://zite.to/1dkKdAF     
    
    
    Testing @canva and it's a freaking awesome tool for marketers. Lets you create amazing designs in minutes! #awesome #lovingIt    
    
    
    How to innovate? Google exec explains http://zite.to/1bMWFq2     
    
    
    Why VCs should stop investing in 'Internet' startups and start investing in 'tech' http://zite.to/1bMgqxX     
    
    
    eCommerce Means Real Business Models on the Internet http://is.gd/s8vTns     
    
    
    Office... morning... http://instagram.com/p/iGLWWhALF_/     
    
    
    Will be even bigger RT @WIRED: Why wearable tech will be as big as the smartphone http://wrd.cm/18OFZPg     
    
    
    Discovering Canva, "a simple new way to design". An amazing tool http://ow.ly/rSbqf     
    
    
    Increased Productivity – the real reason for introducing gamification http://ow.ly/rSt96     
    
    
    Big Data Gets Smart, Personalization Gets Personal http://ow.ly/rSteY     
    
    
    2014 Forecast: Gamification and the Year Ahead in Banking http://ow.ly/rSth9     
    
    
    The Flood of Big Data [Infographic] http://is.gd/T5YQKa     
    
    
    #ecommcena #eCommBeers #ecommCracks #ecommAmigos http://ow.ly/i/44S7x  #ecommerce    
    
    
    Easing the Pain of Keyword Not Provided: 5 Tactics for Reclaiming Your Data http://zite.to/1bOCjge     
    
    
    What’s the big deal with big data? Breaking down the year’s buzzword http://zite.to/1jfLJLQ     
    
    
    15 High Performance Habits That Will Make You Successful http://zite.to/1c9Au3A     
    
    
    Email Subject Lines: Words and Tactics That Boost Open Rates http://zite.to/1dhDM13     
    
    
    Gamify Your Digital Marketing http://zite.to/19STq0C     
    
    
    8 Simple Scientifically Proven Ways to Improve Your Writing http://zite.to/1fmMn4d     
    
    
    Little Girl Gets 3D Printed Hand http://ow.ly/rXuZT  /cc @picoj @martapanera @pabloechanove @joseluisferrero @hectoriglesiasm    
    
    
    @rafabillor @AntBogarin Thanks! Revocando acceso a la app. Abrazo!    
    
    
    http://Overstock.com  Will Start Taking Bitcoin Next Year http://zite.to/JHUMoo     
    
    
    Introducing Open Salaries at Buffer: Our Transparent Formula and All Individual Salaries http://zite.to/1horhnq  nice concept    
    
    
    6 Reasons Why Feedly is the Best Alternative to Google Reader http://is.gd/V6Toqr     
    
    
    Is REST losing its flair – REST API Alternatives http://ow.ly/rWYuo     
    
    
    Merck turns to gamification in diabetes http://ow.ly/rXizU     
    
    
    How To Make LinkedIn Help Your Lead Generation Efforts http://ow.ly/rXiPj     
    
    
    @FitsYourProfile great! :)    
    
    
    Simplify Your Inbound Marketing Process: Focus on Content Assets http://ow.ly/rXjk1     
    
    
    Why Your Gamification Efforts Are Failing http://ow.ly/rXjm0     
    
    
    You can now build an interactive mobile app, no code required, thanks to Facebook http://zite.to/1drUKtY     
    
    
    Why Startups No Longer need a Business Plan http://zite.to/18DsuXM     
    
    
    @hugomunro Yes, but don't make it the "Bible", focus on determining your main hypothesis and spend more time testing and validating those    
    
    
    A KPI dashboard for early-stage SaaS startups – new and improved! http://zite.to/1cYcmj4     
    
    
    FinalCutEando http://instagram.com/p/iO14pGgLEj/     
    
    
    eCommerce: the Perfect Product Page http://zite.to/1gICvWo     
    
    
    How to Make an Infographic (Even When You’re Not a Designer) http://zite.to/1c4lQsO     
    
    
    Email Marketing: 3 resources to help you close the automation gap http://zite.to/1bg0ggy     
    
    
    15 Content Marketing Tips From The Pros http://zite.to/19FR0pM     
    
    
    @happywebcoder En @brainsins_es pujamos por 120€ #RaulBookSale :)    
    
    
    Carmat's groundbreaking five-year artificial heart gets its first patient in France http://zite.to/1biuwHE     
    
    
    The Top UX Predictions for 2014 http://zite.to/1cGwbrt     
    
    
    Python Displacing R As The Programming Language For Data Science http://zite.to/1js2h3i     
    
    
    How Retail Businesses Use Business Intelligence to Maximize Profitability http://zite.to/1l5yGbt     
    
    
    A set of flat and 3D progress button styles where the button itself serves as a progress indicator http://ow.ly/rZK4K     
    
    
    @txampa Que chulada. Disfruta!    
    
    
    P&G Launch 6 New Facebook Stores: “Live Learning Labs” [Screenshots] http://ow.ly/rZKdT  #fCommerce #experiments    
    
    
    The Ultimate Guide to Startup Marketing http://is.gd/h5ZnMl     
    
    
    #AliOli rico, rico... :) http://instagram.com/p/iR21LFALGd/     
    
    
    Curating Content Or Creating It: Which Drives More B2B Conversions? http://ow.ly/rZKf6     
    
    
    @Astillazo LOOOOOOL \cc @al_cuevas    
    
    
    13 Ways to Improve Email Unsubscribe http://ow.ly/rZKbq     
    
    
    Probably the Smartest Thread You’ll Read on (Social) E-Commerce… http://ow.ly/rZKhO  #mustRead    
    
    
    How to Gracefully Transition from Keywords to Topics http://ow.ly/rZKna     
    
    
    Pure Energy http://instagram.com/p/iTKuN-gLJV/     
    
    
    8 Reasons Why You Need to Establish Authority on Google+ http://ow.ly/rZKrX     
    
    
    From the Top @ Brainsins Headquarters http://instagram.com/p/iTk_RFgLDk/     
    
    
    The Ultimate Guide to Startup Marketing http://ow.ly/rZKIr     
    
    
    Die, Flash, Die http://is.gd/8EgHhz     
    
    
    Octalysis of 8 Gamified Alarm Clock http://ow.ly/rZKqG  /v @yukaichou    
    
    
    The 35 Most Spectacular Wildlife Photos From The National Geographic Photo Contest http://ow.ly/rZODM  #awesome /cc @Monlabiaga    
    
    
    Christmas Breakfast @ JoSeK's Home http://instagram.com/p/iV2gR7ALB6/     
    
    
    Why founders should never sacrifice company culture http://zite.to/1l6BKnq     
    
    
    Impala v Hive http://zite.to/1id93Z6  #bigdata    
    
    
    @jordiobdotcom Ratito para el lego, ratito para el twitter, ratito para la PS3, ratito para el lego... #queDuraEsLaNavidad :P XD    
    
    
    The Four Architectures that will inspire your programming http://zite.to/1cYJ7wq     
    
    
    #mustRead RT @FkieCarrero: Very much agreed! "SMB: The Third Market" http://ow.ly/s0HMU  @startupcfo    
    
    
    If You're Content Marketing Isn't Serving One of These 4 Goals You're Wasting Your Time http://zite.to/1cs8cBx     
    
    
    The Trends That Ruled Pinterest In 2013 http://zite.to/19auc0S     
    
    
    Sight, a Short Futuristic Film that Shows A Gamified Future http://is.gd/5V0OPB     
    
    
    Apache Spark for Big Analytics http://zite.to/1eAxNd2  #dataAnalysis    
    
    
    Mi tribuna en @daretail -> "Ni E, ni M, ni S, ni T, ni Símplemente Commerce" http://ow.ly/s4FaJ     
    
    
    The Retailers Guide to Big Data #infographic http://is.gd/RAdXXW     
    
    
    Segmentation 101: Start, Split, Test, Maintain | Targeting & Segmentation http://ow.ly/s45fq     
    
    
    Are These 6 Ecommerce Copywriting Mistakes Costing You Sales? http://ow.ly/s45kQ     
    
    
    14 Most Important Metrics To Focus In Your Digital Marketing Campaign (Infographic) http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/rlyDoCAioZw/14-important-metrics-focus-digital-marketing-campaign-infographic-0725245 …    
    
    
    3 Stages of The Universal Marketing Funnel http://ow.ly/s45lr     
    
    
    #FF to my top 3 followers of the week @jordiobdotcom @ValeraMariscal @javiercuervo   Check it out at:  http://www.gamisfaction.com/josek_net?utm_source=timeline&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=followfriday …    
    
    
    Why B2B Content Marketing Must Go Beyond Random Acts of Publishing http://ow.ly/s45m0     
    
    
    Mission ImposSERPble 2: User Intent and Click Through Rates http://ow.ly/s45mr     
    
    
    Improve product pages by 35 percent — Ecommerce Checklist http://ow.ly/s45nc  #ecommerce    
    
    
    6 Tools for Building Unique Landing Pages http://www.practicalecommerce.com/articles/62537-6-Tools-for-Building-Unique-Landing-Pages …    
    
    
    The Integrated Marketing Imperative: Transition from Optimizing Keywords to Optimize for Customers http://ow.ly/s45oY     
    
    
    How to Develop a Content Marketing Strategy: The First 3 Steps http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/BWg8hw0i97s/develop-content-marketing-strategy-first-3-steps-0725115 …    
    
    
    2013 has been a year of epic proportions for e-commerce in China, and it’s only set to grow http://zite.to/1cT8KeB     
    
    
    To pivot or not to pivot http://is.gd/69H9GH     
    
    
    The Future of How We Shop #infographic http://www.brainsins.com/en/blog/the-future-of-how-we-shop-infographic/2546?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=the-future-of-how-we-shop-infographic …    
    
    
    Top 5 Game-Changing Gadgets of 2013 http://zite.to/1bqvOjG     
    
    
    5 Ways Pinterest Can Make Products More ‘Touchable’ http://zite.to/1fKR08z     
    
    
    How To Disrupt A Market and Bootstrap A Company To $10 Million In Revenue In 3 Years  http://ow.ly/s5r6b     
    
    
    Professional Development for Digital Marketers: How to Up Your Game in 2014 http://ow.ly/s5r7j     
    
    
    How to Overcome the Top 3 B2B Content Marketing Challenges in 2014 http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/oEFRbqPqMgk/overcome-top-3-b2b-content-marketing-challenges-2014-0719748 …    
    
    
    When is a great moment for a SaaS startup to create an affiliate program?  http://ow.ly/s5rl8     
    
    
    #eCommerce goes #local RT @loogic: Elephanti Raises $4.5M To Help Shoppers Find Products In Nearby Stores http://feedly.com/e/0AOz9Ey9     
    
    
    So You’ve Decided To Open-Source A Project At Work. What Now? http://zite.to/1hIDBiL     
    
    
    Mola! :) RT @Thrillka: Shop is open! :) http://etsy.com/shop/Chikai  @BrightonEtsy    
    
    
    @jordiobdotcom XDDD no hay hamburguesa que se me resista :P @Monlabiaga    
    
    
    Chromebooks' success punches Microsoft in the gut http://zite.to/1lo5Zqc     
    
    
    @blairrorani For most people, a small notebook such as yours is all they need, although 10" tablets are a good substitute in most cases    
    
    
    @blairrorani Agree! I still use my laptop for video editing, graphic design and coding, but it's a pleasure to travel+work with a 10" tablet    
    
    
    The Sad State of Sentiment Analysis http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/0Xppy_VrPtc/sad-state-sentiment-analysis-0725232 …    
    
    
    @DollarShaveClub has the most amazing explanation video ever http://www.dollarshaveclub.com/  #startups    
    
    
    Effective Technical Leadership http://ow.ly/s858s  /v @javisantana    
    
    
    Why FourSquare's Decision of Phasing Out Gamification is a Great Mistake http://is.gd/sAc8c6     
    
    
    4 Simple but Effective Remarketing Tips by @bethany_bey http://www.searchenginejournal.com/4-simple-effective-remarketing-tips/82193/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=4-simple-effective-remarketing-tips …    
    
    
    7 Reasons for Free Delivery in Your eCommerce Store http://ow.ly/s7NSD     
    
    
    Extreme Content Marketing With Red Bull http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/A9sJvUzv70A/extreme-content-marketing-red-bull-0723742 …    
    
    
    Essential Elements for Checkout Conversion http://ow.ly/s7NSX     
    
    
    Leading Experts Predict The Content Marketing Trends for 2014 by @murraynewlands http://feeds.searchenginejournal.com/~r/SearchEngineJournal/~3/CN3Eqw1gCf4/ …    
    
    
    Reducing Shopping Cart Abandonment in eCommerce: the Right Price http://ow.ly/s7NTD     
    
    
    +1000 RT @rickygervais: Remember kids, if you don't sin, then Jesus died for nothing.    
    
    
    6 Dataset Lists Curated By Data Scientists http://zite.to/1agXDLL     
    
    
    Scientists exploring computers that can learn and adapt http://zite.to/1cAd8Tm     
    
    
    Deshielo http://instagram.com/p/iifIX5gLO_/     
    
    
    In technology, 2013 was a more amazing year than you think http://zite.to/1jXRldM     
    
    
    Boost Online B2B Lead Conversions Using Retargeting http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/Nqkgb_B1RRw/boost-online-b2b-lead-conversions-using-retargeting-0726171 …    
    
    
    Successful Growth Secrets for the CMO http://ow.ly/s8Iz9     
    
    
    How to Start an Affiliate Marketing Business in 2014 http://ow.ly/s8IAq     
    
    
    We’re About to Lose Net Neutrality — And the Internet as We Know It http://ow.ly/s8IDz     
    
    
    In-App Purchases Take Over App Revenues http://ow.ly/s8IEy     
    
    
    Personal Brand Marketing Tips from 3 Influential Women http://ow.ly/s8IFH     
    
    
    Dile tu algo... @ Brainsins Headquarters http://instagram.com/p/ijOyhEgLJO/     
    
    
    10 Website design trends that we will see in 2014 - http://klou.tt/1fzcm1v9r28ba     
    
    
    How To Grow A Community, Tips For Community Managers: Interview With Ann Smarty http://ow.ly/s8IGi     
    
    
    Why Small Businesses Aren’t Maximizing the Rewards of Content Marketing http://ow.ly/s8IJi     
    
    
    How to Send Perfectly Timed “Abandoned Cart” Emails http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/DnX6msrMBi4/send-perfectly-timed-abandoned-cart-emails-0725137 …    
    
    
    @guiyermoruiz Un placer leerte! :D    
    
    
    11 Secrets to Reduce Bounce Rate Dramatically http://ow.ly/s8IQ0     
    
    
    Shopping Cart Page Recommendation Strategy http://klou.tt/1mqk0cl5rkltd  #eCommerce #CRO #personalization    
    
    
    How to Choose your eCommerce CMS #infographic http://www.brainsins.com/en/blog/how-to-choose-your-ecommerce-cms-infographic/2553?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=how-to-choose-your-ecommerce-cms-infographic …    
    
    
    6 vital e-commerce metrics http://ow.ly/s8IRm  #ecommerce #analytics    
    
    
    Long-Form Video Content Rivals Short, Even on Smartphones http://ow.ly/s8IUw     
    
    
    I'm at Brainsins Headquarters http://4sq.com/1k2M4Sv     
    
    
    Three Ways to Use Surveys to Increase Ecommerce Sales http://ow.ly/s8IUV     
    
    
    Has the Day Arrived for Real-Time See-Commerce ? http://ow.ly/s8IZ9     
    
    
    Emails más interactivos gracias a los GIF animados http://ow.ly/s8Mkz  /v @foto_ecommerce #ecommerce #email #marketing    
    
    
    J.J. Rosen: 'Gamification' helps make learning, earning more fun http://ow.ly/s8ZL5     
    
    
    The 52 Most Breathtaking Photos From Around The World This Year http://ow.ly/s92yL  /cc @MonLabiaga    
    
    
    @Dani_ecommerce @newrubens @ecommbits Vosotros si que sois unos cracks. Que el 2014 sea la releche! @PrincesaSEO    
    
    
    No me gustaría ser sysadmin en Whatsapp esta noche :p    
    
    
    How Sales Leaders Can Use Gamification to Crush Quotas http://ow.ly/s9Al6     
    
    
    Study: 1/3 of Women in U.S. Use Pinterest http://zite.to/1chh1vi     
    
    
    Zappos is going holacratic: no job titles, no managers, no hierarchy http://zite.to/19yKXzV     
    
    
    Why Is Machine Learning (CS 229) The Most Popular Course At Stanford? http://zite.to/1hO9NkA     
    
    
    SVG Drawing Animation http://ow.ly/sarjv  #amazing    
    
    
    7 Great Internet Marketing Tips for 2014 http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/QY4Wq3Lxj04/7-great-internet-marketing-tips-2014-0727503 …    
    
    
    Announcing The Forrester Wave™: Mobile Commerce Solution Providers, Q4 2013 http://ow.ly/sarFK     
    
    
    7 Types of Consumer Personas http://ow.ly/sarGK     
    
    
    This is Your Brain on Content Marketing http://ow.ly/sarKR     
    
    
    5 Essentials You Need Before Starting Your Content Marketing Campaign http://ow.ly/sarMd     
    
    
    Things We Online Marketers Could All Improve Upon in 2014 http://ow.ly/sarNK     
    
    
    Without Meaningful User Experiences there is no Gamification Success http://is.gd/EDvpXm     
    
    
    The Habits of Successful People: Thinking in Ratios http://ow.ly/sas2c     
    
    
    3 Reasons Why Responsive Web Design is the Best Option For Your Mobile SEO Strategy  http://ow.ly/sas36     
    
    
    How to Fulfill Your Content Marketing Plan Through Content Repurposing http://ow.ly/sas49     
    
    
    Gamification (Deployment, Application) Market expected to grow $5.5 Billion By 2018 http://ow.ly/scvsM     
    
    
    The Seven Secret Habits of Twitter Power Users http://ow.ly/sas4L     
    
    
    2014 SEO Playbook: Off-Page Factors http://ow.ly/sas3N     
    
    
    About the new recommendations engine of NYT #recsys : On the Path to Personalization: Part 1 http://ow.ly/scvxl     
    
    
    How a “Soft Launch” Can Help You Launch Marketing Automation http://ow.ly/sas6c     
    
    
    @businessgp A real pleasure! :)    
    
    
    @stogiemonster I also hope to be able to assist #GSummit :) Cheers!    
    
    
    Coca-Cola Reserves a Massive Range of MAC Addresses RT @alobbs: Oh, wow… my latest blog post made it to Slashdot :-)  http://beta.slashdot.org/story/196343     
    
    
    @bhaines0 That would be a good explanation @alobbs    
    
    
    Google’s VP9 Video Codec Gets Backing from ARM, Nvidia, Sony And Others, Gives 4K Video Streaming A Fighting Chance http://zite.to/1cLfPBB     
    
    
    100 growth hacks in 100 days http://zite.to/JLMQSY     
    
    
    2013: The Year Of The Content Marketer? - http://klou.tt/181zk30pu54d9     
    
    
    Welcome To The New Startup Nation http://ow.ly/seIKa  /v @javiercuervo Startups are changing everything    
    
    
    An Interview with Paul Graham: Hackers & Painters 10 Years Later http://zite.to/1eSicpp     
    
    
    @Pedro_Robledo Startups "build the collaboration economy to exchange all types of products and services" @javiercuervo    
    
    
    How Video Can Personalize The Social Selling Cycle http://zite.to/1hR0T67     
    
    
    An awesome new mobile app by @shopify to help small online retailers on the go: Introducing Shopify Mobile http://ow.ly/seTQz     
    
    
    Here's The Answer To Why Bitcoin Has Value http://zite.to/1chc0D7     
    
    
    What changed in web design this year (and what’s next) http://zite.to/1eU6H0W     
    
    
    In 1964, Isaac Asimov Imagined the World in 2014 http://zite.to/1alU0V0     
    
    
    Finally, A Super-Simple Modular Robotics Kit - http://pulse.me/s/Ju6xi     
    
    
    Gamification Comes to the Contact Center http://ow.ly/sbFBa     
    
    
    8 apps to help you get fit in 2014 http://ow.ly/sbFBC  #gamification #health    
    
    
    Na casa da minha nai :) (@ Berkana) http://4sq.com/1e0NUMe     
    
    
    Great interview - Andreessen: Bubble Believers 'Don't Know What They're Talking About' http://zite.to/1auE7f3     
    
    
    @DavBoullosa ;) +1000    
    
    
    100 Growth Hacks in 100 Days: 1 to 10 http://ow.ly/seCTy     
    
    
    It's Time! You Need to Focus on Mobile Email Marketing #infographic http://ow.ly/seFFE     
    
    
    @javiercuervo Don't feed the troll! #sabiduríaPopular    
    
    
    GrovePi easily connects Grove Sensors to your Raspberry Pi.  Web enable your world! http://ow.ly/sgEaY  Niiiiiice!    
    
    
    Affiliate Marketing for Beginners http://ow.ly/scvhL     
    
    
    Meet tech billionaire and real life Iron Man Elon Musk http://zite.to/1avQoQp  What a man!    
    
    
    The Marketer's Guide to Google Analytics: How to Extract Numbers That Drive Action http://ow.ly/scviD     
    
    
    Yes, we can! RT @VictorManriqueY @iversity #GDMooc | Can We Use Normal Game Mechanics For #Gamification Design? - http://kcy.me/u5gb     
    
    
    How To Double Your Content Marketing ROI In 2014 http://ow.ly/scvkF     
    
    
    Top 5 Myths of Starting a Business http://is.gd/aNey2U     
    
    
    Netflix's Hastings: Personalization Is Double-Edged Sword http://ow.ly/scvAf     
    
    
    Awesome idea -> Coin » Use One Coin for All of Your Cards http://ow.ly/qPu6h     
    
    
    Battle Hack showdown in Barcelona Video: http://ow.ly/qRgwL  It was a pleasure to contribute to this awesome event as judges    
    
    
    Animated Opening Type. Really nice CSS effect by @DiegoCayenna http://ow.ly/qTkRh     
    
    
    What are the best tools to create a developers portal? We've been using wordpress but we need a more powerful solution. Thanks!    
    
    
    Sony sells over 1 million PlayStation 4 consoles in just 24 hours http://zite.to/1dHKcHI     
    
    
    Pixar's 22 Rules to Phenomenal Storytelling http://zite.to/1cBd8zU     
    
    
    @puffybsd Thanks! I've been evaluating Apigee, Mashery and 3Scale but wanted to hear recommendations like yours :)    
    
    
    @virtualCableTV Thanks! Didn't know @orchardcms Seems nice but I'd like something more specific to a developers portal to lower the workload    
    
    
    Gamification — should start-ups be interested? http://ow.ly/qU9Tu     
    
    
    The Retailers Guide to Big Data #infographic http://is.gd/RAdXXW     
    
    
    The Complete Guide to Launching a New Website http://zite.to/1gYviBr     
    
    
    When Selling Digital Content, Let the Customer Set the Price http://zite.to/19zlt4h     
    
    
    @almostvoid I find it relevant as they are selling PS4 at a higher rate than the previous generation #psFan :P    
    
    
    5 Advanced Javascript and Web Debugging Techniques You Should Know About http://zite.to/17FkapZ     
    
    
    Steve Case’s Revolution Makes Big Bets on E-Commerce http://zite.to/1gY95Dn     
    
    
    5 Ways to Increase Revenue During the Holidays http://zite.to/1dLxFDe     
    
    
    How Unbounce Uses Landing Pages for Content Marketing http://zite.to/I2ktzX 
#mustRead    
    
    
    Why the Father of the Consumer Internet Invests in Ecommerce http://zite.to/1cEuAn9     
    
    
    Without Meaningful User Experiences there is no Gamification Success http://is.gd/EDvpXm     
    
    
    Techniques for Responsive Typography http://ow.ly/qYbSx     
    
    
    Stop Thinking Keywords, Think Topics http://ow.ly/qYdTa     
    
    
    Headlines That Work: Has Science Finally Settled the Geek/Nerd Debate? http://ow.ly/qYelR     
    
    
    The Beginner’s Guide to Gamification (15 of 90): Scarcity & Impatience http://ow.ly/qYepO  /v @yukaichou    
    
    
    From the Trenches: 23 Entrepreneurs Share Their Most Valuable Lessons Learned http://zite.to/1aPvcDO     
    
    
    B2B Buyers Prefer Short Content; Rely Heavily on Google Searches http://zite.to/1bARVnX     
    
    
    2 important agile marketing insights from HubSpot's CMO http://zite.to/1aPvt9G     
    
    
    Emotion Beats Promotion By 2X http://zite.to/17J4It3     
    
    
    Top 5 Myths of Starting a Business http://is.gd/aNey2U     
    
    
    How to calculate the equity split between co-founders in a startup http://zite.to/188tT8M     
    
    
    30 Tips For Creating Content that Gets Read, Shared, and Talked About at Parties http://zite.to/188hy4k     
    
    
    Massive UK study finds video games have no negative impact on 11,000 kids http://zite.to/18pwtVS     
    
    
    Tech Is Hiring More Women Than Men For The First Time In 10 Years http://zite.to/17O2B1I     
    
    
    SEO Tips for Prestashop Stores http://j.mp/1dnEoqO  via @inboundorg    
    
    
    Top 5 Reasons why Customer-Centric Efforts Fail http://zite.to/1jrjvsb     
    
    
    BigDoor moves beyond gamification to focus on loyalty programs  http://ow.ly/r52Qr  Fear of BadgeVille or #gamification is not enough    
    
    
    Why FourSquare's Decision of Phasing Out Gamification is a Great Mistake http://is.gd/sAc8c6     
    
    
    Gamification: Merchants of Meth or Merchants of Faith http://ow.ly/r52Uu     
    
    
    To Improve SEO, Focus on the Page http://ow.ly/r5EXE  /v @PracticalEcomm    
    
    
    Content Marketing Playbook: 24 Epic Ideas for Connecting with Your Customers [Deck] http://ow.ly/r5Fnh     
    
    
    Applying App Design Concepts to Website Design http://ow.ly/r5FsW     
    
    
    Embracing Paradoxes and Narratives in Education http://ow.ly/r5FF0  #gamification    
    
    
    17 SEO Best Practices That Could Double Your E-Commerce Sales http://ow.ly/r5GjU     
    
    
    Interesting Infographics: How B2B Sales Has Changed http://zite.to/Il58cR     
    
    
    6 Proven Ways to Boost the Conversion Rates of Your Call-to-Action Buttons http://ow.ly/r5GlW     
    
    
    How Google Plus Profiles & Pages Gain Search Authority http://ow.ly/r5Grj     
    
    
    David Ogilvy’s Prophetic “Secret Weapon” of Selling http://ow.ly/r5Gtx     
    
    
    2014 SEO Roadmap: Adopting Semantic Markup http://ow.ly/r5GEE     
    
    
    The New Rules Of Disruption http://zite.to/IbtTZy     
    
    
    Motorola Will Use 3D Printing For Its Customizable Smartphones http://zite.to/I5ifz1     
    
    
    @wernerkeil XDDDD    
    
    
    Signs point up for B2B e-commerce http://zite.to/I4LaU4     
    
    
    I'm at Republic Space (Boadilla del Monte, Madrid) http://4sq.com/18z854i     
    
    
    A merendar http://instagram.com/p/hGv4TRALF_/     
    
    
    Analytics Don’t Lie: Product Content is Content Marketing http://zite.to/1e9m2WQ     
    
    
    #Ecommerce, en clave retail http://ow.ly/r813J  /v @aliciadavara @daretail    
    
    
    Focusing on the top 20 percent of your customers http://ow.ly/r81ju     
    
    
    Want to be a successful founder? Not without these qualities http://zite.to/1fztpdT     
    
    
    Betabeers Madrid. Especial Failshow, 3 diciembre 2013 - Betabeers http://ow.ly/r9e4l     
    
    
    How Design And User Experience Translates To The Bottom Line http://zite.to/17YXwnh     
    
    
    The Golden Age of Watching Other People Play Video Games http://zite.to/1jxhjiU     
    
    
    @juansandesv Así me gusta ;)    
    
    
    Should companies be making more of gamification? http://zite.to/IdcmQK     
    
    
    3 Ways Twitter Is Changing TV Forever http://zite.to/1aGvL76     
    
    
    B2B Content Marketing in 2013 [Infographic] http://is.gd/Bb6lSO     
    
    
    Customer Acquisition http://zite.to/19Vb8Q7  and why you should focus on loyalty and customer service    
    
    
    Arm yourself: The API wars are coming http://zite.to/1aZ4NUb     
    
    
    The Search Engine Market in Russia http://ow.ly/rbSYc  #infographic #search    
    
    
    Here's why 2014 will be the year of the 'Internet of things' http://zite.to/17ORZ5R     
    
    
    Data is the new sexy http://is.gd/YxBPc4     
    
    
    Okay, Google, you officially beat Siri http://zite.to/1c3koGJ     
    
    
    80% of teens shop online, and their favorite web retailer is Amazon http://zite.to/IpDeg1     
    
    
    Python Displacing R As The Programming Language For Data Science http://zite.to/1aTKbA2     
    
    
    Conversion Rate Optimization Infographic http://ow.ly/re4Mc     
    
    
    Six ways to drive conversions using geo-personalisation http://ow.ly/rcEUJ  /v @patriciohunt    
    
    
    Boost Your CTR for the Holidays by Picking Your Best Creative http://zite.to/1blUdg7     
    
    
    Suzana Herculano-Houzel: What is so special about the human brain? http://zite.to/1jGIiIW     
    
    
    A Warning to Ecommerce Startups: The Future of Online is Offline http://zite.to/1b2twab     
    
    
    E-commerce: 10 case studies to help you excel in content marketing, social media and website optimization http://zite.to/1jEOdyb     
    
    
    Email Marketing Trends of 2014 http://ow.ly/rgmDW  #emailMarketing    
    
    
    The Real Future of Social is Search http://zite.to/1dBEACP     
    
    
    Data is the new sexy http://is.gd/YxBPc4     
    
    
    Email Marketing Trends of 2014 http://ow.ly/rgmHr     
    
    
    In defense of the fat startup http://zite.to/17Zp15r     
    
    
    @VictorJuarezP XDDD @jorgegonzalezm9 @ramonvmr @javiercuervo    
    
    
    Mark Zuckerberg Inside Facebook http://is.gd/CrZHkd     
    
    
    To pivot or not to pivot http://is.gd/69H9GH     
    
    
    America's Fastest Growing Enterprise Software Companies of 2013 http://zite.to/1ioyAzp     
    
    
    TV evolution: The war for the start screen http://zite.to/18ekxmi     
    
    
    15 Rocking Content Marketing Tools with Advice from Experts http://zite.to/1inKCJs     
    
    
    Replacing (most of) d3.js with pure SVG + AngularJS http://zite.to/1iqeeWK     
    
    
    How Game Based Learning is Making Training Better http://zite.to/199y130     
    
    
    Consumer drones are coming, and they will change everything http://zite.to/18St3uY     
    
    
    A Company Without APIs Is Like A Computer Without Internet http://zite.to/Imhxhq     
    
    
    Stores Use New Technology To Obsessively Track You http://zite.to/ImqsPN     
    
    
    Sight, a Short Futuristic Film that Shows A Gamified Future http://is.gd/5V0OPB     
    
    
    Onboarding New Users Is Harder Than You Think http://zite.to/1bbdTRd     
    
    
    How to Grow Your Blog to 100,000 Visits a Month Within 1.5 Years http://zite.to/1bdoEz6     
    
    
    Eventazo organizado por @Intelectium Next Generation #ecommerce @WEAREKNITTERS @brokerfashion @brainsins_es @moodyo http://ht.ly/rmnjL     
    
    
    Gym Time http://instagram.com/p/heMXzOgLJ7/     
    
    
    http://DIY.org : Gamification for Makers http://is.gd/QUcrsM     
    
    
    Apple Acquires Twitter Analytics Platform Topsy For $200 Million http://zite.to/IEO2Y1     
    
    
    10 Tops to Make the Most of Pinterest in Your Online Store http://zite.to/18kdett     
    
    
    27 Ways to Reduce Shopping Fears on your Ecommerce Website http://zite.to/1jiFRyU     
    
    
    5 data scientists who became CEOs — and are leading thriving companies http://zite.to/1cTIaDP     
    
    
    20 Beautiful Examples Of Persuasive Ecommerce Design http://zite.to/IMQrk3     
    
    
    Efficiently Simplifying Navigation, Part 1: Information Architecture http://zite.to/1cWNUw5     
    
    
    Why FourSquare's Decision of Phasing Out Gamification is a Great Mistake http://is.gd/sAc8c6     
    
    
    11 SEO Changes That Will Give You Big Results http://zite.to/1kbcNqD     
    
    
    Why Is Google Buying So Many Robot Startups? http://zite.to/1bi5FTY     
    
    
    5 Ways Retailers Benefit from ‘Internet of Things’ http://zite.to/1gE674i     
    
    
    ASOS nails Pinterest this Christmas http://zite.to/1d0nqtS     
    
    
    @NoeliaRuiz81 XDDDDD @aCodigoAbierto    
    
    
    4 Reasons Why B2B Content Marketing is Hard to Get Right http://zite.to/18cPKMa     
    
    
    Without Meaningful User Experiences there is no Gamification Success http://is.gd/EDvpXm     
    
    
    5 experiences commerce websites should replicate from the Apple Store http://zite.to/IPEzgG     
    
    
    US startup valuations reach ten year highs http://zite.to/1f2myqR     
    
    
    7 Black Friday and Cyber Monday Landing Page Examples [with critiques] http://zite.to/1cftQ6A     
    
    
    Cratejoy is a website builder and eCommerce backend for subscription eCommerce stores http://zite.to/1hEyzWQ     
    
    
    10 reasons everyone at your startup should blog http://is.gd/Ei5JKO     
    
    
    Luxury Consumers Respond to Exclusive Access, Not Promotion
http://www.emarketer.com/Article/Luxury-Consumers-Respond-Exclusive-Access-Not-Promotion/1010419#mSvhurCRDzDWkhUd.99 …    
    
    
    Use Hashtags More Effectively in Your Social Media Content: 4 Tactics http://ow.ly/ryMj7     
    
    
    SEO: Leveraging Bing’s Pinterest Integration http://ow.ly/ryMjN     
    
    
    20 beautiful examples of persuasive ecommerce design http://ow.ly/ryMlq     
    
    
    6 of the Most Amazing Mobile eCommerce Experiences of 2013 http://ow.ly/ryMmM     
    
    
    Northern European ecommerce to grow to €31bln http://ow.ly/ryMny     
    
    
    Graphene Is Going to Change the World, specially when Moore's Law doesn't longer apply http://zite.to/IKktE3     
    
    
    Glasses vs Watch: A Battle for the Future Internet http://is.gd/7FYXP5     
    
    
    5 Secrets of High-Converting Email Newsletters http://ow.ly/ryMob     
    
    
    2014 Cheat Sheet: New Methods For Finding B2B Customers [Infographic] http://ow.ly/ryMp9     
    
    
    Damn Son, Update Your Off-Page SEO for 2014 http://ow.ly/ryMrg     
    
    
    Google rumored to launch its own TV set-top box under the Nexus brand next year http://ow.ly/ryPeB     
    
    
    12 Content Marketing Books to Add to Your Holiday Gift List http://ow.ly/ryPyk  Just bought many of them :)    
    
    
    Will gamification stay relevant? http://ow.ly/rySfn  Lots of people screwing it up, but also more relevant example, so it will survive    
    
    
    Hospital fights employee obesity with social sharing and gamification http://ow.ly/rySio     
    
    
    So bad RT @hmason: Creativity is rejected: Teachers and bosses don’t value out-of-the-box thinking. http://slate.me/1gPLu5k     
    
    
    #mustRead for B2B marketers RT @iRhodes 10 Phrases I Want You To Remove From Your B2B Website, Right Now! http://www.rhodesconsultancy.com/planning/10-terms-i-want-you-to-remove-from-your-b2b-website-right-now/ …    
    
    
    Adapt to each user's needs RT @peeplaja Long Form or Short Form? Why Not Both? http://conversionxl.com/long-form-or-short-form-why-not-both/ … guest post by @DholakiyaPratik    
    
    
    The Retailers Guide to Big Data #infographic http://is.gd/RAdXXW     
    
    
    Shopping Cart Page Recommendation Strategy http://ow.ly/rByM4  How to get more from product recommendations in your cart page #ecommerce    
    
    
    @megova Jajaja, falo galego na intimidade :P    
    
    
    Henkel Ibérica abre el primer ShopperLab http://ow.ly/rzMVr  /v @revistaARAL    
    
    
    More important than testing itself RT @peeplaja: My (condensed) answer to how to determine what to test: http://www.growthhackers.com/ask-gh-how-do-you-determine-which-tests-to-run-on-a-site-when-looking-to-optimize-conversion-rates/#comment-1971 …    
    
    
    Google a seguir dando por culo... RT @jordiobdotcom: Cambios en el tracking de emailings desde gMail http://goo.gl/fb/2XPO2  #ecommerce    
    
    
    The Collaborative Economy Is Real (And It's Here) http://zite.to/18QJBG1     
    
    
    Target Tests An Online Store Powered By Pinterest, Called The 'Awesome Shop' http://zite.to/1ffjtDJ     
    
    
    Netflix open sources its data traffic cop, Suro http://zite.to/1dj81Fe     
    
    
    The Future of Content: Upcoming Trends in 2014 http://zite.to/18hY25o     
    
    
    The 13 Best Science and Technology Books of 2013; just buying one of those :) http://zite.to/18z8jrF     
    
    
    Online sales were worth £164bn in 2012, equal to 6% of business turnover http://zite.to/1cmxXxT     
    
    
    1 in 2 Consumers Say That YouTube Videos Have Influenced A Purchase Decision http://zite.to/J2o54G     
    
    
    Stop Tweeting Your Blog Posts Only Once: The Case for Re-sharing on Social Media http://zite.to/1e3CUlQ     
    
    
    The Habits of Successful People: Be Inconsistent http://zite.to/1gmk2yQ  it makes sense    
    
    
    Why Your Offline Business Doesn’t Convert Well to an Ecommerce Business http://zite.to/18ABAm3     
    
    
    @FkieCarrero What happens?    
    
    
    E-Commerce Sites Need 2 Types of Breadcrumbs (68% Get it Wrong) http://zite.to/1dla7Ew     
    
    
    Three key rules of gamification of the workplace http://zite.to/18xh6dJ     
    
    
    How To Know You’ve Hit First Traction In SaaS. The Moment When You’ve Got A Real Company http://ow.ly/rEXSp  /v @RogerPiqueP    
    
    
    10 Ways to Speed Up Your Website – and Improve Conversion by 7% http://zite.to/18UsPWp     
    
    
    Die, Flash, Die http://is.gd/8EgHhz     
    
    
    Tablets Are Becoming A Favorite Shopping Tool, And They're Used Totally Differently From Smartphones http://zite.to/IFE5tE     
    
    
    Survey: Majority Use Smartphones In Stores, Not For E-Commerce http://zite.to/1aVcScE     
    
    
    Shopify Raises $100M To Drop The ‘E’ And Become The Commerce Company That Spans On- And Offline http://zite.to/1jQXHJm     
    
    
    5 Ways to Utilize Thank You Pages for Reconversions http://zite.to/1gZX8e7     
    
    
    @RSaltor Cracks! Enhorabuena! @SelfPackaging    
    
    
    +1000 RT @anitarm: Esta vez querido compi @Joseluisferrero te has superado. Enhorabuena!! Ole, ole,  ole.  #desayunosPhilips    
    
    
    Increased productivity, the real business case for gamification http://ow.ly/rFYbX     
    
    
    Content Marketing in 2014: Are You Prepared? http://zite.to/1bxA5Sd     
    
    
    #mustRead RT @PerryMarshall: What Conversion Tactics Will Make the Biggest Difference in 2014? http://buff.ly/198lJM0     
    
    
    15 Pinterest Users Every Designer Should Follow http://zite.to/1f9p3a9     
    
    
    Real-Life Conversion Lessons: Features vs. Benefits http://zite.to/1jRaMTe     
    
    
    Nokia & deadmau5 'This is Lumia' light show in London http://ow.ly/rJfo5  http://ow.ly/rJfv3  Bad I missed that! /v @PrincesaSEO    
    
    
    #FF to my top 3 followers of the week @brainsins_es @patriciohunt @YouPaparazz   Check it out at:  http://www.gamisfaction.com/josek_net?utm_source=timeline&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=followfriday …    
    
    
    Amigo invisible en @brainsins_es :D http://ow.ly/i/40PfI     
    
    
    SM is part of Content Marketing - > 5 Reasons Social media is Just as Important as Content in Marketing Today http://zite.to/1flXonc     
    
    
    If you are angry with everybody, then the real problem is that you are angry with yourself    
    
    
    Back to school http://instagram.com/p/h3iyUmALK9/     
    
    
    Conversion rate optimisation: eight case studies that show the benefit of UX testing http://zite.to/18WrP48     
    
    
    Tablets in Education Brings Everything to a New Level http://zite.to/IT8WCx     
    
    
    XD RT @aldamiz: Interruption marketing http://www.pinterest.com/pin/46936021090670618/ …    
    
    
    So damn right! RT @jmgomez: The key word in “Data Science” is not Data, it is Science | @leekgroup http://ow.ly/rJ3WD  #datamining    
    
    
    How Retailers Using Facebook’s Custom Audiences Can Track Offline Sales http://zite.to/1kH9Dv8     
    
    
    Absolut con Sprite http://instagram.com/p/h6yZBmgLAi/     
    
    
    The first trailer for Christopher Nolan's next project 'Interstellar' is here http://zite.to/1ddEXyA     
    
    
    Six common conversion killers from ecommerce sites http://zite.to/1jYsFzB     
    
    
    Lessons Learned: Fashionable Maternity Wear Sells http://zite.to/18HqsRd  /v @practicalecomm    
    
    
    Gartner Sticks to its Failing Gamification Prediction http://zite.to/18Zdxje     
    
    
    Tanagustico... http://instagram.com/p/h8QunigLCT/     
    
    
    Taking DynamoDB beyond Key-Value: Now with Faster, More Flexible, More Powerful Query Capabilities http://zite.to/1hPCDni     
    
    
    @jordiobdotcom XDDDDDD    
    
    
    Want Conversions? Start with User-Friendly, Useful Landing Pages http://zite.to/1bINsn0     
    
    
    Why Do Companies Choose Node? Performance, Scalability and Productivity http://zite.to/1bME6GU     
    
    
    Healing the Disconnect Between Ecommerce and Customer Experience http://zite.to/1dxxOK2     
    
    
    About PayPal's Node vs Java “fight” http://zite.to/1eaYepI  great analysis but still would be interesting to have more info from inside PP    
    
    
    B2B Content Marketing in 2013 [Infographic] http://is.gd/Bb6lSO     
    
    
    Big data and analytics trends for 2014 http://zite.to/1ja9moR     
    
    
    5 Predictions On The Future Of Databases (From A Guy Who Knows Databases) http://zite.to/1bFvqRH     
    
    
    As Software Eats The World, Non-Tech Corporations Are Eating Startups http://zite.to/JkAhOB     
    
    
    Why is a shopping mall in Thailand Instagram’s most photographed place in 2013? http://zite.to/1bITiR9     
    
    
    5 Content Marketing Trends & Predictions for 2014 http://zite.to/1dE70rC     
    
    
    Expanding options for mining streaming data http://zite.to/1k5bITW     
    
    
    I'm at Brainsins Headquarters http://4sq.com/198xLad     
    
    
    This will be bigger for Amazon than drones http://zite.to/1cLEZ2H     
    
    
    The Full Stack Marketer http://is.gd/V2ruTy     
    
    
    How One SaaS Startup Reduced Churn 71% Using “Red Flag” Metrics http://zite.to/1jcq2w0     
    
    
    20 Beautiful Examples Of Persuasive Ecommerce Design http://zite.to/JA2cLa     
    
    
    16 Tips for Balancing Website Design and Conversion http://zite.to/IZPAM0     
    
    
    Ecommerce Merchants Should Not Ignore Older Shoppers http://zite.to/18REBhG     
    
    
    Absolutely! RT @ContentVerve: Is Emotion Necessary To Make More Sales? http://conversionxl.com/is-emotion-necessary-to-make-more-sales/ … via @peeplaja    
    
    
    Top 5 Myths of Starting a Business http://is.gd/aNey2U     
    
    
    Hot Ass http://instagram.com/p/iCfktNgLCJ/     
    
    
    @jordiobdotcom :P    
    
    
    #Gamification of reading RT @evgenymorozov Kindle has a new feature called FreeTime that allows kids to earn badges and awards for reading    
    
    
    The LG Chromebase is an all-in-one PC powered by Google’s Chrome OS http://zite.to/1cayKah     
    
    
    IBM: In 5 Years, Buying Local Will Beat Buying Online http://zite.to/1fCGdxD     
    
    
    Gato Cósmico http://instagram.com/p/iEMHUygLFR/     
    
    
    The Top UX Trends of 2013 http://zite.to/JEzGIk     
    
    
    The future of API design: The orchestration layer http://zite.to/1dkKdAF     
    
    
    Testing @canva and it's a freaking awesome tool for marketers. Lets you create amazing designs in minutes! #awesome #lovingIt    
    
    
    How to innovate? Google exec explains http://zite.to/1bMWFq2     
    
    
    Why VCs should stop investing in 'Internet' startups and start investing in 'tech' http://zite.to/1bMgqxX     
    
    
    eCommerce Means Real Business Models on the Internet http://is.gd/s8vTns     
    
    
    Office... morning... http://instagram.com/p/iGLWWhALF_/     
    
    
    Will be even bigger RT @WIRED: Why wearable tech will be as big as the smartphone http://wrd.cm/18OFZPg     
    
    
    Discovering Canva, "a simple new way to design". An amazing tool http://ow.ly/rSbqf     
    
    
    Increased Productivity – the real reason for introducing gamification http://ow.ly/rSt96     
    
    
    Big Data Gets Smart, Personalization Gets Personal http://ow.ly/rSteY     
    
    
    2014 Forecast: Gamification and the Year Ahead in Banking http://ow.ly/rSth9     
    
    
    The Flood of Big Data [Infographic] http://is.gd/T5YQKa     
    
    
    #ecommcena #eCommBeers #ecommCracks #ecommAmigos http://ow.ly/i/44S7x  #ecommerce    
    
    
    Easing the Pain of Keyword Not Provided: 5 Tactics for Reclaiming Your Data http://zite.to/1bOCjge     
    
    
    What’s the big deal with big data? Breaking down the year’s buzzword http://zite.to/1jfLJLQ     
    
    
    15 High Performance Habits That Will Make You Successful http://zite.to/1c9Au3A     
    
    
    Email Subject Lines: Words and Tactics That Boost Open Rates http://zite.to/1dhDM13     
    
    
    Gamify Your Digital Marketing http://zite.to/19STq0C     
    
    
    8 Simple Scientifically Proven Ways to Improve Your Writing http://zite.to/1fmMn4d     
    
    
    Little Girl Gets 3D Printed Hand http://ow.ly/rXuZT  /cc @picoj @martapanera @pabloechanove @joseluisferrero @hectoriglesiasm    
    
    
    @rafabillor @AntBogarin Thanks! Revocando acceso a la app. Abrazo!    
    
    
    http://Overstock.com  Will Start Taking Bitcoin Next Year http://zite.to/JHUMoo     
    
    
    Introducing Open Salaries at Buffer: Our Transparent Formula and All Individual Salaries http://zite.to/1horhnq  nice concept    
    
    
    6 Reasons Why Feedly is the Best Alternative to Google Reader http://is.gd/V6Toqr     
    
    
    Is REST losing its flair – REST API Alternatives http://ow.ly/rWYuo     
    
    
    Merck turns to gamification in diabetes http://ow.ly/rXizU     
    
    
    How To Make LinkedIn Help Your Lead Generation Efforts http://ow.ly/rXiPj     
    
    
    @FitsYourProfile great! :)    
    
    
    Simplify Your Inbound Marketing Process: Focus on Content Assets http://ow.ly/rXjk1     
    
    
    Why Your Gamification Efforts Are Failing http://ow.ly/rXjm0     
    
    
    You can now build an interactive mobile app, no code required, thanks to Facebook http://zite.to/1drUKtY     
    
    
    Why Startups No Longer need a Business Plan http://zite.to/18DsuXM     
    
    
    @hugomunro Yes, but don't make it the "Bible", focus on determining your main hypothesis and spend more time testing and validating those    
    
    
    A KPI dashboard for early-stage SaaS startups – new and improved! http://zite.to/1cYcmj4     
    
    
    FinalCutEando http://instagram.com/p/iO14pGgLEj/     
    
    
    eCommerce: the Perfect Product Page http://zite.to/1gICvWo     
    
    
    How to Make an Infographic (Even When You’re Not a Designer) http://zite.to/1c4lQsO     
    
    
    Email Marketing: 3 resources to help you close the automation gap http://zite.to/1bg0ggy     
    
    
    15 Content Marketing Tips From The Pros http://zite.to/19FR0pM     
    
    
    @happywebcoder En @brainsins_es pujamos por 120€ #RaulBookSale :)    
    
    
    Carmat's groundbreaking five-year artificial heart gets its first patient in France http://zite.to/1biuwHE     
    
    
    The Top UX Predictions for 2014 http://zite.to/1cGwbrt     
    
    
    Python Displacing R As The Programming Language For Data Science http://zite.to/1js2h3i     
    
    
    How Retail Businesses Use Business Intelligence to Maximize Profitability http://zite.to/1l5yGbt     
    
    
    A set of flat and 3D progress button styles where the button itself serves as a progress indicator http://ow.ly/rZK4K     
    
    
    @txampa Que chulada. Disfruta!    
    
    
    P&G Launch 6 New Facebook Stores: “Live Learning Labs” [Screenshots] http://ow.ly/rZKdT  #fCommerce #experiments    
    
    
    The Ultimate Guide to Startup Marketing http://is.gd/h5ZnMl     
    
    
    #AliOli rico, rico... :) http://instagram.com/p/iR21LFALGd/     
    
    
    Curating Content Or Creating It: Which Drives More B2B Conversions? http://ow.ly/rZKf6     
    
    
    @Astillazo LOOOOOOL \cc @al_cuevas    
    
    
    13 Ways to Improve Email Unsubscribe http://ow.ly/rZKbq     
    
    
    Probably the Smartest Thread You’ll Read on (Social) E-Commerce… http://ow.ly/rZKhO  #mustRead    
    
    
    How to Gracefully Transition from Keywords to Topics http://ow.ly/rZKna     
    
    
    Pure Energy http://instagram.com/p/iTKuN-gLJV/     
    
    
    8 Reasons Why You Need to Establish Authority on Google+ http://ow.ly/rZKrX     
    
    
    From the Top @ Brainsins Headquarters http://instagram.com/p/iTk_RFgLDk/     
    
    
    The Ultimate Guide to Startup Marketing http://ow.ly/rZKIr     
    
    
    Die, Flash, Die http://is.gd/8EgHhz     
    
    
    Octalysis of 8 Gamified Alarm Clock http://ow.ly/rZKqG  /v @yukaichou    
    
    
    The 35 Most Spectacular Wildlife Photos From The National Geographic Photo Contest http://ow.ly/rZODM  #awesome /cc @Monlabiaga    
    
    
    Christmas Breakfast @ JoSeK's Home http://instagram.com/p/iV2gR7ALB6/     
    
    
    Why founders should never sacrifice company culture http://zite.to/1l6BKnq     
    
    
    Impala v Hive http://zite.to/1id93Z6  #bigdata    
    
    
    @jordiobdotcom Ratito para el lego, ratito para el twitter, ratito para la PS3, ratito para el lego... #queDuraEsLaNavidad :P XD    
    
    
    The Four Architectures that will inspire your programming http://zite.to/1cYJ7wq     
    
    
    #mustRead RT @FkieCarrero: Very much agreed! "SMB: The Third Market" http://ow.ly/s0HMU  @startupcfo    
    
    
    If You're Content Marketing Isn't Serving One of These 4 Goals You're Wasting Your Time http://zite.to/1cs8cBx     
    
    
    The Trends That Ruled Pinterest In 2013 http://zite.to/19auc0S     
    
    
    Sight, a Short Futuristic Film that Shows A Gamified Future http://is.gd/5V0OPB     
    
    
    Apache Spark for Big Analytics http://zite.to/1eAxNd2  #dataAnalysis    
    
    
    Mi tribuna en @daretail -> "Ni E, ni M, ni S, ni T, ni Símplemente Commerce" http://ow.ly/s4FaJ     
    
    
    The Retailers Guide to Big Data #infographic http://is.gd/RAdXXW     
    
    
    Segmentation 101: Start, Split, Test, Maintain | Targeting & Segmentation http://ow.ly/s45fq     
    
    
    Are These 6 Ecommerce Copywriting Mistakes Costing You Sales? http://ow.ly/s45kQ     
    
    
    14 Most Important Metrics To Focus In Your Digital Marketing Campaign (Infographic) http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/rlyDoCAioZw/14-important-metrics-focus-digital-marketing-campaign-infographic-0725245 …    
    
    
    3 Stages of The Universal Marketing Funnel http://ow.ly/s45lr     
    
    
    #FF to my top 3 followers of the week @jordiobdotcom @ValeraMariscal @javiercuervo   Check it out at:  http://www.gamisfaction.com/josek_net?utm_source=timeline&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=followfriday …    
    
    
    Why B2B Content Marketing Must Go Beyond Random Acts of Publishing http://ow.ly/s45m0     
    
    
    Mission ImposSERPble 2: User Intent and Click Through Rates http://ow.ly/s45mr     
    
    
    Improve product pages by 35 percent — Ecommerce Checklist http://ow.ly/s45nc  #ecommerce    
    
    
    6 Tools for Building Unique Landing Pages http://www.practicalecommerce.com/articles/62537-6-Tools-for-Building-Unique-Landing-Pages …    
    
    
    The Integrated Marketing Imperative: Transition from Optimizing Keywords to Optimize for Customers http://ow.ly/s45oY     
    
    
    How to Develop a Content Marketing Strategy: The First 3 Steps http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/BWg8hw0i97s/develop-content-marketing-strategy-first-3-steps-0725115 …    
    
    
    2013 has been a year of epic proportions for e-commerce in China, and it’s only set to grow http://zite.to/1cT8KeB     
    
    
    To pivot or not to pivot http://is.gd/69H9GH     
    
    
    The Future of How We Shop #infographic http://www.brainsins.com/en/blog/the-future-of-how-we-shop-infographic/2546?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=the-future-of-how-we-shop-infographic …    
    
    
    Top 5 Game-Changing Gadgets of 2013 http://zite.to/1bqvOjG     
    
    
    5 Ways Pinterest Can Make Products More ‘Touchable’ http://zite.to/1fKR08z     
    
    
    How To Disrupt A Market and Bootstrap A Company To $10 Million In Revenue In 3 Years  http://ow.ly/s5r6b     
    
    
    Professional Development for Digital Marketers: How to Up Your Game in 2014 http://ow.ly/s5r7j     
    
    
    How to Overcome the Top 3 B2B Content Marketing Challenges in 2014 http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/oEFRbqPqMgk/overcome-top-3-b2b-content-marketing-challenges-2014-0719748 …    
    
    
    When is a great moment for a SaaS startup to create an affiliate program?  http://ow.ly/s5rl8     
    
    
    #eCommerce goes #local RT @loogic: Elephanti Raises $4.5M To Help Shoppers Find Products In Nearby Stores http://feedly.com/e/0AOz9Ey9     
    
    
    So You’ve Decided To Open-Source A Project At Work. What Now? http://zite.to/1hIDBiL     
    
    
    Mola! :) RT @Thrillka: Shop is open! :) http://etsy.com/shop/Chikai  @BrightonEtsy    
    
    
    @jordiobdotcom XDDD no hay hamburguesa que se me resista :P @Monlabiaga    
    
    
    Chromebooks' success punches Microsoft in the gut http://zite.to/1lo5Zqc     
    
    
    @blairrorani For most people, a small notebook such as yours is all they need, although 10" tablets are a good substitute in most cases    
    
    
    @blairrorani Agree! I still use my laptop for video editing, graphic design and coding, but it's a pleasure to travel+work with a 10" tablet    
    
    
    The Sad State of Sentiment Analysis http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/0Xppy_VrPtc/sad-state-sentiment-analysis-0725232 …    
    
    
    @DollarShaveClub has the most amazing explanation video ever http://www.dollarshaveclub.com/  #startups    
    
    
    Effective Technical Leadership http://ow.ly/s858s  /v @javisantana    
    
    
    Why FourSquare's Decision of Phasing Out Gamification is a Great Mistake http://is.gd/sAc8c6     
    
    
    4 Simple but Effective Remarketing Tips by @bethany_bey http://www.searchenginejournal.com/4-simple-effective-remarketing-tips/82193/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=4-simple-effective-remarketing-tips …    
    
    
    7 Reasons for Free Delivery in Your eCommerce Store http://ow.ly/s7NSD     
    
    
    Extreme Content Marketing With Red Bull http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/A9sJvUzv70A/extreme-content-marketing-red-bull-0723742 …    
    
    
    Essential Elements for Checkout Conversion http://ow.ly/s7NSX     
    
    
    Leading Experts Predict The Content Marketing Trends for 2014 by @murraynewlands http://feeds.searchenginejournal.com/~r/SearchEngineJournal/~3/CN3Eqw1gCf4/ …    
    
    
    Reducing Shopping Cart Abandonment in eCommerce: the Right Price http://ow.ly/s7NTD     
    
    
    +1000 RT @rickygervais: Remember kids, if you don't sin, then Jesus died for nothing.    
    
    
    6 Dataset Lists Curated By Data Scientists http://zite.to/1agXDLL     
    
    
    Scientists exploring computers that can learn and adapt http://zite.to/1cAd8Tm     
    
    
    Deshielo http://instagram.com/p/iifIX5gLO_/     
    
    
    In technology, 2013 was a more amazing year than you think http://zite.to/1jXRldM     
    
    
    Boost Online B2B Lead Conversions Using Retargeting http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/Nqkgb_B1RRw/boost-online-b2b-lead-conversions-using-retargeting-0726171 …    
    
    
    Successful Growth Secrets for the CMO http://ow.ly/s8Iz9     
    
    
    How to Start an Affiliate Marketing Business in 2014 http://ow.ly/s8IAq     
    
    
    We’re About to Lose Net Neutrality — And the Internet as We Know It http://ow.ly/s8IDz     
    
    
    In-App Purchases Take Over App Revenues http://ow.ly/s8IEy     
    
    
    Personal Brand Marketing Tips from 3 Influential Women http://ow.ly/s8IFH     
    
    
    Dile tu algo... @ Brainsins Headquarters http://instagram.com/p/ijOyhEgLJO/     
    
    
    10 Website design trends that we will see in 2014 - http://klou.tt/1fzcm1v9r28ba     
    
    
    How To Grow A Community, Tips For Community Managers: Interview With Ann Smarty http://ow.ly/s8IGi     
    
    
    Why Small Businesses Aren’t Maximizing the Rewards of Content Marketing http://ow.ly/s8IJi     
    
    
    How to Send Perfectly Timed “Abandoned Cart” Emails http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/DnX6msrMBi4/send-perfectly-timed-abandoned-cart-emails-0725137 …    
    
    
    @guiyermoruiz Un placer leerte! :D    
    
    
    11 Secrets to Reduce Bounce Rate Dramatically http://ow.ly/s8IQ0     
    
    
    Shopping Cart Page Recommendation Strategy http://klou.tt/1mqk0cl5rkltd  #eCommerce #CRO #personalization    
    
    
    How to Choose your eCommerce CMS #infographic http://www.brainsins.com/en/blog/how-to-choose-your-ecommerce-cms-infographic/2553?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=how-to-choose-your-ecommerce-cms-infographic …    
    
    
    6 vital e-commerce metrics http://ow.ly/s8IRm  #ecommerce #analytics    
    
    
    Long-Form Video Content Rivals Short, Even on Smartphones http://ow.ly/s8IUw     
    
    
    I'm at Brainsins Headquarters http://4sq.com/1k2M4Sv     
    
    
    Three Ways to Use Surveys to Increase Ecommerce Sales http://ow.ly/s8IUV     
    
    
    Has the Day Arrived for Real-Time See-Commerce ? http://ow.ly/s8IZ9     
    
    
    Emails más interactivos gracias a los GIF animados http://ow.ly/s8Mkz  /v @foto_ecommerce #ecommerce #email #marketing    
    
    
    J.J. Rosen: 'Gamification' helps make learning, earning more fun http://ow.ly/s8ZL5     
    
    
    The 52 Most Breathtaking Photos From Around The World This Year http://ow.ly/s92yL  /cc @MonLabiaga    
    
    
    @Dani_ecommerce @newrubens @ecommbits Vosotros si que sois unos cracks. Que el 2014 sea la releche! @PrincesaSEO    
    
    
    No me gustaría ser sysadmin en Whatsapp esta noche :p    
    
    
    How Sales Leaders Can Use Gamification to Crush Quotas http://ow.ly/s9Al6     
    
    
    Study: 1/3 of Women in U.S. Use Pinterest http://zite.to/1chh1vi     
    
    
    Zappos is going holacratic: no job titles, no managers, no hierarchy http://zite.to/19yKXzV     
    
    
    Why Is Machine Learning (CS 229) The Most Popular Course At Stanford? http://zite.to/1hO9NkA     
    
    
    SVG Drawing Animation http://ow.ly/sarjv  #amazing    
    
    
    7 Great Internet Marketing Tips for 2014 http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/B2CMarketingInsider/~3/QY4Wq3Lxj04/7-great-internet-marketing-tips-2014-0727503 …    
    
    
    Announcing The Forrester Wave™: Mobile Commerce Solution Providers, Q4 2013 http://ow.ly/sarFK     
    
    
    7 Types of Consumer Personas http://ow.ly/sarGK     
    
    
    This is Your Brain on Content Marketing http://ow.ly/sarKR     
    
    
    5 Essentials You Need Before Starting Your Content Marketing Campaign http://ow.ly/sarMd     
    
    
    Things We Online Marketers Could All Improve Upon in 2014 http://ow.ly/sarNK     
    
    
    Without Meaningful User Experiences there is no Gamification Success http://is.gd/EDvpXm     
    
    
    The Habits of Successful People: Thinking in Ratios http://ow.ly/sas2c     
    
    
    3 Reasons Why Responsive Web Design is the Best Option For Your Mobile SEO Strategy  http://ow.ly/sas36     
    
    
    How to Fulfill Your Content Marketing Plan Through Content Repurposing http://ow.ly/sas49     
    
    
    Gamification (Deployment, Application) Market expected to grow $5.5 Billion By 2018 http://ow.ly/scvsM     
    
    
    The Seven Secret Habits of Twitter Power Users http://ow.ly/sas4L     
    
    
    2014 SEO Playbook: Off-Page Factors http://ow.ly/sas3N     
    
    
    About the new recommendations engine of NYT #recsys : On the Path to Personalization: Part 1 http://ow.ly/scvxl     
    
    
    How a “Soft Launch” Can Help You Launch Marketing Automation http://ow.ly/sas6c     
    
    
    @businessgp A real pleasure! :)    
    
    
    @stogiemonster I also hope to be able to assist #GSummit :) Cheers!    
    
    
    Coca-Cola Reserves a Massive Range of MAC Addresses RT @alobbs: Oh, wow… my latest blog post made it to Slashdot :-)  http://beta.slashdot.org/story/196343     
    
    
    @bhaines0 That would be a good explanation @alobbs    
    
    
    Google’s VP9 Video Codec Gets Backing from ARM, Nvidia, Sony And Others, Gives 4K Video Streaming A Fighting Chance http://zite.to/1cLfPBB     
    
    
    100 growth hacks in 100 days http://zite.to/JLMQSY     
    
    
    2013: The Year Of The Content Marketer? - http://klou.tt/181zk30pu54d9     
    
    
    Welcome To The New Startup Nation http://ow.ly/seIKa  /v @javiercuervo Startups are changing everything    
    
    
    An Interview with Paul Graham: Hackers & Painters 10 Years Later http://zite.to/1eSicpp     
    
    
    @Pedro_Robledo Startups "build the collaboration economy to exchange all types of products and services" @javiercuervo    
    
    
    How Video Can Personalize The Social Selling Cycle http://zite.to/1hR0T67     
    
    
    An awesome new mobile app by @shopify to help small online retailers on the go: Introducing Shopify Mobile http://ow.ly/seTQz     
    
    
    Here's The Answer To Why Bitcoin Has Value http://zite.to/1chc0D7     
    
    
    What changed in web design this year (and what’s next) http://zite.to/1eU6H0W     
    
    
    In 1964, Isaac Asimov Imagined the World in 2014 http://zite.to/1alU0V0     
    
    
    Finally, A Super-Simple Modular Robotics Kit - http://pulse.me/s/Ju6xi     
    
    
    Gamification Comes to the Contact Center http://ow.ly/sbFBa     
    
    
    8 apps to help you get fit in 2014 http://ow.ly/sbFBC  #gamification #health    
    
    
    Na casa da minha nai :) (@ Berkana) http://4sq.com/1e0NUMe     
    
    
    Great interview - Andreessen: Bubble Believers 'Don't Know What They're Talking About' http://zite.to/1auE7f3     
    
    
    @DavBoullosa ;) +1000    
    
    
    100 Growth Hacks in 100 Days: 1 to 10 http://ow.ly/seCTy     
    
    
    It's Time! You Need to Focus on Mobile Email Marketing #infographic http://ow.ly/seFFE     
    
    
    @javiercuervo Don't feed the troll! #sabiduríaPopular    
    
    
    GrovePi easily connects Grove Sensors to your Raspberry Pi.  Web enable your world! http://ow.ly/sgEaY  Niiiiiice!    
    
    
    Affiliate Marketing for Beginners http://ow.ly/scvhL     
    
    
    Meet tech billionaire and real life Iron Man Elon Musk http://zite.to/1avQoQp  What a man!    
    
    
    The Marketer's Guide to Google Analytics: How to Extract Numbers That Drive Action http://ow.ly/scviD     
    
    
    Yes, we can! RT @VictorManriqueY @iversity #GDMooc | Can We Use Normal Game Mechanics For #Gamification Design? - http://kcy.me/u5gb     
    
    
    How To Double Your Content Marketing ROI In 2014 http://ow.ly/scvkF     
    
    
    Top 5 Myths of Starting a Business http://is.gd/aNey2U     
    
    
    Netflix's Hastings: Personalization Is Double-Edged Sword http://ow.ly/scvAf     
    
    
    