More great coverage of the #divestment campaign in CNN Money: http://bit.ly/17JEkM2     
    
    
    Thanks @HuffPostGreen for spreading the word about #DrawTheLine this weekend: http://huff.to/156fAKS  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Awesome! Just tweeted to nearly 1 million people RT @FortuneMagazine: One man's quest to loosen fossil fuel's grip http://ow.ly/oZb2D     
    
    
    The epic grassroots movement against Keystone XL that is firing up A LOT of Americans #NoKXL (via @Upworthy) http://www.upworthy.com/you-see-that-thats-the-sweet-sight-of-people-holding-politicians-accountable?g=2 …    
    
    
    Pipeline fighter @janekleeb will be testifying before Congress today. Read her powerful speech here: http://boldnebraska.org/testimony     
    
    
    "America’s national interest is not served by a project that lines the pockets of the few, while risking the lives of the many," @janekleeb    
    
    
    Here's to five years of keeping KXL unbuilt, tar sands in the ground, oil out of our water, and carbon out of our atmosphere.    
    
    
    Since #KXL was proposed 5 years ago, the world has had 3 of 10 hottest years ever & 2013 is on pace to join them (via @MilesGrant)    
    
    
    5 years of delay for Keystone XL. And 40 years of delay for any real climate action out of Congress.    
    
    
    Wow. Despicable, boorish behavior from @RepBillJohnson towards @janekleeb and the American people. What a shill.    
    
    
    .@RepBillJohnson has taken $256,611 of dirty energy money during his career. Any guess why he's pushing for KXL?    
    
    
    I'm not sure "fireworks" and "c-span" are often used in the same tweet. But this KXL hearing just got wild: http://bit.ly/18d4gk6     
    
    
    "My friends on the Republican side of the aisle ought to get their heads out of the tar sands," @janschakowsky #NoKXL    
    
    
    .@RepBillJohnson wants to hear from scientists on KXL? Here are the nation's top saying no to the pipeline: http://bit.ly/18d5f3L     
    
    
    Do these Republican members of Congress really think they can intimidate @janekleeb? She's got more guts than the entire GOP. #NoKXL    
    
    
    I know what will convince President Obama to build Keystone XL … a bunch of Republicans making it a signature issue! Oh, wait. #NoKXL    
    
    
    @OccupyTarSands Not all of it … and many more fights to be had!    
    
    
    Good morning! Time to #DrawTheLine on Keystone XL. Photos already flowing in from around the country.    
    
    
    Coverage of a #DrawTheLine event last night in Two Harbors, MN: http://bit.ly/15eK6HC  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Kid in Bloomington, IN, "I don't like gasoline, I'm scooting for the Earth," http://bit.ly/15eKmGJ  #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    In Middletown, CT, organizers protest outside a TD Bank, financiers of tar sands: http://bit.ly/15eLb2i  #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    Check out the renewable energy powered barn @BoldNebraska just built in the path of KXL: http://Instagram.com/p/ehzjeKj1xK/  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Legendary investor Jeremy Grantham, "I wouldn't own tar sands, and I wouldn't own coal." http://on.wsj.com/1eBNd0l  via @INCRnews    
    
    
    Seeing photos of #DrawTheLine events from Alaska to Nebraska. We're everywhere! #NoKXL    
    
    
    Protests in Vermont are often really, really cute: http://bit.ly/18hYVIq  #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    Listen to @SierraClub Exec. Director Mike Brune, "It's time to draw the line." http://huff.to/18hZbH7  #NoKXL #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    This baby has the right message, "No pipeline, No Tankers, No Problem" http://bit.ly/18hZvps  #NoKXL #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    Rallies from Nebraska to NYC for #DrawTheLine today: http://bit.ly/18i1mKN  #NoKXL    
    
    
    @RachelWolfDC @BarackObama @danieljkessler You love it. But Obama, don't hold back just for my tweets.    
    
    
    Check out our storify from #DrawTheLine: http://bit.ly/18i2eiC     
    
    
    It's time to pass judgement on KXL! Rally at the courthouse in Dahlonega, Georgia: http://bit.ly/1gMfu0d  #NoKXL #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    @350Madison You guys rock! Best photos of the day so far.    
    
    
    @DivestUNF You guys rock! Awesome photos … keep on divesting and drawing lines!    
    
    
    In Athens, GA they're rallying with a civil war era double-barreled cannon, another famous bad idea! http://bit.ly/18i2MVE  #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    @duncanwrites Activism + history nerds = making my dreams come true.    
    
    
    Oh no, pro-KXL fish people are rallying for climate inaction in Florida: http://bit.ly/1gMhc1B  #NoKXL    
    
    
    #DrawtheLine in Boston, because Keystone XL is wicked stupid: http://bit.ly/1gMhtBs  #NoKXL    
    
    
    "Not by sea, Not by Road, Not by Pipe" #DrawTheLine in Nashville, TN: http://bit.ly/18i3SRt     
    
    
    @stopKXL That's right!    
    
    
    Watch out Amherst, MA, a 100 ft tar sands pipeline dragon is marching through town: http://bit.ly/14u4l1v  #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    Occupy the Pipeline: pic.twitter.com/zPz6dgBfga    
    
    
    Wow: Amy Goodman, Vandana Shiva, Christiana Figueres, Jane Goodall, May Boeve & more #DrawTheLine together: pic.twitter.com/5Eplqyf6pC    
    
    
    Jealous! RT @TUGreenClub: On our way to the French Quarter for the second line! #green #nola #NoKXL @350 pic.twitter.com/dRTyhjeSOM    
    
    
    Waitsfield, VT will #DrawTheLine on KXL because "Failure to do so betrays our children" pic.twitter.com/wB02ITSRM6    
    
    
    Just heard from Mobile, AL that despite the pouring rain, all 3 news channels turned out to cover #DrawTheLine    
    
    
    They've got a 90-ft pipeline in Santa Barbara, CA! #DrawTheLine #NoKXL pic.twitter.com/OJpn88aTAc    
    
    
    If we #DrawTheLine on KXL, hopefully Josh Fox @gaslandmovie won't need that life-vest: pic.twitter.com/O7YAvnX2mU    
    
    
    Awesome! A great #DrawTheLine photo from Pakistan #NoKXL: pic.twitter.com/4TFe0P8OLM    
    
    
    Definitely the best #DrawTheLine mustaches I've seen today: http://bit.ly/1b2ACSw  #NoKXL    
    
    
    .@LEETERRYNE Tell that to the families in Kalamazoo and Mayflower. Keystone 1 spilled 13 times in its first year #NoKXL    
    
    
    @Sierraclub Thanks for Drawing the Line with us today! Great to see @bruneski's piece up in Huffpo!    
    
    
    Check out (and share!) this awesome #DrawTheLine Flickr set. Many more coming in: http://bit.ly/DTL-photos  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Awesome to see such a big crowd up in Seattle! They're divesting from fossil fuels & drawing the line: http://bit.ly/16oBj00  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Thinking of all our friends in Hong Kong, Philippines, and Taiwan who are preparing for Usagi's impact. Stay safe: http://wapo.st/16oCAUS     
    
    
    Irony alert @KDVR: Oil spills now exceed 25,000 gallons due to Colorado flooding http://on.kdvr.com/6Ju8hkK     
    
    
    Best lighting award goes to Tuscon's #DrawTheLine event. Beautiful photo: http://bit.ly/15gXOVi  #NoKXL    
    
    
    @DivestDuke Y'all rock! Great work today. Let's go get 'em.    
    
    
    Great update from the #DrawTheLine event in Seattle. Trainings, speeches, and strong commitment to action: http://bit.ly/15gYfig     
    
    
    I'm hosting a screening of "The Future of Energy" in SF tonight at the Palace of Fine Arts tonight. Come by: http://on.fb.me/15gYwSj     
    
    
    Check out this @HuffPostGreen slideshow of #DrawTheLine events that happened around the country today: http://huff.to/15gYEkL  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Great article in @thedailybeast by @billmckibben, "So now the real #divestment fight begins."http://thebea.st/15gw4oV     
    
    
    Whoa. Didn't expect to talk to quite that many people at the Future of Energy launch, but good fun! Fired up. pic.twitter.com/qepgv7Atdv    
    
    
    @lalemmer Thanks so much for turning out. You all rock. Let's go win this thing.    
    
    
    Great to see spanish language coverage of our #DrawTheLine event in Miami Beach: http://bit.ly/15m3KfG     
    
    
    The more Congress plays football with KXL, the less likely it is to get approved. #NoKXL    
    
    
    "As Colorado floods worsen, #divestment gets personal" via Harvard Law Record: http://bit.ly/16mgsRC     
    
    
    Great in-depth article on Ann Arbor, MI's deliberations about fossil fuel #divestment: http://bit.ly/16tNzwi     
    
    
    Climate risk = financial risk. Making that equation sink in is going to be key to winning on fossil fuel divestment.    
    
    
    Great oped from @350 co-founder Kelly Blynn on fossil fuel #divestment in Washington, DC: http://bit.ly/16mhiOi     
    
    
    As a history geek, I love this article on past and present divestment campaigns at Brown: http://bit.ly/16mhqgT     
    
    
    Here's an AP article on @BOldNebraska's kick-ass solar-powered barn they've built in the proposed path of KXL: http://huff.to/1b7tX9C     
    
    
    Good article about students protesting KXL in Iowa. Isn't that an important political state or something? http://bit.ly/1b7tSmp  #NoKXL    
    
    
    More #divestment wins in New Zealand! The dioceses of Wellington and Waiapu are dumping fossil fuels: http://bit.ly/16mhvRO     
    
    
    "Energy is going to be a big factor in 2014, there's no doubt about it." http://bit.ly/1aiVoc7  via @CoralMDavenport    
    
    
    I agree with Michael Klare: it's not enough to promote the solution, you've also got to fight the problem http://aje.me/16mi1iz     
    
    
    Just like we need a diversity of new energy sources to solve climate change, we also need a diversity of new political strategies.    
    
    
    The average American family pays roughly $6,000 a year in subsidies to big business: http://bit.ly/18SMaAd  #outrage    
    
    
    Rejecting KXL is a "no-brainer" for Obama, says @billmckibben on CTV news: http://bit.ly/1fcLqzn  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Yes! Vermont just threw a huge roadblock in the way of a proposed Northeast tar sands pipeline: http://bit.ly/19yHmAU     
    
    
    WaPo: The "president will face a revolt from his political base should he sign off on the pipeline"http://wapo.st/15q7jqt  #NoKXL    
    
    
    This should be required reading in the West Wing this morning: http://wapo.st/15q7jqt  #NoKXL    
    
    
    "If anything, the willingness of people to go to jail over this is expanding," @LCVoters' Gene Karpinski on #NoKXL: http://wapo.st/15q7jqt     
    
    
    Is the world's largest coal company deceiving shareholders about their recoverable reserves? @Greenpeace says yes: http://bit.ly/15qeZZM     
    
    
    @FossilFreeANU @DrRimmer Honored! Thanks for all the fantastic work you guys are doing.    
    
    
    The annual carbon emissions from Keystone XL would be more than all of the 26 million cars in Canada. #NoKXL    
    
    
    More coverage of #DrawTheLine events in Des Monies, Iowa: http://dmreg.co/15q8NRI  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Great coverage from @HuffPostGreen of last weekend's #DrawTheLine event in DC: http://huff.to/15q92fB  #NoKXL    
    
    
    UN high commissioner for human rights, Mary Robinson joins the push to leave fossil fuels in the ground: http://bit.ly/15q9B9g     
    
    
    Mary Robinson's words are a big step forward for the fossil fuel #divestment campaign: http://bit.ly/15q9B9g     
    
    
    The idea of "unburnable carbon" has moved from think tanks to front pages in record speed: http://bit.ly/15q9B9g  #divestment    
    
    
    This might be the most beautiful online activism I've ever seen. Nice work @ClimateReality: http://whatilove.org     
    
    
    "Fossil fuel reserves must be left in the ground," former Irish President Mary Robinson: http://bit.ly/15q9B9g  #divestment    
    
    
    Leef peepers beware, climate change is dulling fall colors: http://wxch.nl/15qb7ba  #connectthedots    
    
    
    Important new study strengthens the connection between climate change and extreme weather: http://usat.ly/15qbiU4     
    
    
    Climate change could increase springtime severe thunderstorms by as much as 40% over the eastern U.S. by century's end.    
    
    
    Many economic models "grossly underestimate" climate risk says Lord Nicholas Stern: http://bit.ly/16XqPZM     
    
    
    The climate crisis could increase the number of hungry people in the world by 20%. That's a human rights crisis: http://bloom.bg/15qcSoX     
    
    
    Will University of Minnesota be the first of the Big Ten to divest from fossil fuels? http://bit.ly/15qdESL     
    
    
    At University of Delaware, students are connecting the dots between sea level rise and the need for divestment: http://bit.ly/15qdQkV     
    
    
    Great oped in the Harvard Crimson supporting fossil fuel #divestment: http://bit.ly/15qeiQj     
    
    
    Over 1,000 people donated to help @BoldNebraska build a solar & wind powered barn in the path of KXL: http://on.fb.me/15qglUk     
    
    
    Canada's promises to cut emissions in exchange for KXL are "too little, too late": http://bit.ly/1amH0Qb  #NoKXL    
    
    
    @DivestTulane @BoldNebraska I don't know, NOLA and Nebraska might be tied in my book …    
    
    
    WTF? US Trade representative is pushing the EU to weaken its stance on tar sands. This is a bombshell: http://huff.to/18o2Cw3     
    
    
    This bombshell of a story calls into question the administration's claims that they're giving KXL a fair review: http://huff.to/18o2Cw3     
    
    
    It's not enough for the US to have crappy climate laws at home? We need to go mess up everyone else's too? http://huff.to/18o2Cw3     
    
    
    Headed over to City Lights to catch @PlatformLondon and @PriceofOil's presentation of "The Oil Road"    
    
    
    Scientists are as sure about humans causing climate change as they are about cigarettes killing humans: http://bit.ly/16zG8DJ     
    
    
    We need to turn Big Oil into the Big Tobacco of this generation, a political pariah that has lost its social license.    
    
    
    GOP would shut-down government and furlough 100,000+ federal employees to push a pipeline that would create 30 jobs? #NoKXL    
    
    
    Pressure builds on Norway to divest tar sands holdings: http://bit.ly/170X9Lb  (via @billmckibben) #divestment    
    
    
    It's good to research the cost of climate to the economy, but better to remember there's no economy on a dead planet: http://nyti.ms/170XugV     
    
    
    Great to have @billmckibben in the @350 Oakland office today talking #divestment & #NoKXL strategy pic.twitter.com/KQ5vsB5IHJ    
    
    
    Hahaha! I've never wanted to get a manicure before, but this is priceless  http://bit.ly/1fozZEN  Thanks @ILoveFossilFuel!    
    
    
    While the #divestment movement was spreading to 300 campuses, our friends at @ILoveFossilFuel were…getting manicures pic.twitter.com/t5KkIizX31    
    
    
    @RL_Miller hahah. I want our own fossil free or climate hawk manicure now.    
    
    
    PricewaterhouseCoopers says climate change is the "mother of all risk," so why are investors ignoring it? http://bit.ly/185LQ4c     
    
    
    Two students break down the hottest movement on college campuses today: #divestment: http://bit.ly/185M0se     
    
    
    "We want to work with our boards on #divestment, but we also know sometimes it takes a little…convincing," http://bit.ly/185M0se     
    
    
    Meet Jenny, one of our @350 crew coordinating the fossil fuel #divestment campaign: http://on.fb.me/1fIM70T     
    
    
    This fall, 10,000+ youth leaders will converge in Pittsburgh, PA to fight for our future. Join me at #PowerShift 2013 http://www.wearepowershift.org/register     
    
    
    Poor Harper, he needs to learn that no really means no. Keep your pipeline at home: http://bit.ly/18sd7OU  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Harper says "There is no Plan B" for Canada if Obama turns down Keystone XL: http://bit.ly/18sd7OU     
    
    
    Harper's comments undermine the State Department analysis that KXL isn't a critical piece of tar sands infrastructure. #NoKXL    
    
    
    What exactly is PM Harper going to do if we deny Keystone XL? Drown us in maple syrup? Bury us in maple leaves? #NoKXL    
    
    
    Who's commitment do you think is stronger, an oily politician or a rancher fighting for his home? Harper is going to lose. #NoKXL    
    
    
    Canadian PM Harper's new brilliant negotiating strategy: locking himself inside of bathrooms: http://read.bi/1baaFNn     
    
    
    Great front page story on @HuffPostGreen on the "ugly toll" KXL would have on endangered species: http://huff.to/1fJIjMZ     
    
    
    Whisky is threatened by climate change. Enough said. http://bit.ly/1fJJV9n  via @ClimateReality    
    
    
    .@CHedegaardEU That's fantastic, although it certainly would be nice to get beyond dialogue and into more action.    
    
    
    Exxon is killing whales: http://huff.to/1fJKQXB  via @Oceana @HuffPostGreen    
    
    
    More economic analysis showing why KXL is so critical to the expansion of the tar sands: http://bit.ly/1eKVOx6  #NoKXL    
    
    
    The math that @billmckibben laid out in @RollingStone last summer is now at the center of the climate debate: http://bloom.bg/1avveD9     
    
    
    IPCC concludes that 60-80% of current fossil fuel reserves are unburnable, but Exxon alone spends $100 million day looking for more.    
    
    
    The more the idea of a "carbon budget" goes mainstream, the stronger the case for fossil fuel #divestment becomes.    
    
    
    Want to wonk out on the IPCC? @TheEconomist talks radiative forcing & climate sensitivity here. Sexy: http://econ.st/1avx46Q     
    
    
    World's scientists say civilization is on the brink. Congress does...nothing.    
    
    
    This would be a great time for @BarackObama to get up on the WH roof with those solar panels and tell us he's denying KXL.    
    
    
    Sec Kerry says climate requires an "all hands on deck" approach. That starts with saying #nokxl    
    
    
    The media should be connecting the IPCC report to the economy. Leaving 80% of fossil reserves underground would have huge implications.    
    
    
    @luckytran The IPCC could use your help. Illuminate the AR5!    
    
    
    I want a song. @eilperin: When it's IPCC day, @Revkin busts out w/ not one, but 2 analyses: http://nyti.ms/1eN2wCM  & http://nyti.ms/1bMEZ3y     
    
    
    @luckytran how about, "We. Are. F***ed. "    
    
    
    .@USChamber Curious what you all think of the IPCC report. Any chance you'll stop bankrolling climate deniers in Congress?    
    
    
    Up in @HuffPostGreen, "Will Pres. Obama Let Republicans Bully Him Into Approving Keystone XL?" http://huff.to/16POOHf  #NoKXL    
    
    
    When it comes to politics, the answer on Keystone XL is as clear as the science: reject this pipeline: http://huff.to/16POOHf     
    
    
    @SwarthmoreMJ good luck! We'll be tuned in.    
    
    
    @nprnews @NPRInskeep @BarackObama Will he stand up to Big Oil and say no to the Keystone XL pipeline?    
    
    
    All 5 candidates running to fill @MarkeyMemo's old seat endorsed fossil fuel #divestment at a recent candidate forum!    
    
    
    In MA house race, candidates try to outdo each other on the environment, supporting #NoKXL & #divestment: http://bit.ly/16ZO16v     
    
    
    The Anglican Church is leading the charge for fossil fuel #divestment in New Zealand: http://bit.ly/1bXMJjo     
    
    
    An update from the growing #divestment campaign at George Washington: http://bit.ly/16ZOmWO     
    
    
    Another evening spent drinking bourbon and comparing climate models #yolo    
    
    
    Maybe the GOP climate plan is to just shutdown global warming when physics refuses to negotiate with them?    
    
    
    The #divestment movement is directly confronting industry today, as @billmckibben confronts Jim Rogers, former Duke CEO, at #Brown.    
    
    
    It's so wildly inspiring to look back through the photos from February's #ForwardOnClimate: http://bit.ly/1bzOXmb     
    
    
    @eschor @janekleeb glad to hear you're safe.    
    
    
    Thinking about our political/reporter friends at the capitol today, hope y'all are safe over there.    
    
    
    Harvard says it won't divest from fossil fuels. We say, game on: http://buswk.co/18VqRAj  #divestment    
    
    
    32 local chambers of commerce are pushing for clean energy in DC right now. Congress should follow: http://bit.ly/1cac9dx     
    
    
    Boom! @TransCanada delays Energy East. Protest will delay it even more: http://bit.ly/18VsxcM     
    
    
    This is what they should do with the Keystone XL pipeline pic.twitter.com/X3cbR76Xrz    
    
    
    .@350 plans in art parks. Storm king: pic.twitter.com/J8GguAJYXv    
    
    
    Developing new fossil fuel reserves is like "amassing typewriters right before the computer age." (via @SaqibSansU) #divestment    
    
    
    For 1st time ever, a tropical storm, blizzard, tornado, and extreme wild fire are simultaneously threatening the US: http://bit.ly/1fOV0Zo     
    
    
    Amanda=badass @guardianeco: Climate Council raises $1m through itObama-style fundraising drive http://gu.com/p/3jakt/tf     
    
    
    Great interview with @BillMcKibben on Morning Joe about his transformation from writer to activist: http://nbcnews.to/1a9gVmX     
    
    
    Meet the Nebraskans who are taking down Keystone XL. American heroes: http://bit.ly/1a9h1ej  #NoKXL    
    
    
    .@revkin Do you think Harvard should have stayed invested in apartheid South Africa? http://nyti.ms/177lZFg     
    
    
    Stavins totally dodges the moral implications of fossil fuel investment:  http://nyti.ms/177lZFg  @Revkin    
    
    
    @duncanwrites ++    
    
    
    @Revkin Same could be said for Polaroid in the 1980s: fundamentally? no. As currently operating? Yes.    
    
    
    @Revkin if Harvard said they'd only invest in best in class, it would be different. But they're avoiding the entire issue.    
    
    
    @Revkin And I'm headed off to Hardly Strictly Bluegrass in Golden Gate Park. Climate debate can wait!    
    
    
    Solving climate change is, above all, an act of imagination.    
    
    
    .@350 athlete @RozSavage has a new book #StopDriftingStartRowing. Check it out: http://amzn.to/14kxRTc  (US) or http://amzn.to/148oaKZ  (UK)    
    
    
    Oxford University study concludes that fossil fuel divestment campaign has grown faster than apartheid or tobacco: http://bit.ly/1b52SQt     
    
    
    Think fossil fuel #divestment won't make an impact? Oxford University says think again in the @guardian: http://bit.ly/1b52SQt     
    
    
    "The outcome of the stigmatization process...poses the most far-reaching threat to fossil fuel companies and the vast energy value chain."    
    
    
    In the 19th century, Quakers pushed to end the slave trade. In the 21st, they're calling for fossil fuel divestment: http://bit.ly/1bVBOnQ     
    
    
    Quakers helped move the British Empire's economy away from slavery. Can they move the UK's away from fossil fuels? http://bit.ly/1bVBOnQ     
    
    
    @oharjo well, it took them over 100 years, so yeah … for sure.    
    
    
    @oharjo Excellent news!    
    
    
    Writer Rebecca Solnit calls on the SF Retirement Board to divest from fossil fuels: http://bit.ly/1bVHcr7  via @SFGate    
    
    
    As a big fan of "Bury the Chains," I'm very excited to see the Quakers joining the fossil fuel #divestment campaign: http://bit.ly/1bVBOnQ     
    
    
    @PaulRogersSJMN SFERS Board is going to be debating divestment at 5pm tomorrow. Should be some fireworks if you want to come up for it!    
    
    
    When do we get to furlough non-essential members of Congress? Can we start with the climate deniers?    
    
    
    Head of the OECD warns governments there is no "climate bailout option": http://mobile.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-24450438?utm_source=Daily+Carbon+Briefing&utm_campaign=f418e93b65-DAILY_BRIEFING&utm_medium=email&utm_term=0_876aab4fd7-f418e93b65-303421477 …    
    
    
    Crowd fund a great new climate leader: http://m.good.is/posts/with-hero-hatchery-you-can-help-support-climate-activists …    
    
    
    SF Retirement Board could vote on fossil fuel divestment today: http://m.sfexaminer.com/sanfrancisco/san-francisco-retirement-fund-board-could-vote-to-divest-from-fossil-fuel-companies/Content?oid=2600760 …    
    
    
    We're lucky to have such brave leaders as @kuminaidoo and the Arctic 30. Russia should be ashamed: http://gu.com/p/3jdcp/tw     
    
    
    @PaulRogersSJMN you bet.    
    
    
    SF friends, join us at 5:00pm this afternoon to push the city's retirement board to divest from fossil fuels: http://on.fb.me/1hCAWVV     
    
    
    "It takes a peculiar kind of genius to see the monster and to see that it might begin to be pushed back by small actions," Rebecca Solnit    
    
    
    New study concludes "the most traumatic" weather events will be the new norm: http://nyti.ms/15VYs04     
    
    
    "Climate departure": it's as bad as it sounds…and coming sooner than you think http://nyti.ms/15VYs04     
    
    
    Biking down to the SF retirement board meeting. Hoping they take another step towards #divestment today.    
    
    
    Just worked with a nurse from SEIU on her testimony for the retirement board hearing. Powerful stuff!    
    
    
    We're just about to get underway here at the SF retirement board meeting to discuss fossil fuel divestment #divestSF    
    
    
    Supervisor @AvalosSF introduces our #divestment resolution. He's a real leader in this growing movement.    
    
    
    .@AvalosSF reminds the retirement board that the Board of Supervisors UNANIMOUSLY approved a resolution urging them to divest #divestSF    
    
    
    "How do you want to be seen by future generations?" @AvalosSF asks the SF Retirement Board, pushing them to #divestSF    
    
    
    "Carbon is artificially cheap in our economy. And absent regulations, we have to do something to disrupt the business model," SF Sup. Breed    
    
    
    "The risk increment of divestment is so small it's almost immaterial," financial advisor Paul Solli, Aperio Group #divestSF    
    
    
    “The amount of risk of holding on to these stocks is much higher than the risk of divesting," retiree Jack Fleck #divestSF    
    
    
    "Ignoring the climate risk is irresponsible and reckless," @350 Senior Analyst Brett Fleishman    
    
    
    Choking up a bit listening to SF mom Kim Pikul testifying on behalf of her baby boy, urging the retirement board to #divestSF    
    
    
    "We should be investing in things that we're proud of, not companies that are destroying the environment," another SF retiree #divestSF    
    
    
    Powerful to hear so many retirees, nurses, transportation workers, union members & city employees pushing to #divestSF #divestment    
    
    
    Great to see students from SF State at #divestSF hearing. They divested, now it's the city's turn! pic.twitter.com/cIAo6PxdcX    
    
    
    Awesome to have members of @seiu1021 in the house pushing to #divestSF from fossil fuels!    
    
    
    SFERS staff say they have the resources to pursue #divestment if the board approves it. This is doable, it's just a matter of will.    
    
    
    "You got my attention with Jeremy Grantham," SF Retirement Board member #divestSF #divestment    
    
    
    President of SFERS says he'd support first two levels of #divestment. This is getting interesting. #divestSF    
    
    
    Resolution to start active shareholder advocacy loses, but board votes to research the issue. It's a small step, now we push hard.    
    
    
    On BART to the Oakland Coliseum for Game 5 and the announcer is shouting, "Game Train! Game Train!" I love this town.    
    
    
    GRAND SLAM!!!!!!!    
    
    
    The Republican Gov's office in PA was "too busy" to send out a press release about the state's new climate report: http://bit.ly/GZToMp     
    
    
    More momentum for #divestment RT @enviroblack: Major pension fund gets of out of fossil fuels http://goo.gl/57U5nf     
    
    
    "This sustainable approach isn’t about charity, but about enhancing returns," says $38-billion Swedish pension fund: http://bit.ly/19N7rBG     
    
    
    Know someone applying to college? Check out this amazing Climate Justice scholarship from Sterling College: http://bit.ly/GVCvCW     
    
    
    Recently heard that Cambridge Associates has gotten 20x more inquiries on ESG issues in last 6 months than the past 3 years combined.    
    
    
    Study finds that mercury levels are rising around the tar sands in Alberta: http://bit.ly/1alSfGP     
    
    
    Excited to be heading up to Seattle on Wednesday to join @mayormcginn & @mayorinnovation at the Seattle Divestment Forum #citydivest    
    
    
    “You can get 100,000 ticks on a moose." That's something I never want to picture again: http://nyti.ms/1alSFwQ     
    
    
    Wow. Moose watching is a $115 million a year industry in NH … one now threatened by climate change: http://nyti.ms/1alSFwQ     
    
    
    Here in Seattle at a divestment event with Goodfunds Wealth Management. Room is buzzing w/ excitement for #CityDivest forum.    
    
    
    Just learned that most people don't jay walk in Seattle. Hard for someone who grew up in Boston to handle ...    
    
    
    If only the Tigers would cave like Republicans.    
    
    
    I love hearing about investment firms like Trillium that are taking #divestment far beyond our original top 200 fossil fuel companies list    
    
    
    We need to expand the idea of sustainable reinvestment beyond solar and wind to efficiency, batteries, tech, transit, water management, etc    
    
    
    Will Lana from Trillium: the financial community has done far more complicated things than figure out how to divest from fossil fuels.    
    
    
    The $140 million Russell Family Foundation divested from the Filthy 15 coal companies after reading @billmckibben's Rolling Stone article    
    
    
    The Russell 3000 is one of the most famous economic indexes. The family behind it has divested from coal -- and wants to do more.    
    
    
    @DaveBaldwinJax insane    
    
    
    @SimonCopland here here!    
    
    
    At Seattle City Hall about to kick off the #CityDivest forum w/ a press conference w/ @mayormcginn and others.    
    
    
    Tune in live to http://Seattle.gov/mayorlive  for our #CityDivest press conference staring momentarily    
    
    
    "We're the first generation to see the impacts of climate change and the last that can do anything about it," @mayormcginn #CityDivest    
    
    
    The Santa Clara Water District didn't just divest from fossil fuels, they're also going carbon neutral by 2020. #CityDivest    
    
    
    Interest in Green Century's fossil free fund has grown 50% since the #divestment campaign began 11 months ago. #CityDivest    
    
    
    "This is a crisis in which we're witnessing the largest changes in human civilization," Bob Massie @NewEconomics #CityDivest    
    
    
    "Now, we may be facing the mother of all bubbles," @NewEconomics Bob Massie on the carbon bubble #CityDivest    
    
    
    "We know that it's the right thing for our planet and our finances. And we know it's effective," Bob Massie on #divestment    
    
    
    "Why would we invest in something that makes things worse? It contradicts our values as a city," Seattle @mayormcginn #CityDivest    
    
    
    We're kicking off our #CityDivest forum in Seattle tonight. Great to have so many leaders like @AvalosSF here: pic.twitter.com/po22LTMzAj    
    
    
    Amazing to be in Seattle City Hall talking about fossil fuel #divestment. This movement has already come a long way pic.twitter.com/VF46YuFp6T    
    
    
    "Political reality? What about actual reality," Seattle @mayormcginn on pushing for climate action #CityDivest    
    
    
    Rockefeller Family Fund had 60% of its portfolio invested in companies doing business in South Africa & still divested. Fossil fuels easier    
    
    
    "You can be a caboose waiting to be dragged along or you can be an engine that is driving change," @NewEconomics Bob Massie #CityDivest    
    
    
    Main day of the Seattle Divestment Forum about to kick off. Follow #CityDivest for updates: pic.twitter.com/QnvAKEUsMG    
    
    
    Al Gore: "The carbon bubble is going to burst -- it's time to sell oil stocks": http://yhoo.it/18sTiYc  #CityDivest #Divestment    
    
    
    In @HuffPostGreen: @BillMcKibben and the fossil fuel #divestment movement heads to Europe: http://ow.ly/pWFkt     
    
    
    "I want to thank the young people at the forefront of this movement," Geeta Aiyer, Boston Common Asset Management #CityDivest    
    
    
    "There is no basis to believe that there are structurally higher returns in energy" Geeta Aiyer, Boston Common Asset Management #CityDivest    
    
    
    Banks competed to offer South Africa free portfolios in the 80s. Soon, they'll be competing over fossil free portfolios. #CityDivest    
    
    
    Great to have @SethYurdin, Providence City Council Majority Leader, here at the #CityDivest forum @BrownDivestCoal @DivestRISD    
    
    
    It's good to focus on divesting from high carbon projects, but the whole industry is at fault for blocking climate action #CityDivest    
    
    
    Nice! Prince Charles says pension funds must become more sustainable or risk a "miserable future" http://bbc.in/18t054a     
    
    
    Brown students call on coal-connected trustees to recuse themselves from upcoming #divestment vote: http://bit.ly/GU3QoL     
    
    
    Big time oil executive says the chances of the full Keystone XL getting built are dwindling: http://bloom.bg/GU4se9  #NoKXL    
    
    
    @sejorg Thanks for the retweet! It's going to be an interesting vote at Brown.    
    
    
    Good AP article on the diverse movement showing up at #PowerShift this weekend: http://nyti.ms/GU4KBN     
    
    
    "It's people on front-line communities who are crucial to leading this fight," @billmckibben in NYT/AP: http://nyti.ms/GU4KBN     
    
    
    Divesting from fossil fuels is just the first step towards creating a less carbon intensive portfolio. #CityDivest    
    
    
    @radical_rachael welcome to my world for the last year! i never thought i'd be talking about compound annualized growth …    
    
    
    "Finding Greater Alpha" is another economic term that would be a great indy rock band name. #CityDivest    
    
    
    Western Washington University foundation representatives are here because 80% of their students voted for divestment #CityDivest    
    
    
    Seattle has owns $89.4 million of top 200 fossil fuel company stock, that's 16 million tons of carbon. #CityDivest    
    
    
    It took just a day of trading to help an NGO reduce the carbon in their portfolio by 70% #CityDivest    
    
    
    Divestment and reinvestment isn't just good for a city's pension, it could increase local GDP #CityDivest    
    
    
    Total amount of city & foundation capital represented here at #CityDivest is over $40 billion.    
    
    
    "Most of the best financial investors in America don't know that low carbon portfolios can outperform," Ken Locklin, Impax #CityDivest    
    
    
    We've got suits and students: both city officials at #CityDivest & youth at #PowerShift are talking #divestment today!    
    
    
    I'd like to see @AsYouSow founder @TomVanDyck take on any university board in the country. This guy is a #divestment machine. #CityDivest    
    
    
    Interesting: how do we develop shareholder engagement that leads to derivative suits down the road? #CityDivest    
    
    
    49% of all millenials w/ a net worth of over $1m are putting an ESG screen on their investments #CityDivest    
    
    
    Whoa! @WValderrama (Fez from that 70's show) is starring in a new climate action movie: http://bit.ly/1cDuUUy     
    
    
    "People of color and women on boards has shown to add value," @TomVanDyck at #CityDivest    
    
    
    Here's a picture of some of the city officials here at #CityDivest, true leaders! pic.twitter.com/MIyGofss2x    
    
    
    "Look, it's not a line chart, it's a bar chart!" #divestmentjokes #CityDivest    
    
    
    The #divestment campaign is "a breath of fresh air moving through the financial community," Leslie Samuelrich @GreenCenturyNRG    
    
    
    @JonCarsonOFA @OFA Thought you'd like this video w/ @WValderrama...from Voto Latino to climate: http://bit.ly/1cDuUUy     
    
    
    @kate_sheppard Fez made a climate video: http://bit.ly/1cDuUUy     
    
    
    @JonCarsonOFA Thanks! They're coming out with a few more hollywood style climate vids in the coming weeks.    
    
    
    @JonCarsonOFA Environmental Media Association    
    
    
    @src2 @MSQRD @TomVanDyck more importantly, we got to have some beers watching the Red Sox win last night.    
    
    
    @radical_rachael great to meet you today. Keep up the awesome work!    
    
    
    Boom! 73.7% of Columbia students just voted to support fossil fuel #divestment: http://www.columbiaspectator.com/2013/10/18/heinrich-wins-senate-seat-divestment-passes-overwhelmingly …    
    
    
    I wonder how many Wall Street types sit on Columbia's board. Anyone know?    
    
    
    Back of America, Goldman Sachs, & Citi are all well represented on Columbia's board. Exactly who we want to pressure about #divestment    
    
    
    @iscarabaid well, not all of them, but a lot for sure    
    
    
    @MilesHalpine thanks. Looks like about half in finance.    
    
    
    @NickKristof you should try the sierra high route! Mostly backcountry, almost all over 8,000 ft.    
    
    
    Hahah! That's my Red Sox hat on @bruneski pic.twitter.com/tv4aE7KW8Z    
    
    
    At a #PowerShift panel about stories from the #divestment movement. Such creative and strategic work happening on campus.    
    
    
    Tufts students & faculty are meeting with their board on Monday to push for #divestment.    
    
    
    "If you guys get a letter of rejection it's a good thing, because it brings attention to your campaign." #divestment    
    
    
    Brown students tag #divestment photos so they show up in the college's Instagram feed. Good tactic!    
    
    
    Anti-apartheid veteran sharing lessons with students in the fossil fuel #divestment movement #powershift pic.twitter.com/FPbCqgxEQz    
    
    
    Listening to a Tulane student answer a Yale student's question about how to run a #divestment referendum on campus. #powershift    
    
    
    "Don't just write for your friends, write for THEIR friends," @engagejoe rocking social media strategy #powershift    
    
    
    "We met teachers, moms, everyday people who are ready to risk their freedom to stop this pipeline," @RAN Todd Zimmer #powershift #nokxl    
    
    
    .@billmckibben and a NYT photographer heading off to do an outdoor photo shoot pic.twitter.com/xNuITAOD75    
    
    
    Backstage watching @MauraCowley of @energyaction rock the mic at tonight's #powershift plenary pic.twitter.com/8vAKq4Oi92    
    
    
    "How do we push the fossil fuel industry into the public eye and show they are worse than the tobacco industry?" @MauraCowley    
    
    
    "In the 20th century, they fought for equality. In the 21st century, we're fighting for existence," @RevYearwood #powershift    
    
    
    "If you don't like @TransCanada make some noise!" And thousands scream... #powershift    
    
    
    Kicking off #KeystoneFAIL presentation at #powershift. This rocks pic.twitter.com/mf0M045I8s    
    
    
    @WiseRiseInfo we know! And great to see so many Canadians fighting the tar sands too!    
    
    
    "I came here to tell you the truth. That's one thing the government or industry will never have," @clameman #powershift #keystoneFAIL    
    
    
    Stand strong @IdleNoMore4, thousands here at #powershift support you! #elsipogtog #cdnpoli    
    
    
    "We will no longer allow governments to play environmental roulette with our lives," @clameman #powershift    
    
    
    .@billmckibben rallying the crowd at #powershift pic.twitter.com/EgRcckpEZA    
    
    
    "We've got to play defense, but it's more fun to play offense," @billmckibben on KXL and divestment #powershift    
    
    
    Brothers in climate: @bruneski & @billmckibben backstage at #powershift pic.twitter.com/ThBjwldvyl    
    
    
    "We're the generation that elected the first black president. We can stop a damn pipeline," Ishmael Buckner, former Obama staff #powershift    
    
    
    We've got way better jams than the coal industry. @JasiriX rocking #powershift rally pic.twitter.com/acwh4jOuFj    
    
    
    "It does the heart good to see all you young people out there fighting for me," Terri Blanton, @kftc #powershift    
    
    
    Never thought I'd be listening to a 13-yr old rapping about a climate recovery plan. Epic. #powershift    
    
    
    Don't frack Sponge Bob! pic.twitter.com/apO0JG98kX    
    
    
    @abigailwick Hi! Saw some of your coverage & thought you might be interested in this tour we're doing: http://gofossilfree.org/europe-tour/     
    
    
    Powerful response to Pres. Faust's #divestment decision from Harvard Law Students: http://bit.ly/19XdL3F     
    
    
    "We believe that the Harvard motto, 'Veritas,' is more than just a slogan," HLS Divest Harvard: http://bit.ly/19XdL3F  #divestment    
    
    
    This 1991 article tobacco #divestment reads exactly like our strategy around fossil fuels: http://bit.ly/19Xg2fn     
    
    
    Harvard's endowment isn't a political tool? What about when it divested from tobacco in 1990? http://nyti.ms/1a8XcpN     
    
    
    Big Tobacco threatened to pull research funding if schools divested. Will Big Oil try the same tactic? http://bit.ly/HedBhs     
    
    
    @peterrothberg @chloemaxmin wicked smart.    
    
    
    Good news! Ann Arbor city council votes to support fossil fuel divestment: http://annarborchronicle.com/2013/10/22/ann-arbor-oks-fossil-fuel-divestment/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=ann-arbor-oks-fossil-fuel-divestment …    
    
    
    Local NPR story on last week's #CityDivest forum: http://bit.ly/1adtj7I     
    
    
    Nice! Al Gore says Obama will reject the Keystone XL pipeline "atrocity": http://finance.yahoo.com/blogs/daily-ticker/keystone-pipeline-atrocity-president-obama-reject-al-gore-123018132.html …    
    
    
    Help fund a book that will tell the story of how corporations & militaries are looking to cash in on climate change: http://bit.ly/1aiNGQJ     
    
    
    @writerfarmer hahha. Yes, typo.    
    
    
    Flying Aer Lingus via Dublin on the way to Berlin to kick off our #FossilFree Europe tour and half the line are red heads. My people!    
    
    
    Good sign: Carol Browner predicts that Obama will reject KXL: http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/330461-ex-white-house-climate-guru-predicts-obama-will-say-no-to-keystone … #NOKXL    
    
    
    @HuffPostGreen a "ridocity"?    
    
    
    BREAKING: Foothill-De Anza in CA becomes the first community college in the country to divest from fossil fuels! #divestment    
    
    
    Foothill-De Anza Community College just schooled #Harvard: divestment matters, it's responsible, and it's the moral thing to do.    
    
    
    A state school, community college, and liberal arts colleges have divested from fossil fuels. Will #Brown be the first Ivy?    
    
    
    More info on Foothill-De Anza, the 1st community college in the country to divest from fossil fuels: http://bit.ly/1fYpozQ     
    
    
    So proud of CA starting to lead the way on #divestment. SF, SF State, Berkeley, Richmond, Santa Monica, Santa Clara, De Anza -- yeehaw!    
    
    
    Alums! @BrownUniversity is voting on divesting from coal this weekend. Tell them to vote yes & RT to spread the word!    
    
    
    Just arrived in Berlin: graffiti, cafes & fallen leaves. #FossilFree tour starts on Sunday!    
    
    
    Problem? Over 50% of Oxford University’s grants for its Institute for Energy Studies come from oil and gas companies: http://bit.ly/1d61GOf     
    
    
    Only 3 out of 250 studies authored at Oxford's oil funded Institute for Energy Studies were on renewable energy. #fossilfree    
    
    
    Big weekend for #divestment at @BrownUniversity. Congratulations to @BrownDivestCoal for all the great work: http://bit.ly/1d60gTS     
    
    
    Has Harvard made a "Faust-ian" bargain with the fossil fuel industry? http://bit.ly/1aolU5p     
    
    
    Great article about how #divestment movement is building in MA: http://bit.ly/1d60DxK     
    
    
    My new favorite German word: Desinvestitionskampagne. #FossilFree    
    
    
    Great article in USA Today on US #PowerShift: http://usat.ly/1d61rTn     
    
    
    Great article in the @guardian about the growing fossil fuel #divestment campaign coming the UK: http://bit.ly/1hkdjE3     
    
    
    @climatehc Thanks for the retweet! Hope to see you in London on Nov 1: http://bit.ly/1c8Qzmz     
    
    
    @nwoje @emma_biermann @billmckibben @carbontrouble @mattoakland @hodabaraka getting excited!    
    
    
    Getting ready for our 1st #FossilFree Europe tour stop here in Berlin. Thanks to @boell_stiftung for hosting!    
    
    
    Working on a press release for this evening's #FossilFree Berlin tour stop w/ @hodabaraka pic.twitter.com/R64IbPjaML    
    
    
    Some of the cast & crew of tonight's #FossilFree Berlin show @carbontrouble @MattOakland @billmckibben @nwoje pic.twitter.com/xfz8cIPDUg    
    
    
    Press Release from @BrownDivestCoal & @GoFossilFree on @BrownUniversity saying "no" to coal #divestment: http://bit.ly/1a8QLyW     
    
    
    Brown's reasons not to divest don't hold up. Here's why: http://bit.ly/1a8QLyW  #divestment    
    
    
    Outrageous: .@BrownUniversity Pres. Paxson says coal doesn't pose enough social harm to warrant divestment.    
    
    
    .@BrownUniversity says #divestment doesn't make an impact. Academic studies (oh, and history) say different: http://bit.ly/1a8QLyW     
    
    
    Bad PR move: @BrownUniversity announces it won't divest from coal on the anniversary of Hurricane Sandy.    
    
    
    Scandalous: Numerous @BrownUniversity board members have big financial stakes in the coal industry: http://bit.ly/1a8SeoT     
    
    
    Just banged out a press release on Brown. Now upstairs w/ 200+ at #FossilFree Berlin show. #Divestment is global!    
    
    
    Great panel discussion with German allies & experts at #FossilFree Berlin event: pic.twitter.com/Q0pdrMUfeE    
    
    
    Studies say coal causes 13,000+ deaths a year. That's not enough of a "social cost" for Brown to divest?    
    
    
    Up on @HuffPostGreen, Brown's Misguided Vote to Not Divest from Coal: http://www.huffingtonpost.com/jamie-henn/brown-university-coal_b_4168174.html … #divestment    
    
    
    Great comment from Tadzio Muller: we need to learn how to better respond to climate disasters. #FossilFree    
    
    
    @HealthyPlanetUK so true!    
    
    
    Busy Sunday for the #climate movement: #TurnTheTide in NYC, #FossilFree in Berlin, #Divestment decision at Brown, & more!    
    
    
    Great to hear that @klima_allianz is working on a coal #divestment campain against #Kfw-Bank. We're excited to join them!    
    
    
    Activists here at #FossilFree Berlin from Serbia, Norway, Spain & beyond. Amazing audience.    
    
    
    Great article on @commondreams about today's #TurnTheTide mobilization in NYC. Thanks team! http://bit.ly/1bt4XoY     
    
    
    #FossilFree Berlin show is a wrap. Time to go find a beer...    
    
    
    Great piece from @billmckibben in @TomDispatch on KXL and Obama: http://www.tomdispatch.com/post/175765/tomgram%3A_bill_mckibben%2C_can_obama_ever_stand_up_to_the_oil_industry/#more …    
    
    
    Some good campaign planning (and chatting) over kolsch w/ @Greenpeace & @klima_allianz --now, on to Amsterdam! #FossilFree    
    
    
    Pitch Perfect: "Coal Companies Thrilled University Finally Acknowledges Their Voices" http://bit.ly/HqKDer     
    
    
    There have been 32 billion-dollar weather disasters in 2013: http://bit.ly/17nvt6c  #connectthedots    
    
    
    Cool! Our blog pushing back on the @BrownUniversity divestment decision is on the front page of @HuffPostGreen: http://huff.to/HoR56v     
    
    
    Letter after letter from the @BrownUniversity community slamming the Board's decision not to divest: http://bit.ly/HoRje0     
    
    
    Brown's decision not to divest shows "appalling narrowness in the Corporation’s concept of its mission": http://bit.ly/HoRje0     
    
    
    "The administration is throwing our generation under the bus out of political cowardice," Gabriel Schwartz, @BrownUniversity ’13    
    
    
    @HuffPostGreen Thanks team! Some more powerful letters from students here: http://bit.ly/HoRje0     
    
    
    "Our administration has an inordinate fondness for creating committees. If only it felt the same way about leadership," Emily Kirkland ’13    
    
    
    Keystone XL has become "an X-ray for a flagging presidency" writes @billmckibben: http://bit.ly/HoS8DG     
    
    
    @ALIGNny Thanks for the amazing work. The event looked beautiful and powerful!    
    
    
    Divestment … in German! Check out this interview with @billmckibben in Klimaretter: http://bit.ly/1iphhcb     
    
    
    Great video of UVM students marching on their board of trustees to demand #divestment: http://bfpne.ws/1amruXX     
    
    
    Channel 5 News: "Protest erupts at UVM over climate change" http://bit.ly/1amrA1S  #divestment    
    
    
    Student #divestment activists are escalating on campuses across the US…it's going to be an action packed fall!    
    
    
    Just spent 2 hrs biking around Amsterdam, this is the way a city should be! Excited for our #FossilFree show tonight.    
    
    
    "Fossil fuel campaign is gathering momentum," @billmckibben in the @guardian: http://bit.ly/1aR9nEv  #divestment    
    
    
    Getting ready for our big #FossilFree event in Amsterdam tonight w/ @kuminaidoo & @billmckibben. 900+ expected! pic.twitter.com/GWiMfXS7PS    
    
    
    Huge crowd here in Amsterdam watching @ChasingIce & getting ready for #FossilFree presentation up next!    
    
    
    Ice cream break backstage w/ @hodabaraka & @nwoje at #fossilfree  Amsterdam: pic.twitter.com/n9ZcY11nDE    
    
    
    Big applause for @kuminaidoo & @billymckibben as #FossilFree Amsterdam show starts up!    
    
    
    Greenpeace International's @kuminaidoo at #FossilFree Amsterdam pic.twitter.com/pFbrequan7    
    
    
    "You either transform quickly now or you die in the medium to long term," @kuminaidoo challenging fossil fuel companies #FossilFree    
    
    
    "They have to understand, nature does not negotiate," @kuminaidoo #FossilFree    
    
    
    "I have no doubt that those of us standing up for climate justice will be vilified now, but history will absolve us," @kuminaidoo    
    
    
    "You all here in the Netherlands have the best target in the world to go after: Shell," @kuminaidoo, #FossilFree Amsterdam    
    
    
    "It's a challenge to speak with honesty…and not freak people out," @kuminaidoo. So True. #FossilFree Amsterdam.    
    
    
    Copenhagen failed "because the power of the fossil fuel industry was great enough to block change," @billmckibben #FossilFree    
    
    
    "It's crazy to think about making money by breaking the one planet that we have," @billmckibben #FossilFree Amsterdam    
    
    
    "We're sort of activism for people who are afraid of heights," @billmckibben joking about @350 vs. @Greenpeace #FossilFree    
    
    
    "If we're going to take effective action,we must take that action in the places where we have leverage," @billmckibben on #divestment    
    
    
    .@KumiNaidoo, who worked to end apartheid in South Africa, sharing how #divestment helped the cause…and can help again on climate.    
    
    
    The town of Boxtel, Netherlands banned fracking & 100 Dutch towns followed…now they're leading the #divestment movement! #FossilFree    
    
    
    Climate "is a structural problem & at the heart of it is that the fossil fuel industry is allowed to pollute for free," @billmckibben    
    
    
    Great to see @billmckibben & @kuminaidoo on stage together -- powerful alliance! pic.twitter.com/nTIjn48oLR    
    
    
    "We've got to go after them all," @billmckibben answering a question about coal vs. oil vs. gas. Game on! #FossilFree    
    
    
    "We've got to get to Edinburgh, but you've got to get outside & sign up for this campaign!" @billmckibben. On we go! #FossilFree    
    
    
    Great piece from @radical_rachael in @yesmagazine on the #CityDivest forum in Seattle. Check it out: http://bit.ly/17vf2mf     
    
    
    .@billmckibben pops the carbon bubble and launches the #FossilFree Netherlands campaign pic.twitter.com/C4RLICsm4q    
    
    
    Right where we want it: @algore warns of the carbon bubble & calls for #divestment in the WSJ: http://on.wsj.com/17XHDNH     
    
    
    Great @billmckibben interview in Open Democracy about the growing UK fossil fuel #divestment movement: http://bit.ly/16lO53u     
    
    
    It's a good thing the #FossilFree Europe tour is going so well right now, because it's killing me not to be in Boston for the World Series!    
    
    
    The #FossilFree Tour arrives in Edinburgh! pic.twitter.com/QGQzhWyXc7    
    
    
    Nature tosses up a rainbow to welcome #FossilFreeEurope to town: pic.twitter.com/4yrRtKnzra    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wonderful #FossilFree event at the University of Edinburgh tonight. Students are fired up! pic.twitter.com/KCKPGhlhL1    
    
    
    @abigailwick sorry to miss you! Just wrapped up an event in Edinburgh. Off to Birmingham tonight!    
    
    
    Listening to the World Series w/ @billmckibben & the #FossilFree team as we bus down from Edinburgh to Birmingham at 12:30am.    
    
    
    Just checking out this great piece from @chrislhayes on the #TurnTheTide rally last weekend: http://on.msnbc.com/HgCRnF     
    
    
    Fascinating essay by @NaomiAKlein on the radical implications of the latest climate science: http://www.newstatesman.com/2013/10/science-says-revolt …    
    
    
    Maybe we need fewer papers on the rapid deployment of renewables & more on the rapid spread of mass resistance: http://www.newstatesman.com/2013/10/science-says-revolt …    
    
    
    So, so great to see former Irish Pres. Mary Robinson pushing for fossil fuel #divestment: http://www.democracynow.org/2013/10/29/former_irish_president_climate_justice_advocate …    
    
    
    Whoa! Check out the incredible setting for our #FossilFree Birmingham show: pic.twitter.com/abxSy8gH1w    
    
    
    Giles Goddard, Canon of St. John's Waterloo, is pushing for the Church of England to divest from fossil fuels #FossilFree    
    
    
    Ouch: University of Birmingham gave Tony Hayward a "leadership" award right after the BP Oil Spill. #FossilFree    
    
    
    I love seeing photos of the US #divestment movement up here on the screen in Birmingham, UK. #FossilFree is going global!    
    
    
    Brilliant article on the carbon bubble by @ryanlcooper in WaPo. A must read: http://wapo.st/1clzV3b     
    
    
    In the Globe and Mail: "Global carbon budget is a harsh reality check for Canadian investors," http://bit.ly/1dVh0QQ     
    
    
    @ryanlcooper Out of the main account! RT @350: How the carbon economy will come crashing down: http://wapo.st/1cssX0z  #DivestNow    
    
    
    @PlatformLondon Exactly right! Excited to think about other ways to keep going after their social license…we need lots of approaches.    
    
    
    Getting ready for the grand finale of the #FossilFree Europe Tour here in London. Big show w/ @kuminaidoo, @billmckibben & more!    
    
    
    Just heard that 3 movie theaters in Sweden are live-streaming tonight's #FossilFree London show. You can too: http://bit.ly/HwmG6t     
    
    
    Vote @mayormcginn! @ezraklein: Comcast is donating to defeat mayor who is bringing gigabit fiber to Seattle http://wapo.st/1dUwzrW     
    
    
    @DivestMcGill We'll see what we can do!    
    
    
    @mayboeve woot woot!    
    
    
    Hanging with @billmckibben side stage as Filastine fires up the crowd at #FossilFree London: pic.twitter.com/5l86VBrvcj    
    
    
    Fired up crew here in London! It's going to be a good #FossilFree finale. You can watch here: http://gofossilfree.org/europe-tour/     
    
    
    "My theory of change used to be, people will read my book and they will change," @billmckibben #FossilFree    
    
    
    Shout out from @billmckibben to @CarbonBubble -- their analysis sparked the #FossilFree #divestment movement.    
    
    
    @camillaborn @NicSeton Good quick response :) and so glad you're campaigning with us!    
    
    
    "We're a few miles from one of the greatest centers of the financial wealth in the world," @billmckibben Time for it to divest!    
    
    
    "We are prepared to take leadership when our political & business leaders are suffering from cognitive dissonance," @kuminaidoo #FossilFree    
    
    
    @hi_n_a_t great job tonight. Excited to kick some fossil fuel ass over the coming months!    
    
    
    @hi_n_a_t here in london!    
    
    
    Always embarrassed when @billmckibben calls the @350 team on stage, but makes for a good photo #FossilFree: pic.twitter.com/9hOClGO7ME    
    
    
    "If we have to leave 80% of fossil fuels in the ground, we certainly can't be using tar sands or fracking," @nodashforgas #FossilFree    
    
    
    The NYT explains how Poland is really COALand, the craziest place for UN Climate Talks: http://nyti.ms/16q3pMF     
    
    
    New report from @MeteosFutures says energy investors could end up "shipwrecked" if they don't change course: http://bit.ly/16ZF9DD     
    
    
    A former SEC Commissioner makes the financial case for fossil fuel #divestment. Few excuses left: http://huff.to/16ZFvKu     
    
    
    Any $ spent searching for new reserves is "wasted capital, an offense against stockholders in terms financial alone," http://huff.to/16ZFvKu     
    
    
    Former SEC Commissioner argues that soon, holding fossil fuel stock could be seen as negligible under fiduciary law: http://huff.to/16ZFvKu     
    
    
    Check out this video of our #FossilFree tour stop in the Netherlands: http://bit.ly/16ZHG0A     
    
    
    Want to help out a fossil fuel #divestment campaign at your alma mater? Become a "donor for divestment": http://bit.ly/18T0poV     
    
    
    UK's Cambridge colleges have over £1 billion invested in fossil fuel companies: http://bit.ly/HCPhah  #divestment #FossilFree    
    
    
    Great article about #divestment in the US and Canada: http://bit.ly/1ecN96u  #FossilFree    
    
    
    Brown might not want to divest from coal, but Norway does: http://bit.ly/1ecNNRq  #FossilFree    
    
    
    Nuns fighting pipelines: http://bit.ly/1ecP7Un  #NoKXL    
    
    
    An incredibly powerful and morally charged letter from @BrownDivestCoal to Brown's president: http://www.browndailyherald.com/2013/11/04/brown-divest-coal-open-letter-president-paxson-corporation/ … #divestment    
    
    
    I love that @BrownDivestCoal signed their letter "Yours in protest." The campaign is only going to grow. #divestment #FossilFree    
    
    
    Working from a pub in London and some guy is signing Nessun Dorma at the top of his lungs. Equally amazing and annoying.    
    
    
    Scientists have concluded that coal trains are poisoning and polluting the Northwest. Time to shut them down: http://earthfix.opb.org/energy/article/new-research-provides-evidence-of-coal-dust-escapi/ …    
    
    
    Ok, now they're playing London Calling in the pub...seems a bit more appropriate.    
    
    
    Our friends at @linea_caffe (from the creators of Mission Chinese) are raising money for @350. If you're in SF, check them out!    
    
    
    @Clara_Vondrich @MayorInnovation not yet completely, but they're getting close!    
    
    
    HUGE: Norway's $800b pension fund, the largest in the world, is on the way to divesting from coal: http://bit.ly/16FdNjG     
    
    
    Check out this Dutch coverage of our #FossilFree campaign: http://bit.ly/1ejxBOr     
    
    
    Last year, the fossil fuel industry cut 3,785 jobs in the US while solar created 14,000. So there. http://huff.to/1ejy96X     
    
    
    Carbon Tracker's @JeremyLegget's analysis sparked the fossil fuel divestment campaign. His new book is a must read: http://bit.ly/1bZPFs0     
    
    
    Dreamt last night that I met the Pope and he told me he was leading a fossil fuel #divestment campaign at the vatican.    
    
    
    Listening to Hot Chip, writing out campaign plans on google docs. Typical morning.    
    
    
    Climate activists in the Philippines call for action as Haiyan batters their islands: http://bit.ly/1hSgAL3  #COP19    
    
    
    Throwing a coal summit next to the UN Climate Talks is like organizing a cigarette expo next to a gathering of cancer experts #COP19    
    
    
    Let's hope Super Typhoon Haiyan is a wake-up call for the negotiators at the #COP19 UN Climate Summit: http://huff.to/19Lrkra     
    
    
    When you juice up mother nature with steroids like carbon dioxide, you get grand slam storms like Haiyan: http://huff.to/19Lrkra     
    
    
    @HuffPostGreen It's like a cigarette and cancer summit side-by-side! Classy.    
    
    
    Good luck to climate champ & @350 ally Mohamed Nasheed & @MDPnews in the Maldives election today!    
    
    
    @hodabaraka thanks! :)    
    
    
    Rich countries can't find the $ for climate finance, but they have no problem shelling out over $500 billion a year in fossil fuel subsidies    
    
    
    The Philippines loses nearly 5% of its economy every year due to storms. And it's only getting worse: http://bit.ly/18hnt1d     
    
    
    I don't understand how #COP19 negotiators can read this piece by @john_vidal on Haiyan and not be moved to action: http://bit.ly/18hnt1d     
    
    
    NYT says the fight about KXL has "roiled United States politics." Indeed: http://nyti.ms/1bpAAQo  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Ok, I'm biased, but this is the best column I've read on the fight against KXL in a long long time: http://bit.ly/1aNt1q9  via @ryanlcooper    
    
    
    Naples archbishop denies communion for polluters: http://huff.to/1aNtRTQ     
    
    
    Devastatingly powerful speech by Philippines negotiator @YebSano at #COP19 calling for action. He'll be fasting until the talks deliver it.    
    
    
    Please share Philippines' climate negotiator @YebSano's powerful #COP19 speech. It's a voice that must be heard: http://bit.ly/1hzuQe1     
    
    
    "What my country is going through as a result of this extreme climate event is madness," Philippines #COP19 negotiator @YebSano    
    
    
    Philippines negotiator @yebsano went off his prepared remarks to announce his fast & praise climate activists. Should be video soon. #cop19    
    
    
    @jbzedelegation it was off script.    
    
    
    @Minikindra yes. It was off his prepared remarks. Should be video soon.    
    
    
    Here's @YebSano's emotional speech at #COP19, including paragraph announcing his fast for climate action: http://bit.ly/1btJpsz     
    
    
        
    
    
    @EcoWatch Thanks for the repost!    
    
    
    Philippines negotiator @YebSano thanked activists today for climbing oil rigs, blocking pipelines, & committing civil disobedience.#COP19    
    
    
    @duncanwrites not yet. it was off his prepared remarks and i couldn't transcribe it b/c i got pushed around by security. video soon, i hope.    
    
    
    @duncanwrites for sure.    
    
    
    Stand in solidarity with the Philippines and join their call for climate action at #COP19: http://bit.ly/1buIqZ4     
    
    
    Watching "wrecking ball" at #cop19 is a surreal experience. This place is so weird: pic.twitter.com/NaWFbVBZZL    
    
    
    Powerful NYT #climate essay: "Now we have to learn how to die not as individuals, but as a civilization," http://nyti.ms/1aP1ODC     
    
    
    @jaisalnoor jamie@350.org    
    
    
    89% of Poles want more renewable energy. Why is their government blocking progress? http://bit.ly/17rX0TK  #cop19    
    
    
    .@CANIntl Director @whmaidan announces he & others will join @yebsano in his fast for climate action #COP19 pic.twitter.com/Rv2gLNuiSG    
    
    
    "What happened in the Philippines is beyond adaptation," @KellyDent of @Oxfam at CAN Press Conference #COP19    
    
    
    .@Oxfam calls for immediate action on "loss & damage" here in Warsaw. Learn more about the issue here: http://bit.ly/17rXPvW  #COP19    
    
    
    "The money on the table must be real. It cannot be murky, dodgy dollars," @KellyDent of @Oxfam on the need for climate finance #COP19    
    
    
    Oxfam's @KellyDent slams Australia for their shameful refusal to cut emissions or offer finance. "The timing is brutal." #COP19    
    
    
    "Young people have come from around the world to reclaim these discussions," @LouisaCasson of @ukycc #COP19    
    
    
    "The fossil fuel industry cannot exist as part of a sustainable future," @LouisaCasson of @ukycc #COP19 pic.twitter.com/tnZkx8H3kW    
    
    
    This petition calling for solidarity with the Philippines and action at #COP19 is growing fast: http://bit.ly/1buIqZ4     
    
    
    @ClimateCFO Genius.    
    
    
    "Humanitarian relief does not absolve countries from their need to reduce emissions," @KellyDent from @Oxfam #COP19    
    
    
    Here's a press release on how the #divestment campaign is growing at #COP19: http://bit.ly/17rZLV6     
    
    
    These are the things banned at #COP19: banners, fire works, flags, spray paint, and scary masks: pic.twitter.com/YDclKNFA9i    
    
    
    Solidarity action with the Philippines about to begin at #COP19. Show your support here: http://bit.ly/1buIqZ4     
    
    
    Crowd gathers as @yebsano and other people fasting in solidarity prepare to speak: pic.twitter.com/CWzjYPjzIq    
    
    
    Filipino negotiator @yebsano's fast for climate action is spreading around the world pic.twitter.com/YmA1oL8mZw    
    
    
    1067 dead from Bopha in 2012. 10,000+ from Haiyan. How many more will it take for politicians to act? #COP19 pic.twitter.com/R9NbvWwRjP    
    
    
    Here are some more photos from today's #WeStandWithYou action at #COP19: http://bit.ly/1aCn09N     
    
    
    @democracynow Here are photos from a rally at #COP19 with @yebsano today, thanking the world for their solidarity: http://bit.ly/1aCn09N     
    
    
    @sanfranphoto thanks for the favorite!    
    
    
    World Energy Outlook says climate action will require 74% of oil reserves to stay untouched.    
    
    
    Join @Sum_of_us and call on fossil fuel companies to pay for the clean-up to Typhoon Haiyan: http://bit.ly/HUYMAQ  #COP19    
    
    
    Here's the poster for a #divestment side event we're doing at #COP19 tomorrow. If you're here, join: pic.twitter.com/cZu6ofLu2D    
    
    
    @yesmagazine thanks for the post!    
    
    
    @nwoje it's my old title :)    
    
    
    If you're invested in fossil fuels, you have a share in Haiyan's devastation: http://ow.ly/qL313     
    
    
    Negotiators at #COP19 are greeted this morning with photos of the #Arctic30 pic.twitter.com/gSarRvcAWC    
    
    
    Watching CNN coverage of #COP19, @YebSano, and yesterday's #WeStandWithYou action    
    
    
    CNN coverage is doing a good job connecting the dots between typhoons and climate: pic.twitter.com/0eC32YmLcm    
    
    
    Canada applauds Australian attempts to repeal their carbon price--and they want us to think they care about climate? http://bit.ly/HMjJOH     
    
    
    Check out this graphic CNN is using to explain extreme weather: pic.twitter.com/zKX4ROiQWv    
    
    
    Typhoon Haiyan, sponsored by ExxonMobil: http://bit.ly/17TfahK  #COP19    
    
    
    At #COP19? Join @WWF @350 @tcktcktck @CarbonBubble for a Carbon Bubble & Divestment side event in Room Cracow, 15:00-16:30    
    
    
    @PlatformLondon "The philosophers have only interpreted the world in various ways. The point however is to change it." - Marx    
    
    
    Great NYT piece on the inequality of climate change: http://nyti.ms/1j4c8GS  #COP19    
    
    
    Check out these awesome photos from #PowerShift Vietnam: http://on.fb.me/1i9f3Au     
    
    
    Packed room for our carbon bubble and divestment side event at #COP19 (Room Cracow)    
    
    
    @DivestTulane thanks all! Same could be said of Katrina....    
    
    
    Check out this awesome info graphic on #divestment from students at MIT & Harvard: http://bit.ly/186ZJAD     
    
    
    Pls share this moving video of letters from the #Arctic30…they're voices the world needs to hear: http://bit.ly/1870sSg     
    
    
    Here's a crazy idea: let's end fossil fuel subsidies and put the money into mitigation & adaptation. #COP19    
    
    
    At the Warsaw Stock Exchange to hear talk about the @CarbonBubble & #divestment in the belly of the beast.    
    
    
    Financial regulators missed the housing bubble and it crashed the economy. Are they missing the carbon bubble now?    
    
    
    Want to make businesses more sustainable? Get more women CEOs and board members: they're better at understanding risks like climate.    
    
    
    Join a Reddit Ask Me Anything on fossil fuel #divestment to tonight at 12pm ET (6pm CET). Follow #divestcop for more. #COP19    
    
    
    @GreenCrossInt Is it true that Dr. Kulczyk is investing in a 2000MW coal fired power plant in Poland?    
    
    
    It feels oddly historic to be sitting in a stock exchange listening to discussion about the @CarbonBubble. Profoundly radical implications.    
    
    
    Disturbing: UNEP's Polish representative is celebrating corporate involvement in #COP19 and says regulations should be flexible.    
    
    
    Correction, it was a UN Global Compact representative who is promoting corporate partnership here at #COP19    
    
    
    With the Pope coming out against fracking, is it time to launch a Vatican #divestment campaign?    
    
    
    Japan going from nuclear to coal is like switching from heroine to cocaine: they'll both mess you up. Time to go clean! #COP19    
    
    
    This deflated earth could be a symbol of the feeling at #cop19 about Japan & Australia: pic.twitter.com/Swx998UGwD    
    
    
    Japan has only 2% non-hyrdo renewable energy. Huge opportunity there, but not if the government embraces coal. #COP19    
    
    
    UK government says it's "deeply disappointed" in Japan's moves to reduce it's emissions targets. #COP19    
    
    
    If only this photo was true! http://bit.ly/I3hkyN  #FreeTheArctic30    
    
    
    Great webinar coming up on how to divest your institution (or environmental group) from fossil fuels: http://bit.ly/I3hCpB     
    
    
    Whoa: by the US Gov's own numbers, the CO2 released by KXL could cost society $24b over its lifetime: http://bit.ly/I3ijPw  #NoKXL @eschor    
    
    
    At #COP19: "Natural Gas Cares for the World": pic.twitter.com/dVKsW4LAUb    
    
    
    I love that there are posters with titles like "Day of the Cryosphere" at #COP19. This place is supremely dorky.    
    
    
    "I dream about #divestment every night," Emily Williams, @CalSSC at the #DivestCOP side event #COP19    
    
    
    Very cool to hear voices from Africa, Latin America & beyond talking about #divestment, reinvestment, and challenging fossil fuels    
    
    
    How could #divestment campaigns (or related efforts) work in the Global South? #COP19 #DivestCOP    
    
    
    Why is the World Bank (@wbclimatechange) still investing more in dirty energy projects than clean? asks @Msnyamburah from Kenya #DivestCOP    
    
    
    "This is a political campaign and it goes to the core of our democracy," @camillaborn of @UKYCC #DivestCOP #COP19    
    
    
    Awesome to have badasses from @BrownDivestCoal here at #COP19. They're still going strong--and connecting globally! #DivestCOP    
    
    
        
    
    
    Japan's decision to weaken its reduction targets is a "slap in the face for poor countries" says @Oxfam's @KellyDent #COP19    
    
    
    "Great stories happen to those who can tell them," - Ira Glass    
    
    
    Our friends at @yesmagazine have launched #Commonomics, a new series about strong & inclusive local economies http://j.mp/1aWlu8H     
    
    
    Big crowd for the #Cop19 climate justice march--and a dramatic backdrop: pic.twitter.com/LcVQIQzHJ4    
    
    
    Penguins marching for humans at #COP19 climate justice march pic.twitter.com/wuo5mUCqHR    
    
    
    Crew from @democracynow interviewing #COP19 fasters from @SustainUSAgents pic.twitter.com/CZ9lqNeacA    
    
    
    The crew from @pacja1 always has the best cheers! #COP19 pic.twitter.com/kYGDvZLVU7    
    
    
    Big police presence at the #cop19 march pic.twitter.com/pOCzFLeil0    
    
    
    Every march needs a samba band! #cop19 pic.twitter.com/z0LLoO26Zj    
    
    
    Leave it to the Brazilians to teach everyone samba during the #cop19 march pic.twitter.com/PqiXDaTZO8    
    
    
    Not sure the police know quite what to do with a planet rolling down the street #cop19 pic.twitter.com/lRxqedJP7Q    
    
    
        
    
    
    Maybe "Warsaw Shore" has a sea level rise message? I doubt it. pic.twitter.com/vc8zcxgqd0    
    
    
    "Our future--your call" #cop19 pic.twitter.com/RPP2EihQ5H    
    
    
    Ok, "No warming, no cry" might be my favorite placard yet #cop19    
    
    
        
    
    
    "If we fuck with nature, nature will fuck with us." Indeed. #cop19 pic.twitter.com/Rw9aocJ31g    
    
    
    System change, not climate change pic.twitter.com/BW8kieuDcb    
    
    
    "If the climate was a bank  it already would have been saved." #cop19 pic.twitter.com/eZGHyX9PpR    
    
    
    Pic of the front of the #COP19 climate march from above: pic.twitter.com/gpaI8uT9c5    
    
    
    "Money, not the right kind of green." #climatemarch #COP19 pic.twitter.com/B4fUAr0meK    
    
    
    Europeans really know how to do face paint. Here was one of my favorites from the #climatemarch #COP19 pic.twitter.com/yxU5JRdUaH    
    
    
    "Time=Up" #climatemarch #cop19 pic.twitter.com/iPkCrJ8f31    
    
    
    Here's a set of photos from today's #ClimateMarch at #COP19. Feel free to use any you want! http://bit.ly/17yoSQZ     
    
    
    We could really use Batkid here at #COP19: http://bit.ly/1ea5kr4     
    
    
    Honored that @guardian readers picked @350 & @GoFossilFree as top climate campaigns. You all make them happen! http://bit.ly/17aWIyk     
    
    
    Up on @HuffPostGreen, "Thousands March Outside UN Climate Talks in Warsaw" http://huff.to/1ea92kt  #COP19 #ClimateMarch    
    
    
    @eschor hahaha--agreed.    
    
    
    About to go on KPFA to talk about #COP19, climate, and Typhoon Haiyan. Tune in if you're in the SF area!    
    
    
    And off the radio…but still a good station to listen to!    
    
    
    Since 2005, banks have given €118bn to coal. Every cent is a bet against our future.    
    
    
    Ok pundits: does Obama's weekly address on energy contain clues on KXL? http://huff.to/1bwjw9P  #NoKXL    
    
    
    @JazCummins just talking about this with @loubgray in Warsaw last night. It's the hot trend!    
    
    
    Preparations underway for tomorrow's action outside the #Cop19 coal summit pic.twitter.com/pVUz8F0rIK    
    
    
    Get ready to #Cough4Coal tomorrow in protest of the coal industry summit at #cop19 pic.twitter.com/f7wWxcgXwz    
    
    
    "Whatever you’re meant to do, do it now. The conditions are always impossible," Doris Lessing. Here's to the revolutionaries.    
    
    
    Boom! Check out @greenpeace's "Who Rules Poland?" banner hang at #cop19 coal summit pic.twitter.com/4DsWwgF6kD    
    
    
    Polish firefighters prepare climbing gear to get @greenpeace climbers down pic.twitter.com/QyBzBEKtqE    
    
    
    Serious issue, but these @greenpeace climbers look like they're having a (cold) good time pic.twitter.com/BgJqx7B4TN    
    
    
    You though the #Arctic30 would intimidate @Greenpeace? Think again: pic.twitter.com/wrUiVAegAq    
    
    
    Police are finally getting the @greenpeace banner down...message accomplished: pic.twitter.com/HnhpNxBotx    
    
    
    Party continues! Medical students getting ready for #Cough4Coal action pic.twitter.com/sbkSCxSAO8    
    
    
    Medical student doing an interview with Reuters about coal's health impacts #cop19 pic.twitter.com/VVdFY2HOcB    
    
    
    Just ran into @AmyGoodman_DN at the #Cough4Coal #cop19 protest. Always good to have @democracynow in the house.    
    
    
    .@CFigueres @WorldCoal @UN_ClimateTalks The only thing coal should do is stay in the ground. #cop19    
    
    
    More interviews in the midst of #Cough4Coal #Cop19 protest pic.twitter.com/Eu8BqQZS5z    
    
    
    Polish crane vs. @Greenpeace crane: pic.twitter.com/8fLfffBvYa    
    
    
    "We are the champions!" The giant lungs triumph over the coal lobby #cough4coal #COP19 pic.twitter.com/C9S2IdI9od    
    
    
    Creative action beats boring conference every time. Sorry, coal industry. #Cop19 #Cough4Coal pic.twitter.com/i11MF5zKI6    
    
    
    Here's a PDF of UN Climate Sec @CFigueres speech at the Coal and Climate Summit: http://bit.ly/1bIhy9S  #COP19    
    
    
    Check out photos from today's awesome #Cough4Coal action in front of the the coal industry summit: http://bit.ly/1bIiICt  #COP19    
    
    
    Great blog & photos from @hodabaraka on today's #Cough4Coal action: http://bit.ly/1bIlRSH     
    
    
    Packed crowd at the @CANIntl press conference. Welcome to the second week of #Cop19 pic.twitter.com/8mOTyX5Goz    
    
    
    Just wrapped up a #ReclaimPower press conference at #COP19. Always an honor be on stage w/ @FoEInt @pacja1 & Jubilee South's @lnacpil    
    
    
    A look of determination from anti-coal activists. These are powerful women #Cough4Coal #COP19 #PeopleBeforeCoal pic.twitter.com/9t0CC67Nsv    
    
    
    Any talk of "clean coal" is just brain pollution from the industry. #Cough4Coal #PeopleBeforeCoal #COP19 pic.twitter.com/cH3GuQGrUl    
    
    
    Youth bring the message of #PeopleBeforeCoal directly into #cop19 pic.twitter.com/QAjnGuOwH0    
    
    
    The #Cop19 referee is kicking the coal industry out of the climate talks! pic.twitter.com/3jWJQAc1bo    
    
    
    "Kick Coal Out of the Climate Talks" #cop19 #ReclaimPower pic.twitter.com/eVv2hZVZNO    
    
    
    Pres. George W. Bush says "Build the damn thing!" to Keystone XL…because a Bush endorsement will convince Obama. #NoKXL    
    
    
    We're joining w/ Filipino negotiator @YebSano to deliver the #WeStandWithYou petition at #COP19 today. Join us: http://bit.ly/1buIqZ4     
    
    
    Media advisory about today's petition delivery w/ @YebSano at #COP19: http://bit.ly/1efttwl  Pls share.    
    
    
    Ah, the mad dash before an action! Dropping off final advisories than we're a go in 30 mins.    
    
    
    HUGE press for #WeStandWithYou petition delivery w/ @yebsano at #COP19 pic.twitter.com/Xb50nV6Flb    
    
    
    "#WeStandWithYou to shine a spotlight on the real culprit: the fossil fuel industry," @hodabaraka #cop19 pic.twitter.com/L2C6mrZHxy    
    
    
    THANK YOU to everyone who signed petitions to stand with the Philippines. Your voices are being heard: pic.twitter.com/iIg1C4FJej    
    
    
    CNN, BBC, Reuters & many more covering #WeStandWithYou delivery. Word is spreading: pic.twitter.com/R1lIMLVXBP    
    
    
    .@350's @hodabaraka standing w/ @yebsano to deliver global voices calling for action pic.twitter.com/GkNN0URCS4    
    
    
    Yup, this is the type of picture a press person likes to see #COP19: pic.twitter.com/K3uSMjPJ4r    
    
    
    Silje from Friends of the Earth is fasting for action w/ @yebsano #WeStandWithYou pic.twitter.com/7g3cINZMlq    
    
    
    Amazing #WeStandWithYou petition delivery at #COP19 today. Here's the full report: http://bit.ly/1ddTizU     
    
    
    @JakopDalunde Here you go: http://bit.ly/1ddTizU     
    
    
    Press Release: Filipino Negotiator @YebSano Delivers 600,000+ Signatures on Petition to #COP19: http://bit.ly/1ddTizU     
    
    
    Here's a transcript of @YebSano's speech at the #WeStandWithYou #COP19 petition delivery: http://bit.ly/1cEUbwu     
    
    
    Video of today's #WeStandWithYou delivery w/ @350's @HodaBaraka & @YebSano at #COP19: http://bit.ly/17IlS4F     
    
    
    "We are deeply moved and deeply touched by this expression of solidarity," Filipino negotiator @YebSano: http://bit.ly/17IlS4F  #COP19    
    
    
    Up on @HuffingtonPost: "The Call for Climate Justice Grows at UN Talks" http://huff.to/1h0NCtI  #COP19 #WeStandWithYou    
    
    
    Check out this highlight reel of @YebSano's opening #COP19 speech, cut w/ scenes from Haiyan: http://bit.ly/1h142lI     
    
    
    These dancing chickens aren't helping the sense that I'm slowly loosing my mind here at #cop19: pic.twitter.com/kJX10ej0Oc    
    
    
    Well, that's a curveball: Korolec will remain #COP19 president, but is fired as environment minister: http://wapo.st/1hWQJnQ     
    
    
    Poland fires its pro-fossil-fuel environment minister for not being pro-fossil-fuel enough: http://wapo.st/1hWQJnQ  #COP19    
    
    
    @loubgray then there's this guy pic.twitter.com/qEuQ2LNdLK    
    
    
    Huffpo just listed the 20 Awesome US Cities to visit…and used a @350 action photo for Asheville, NC: http://huff.to/17poeZ7     
    
    
    @ElizaTalks Great to connect today! On we go, stirring up trouble...    
    
    
    Hilarious photos: Carbon bubbles visit the Bank of England: http://bit.ly/17pqvU8  #Divestment #FossilFree    
    
    
    Wow. Just 90 companies have caused 2/3 of global GHG emissions: http://bit.ly/17pudgz     
    
    
    "Coal seen as the new tobacco" This is exactly the point of the #FossilFree #divestment campaign: http://bloom.bg/1dh3sjg     
    
    
        
    
    
    One of the challenges of a global conference is knowing which direction to pass people in the halls. I keep crashing into Brits.    
    
    
    #Cop19 walkout beginning: turning our back on polluters, not the process pic.twitter.com/SGUoE5Fup9    
    
    
        
    
    
    Handling the media scrum at #WeStandWithYou walkout at #COP19 pic.twitter.com/m8JwcpzDqq    
    
    
    "Industrialized countries have effectively held these talks hostage,"Assad Rehman @FoEint #WeStandWithYou #COP19 #Volveremos    
    
    
    As #WeStandWithYou vigils happen around the world, huge coalition walks out of #COP19 in protest.    
    
    
    "There are no jobs on a dead planet," Executive Secretary of International Trade Union Confederation #Volveremos #WeStandWithYou    
    
    
    "We walk out of here to help mobilize people around the world." #WeStandWithYou #Volveremos #COP19    
    
    
    "People deserve better than what we've seen here the last two weeks," ITUC Exec Secretary #COP19 #Volveremos #WeStandWithYou    
    
    
    "I'm here to salute your courage," Former Africa Group Chair & key negotiator #COP19 #COP19 pic.twitter.com/sVSlxpnzU2    
    
    
    "The real hooligans are the CEO's of fossil fuel companies,"@kuminaidoo #WeStandWithYou #COP19    
    
    
    "We need more than just sympathy. We need solidarity," Filipino activist at #COP19 walkout #WeStandWithYou    
    
    
    #Volveremos means we will be back, stronger and more committed.    
    
    
    Civil society proceeds out of the talks #westandwithyou pic.twitter.com/FWUnVRU9Vi    
    
    
    It's a big step for groups like WWF, Oxfam, & ActionAid to make a move like this--movement is getting more fired up! #Volveremos #cop19    
    
    
    HUGE numbers of civil society walking out on #COP19. Pic: pic.twitter.com/VirAWJDiJZ    
    
    
    Democracy Now broadcasting live on the walkout from #COP19: http://bit.ly/1ejX3kv     
    
    
    Polluters talk, we walk #Volveremos #COP19 #WeStandWithYou pic.twitter.com/vZao9aNS9p    
    
    
    Amazing feeling to march w/ movements from around the world. #WeStandWithYou & grow stronger every day #COP19 pic.twitter.com/jSjNI6ySQg    
    
    
    Awesome! Our first #WeStandWithYou vigil photos are coming in as sun sets in Indonesia: http://bit.ly/1ek0t6y     
    
    
    Meet Public Enemy Number 90: the companies that are causing 2/3 of global GHG emissions: http://bit.ly/1ek0MhI     
    
    
    Media coverage beginning to come in from today's #COP19 walkout. Here's Reuters: http://reut.rs/1ek0Uhk     
    
    
    Nice! 83% of participating Yale students vote to support fossil fuel #divestment: http://bit.ly/1ek17RH .    
    
    
    Civil society from around the world meeting inside a convergence space in Warsaw #Cop19 pic.twitter.com/3OPjkkMaE4    
    
    
    Look at this room: big NGOs, youth, global south movements. Start of something big pic.twitter.com/pk2tMa8ED6    
    
    
    Getting goosebumps surrounded by so many amazing activists. Forget #COP19 Now, the real work begins: pic.twitter.com/A7u8nLQDKC    
    
    
    There are probably at least 50 countries just in this room. Talk about a global movement #Volveremos pic.twitter.com/QFuifb1KWv    
    
    
    Impossible not to have hope when you look at the growing climate movement: diverse, global & growing. #WeStandWithYou #Volveremos    
    
    
    Check out @350's amazing @hodabaraka explaining the #Cop19 walkout in the @guardian! http://ow.ly/r38Za     
    
    
    Beautiful photo from a #WeStandWithYou vigil in Fiji! http://bit.ly/19Lo0rY  #COP19    
    
    
    Pretty boring AP article on today's #Volveremos #COP19 walkout, but great photo! http://bit.ly/1fZkU9C     
    
    
    #Volveremos We will be back! But for now, we nap #COP19 pic.twitter.com/sn2H9nUAlD    
    
    
    Some thoughts on yesterday's #COP19 walkout, up in @yesmagazine: http://bit.ly/1aBPu88  #Volveremos #WeStandWithYou    
    
    
    Delegates at #COP19 might not want to talk about the carbon budget, but physics doesn't negotiate http://in.mobile.reuters.com/article/idINL5N0J10FN20131121?irpc=932 …    
    
    
    Climate Justice Assembly starts up at the convergence center outside #cop19 pic.twitter.com/mVAxM6bTQY    
    
    
    Great piece on the ongoing climate fast & activism at #cop19 #westandwithyou http://motherboard.vice.com/blog/there-are-now-100-people-refusing-to-eat-until-leaders-take-on-climate-change …    
    
    
    Can't read a word of it, but love seeing coverage of #WeStandWithYou in Arabic: http://www.al-akhbar.com/node/195567  #cop19    
    
    
    "Ministers should talk less and listen to the people," Representative from Venezuela visiting #COP19 convergence space.    
    
    
    Representative from Venezuela inviting civil society to a pre-COP20 social forum next year: pic.twitter.com/6r5xgJE3hn    
    
    
    Venezuela is hosting a @SocialPreCOP in Caracas 14-18 October 2014 before the climate talks in Lima.    
    
    
    Presenting plans from breakout groups at #COP19 Convergence Space #Volveremos #WeStandWithYou pic.twitter.com/VYOP6N4HIN    
    
    
    55% of Americans believe extreme weather events are connected to climate change, 22% unsure & only 23% say no: http://huff.to/1bYaVk3     
    
    
    It wouldn't be a COP without the giant heads! http://bit.ly/1jsN5xv  #COP19    
    
    
    This powerful call for action from an @Avaaz member in the Philippines on @Huffpostgreen is a must read: http://huff.to/1doTjRz  #COP19    
    
    
    Singapore is stretching the metaphors at #COP19, "We need an appendectomy, not just a circumcision." Ouch.    
    
    
    Don't count on our politicians to avert the climate crisis. In many ways, they are the crisis: http://bit.ly/18foqwR     
    
    
    We engage in shareholder advocacy, as if "sweet reason by itself stood a chance of outtalking sweet crude oil" http://bit.ly/18foqwR     
    
    
    The fossil fuel #divestment campaign is making, "previously unthinkable conversations become thinkable" http://bit.ly/18foqwR  #FossilFree    
    
    
    The climate movement is the "hinges on which the door to a livable future swings," http://bit.ly/18foqwR     
    
    
    If you read one piece on the fossil fuel #divestment movement, read @toddgitlin in @tomdispatch: http://bit.ly/18foqwR     
    
    
    "The science, the storms, and the suffering are all screaming at us to
take urgent action," @AMBMoses #Cop19    
    
    
    @tomzellerjr hence, #divestment.    
    
    
    Amazing! A "Parts Per Million" arts intervention from @liberatetate protests BP sponsorship of #TateModern http://bit.ly/1iE4DJl     
    
    
    Much love from @350 to our friends at @liberatetate. Few things make us happier than wonky/artistic protest! http://bit.ly/1iE4DJl     
    
    
    A few days after carbon bubbles visit the Bank of England, carbon particles intervene at #TateModern. CO2 is acting up!    
    
    
    @liberatetate You better believe it. Send it to me via email and we'll get our team on it.    
    
    
    Inclusion of loss & damage in the #COP19 outcome is an important. Countries acknowledge that climate change is already causing major impacts    
    
    
    After #COP19, the UNFCCC process is still on life support, despite efforts by big polluters to pull the plug.    
    
    
    @Alberto_Zoratti true, but a hell of a fight just to get it there. a first step in a longer battle.    
    
    
    #WeStandWithYou tumblr already full of photos from around the world. Add yours here: http://westandwithyou.tumblr.com/  #COP19 #volveremos    
    
    
        
    
    
    @anjaliapp thanks!    
    
    
    WWF calls the lack if urgency at #COP19 "sickening."    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Massive public pressure" is needed to rescue a climate deal, says @Oxfam. Our crew at @350 couldn't agree more!    
    
    
    I think #COP19 has helped toughen up the climate movement. We're coming out geared up for a fight with the fossil fuel industry.    
    
    
    @TasneemEssop @climateWWF The Panda really showed its teeth this COP. Looking forward to kicking some more butt together.    
    
    
    Nothing like a little mainstream media to start the day. WaPo profiles the growing fossil fuel divestment movement: http://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/on-campuses-a-fossil-fuel-divestment-movement/2013/11/25/45a545e6-52fc-11e3-a7f0-b790929232e1_story.html …    
    
    
    @jisham and a big one to you! The original inspiration! I feel like I'm still taking "what works" 8 years later!    
    
    
        
    
    
    This is big: Bloomberg LP Launches First Tool That Measures Risk of 'Unburnable Carbon' Assets: http://bit.ly/IIMCfz     
    
    
    Great article in AP about how fossil fuel #divestment campaign is escalating across the US: http://bit.ly/IqtKl5     
    
    
        
    
    
    Turns out when schools say "no" to #divestment, it just motivates students even more:  http://bit.ly/IqtQsX     
    
    
    "We don't like those oil guys expecting us, to fold up at their every beck and call," #NoKXL song: http://bit.ly/1dPc4O8     
    
    
        
    
    
    "Without KXL, the Western Canadian oil-sands industry seems doomed to a long struggle," http://buswk.co/1kagBZe     
    
    
    #ConnectTheDots cost of extreme weather events has soared by 60% in just 30 years: http://dailym.ai/1bIicGi     
    
    
    Awesome piece in @USAToday on the growing--and intensifying--fossil fuel #divestment movement: http://usat.ly/IEwXgv     
    
    
    If you care about climate, you should care about the Trans Pacific Partnership. Here's the deal: http://bit.ly/IEx77r     
    
    
    #AskJimKim: Will there be accountability at @WorldBank, or will you allow @IFC_org to ignore CAO's damning Tata Mundra #coal plant findings    
    
    
    Global #coal lobbyist says "deaths from coal burning" should be weighed against "the benefits." Sickening: http://huff.to/1eNeedC     
    
    
    "It's like Kahn Academy meets the McCarthur Genius Award." Check out @HeroHatchery & help fund a climate hero: http://bit.ly/1cZyCqr     
    
    
    "It always seems impossible until its done," said Nelson Mandela. Let's live that out. Thank you for everything, Madiba.    
    
    
    Powerful tribute to Nelson Mandela from Ghana's president: http://nyti.ms/1iEa7X0     
    
    
    On Mandela's first trip to the US he went to UC Berkeley to thank students there for the #divestment movement.    
    
    
    Obama writes about how he first became politically active working on anti-apartheid #divestment campaign: http://bit.ly/ILLo2z     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Instead of sponsoring the #TateModern, BP should start sponsoring the Thames Barrier: http://nyti.ms/1kiKNRV     
    
    
    A storm surge with 8-inches of sea level rise is forcing Europe to deploy all its storm barriers. If seas rise 7ft, how do we adapt to that?    
    
    
    Press Release: After Initial Rejections, Students Escalate Campaign for Fossil Fuel Divestment: http://bit.ly/1cqyT7E  #FossilFree    
    
    
    There's a new nail in Keystone XL's coffin and its name is John Podesta. Check out his speech on tar sands: http://bit.ly/18kkoTK     
    
    
    Fossil fuel #Divestment (and @350) get a big shout out in Australian parliament: http://bit.ly/1kw3NN1     
    
    
    "Oil extraction from tar sands is polluting, destructive, expensive, and energy intensive," John Podesta: http://bit.ly/18kkoTK     
    
    
    "Unconventional sources of fossil fuels cannot be our energy future," John Podesta:  http://bit.ly/18kkoTK  #NoKXL    
    
    
    Climate change is making deserts more deserted -- and it will have big consequences around the world: http://bit.ly/1e4SCNJ     
    
    
    I don't tend to agree with Sen. Jim Inhofe, but he's probably right that Obama will keep delaying KXL: http://bit.ly/1e4TFgu     
    
    
        
    
    
    Colleges are now proud to have divested from apartheid, but many of them resisted for years. Same scenario with fossil fuel #divestment.    
    
    
    @swiftnotswallow @williammclennan genius!    
    
    
    On an all-staff call w/ the @350 team. 15+ countries and some of the most amazing organizers on the planet. So much fun.    
    
    
    Good reminder of how Harvard fought student demands to divest from apartheid for years before finally caving: http://bit.ly/18m9CMF     
    
    
    I love watching @VanJones68 throw down on just about anything, but especially on Keystone XL. Dynamite: http://bit.ly/1d8bAO8     
    
    
    @zcolman I was about to say the same thing…    
    
    
    "People who meet 3x a year to make financial decisions do not make up our institutions," http://bit.ly/1dqAMzQ     
    
    
    "No is just a motivator to build our power until there is no option but yes," #divestment activists: http://bit.ly/1dqAMzQ     
    
    
    Awesome #RejectionDenied video from student fossil fuel #divestment activists. We're just getting started: http://bit.ly/1dqAMzQ     
    
    
    This is lunacy: "We absolutely think we can maintain growth in oil and gas, and achieve greenhouse gas reductions,"http://lat.ms/1dG6Uj5     
    
    
        
    
    
    New piece from @BillMcKibben in @RollingStone casts some serious doubts on Obama's commitment to climate action: http://rol.st/1dK9gO7     
    
    
        
    
    
    In 2012, U.S. coal exports were the equivalent of putting 55 million new cars on the road: http://rol.st/1bXGQkT     
    
    
    After the latest ERM scandal, Sec Kerry should throw out their biased KXL review and do a real study: http://politi.co/18U0m0n     
    
    
    Awesome timeline of all the fossil fuel #divestment campaign has done this last semester: http://bit.ly/18U0ZHu     
    
    
    Thinking about personal #divestment options? Help us help you and the #climate – take our survey!http://bit.ly/JEjcjn     
    
    
    @BillyWimsatt Hey there friend! I'm in Brooklyn right now and then all January. Let's hang!    
    
    
    John Kerry connects Typhoon Haiyan to climate change. He shouldn't approve a pipeline that makes it worse: http://nyti.ms/JB3bdn     
    
    
    @Guay_JG I like the "no one wants to invest in us...invest in us!" Argument    
    
    
    US decides not to update pipeline safety standards. Not like there were any accidents this year...oh, wait: http://thkpr.gs/1kzZ8wb     
    
    
    