Checkpoint! Lunchtime! Time extended!    
    
    
    How has the perception of #gamification changed over the past few years? (Video) http://ow.ly/o57lR  @mherger @egfnyc    
    
    
    Great news! Game designers are also using Gamification Model Canvas! Thank you for improving it! http://ow.ly/o58PW     
    
    
    MT @amyjokim: There's a difference between user-centric design and building a user-centric business http://bit.ly/17HXhgB  from @khoi    
    
    
    @brasscount thanks Spence! Be part of the project sending us your most valuable feedback about using it.    
    
    
    @rawksoup thank you Bob!    
    
    
    Excellent article Jamie! MT @JamieMadigan: Are more likely to enjoy a game if you paid more for it? http://www.psychologyofgames.com/2013/08/its-not-so-bad-cognitive-dissonance-and-cheap-games/ …    
    
    
    Del CRM al PRM: Player Relationship Management http://ow.ly/o9AZ9  #games #gamification    
    
    
    Ok, let's go! let's create! #gamification http://instagram.com/p/dUC0CXn9O-/     
    
    
    Hey gamifier! What do you think about this? #gamification #ux #advergaming #serious #games pic.twitter.com/ipfoAT0sQf    
    
    
    @leupoki thanks Mario! Send us your most valuable feedback about using it! Game On!    
    
    
    Qué bonito es el amor! RT @josek_net: When a Relationship Becomes a Game http://ow.ly/nWPo0  Gamified love? #gamification    
    
    
    The open-source #gamification design framework. Download it, use it, improve it! http://ow.ly/obX3D     
    
    
    MT @GamiWorldCon: Come with us to the Enterprise Gamification Forum New York! @egfnyc Unlock your promo code here! http://bit.ly/MF7Wze     
    
    
    Awesome short-film about the flow! (Video) http://ow.ly/ogkJy     
    
    
    The game's inception near @SeminOzmorali RT @David_Mullich: The oldest known gaming tokens have been found in Turkey http://mashable.com/2013/08/14/oldest-gaming-tokens/ …    
    
    
    Definitely, the feedback is the food of champions    
    
    
    Reimagining the 21st-century classroom http://ow.ly/ojABW  #UX    
    
    
    The connected UX http://ow.ly/ojAO7  #research #UX    
    
    
    Awesome projects have already downloaded and used the #gamification canvas! Great news coming soon, check it out! http://ow.ly/ojHwa     
    
    
    @TreDigital thanks Maria    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom thanks HiSocial for that RTs! You are the best!    
    
    
    @EfeRios thank you Juan!    
    
    
    @ChristianXandu Merci Christian!    
    
    
    @thespacewofford great! #gamification is our mission =)    
    
    
    @ChookzN you're welcome!    
    
    
    Cool! RT @marigo: What’s the Difference Between Games and Gamification? https://www.edsurge.com/n/2013-08-20-what-s-the-difference-between-games-and-gamification … #edtech via @EdSurge #gamification    
    
    
    @ChookzN we need 30 tweets at least to discuss this! sergio at gameonlab dot com    
    
    
    The concept "churn rate" arrives to #games http://ow.ly/olNiQ  #businessication    
    
    
    Study: To The Human Brain, Me Is We http://ow.ly/olN68  #fellowship    
    
    
    @hwmturistico thanks!    
    
    
    Have you ever thought that you might need to take some shortcuts to launch a design quickly? http://ow.ly/olNFZ  #UX    
    
    
    No hay #gamification sin #UX http://ow.ly/onrJG  #archives    
    
    
    Interesting article about #dopamine and #games http://ow.ly/onrtP     
    
    
    @alexcoley @eModJesse gamification! not gasification! LOL check it out and send us your most valuable feedback canvas at gameonlab dot com    
    
    
    Help! Could someone make a theory about this coincidence? http://bit.ly/1dxntBS  #gamification #bmgen pic.twitter.com/fwQZ1EAYQR    
    
    
    @daverage @AndreaKuszewski thank you Andrzej! a very solid article with many interesting references    
    
    
    @daverage @AndreaKuszewski I'm looking forward to it!    
    
    
    Like! RT @aureamemotech: CfP  “Rethinking Gamification” Deadline 15th September 2013 http://projects.digital-cultures.net/gamification/call-for-papers/ …    
    
    
    @iCartic thanks!    
    
    
    4 Ways to Make Employee Learning Memorable http://ow.ly/orehM  #gamification    
    
    
    @neutrain thanks Lucy! Have a good weekend    
    
    
    #businessication RT @HobbyGameDev: Influence of Business Models on Game Design http://www.hobbygamedev.com/adv/influence-of-business-models-on-game-design/ …    
    
    
    @jose_ignacio_mi Hi! Check the books of @kkapp about #education and #gamification    
    
    
    The @egfnyc countdown has begun: 23 days left! http://egfnyc.com     
    
    
    @anikolehmann could be a great context to explore but, polemic weapon? Share your thoughts with me! sergio at gameonlab dot com    
    
    
    "You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else." Albert Einstein    
    
    
    Movistar implements #gamification to optimize their Call Centers http://ow.ly/otjie     
    
    
    Like! RT @stephentotilo: Inspiring, short Q&A with Jane McGonigal (@avantgame) about gamers' potential in the world http://kotaku.com/quick-q-a-why-she-thinks-gamers-can-improve-the-world-1239636430 …    
    
    
    Thanks Reuven! RT @reuvengorsht: The management trouble with Generation X http://zite.to/19cEVpq     
    
    
    @tobyberesford great! thank you Toby!    
    
    
    10 Proven Gamification Strategies for Publishers to Maximize Engagement http://ow.ly/ovdkf     
    
    
    Gamification 2 Years On: what is it now, why is it still important? by @daverage http://ow.ly/ovdpV     
    
    
    Using play to motivate employees and engage customers http://ow.ly/ovdye  #gamification    
    
    
    The very best top 100 Game Based Learning and Gamification Resources http://ow.ly/owlYv  #gamification    
    
    
    @Nandini_M thnx Nandini! Have a good day!    
    
    
    Great infographic about #education technology through 2040 http://ow.ly/oxI54  #gamification    
    
    
    "Creativity is contagious. Pass it on." Albert Einstein via @ideas4all    
    
    
    Don't play Candy Crush, because once you do, you won't be able to stop http://ow.ly/oyDXz  #games    
    
    
    Great Kickstarter project: Robot Turtles, The Board Game for Little Programmers http://ow.ly/oyEjF  via @avantgame    
    
    
    @GoSpinthebottle @avantgame that's great! Good luck!    
    
    
    @avantgame or just the canvas @ http://gameonlab.com     
    
    
    Mom Gamers Study: A New Generation of Gamer http://ow.ly/oA0xn     
    
    
    The cost of acquiring mobile app users soars to highest level in 2 years http://ow.ly/oA0Xs     
    
    
    Some advices from @gamasutra, creating games for kids http://ow.ly/oA11F  #games    
    
    
    @Seriosity thanks!    
    
    
    @GoSpinthebottle @gamasutra yep! It's a good source for a lot of people!    
    
    
    Research: Status as a lever! RT @HarvardResearch: Want to encourage people to do the right thing? http://hvrd.me/11hQfvw     
    
    
    Congrats! RT @charlieykim: Great writeup in @HuffPostBiz on @NextJump #Gamification of Fitness http://huff.to/1dJm7mP     
    
    
    Make Your Knowledge Workers More Productive @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/09/make_your_knowledge_workers_more_productive.html …    
    
    
    LOL RT @reuvengorsht: 23 Things That Could Only Exist In Silicon Valley - http://bzfd.it/1fAgpA0     
    
    
    Great concept! Dopamine Driven Design http://ow.ly/oCqq2  #games #interactive    
    
    
    “The soul of a game is its players.” RT @daverage: Extended Player Psychographics http://bit.ly/1cMbtsx     
    
    
    @daverage thank you Andrzej ;) we're building and that's great!    
    
    
    @oz_michael thanks Michael! Use it for your projects or clients and send us your most valuable feedback!    
    
    
    @ThinkMarketingM I'll try! Thank you!    
    
    
    "Games Lubricate the Body and the Mind" - Benjamin Franklin    
    
    
    If you want to understand what #gamification is, you must watch this film http://ow.ly/oHm7w     
    
    
    Gamification: hype or hit? http://ow.ly/oGuqX     
    
    
    "Hand me an award and watch carefully" #gamification by Dilbert http://ow.ly/oHsqt  LOL    
    
    
    @Technology_Adv it's great!    
    
    
    @FCathala thanks Fabrice!    
    
    
    BNZ Targets Youth Money With Gamification and Social Media Banking http://ow.ly/oIXZE     
    
    
    Nike remaps the London Tube based on Fuelband Points http://ow.ly/oIY4G  #gamification    
    
    
    @Sir_William_Sua thnx William!    
    
    
    Why Apple doesn't need #gamification today to engage people?    
    
    
    Game On! 6 Tips for Gamification in a Global Workforce http://ow.ly/oIY7W     
    
    
    NPD report: Kids playing mobile devices nearly as much as consoles and PC http://ow.ly/oLO73     
    
    
    Why #gamification and #bigdata go hand-in-hand http://ow.ly/oLOEK  via @barrykirk    
    
    
    How Albert Einstein, Steve Jobs and Maria Popova got more creative http://ow.ly/oLP3w     
    
    
    What are Users Up to When they Have an Experience? http://ow.ly/oNyHQ  #UX    
    
    
    Why Gone Home is so immersive http://ow.ly/oNyPU  #psicology #games    
    
    
    What Games Are: plus ça change http://ow.ly/oNyZY  #games    
    
    
    Minor changes on Gamification Model Canvas, download the new poster and game on! http://ow.ly/oOH7t     
    
    
    MT @Bunchball: It's Not a Game: It's #Gamification http://huff.to/1e1R5Xs     
    
    
    "How I teach game design" by @zimmermaneric http://ow.ly/oTEzb     
    
    
    The Role of Big Data in Personalizing the Healthcare Experience http://ow.ly/oTE1j  #gamification #mobile #sensors    
    
    
    5 Ways Leaders Win At Gamification Technology http://ow.ly/oTDdg  via @VictorManriqueY    
    
    
    @philippedewamme Hi! Dynamics are the reasons why players perform behaviors. The dynamic is the nearest concept to motivation in a game.    
    
    
    Playing your employees: a game design problem http://ow.ly/oTDGV     
    
    
    @philippedewamme well said! it's a tool for "how", not a theory paper about motivation    
    
    
    @philippedewamme intrinsic motivation only can be achieve if your target behaviors = desired behaviors by your players    
    
    
    Dopamine Driven Design http://ow.ly/oCqq2  #games #interactive    
    
    
    Psychology and Design, the top 10 presentations http://ow.ly/oW5ub  #UX #psychology #gamification    
    
    
    @crocksberlin thanks!    
    
    
    Disruptors: My Negative User Type by @daverage http://ow.ly/oW5oQ  #gamification    
    
    
    Does respeccing your character in Diablo 3 make you happy? http://ow.ly/oYIoX  #games #psychology    
    
    
    @TheHeroPlan thanks fighters!    
    
    
    Design for Experience: Bridging Digital and Physical Experiences http://ow.ly/p0HwD     
    
    
    @gregoiredore @Serious_Factory @ToFloOW @FredGechter @InfosdeTwittter @Nico_Demoulin @lewebdigital @euKlide @EBoccas @geodore @s_delmas thnx    
    
    
    ¡Jugando a ganar! http://read.bi/15pcPVM  #gamification    
    
    
    @georginaelus @Seriosity thanks Georgina!    
    
    
    @s_delmas @gregoiredore @Szelerski @Serious_Factory @ToFloOW @FredGechter @InfosdeTwittter @Nico_Demoulin @lewebdigital @euKlide @EBoccas !!    
    
    
    @troymickins @Seriosity thanks Troy!    
    
    
    @marco_ricci thanks Marco! #FF back    
    
    
    @Heirenns thanks for RT!    
    
    
    @JavitxuTranche gracias Javitxu! Buen finde!    
    
    
    “Life is like Tetris, if it doesn't fit, just flip it over”. Sabine Hein.    
    
    
    No. 1 Priority for CMOs: Figuring Out How Best to Engage with Customers http://ow.ly/p6YZQ     
    
    
    The 6 Pillars of The Digital Workplace http://ow.ly/p6Z4r     
    
    
    Does #gamification work? A look into research http://ow.ly/p6Zbw     
    
    
    @dmeusburger thanks Daniel! Have a good day!    
    
    
    @poida thanks for RT! ;)    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom thnx friends!    
    
    
    Design for Experience: Promoting Empathy For Users http://ow.ly/p9npy     
    
    
    Onboarding Techniques and Examples for Your New Players http://ow.ly/p9mV2  #UX #gamification    
    
    
    A Five-Step Process For Conducting Player Research http://ow.ly/p9ngi  #UX #gamification    
    
    
    Download for free the canvas to break down the game design into understandable elements for your project! http://ow.ly/p9pQK     
    
    
    Data-Driven Design In The Real World http://ow.ly/pcmmQ     
    
    
    The maps transforming how we interact with the world http://ow.ly/pcn9d  #bigdata #interactive #maps    
    
    
    @RuizC_AntJ @gersonbeltran @Charly_BG thanks Antonio! ;)    
    
    
    @rockyoo @WonderfulCA thanks Barbara! ;)    
    
    
    @BaruchDon thank you Don!    
    
    
    @AMIconsultancy thanks for sharing! ;)    
    
    
    Great! RT @shanesnow: Great post: How to Find Happiness http://huff.to/1gzZPRx  by @charlieykim    
    
    
    @Official_Tobi @mherger check it out http://invoost.com  good luck with that project!    
    
    
    Game On! Download for free the Gamification Model Canvas and get results! http://ow.ly/pgsTG     
    
    
    @oyajimbo @baibbb @Ilotimo @AnaCristinaPrts @llsvldt @RainDeer3 @edmodo @MainwoodDavid @gzicherm @teacherkristina @touqo thnx!    
    
    
    @gruvjunky thanks John! Send us your valuable feedback canvas@gameonlab.com and have a good day!    
    
    
    Design helps businesses grow: Action plan to promote design-driven innovation from European Commission http://ow.ly/pktAA     
    
    
    Lean UX and System Design by @amyjokim http://ow.ly/pktLk     
    
    
    Gamification: remedies the fatigue caused by relentless internal change http://ow.ly/pn3gl  #gamification    
    
    
    @JimHunt thanks Jim!    
    
    
    @Buray22 thanks Christopher!    
    
    
    Gamification: why playing games could be the future of training and e-learning http://ow.ly/pn37F  #gamification    
    
    
    Mobile Gamification is a serious market http://ow.ly/pn3cO  #gamification    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom thanks!    
    
    
    @troymickins thanks Troy!    
    
    
    @giomotivation @AlfredPoor @TatianaKelsh @Jay_Henrickson you too!    
    
    
    @bucharesttutor thanks Vijay! ;)    
    
    
    @Eowathiel Game On!    
    
    
    @GrahamMcCormick @VedRistic @CarolLeaman Game On!    
    
    
    Powerful Workflow Tips, Tools And Tricks For Web Designers http://ow.ly/prVwp     
    
    
    @LPralleKeehn great! good luck and game on!    
    
    
    How Your Product Can Benefit From User Feedback http://ow.ly/prVtQ     
    
    
    What's Next? The evolution of Social Games http://ow.ly/prVHI     
    
    
    Gamification Must Drive Software Ergonomics http://ow.ly/pugqo     
    
    
    @AnnAmandaBee thanks Ann! Have a good day!    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom gracias chic@s! Buen finde!    
    
    
    @tobyberesford thanks Toby!    
    
    
    A lot of people downloaded Gamification Model Canvas, are using it and have helped us to improve it, thank you! http://ow.ly/pySi8     
    
    
    How Gamification Is Going To Change The Workplace http://ow.ly/pB5OZ     
    
    
    Salespeople Thrive off Competition, so Up Their Game http://ow.ly/pB5Ud  #gamification    
    
    
    Why you don't burn out on Candy Crush Saga? http://ow.ly/pB6pS  #psychology #games    
    
    
    10 Examples of Gamification to Influence Employee Behavior http://ow.ly/pDpUQ     
    
    
    A simple, science-backed way to solve the employee-engagement problem http://ow.ly/pDq8B     
    
    
    @openstudy great!    
    
    
    @barbaramcveigh @daverage thanks Barbara! Great article!    
    
    
    @pyramedium @Jalaizdo thanks Gregory!    
    
    
    @LPralleKeehn thanks Leslie! Have a good day!    
    
    
    @cptup thanks Captain!    
    
    
    @nanouk thanks Isabelle for RT! ;)    
    
    
    @gersonbeltran @AntonioVChanal @RuizC_AntJ @eoi @PuroMarketing @sbonet poco a poco! Game On!    
    
    
    @jimbonicholls @TonyVidler thanks Jim!    
    
    
    @TonyVidler thanks Tony!    
    
    
    @playmeapp that looks great! good luck with the project!    
    
    
    @Velocify @mikewatts502 @chazzagarcia @brandtpage @MarketingApes @PaulSlakey @LATechSummit #FF back    
    
    
    @BenWightwick thanks Ben! Send us your most valuable feedback! canvas@gameonlab.com    
    
    
    @boomboxinc thanks for RT! Have a good weekend!    
    
    
    @PPCRocks thanks for RT! :_)    
    
    
    @BahiaJagdeep that's great! Did you check the canvas out?    
    
    
    Incorporating More Quiet Into The UX Design Process http://ow.ly/pQ1bL  #UX    
    
    
    Smart, Effective Strategies To Design Marketing Campaigns http://ow.ly/pQ1Db     
    
    
    Editor in Chief Amy Cosper on Gamification and the Importance of Play http://ow.ly/pQ2QJ  #gamification    
    
    
    Awesome projects have already downloaded and used the #gamification canvas! Great news coming soon, check it out! http://ow.ly/pRpT7     
    
    
    How UX can help us rethink our views of the brain http://ow.ly/pQ1mF  #UX    
    
    
    Less Humble Bundles Are More http://ow.ly/pQ1Xr  #psychology #games    
    
    
    Why Your Mobile Game Failed: Complexity Kills! http://ow.ly/pQ2Dj  #mobile #games    
    
    
    Why Your Business Should Get in on the Gamification Trend http://ow.ly/pQ2Vx  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification Model Canvas has been downloaded in +80 countries around the world! http://ow.ly/pRpZI  #gameon    
    
    
    @Rima_Design @uxmag thanks for mention! =)    
    
    
    @ValeraMariscal @MyriamCarrel @nor7992 @AnaisRG @yukaichou @mherger @imaginateca @virginiog @lramosneira @LourdesLopezRom #FF back!    
    
    
    @AlexBeaussier @mdial thanks for mention Alex! Have a good weekend!    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom thanks for RT my friends!    
    
    
    @daverage yes! Thank you! But I need time to review it! I'll write you soon!    
    
    
    Honor Thy Player’s Time http://ow.ly/pQ2Ju  #games    
    
    
    Design your own game-based solution with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://amzn.to/178RKPS     
    
    
    Download for free the canvas to break down the game design into understandable elements for your project! http://ow.ly/p9pQK     
    
    
    The Developer’s Journey: LeanUX meets the Customer Lifecycle by @amyjokim http://ow.ly/q5zdS     
    
    
    Gamification In Leadership Development: How Companies Use Gaming To Build Their Leader Pipeline http://ow.ly/q5Bnl     
    
    
    Workshop Open Focused sobre #gamification, employee engagement y #RRHH en La Salle Madrid 30/10 ¡plazas limitadas! http://ow.ly/q5CKD     
    
    
    Why you were not wasting your time playing video games http://ow.ly/q5Bsf  #gamification    
    
    
    Design your own game-based solution with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://amzn.to/178RKPS     
    
    
    Five Ways People Adopt And Love Change http://ow.ly/qelKT  #UX    
    
    
    Use Gamification to Effectively Convey Company Goals and Motivate Employees http://ow.ly/qelVa  #gamification    
    
    
    The Nike+ gamification platform delivers valuable big data insights http://ow.ly/qemTb  #gamification #bigdata    
    
    
    Design for Experience: Interactive Component of an Advertising Campaign http://ow.ly/qelOz  #UX    
    
    
    Calculating the ROI of Social Data http://ow.ly/qelYJ     
    
    
    Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://amzn.to/178RKPS     
    
    
    Measuring and Influencing User Behavior with Gamification http://ow.ly/qemPY  #gamification    
    
    
    Four Myths About UX and How to Bust Them http://ow.ly/qelRS  #UX    
    
    
    From Zero to Profitability in the Educational App Market http://ow.ly/qem2v  #game #design    
    
    
    Check it out! The canvas to break down the game design into understandable elements! http://ow.ly/qemoU     
    
    
    Verizon launches its home health platform with EHR support, gamification http://ow.ly/qemVe  #gamification    
    
    
    Fun Times! Work, Games and Culture #TChat Recap http://ow.ly/qen1P     
    
    
    The Myth of Agile Empowerment http://ow.ly/qem5J  #game #design    
    
    
    @kikericart @CM_Madrid @Soulsightmadrid gracias Enrique! :_)    
    
    
    @Leticiaalameda @Soulsightmadrid @CM_Madrid thanks for coming Leticia! Good luck!    
    
    
    @pretavoyager @CM_Madrid @jatubio thanks for coming Anne!    
    
    
    Gamification Punches out Punch Card Programs Everywhere http://ow.ly/qemZb     
    
    
    Innovation Gamified: A Lesson From The XBox Generation http://ow.ly/qen3L     
    
    
    @gamkt sorry! Try this! http://blog.mindjet.com/2013/10/innovation-gamified-xbox/ …    
    
    
    @tobyberesford thanks Toby!    
    
    
    People around the world are running workshops about #gamification with Game On! Toolkit, what are you waiting for? http://ow.ly/qjjuR     
    
    
    The Role of Gamification in the Contact Center and Back Office http://ow.ly/qsqB9     
    
    
    Driving the wrong behaviours with rewards http://ow.ly/qsqG2  #gamification    
    
    
    WoWinSchool: How to use WoW and MMORPGs to Engage Students http://ow.ly/qspzY     
    
    
    Saucy Necromancers And the Psychology of Self-Perception http://ow.ly/qspvG  #psycology #games    
    
    
    Choose a session mode of Game On! Toolkit and build your own game-based solutions! http://ow.ly/qsrYI  #gamification    
    
    
    Design for Experience: Experience that Makes a Difference http://ow.ly/qsqjF  #UX    
    
    
    Safecracking the Brain: What neuroscience is learning from code-breakers and thieves http://ow.ly/qsqLQ     
    
    
    Andrea Kuszewski on The Science of Motivation: Neurology, Psychology, Gamification http://ow.ly/qspE0     
    
    
    Game On! Download for free the Gamification Model Canvas and get results! http://ow.ly/pgsTG     
    
    
    Understanding the Importance of User Research with Steve Portigal http://ow.ly/qsqnX     
    
    
    Google’s Niantic Labs to launch massive augmented reality game on Dec. 14 http://ow.ly/qspNb     
    
    
    Peering into the future of augmented reality games http://ow.ly/qsq85     
    
    
    How Game Based Learning Can Be Used For Training http://ow.ly/qspH0     
    
    
    A New Perspective on Game Writing http://ow.ly/qspVv  #games #storytelling    
    
    
    The Quick Guide for Gamification Model Canvas from UX Magazine http://ow.ly/qsrEh     
    
    
    Five Principles of Writing for Users http://ow.ly/qsqr1     
    
    
    Businessication: Adopting E-Comm Best Practices for Max Player Conversion in Online Games http://ow.ly/qsq35  #games    
    
    
    Gamification Model Canvas, the making of http://ow.ly/qAqL7  Gamasutra Featured Post    
    
    
    Infographic: The Neurology of Gaming http://ow.ly/qsqV7     
    
    
    @chrisnronald yep! It's great!    
    
    
    @rafabillor @VictorManriqueY @kokopus_dark @daverage @gzicherm thanks my friend! #FFback!    
    
    
    @TFOCanada thnx for the mention!    
    
    
    Five Tips for Conducting Scientific Research in the UX World http://ow.ly/qsqv5     
    
    
    What are rewards? Decoding the Game http://ow.ly/qsqeW     
    
    
    Customer Spotlight: KLM’s Meet & Seat Connects Flyers Through Social http://ow.ly/qspJv     
    
    
    Biofeedback and video games: What does the future have in store? http://ow.ly/qsqbD     
    
    
    Vendors should educate users on business gamification http://ow.ly/qsr0k  #gamification    
    
    
    Design your own game-based solution with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://ow.ly/qss0Y  #gamification    
    
    
    9 trends for the next decade of video games: gamification http://ow.ly/qGGxK     
    
    
    Gamification Model Canvas: Game and Business Perspective http://ow.ly/qGI55     
    
    
    The Quest for Honest Feedback http://ow.ly/qGGMd  #game #design #tips    
    
    
    Choose a session mode of Game On! Toolkit and build your own game-based solutions! http://ow.ly/qsrYI  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification as a Content Marketing Tactic, How Brands Are Engaging Consumers http://ow.ly/qIa2P     
    
    
    With the luster of social games gone, what now? http://ow.ly/qGGes  #social #games    
    
    
    Jesse Schell: Games Will Lead the Future of Engagement with Pleasure http://ow.ly/qGHXL     
    
    
    Predicting Behavior: Dissecting rewards http://ow.ly/qGGQk  #gamification    
    
    
    Accenture improves effectiveness and efficiency of Recruiting for Semiconductors through Gamification techniques http://ow.ly/qIaaL     
    
    
    All work and all play, are you doing what you love right now? So, start! http://ow.ly/qLRpI     
    
    
    Balfour Beatty CIO on improving safety with drones and gamification http://ow.ly/qIao4     
    
    
    Mid-Core Success: Players Retention http://ow.ly/qGGnm  #game #design #tips    
    
    
    Five Tips to Keep People Playing Your Game http://ow.ly/qGH17     
    
    
    People around the world are running workshops about #gamification with Game On! Toolkit, what are you waiting for? http://ow.ly/qjjuR     
    
    
    The Psychology of Video Game Nostalgia http://ow.ly/qGHT6     
    
    
    The Way We Work Now http://ow.ly/qGHKo     
    
    
    @applicantes @kwerb the link is broken :(    
    
    
    Design your own game-based solutions with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://ow.ly/qSNua  #gamification    
    
    
    The 'Internet of Toys': Toymail Connects Kids to Their Loved Ones http://ow.ly/qV6eW  #UX    
    
    
    How Not to Compare the Xbox One and Playstation 4 http://ow.ly/qV6ml  #psycology #game #sales    
    
    
    Designing a simple “Thin Layer” gamified system http://ow.ly/qV6z2  #gamification    
    
    
    Game Play Has No Negative Impact on Kids, UK Study Finds http://ow.ly/qV6EL     
    
    
    Run your own #gamification workshop with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon to Europe. http://ow.ly/qV9Wf     
    
    
    Experience Design is a Perspective, not a Discipline http://ow.ly/qV6Pw  #UX    
    
    
    Swinburne University of Technology free course: Concepts in Game Development http://ow.ly/qV6SV     
    
    
    BB&T is Training Leaders Through their Mobile Legacy Game http://ow.ly/qV73X     
    
    
    @MrVecino @ashmaurya @TheHeroPlan that’s great! congrats!    
    
    
    Del CRM al PRM, Player Relationship Management http://ow.ly/qV7ia  #gamification    
    
    
    Check it out! Gamification Model Canvas is now available for your project! http://ow.ly/qV7dF     
    
    
    Empathy in Game Design, or Why Some People Like Beyond: Two Souls http://ow.ly/qV7oq  #game #design    
    
    
    Four Steps to Customer Experience Maturity http://ow.ly/qV7AS  #UX    
    
    
    Cost-per-engagement y #gamification http://ow.ly/qV7IA     
    
    
    Four factors driving gamification in healthcare http://ow.ly/qV7N8  #gamification    
    
    
    Bored with reading #gamification benefits? Let's do it! Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/qVa5q     
    
    
    Can chaos empower the user experience? http://ow.ly/qV7Wj  #UX #game #design    
    
    
    Hi Uxers! Check it out! Build your own gamified user experience with Gamification Model Canvas! http://ow.ly/qV84Z     
    
    
    Getting Your Gamification On: Four Tips for Financial Services Companieshttp://ow.ly/qV8tZ    
    
    
    The Habits Of Successful New Web Professionals http://ow.ly/qV8xw     
    
    
    Check this project! They are mapping the 3D structure of neurons and over 80K people from 130 countries already do http://ow.ly/qV8Up     
    
    
    Check out "Barcelona - Gamification Model Canvas Workshop" http://gameonlab-barcelona.eventbrite.com/?aff=estw  vía @eventbrite    
    
    
    Five Principles for Accommodating User Needs In Developer-Led Projects http://ow.ly/qV8Ye  #UX    
    
    
    Designing a game that breaks friendships http://ow.ly/qV93i  #game #design    
    
    
    Learn and practice gamiﬁcation by designing your own game-based solutions with Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/qVawj     
    
    
    Design for Experience: Work Environment for Digital Practitioners http://ow.ly/r93h4  #UX    
    
    
    Educators! Check it out! A game-based classroom response system http://ow.ly/r93m4  #gamification    
    
    
    Game design experts explain the essential skills to keep players engaged http://ow.ly/r93bb  #gamification    
    
    
    Designing Without Words http://ow.ly/r940O  #game #design    
    
    
    Now you can integrate the game and business perspective with our free #gamification canvas! Check it out! http://ow.ly/r94bc     
    
    
    Want to bake in an engaged user experience? It’s a piece of cake http://ow.ly/r93oi  #UX    
    
    
    The 5 Hidden Superpowers of Balanced Creative Teams http://ow.ly/r93rS     
    
    
    What Is The Legal Status Of Virtual Goods? http://ow.ly/r93ur     
    
    
    Gamification Roundup: Google Glass App, Candy Campaigns, and Healthcare http://ow.ly/r945z     
    
    
    Gaming to Engage the Healthcare Consumer http://ow.ly/r93wT  #gamification #report    
    
    
    Integrating individual rewards with community engagement (future of retail) http://ow.ly/r93Cp     
    
    
    What Neuroscience Says About The Link Between Creativity And Madness http://ow.ly/r93GB     
    
    
    Talks from Gamification World Congress now available for everyone! Game On! http://ow.ly/rdNBV     
    
    
    In narrative games, self-expression doesn't mean 'empowerment' http://ow.ly/r93Jz  #game #design    
    
    
    How to Power Marketing Campaigns with Social Data http://ow.ly/r93M6     
    
    
    Screen play thoughts: A speculative look at trends in video game addiction http://ow.ly/r93OW     
    
    
    Game On! Lab Workshop en el Mobile World Centre de Barcelona! 10/12 @MW_Centre http://ow.ly/rh9fB  Game On!    
    
    
    "You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else" - Albert Einstein pic.twitter.com/ANV1Hbxz9M    
    
    
    Embracing Paradoxes and Narratives in Education http://ow.ly/r93Ru  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification User Types 2.0 by @daverage http://ow.ly/r93V3     
    
    
    Meaningful Choice in Games: Practical Guide & Case Studies http://ow.ly/r93XT  #game #design    
    
    
    Última oportunidad! Reserva tu sitio a precio early bird para el workshop de #gamification en Barcelona http://ow.ly/rgTyG  Game On!    
    
    
    Happy Half Year! http://gamificationmodelcanvas.com  #gamification pic.twitter.com/bDGxjSwsxY    
    
    
    Great article! The Psychology of Video Game Avatars http://ow.ly/rlFZC     
    
    
    4 effective strategies Candy Crush teaches us about Gamification for Corporate Training http://ow.ly/rlGlL     
    
    
    The best christmas gift for marketers, HR managers, innovators and educators this year: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rlGW3     
    
    
    This is not a game: Why #gamification is becoming a multi-billion dollar way to motivate people http://ow.ly/rmHB3     
    
    
    Candy Crush-style game helps scientists fight tree disease http://ow.ly/rmKPg  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification: 5 Cosas Serias que Aprendí Jugando al Angry Birds http://ow.ly/rmSbw     
    
    
    Emotional Monetization - Driving Revenues Through Emotion http://ow.ly/rmPV8  #game #design    
    
    
    Watch BitCoins transactions happen across the world http://ow.ly/rmPnL     
    
    
    Check it out! The ultimate gamification design kit: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rmSQX     
    
    
    The Secret to Implementing Serious Learning Games http://ow.ly/rmJJg     
    
    
    The Top 20 Companies with Employees That Have Gamification in Their LinkedIn Profile http://ow.ly/rmPB4     
    
    
    Play Nice: Building the Well-Behaved Game http://ow.ly/rmQ4k     
    
    
    The power of feedback mechanisms http://ow.ly/rmKct  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification: Quests, Objectives, Goals and more by @daverage http://ow.ly/rmPJU     
    
    
    @daverage you’re the best!    
    
    
    Beyond the Buzz: Combining Big Data Analytics & Gamification in Recruiting & Hiring http://ow.ly/rmKzB     
    
    
    Levels of Abstraction in Game Design http://ow.ly/rmQsR     
    
    
    @David_Mullich thnx David! #FF back! Have a good weekend    
    
    
    Will gamification stay relevant? http://ow.ly/rA1Cd  #gamification    
    
    
    These 3 Trends will drive Enterprise Software Development in 2014 http://ow.ly/rA1Kk  #gamification    
    
    
    In The Hospital Of The Future, Big Data Is One Of Your Doctors http://ow.ly/rA1TM  #bigdata    
    
    
    Ouch! New link! Game On! In The Hospital of The Future, Big Data is One of Your Doctors http://bit.ly/1bjD19h     
    
    
    @extremezealand thnx! New link posted!    
    
    
    @mogarick thnx! link re-posted!    
    
    
    Gamification Model Canvas World Tour starts now! pic.twitter.com/TTNi0ZlZ9w    
    
    
    Thanks for the feedback! Some minor changes has been applied to Gamification Model Canvas! Check it out! http://ow.ly/rHfc3     
    
    
    Gamification Trends To Watch in 2014 http://ow.ly/rNiZN  #gamification    
    
    
    Three key rules of gamification of the workplace http://ow.ly/rNjp7     
    
    
    Five UX Lessons from Hollywood http://ow.ly/rNiqz  #UX    
    
    
    The Slow Gamification of K-12 Classrooms http://ow.ly/rNkm0     
    
    
    Check it out! The ultimate gamification design kit: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rmSQX     
    
    
    The best christmas gift for marketers, HR managers, innovators and educators this year: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rlGW3     
    
    
    How Social Learning and Feedback Ensures Successful Employee Training http://ow.ly/rNj2T     
    
    
    Trip Hawkins’ new game helps kids learn about their feelings http://ow.ly/rNjlt     
    
    
    Thematic Storytelling Through Menu Design http://ow.ly/rNjIQ     
    
    
    How Your Game Can Change the World http://ow.ly/rNjNV     
    
    
    Build your concept with Gamification Model Canvas, check it out! http://ow.ly/rNTRH     
    
    
    How Your Game Can Change the World (part 2) http://ow.ly/rNj4P     
    
    
    Learn and practice gamification by designing your own game-based solutions with Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rNmw0     
    
    
    The Psychology Behind Information Dashboards http://ow.ly/rNisd  #UX    
    
    
    Why government health departments are spending millions on mobile gaming http://ow.ly/rNkHz     
    
    
    Who Needs Interactivity? http://ow.ly/rNjTf     
    
    
    Using the Gamification User Types in the Real World by @daverage http://ow.ly/rNj93     
    
    
    Will Rovio recapture its glory as Angry Birds Go! debuts on a global stage? http://ow.ly/rNjn8     
    
    
    Gartner Sticks to its Failing Gamification Prediction http://ow.ly/rNktk     
    
    
    Now you can download for free the most used tool: Gamification Model Canvas http://ow.ly/rNUBm  Game On!    
    
    
    4 Ways Gamification Can Help Your Business http://ow.ly/rNkBI     
    
    
    Using Gamification in Business for Customer Engagement http://ow.ly/rNkFn     
    
    
    The 5 trends that defined the game industry in 2013 http://ow.ly/rNjCL     
    
    
    Run your own #gamification workshop with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon to Europe. http://ow.ly/qV9Wf     
    
    
    Mechanics are the Message: Designing a Game for Change in 3 Months http://ow.ly/s0tQJ     
    
    
    The processes behind King's Candy Crush http://ow.ly/s0tMa  #game #design    
    
    
    Turning Customer Support Into a Game http://ow.ly/s0tWQ  #gamification    
    
    
    You Don't "Always Lose" in Tetris: The Real Nature of Single-Player Competition http://ow.ly/s0tL5  #game #design    
    
    
    Using Gamification in Business for Customer Engagement http://ow.ly/s0tYP     
    
    
    Play at Work: Increase Employee Engagement through Gamification http://ow.ly/s0u4P     
    
    
    Reserva tu sitio en México DF: Gamification Model Canvas Workshop 29/01. Gamification, Networking & Business http://ow.ly/s0uc9     
    
    
    Game Design Theory Applied: A Layered Rewards System http://ow.ly/s4lyw     
    
    
    50 Something Gaming Academics on Twitter http://ow.ly/s4lB3     
    
    
    2014 Forecast: Gamification and the Year Ahead in Banking http://ow.ly/s4lSK     
    
    
    Using Brainwriting For Rapid Idea Generation http://ow.ly/s4lHq     
    
    
    The Top UX Predictions for 2014 http://ow.ly/s4lKX     
    
    
    Who Goes to Work to Have Fun? It Depends On What You Mean By "Fun" http://ow.ly/s4lO9     
    
    
    Playing with Gamification: Employee and Consumer Perspectives http://ow.ly/s4lYT     
    
    
    Highlights from Neuroscience 2013 http://ow.ly/s4m35     
    
    
    @devegape @Humannova @MJohnsonLoyalty @delaossaandres @clubpaul @TheMediaBag @plandenegociosb @AbelFernndezCal #FF back ;)    
    
    
    Battleship: The Ultimate Chocolate Combat Game LOL pic.twitter.com/jI4ZB6liiH    
    
    
    @David_Mullich thanks David! Merry Xmas and gamified new year! =)    
    
    
    Check it out! The ultimate gamification design kit: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/s4n8X     
    
    
    Run your own #gamification workshop with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon to Europe. http://ow.ly/s4nJb     
    
    
    The Potential of Gamification for Student Recruitment http://ow.ly/s4mek     
    
    
    Messification: Why Games Should Be Designed to Be Games First http://ow.ly/s4m9f     
    
    
    Infographic: The Most Popular Toys Of The Past 50 Years http://ow.ly/s4mjo     
    
    
    How online gamers organize themselves and what organizations can learn from them http://ow.ly/s4mtJ     
    
    
    Merck turns to gamification in diabetes http://ow.ly/s4mJU     
    
    
    6 Exciting Gaming Trends to Watch in 2014 http://ow.ly/s4mAT     
    
    
    The Best Board Games of 2013 http://ow.ly/s4mGq     
    
    
    Happy New Year! Game On 2014!    
    
    
    Remember from now on we’re in 2014!    
    
    
    The Platform and the Player: exploring the (hi)stories of Elite http://ow.ly/scFx5     
    
    
    How Your Game Can Change the World http://ow.ly/scFzX     
    
    
    Psycology of Games: Fake Feels and Free Passes http://ow.ly/scFGL     
    
    
    Increased productivity, the real reason for introducing gamification http://ow.ly/scG4R     
    
    
    Gamification Comes to the Contact Center http://ow.ly/scFEb     
    
    
    Design Microsoft's Surface Into the Classroom Experience http://ow.ly/scFLP     
    
    
    Great compilation by @yukaichou: A Comprehensive List of 90+ Gamification Cases with ROI Stats http://ow.ly/scGru     
    
    
    29/01 México DF - Gamification Model Canvas Workshop http://www.eventbrite.com/e/entradas-mexico-df-gamification-model-canvas-workshop-9628042735?aff=estw … vía @eventbrite    
    
    
    Great article about Multiplayer Logistics http://ow.ly/scFRQ     
    
    
    J.J. Rosen: Gamification helps make learning, earning more fun http://ow.ly/scGwR     
    
    
    Is gamification an insult to our humanity? http://ow.ly/scFWQ     
    
    
    Three Retailers Using Gamification to Engage Employees http://ow.ly/scG27     
    
    
    Top Instructional Design Trends and Outlook for 2014 http://ow.ly/scG8N     
    
    
    Check it out! The ultimate gamification design kit: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/sdxqc     
    
    
    Game Design Theory Applied: Endogenous Value http://ow.ly/scGgG     
    
    
    Shocking Grasps: An Archaeology of Electrotactile Game Mechanics http://ow.ly/scGdI     
    
    
    Become a game designer with Game On! Toolkit. Check it out! http://ow.ly/sdwpq     
    
    
    Checkpoint! Lunchtime! Time extended!    
    
    
    How has the perception of #gamification changed over the past few years? (Video) http://ow.ly/o57lR  @mherger @egfnyc    
    
    
    Great news! Game designers are also using Gamification Model Canvas! Thank you for improving it! http://ow.ly/o58PW     
    
    
    MT @amyjokim: There's a difference between user-centric design and building a user-centric business http://bit.ly/17HXhgB  from @khoi    
    
    
    @brasscount thanks Spence! Be part of the project sending us your most valuable feedback about using it.    
    
    
    @rawksoup thank you Bob!    
    
    
    Excellent article Jamie! MT @JamieMadigan: Are more likely to enjoy a game if you paid more for it? http://www.psychologyofgames.com/2013/08/its-not-so-bad-cognitive-dissonance-and-cheap-games/ …    
    
    
    Del CRM al PRM: Player Relationship Management http://ow.ly/o9AZ9  #games #gamification    
    
    
    Ok, let's go! let's create! #gamification http://instagram.com/p/dUC0CXn9O-/     
    
    
    Hey gamifier! What do you think about this? #gamification #ux #advergaming #serious #games pic.twitter.com/ipfoAT0sQf    
    
    
    @leupoki thanks Mario! Send us your most valuable feedback about using it! Game On!    
    
    
    Qué bonito es el amor! RT @josek_net: When a Relationship Becomes a Game http://ow.ly/nWPo0  Gamified love? #gamification    
    
    
    The open-source #gamification design framework. Download it, use it, improve it! http://ow.ly/obX3D     
    
    
    MT @GamiWorldCon: Come with us to the Enterprise Gamification Forum New York! @egfnyc Unlock your promo code here! http://bit.ly/MF7Wze     
    
    
    Awesome short-film about the flow! (Video) http://ow.ly/ogkJy     
    
    
    The game's inception near @SeminOzmorali RT @David_Mullich: The oldest known gaming tokens have been found in Turkey http://mashable.com/2013/08/14/oldest-gaming-tokens/ …    
    
    
    Definitely, the feedback is the food of champions    
    
    
    Reimagining the 21st-century classroom http://ow.ly/ojABW  #UX    
    
    
    The connected UX http://ow.ly/ojAO7  #research #UX    
    
    
    Awesome projects have already downloaded and used the #gamification canvas! Great news coming soon, check it out! http://ow.ly/ojHwa     
    
    
    @TreDigital thanks Maria    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom thanks HiSocial for that RTs! You are the best!    
    
    
    @EfeRios thank you Juan!    
    
    
    @ChristianXandu Merci Christian!    
    
    
    @thespacewofford great! #gamification is our mission =)    
    
    
    @ChookzN you're welcome!    
    
    
    Cool! RT @marigo: What’s the Difference Between Games and Gamification? https://www.edsurge.com/n/2013-08-20-what-s-the-difference-between-games-and-gamification … #edtech via @EdSurge #gamification    
    
    
    @ChookzN we need 30 tweets at least to discuss this! sergio at gameonlab dot com    
    
    
    The concept "churn rate" arrives to #games http://ow.ly/olNiQ  #businessication    
    
    
    Study: To The Human Brain, Me Is We http://ow.ly/olN68  #fellowship    
    
    
    @hwmturistico thanks!    
    
    
    Have you ever thought that you might need to take some shortcuts to launch a design quickly? http://ow.ly/olNFZ  #UX    
    
    
    No hay #gamification sin #UX http://ow.ly/onrJG  #archives    
    
    
    Interesting article about #dopamine and #games http://ow.ly/onrtP     
    
    
    @alexcoley @eModJesse gamification! not gasification! LOL check it out and send us your most valuable feedback canvas at gameonlab dot com    
    
    
    Help! Could someone make a theory about this coincidence? http://bit.ly/1dxntBS  #gamification #bmgen pic.twitter.com/fwQZ1EAYQR    
    
    
    @daverage @AndreaKuszewski thank you Andrzej! a very solid article with many interesting references    
    
    
    @daverage @AndreaKuszewski I'm looking forward to it!    
    
    
    Like! RT @aureamemotech: CfP  “Rethinking Gamification” Deadline 15th September 2013 http://projects.digital-cultures.net/gamification/call-for-papers/ …    
    
    
    @iCartic thanks!    
    
    
    4 Ways to Make Employee Learning Memorable http://ow.ly/orehM  #gamification    
    
    
    @neutrain thanks Lucy! Have a good weekend    
    
    
    #businessication RT @HobbyGameDev: Influence of Business Models on Game Design http://www.hobbygamedev.com/adv/influence-of-business-models-on-game-design/ …    
    
    
    @jose_ignacio_mi Hi! Check the books of @kkapp about #education and #gamification    
    
    
    The @egfnyc countdown has begun: 23 days left! http://egfnyc.com     
    
    
    @anikolehmann could be a great context to explore but, polemic weapon? Share your thoughts with me! sergio at gameonlab dot com    
    
    
    "You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else." Albert Einstein    
    
    
    Movistar implements #gamification to optimize their Call Centers http://ow.ly/otjie     
    
    
    Like! RT @stephentotilo: Inspiring, short Q&A with Jane McGonigal (@avantgame) about gamers' potential in the world http://kotaku.com/quick-q-a-why-she-thinks-gamers-can-improve-the-world-1239636430 …    
    
    
    Thanks Reuven! RT @reuvengorsht: The management trouble with Generation X http://zite.to/19cEVpq     
    
    
    @tobyberesford great! thank you Toby!    
    
    
    10 Proven Gamification Strategies for Publishers to Maximize Engagement http://ow.ly/ovdkf     
    
    
    Gamification 2 Years On: what is it now, why is it still important? by @daverage http://ow.ly/ovdpV     
    
    
    Using play to motivate employees and engage customers http://ow.ly/ovdye  #gamification    
    
    
    The very best top 100 Game Based Learning and Gamification Resources http://ow.ly/owlYv  #gamification    
    
    
    @Nandini_M thnx Nandini! Have a good day!    
    
    
    Great infographic about #education technology through 2040 http://ow.ly/oxI54  #gamification    
    
    
    "Creativity is contagious. Pass it on." Albert Einstein via @ideas4all    
    
    
    Don't play Candy Crush, because once you do, you won't be able to stop http://ow.ly/oyDXz  #games    
    
    
    Great Kickstarter project: Robot Turtles, The Board Game for Little Programmers http://ow.ly/oyEjF  via @avantgame    
    
    
    @GoSpinthebottle @avantgame that's great! Good luck!    
    
    
    @avantgame or just the canvas @ http://gameonlab.com     
    
    
    Mom Gamers Study: A New Generation of Gamer http://ow.ly/oA0xn     
    
    
    The cost of acquiring mobile app users soars to highest level in 2 years http://ow.ly/oA0Xs     
    
    
    Some advices from @gamasutra, creating games for kids http://ow.ly/oA11F  #games    
    
    
    @Seriosity thanks!    
    
    
    @GoSpinthebottle @gamasutra yep! It's a good source for a lot of people!    
    
    
    Research: Status as a lever! RT @HarvardResearch: Want to encourage people to do the right thing? http://hvrd.me/11hQfvw     
    
    
    Congrats! RT @charlieykim: Great writeup in @HuffPostBiz on @NextJump #Gamification of Fitness http://huff.to/1dJm7mP     
    
    
    Make Your Knowledge Workers More Productive @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/09/make_your_knowledge_workers_more_productive.html …    
    
    
    LOL RT @reuvengorsht: 23 Things That Could Only Exist In Silicon Valley - http://bzfd.it/1fAgpA0     
    
    
    Great concept! Dopamine Driven Design http://ow.ly/oCqq2  #games #interactive    
    
    
    “The soul of a game is its players.” RT @daverage: Extended Player Psychographics http://bit.ly/1cMbtsx     
    
    
    @daverage thank you Andrzej ;) we're building and that's great!    
    
    
    @oz_michael thanks Michael! Use it for your projects or clients and send us your most valuable feedback!    
    
    
    @ThinkMarketingM I'll try! Thank you!    
    
    
    "Games Lubricate the Body and the Mind" - Benjamin Franklin    
    
    
    If you want to understand what #gamification is, you must watch this film http://ow.ly/oHm7w     
    
    
    Gamification: hype or hit? http://ow.ly/oGuqX     
    
    
    "Hand me an award and watch carefully" #gamification by Dilbert http://ow.ly/oHsqt  LOL    
    
    
    @Technology_Adv it's great!    
    
    
    @FCathala thanks Fabrice!    
    
    
    BNZ Targets Youth Money With Gamification and Social Media Banking http://ow.ly/oIXZE     
    
    
    Nike remaps the London Tube based on Fuelband Points http://ow.ly/oIY4G  #gamification    
    
    
    @Sir_William_Sua thnx William!    
    
    
    Why Apple doesn't need #gamification today to engage people?    
    
    
    Game On! 6 Tips for Gamification in a Global Workforce http://ow.ly/oIY7W     
    
    
    NPD report: Kids playing mobile devices nearly as much as consoles and PC http://ow.ly/oLO73     
    
    
    Why #gamification and #bigdata go hand-in-hand http://ow.ly/oLOEK  via @barrykirk    
    
    
    How Albert Einstein, Steve Jobs and Maria Popova got more creative http://ow.ly/oLP3w     
    
    
    What are Users Up to When they Have an Experience? http://ow.ly/oNyHQ  #UX    
    
    
    Why Gone Home is so immersive http://ow.ly/oNyPU  #psicology #games    
    
    
    What Games Are: plus ça change http://ow.ly/oNyZY  #games    
    
    
    Minor changes on Gamification Model Canvas, download the new poster and game on! http://ow.ly/oOH7t     
    
    
    MT @Bunchball: It's Not a Game: It's #Gamification http://huff.to/1e1R5Xs     
    
    
    "How I teach game design" by @zimmermaneric http://ow.ly/oTEzb     
    
    
    The Role of Big Data in Personalizing the Healthcare Experience http://ow.ly/oTE1j  #gamification #mobile #sensors    
    
    
    5 Ways Leaders Win At Gamification Technology http://ow.ly/oTDdg  via @VictorManriqueY    
    
    
    @philippedewamme Hi! Dynamics are the reasons why players perform behaviors. The dynamic is the nearest concept to motivation in a game.    
    
    
    Playing your employees: a game design problem http://ow.ly/oTDGV     
    
    
    @philippedewamme well said! it's a tool for "how", not a theory paper about motivation    
    
    
    @philippedewamme intrinsic motivation only can be achieve if your target behaviors = desired behaviors by your players    
    
    
    Dopamine Driven Design http://ow.ly/oCqq2  #games #interactive    
    
    
    Psychology and Design, the top 10 presentations http://ow.ly/oW5ub  #UX #psychology #gamification    
    
    
    @crocksberlin thanks!    
    
    
    Disruptors: My Negative User Type by @daverage http://ow.ly/oW5oQ  #gamification    
    
    
    Does respeccing your character in Diablo 3 make you happy? http://ow.ly/oYIoX  #games #psychology    
    
    
    @TheHeroPlan thanks fighters!    
    
    
    Design for Experience: Bridging Digital and Physical Experiences http://ow.ly/p0HwD     
    
    
    @gregoiredore @Serious_Factory @ToFloOW @FredGechter @InfosdeTwittter @Nico_Demoulin @lewebdigital @euKlide @EBoccas @geodore @s_delmas thnx    
    
    
    ¡Jugando a ganar! http://read.bi/15pcPVM  #gamification    
    
    
    @georginaelus @Seriosity thanks Georgina!    
    
    
    @s_delmas @gregoiredore @Szelerski @Serious_Factory @ToFloOW @FredGechter @InfosdeTwittter @Nico_Demoulin @lewebdigital @euKlide @EBoccas !!    
    
    
    @troymickins @Seriosity thanks Troy!    
    
    
    @marco_ricci thanks Marco! #FF back    
    
    
    @Heirenns thanks for RT!    
    
    
    @JavitxuTranche gracias Javitxu! Buen finde!    
    
    
    “Life is like Tetris, if it doesn't fit, just flip it over”. Sabine Hein.    
    
    
    No. 1 Priority for CMOs: Figuring Out How Best to Engage with Customers http://ow.ly/p6YZQ     
    
    
    The 6 Pillars of The Digital Workplace http://ow.ly/p6Z4r     
    
    
    Does #gamification work? A look into research http://ow.ly/p6Zbw     
    
    
    @dmeusburger thanks Daniel! Have a good day!    
    
    
    @poida thanks for RT! ;)    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom thnx friends!    
    
    
    Design for Experience: Promoting Empathy For Users http://ow.ly/p9npy     
    
    
    Onboarding Techniques and Examples for Your New Players http://ow.ly/p9mV2  #UX #gamification    
    
    
    A Five-Step Process For Conducting Player Research http://ow.ly/p9ngi  #UX #gamification    
    
    
    Download for free the canvas to break down the game design into understandable elements for your project! http://ow.ly/p9pQK     
    
    
    Data-Driven Design In The Real World http://ow.ly/pcmmQ     
    
    
    The maps transforming how we interact with the world http://ow.ly/pcn9d  #bigdata #interactive #maps    
    
    
    @RuizC_AntJ @gersonbeltran @Charly_BG thanks Antonio! ;)    
    
    
    @rockyoo @WonderfulCA thanks Barbara! ;)    
    
    
    @BaruchDon thank you Don!    
    
    
    @AMIconsultancy thanks for sharing! ;)    
    
    
    Great! RT @shanesnow: Great post: How to Find Happiness http://huff.to/1gzZPRx  by @charlieykim    
    
    
    @Official_Tobi @mherger check it out http://invoost.com  good luck with that project!    
    
    
    Game On! Download for free the Gamification Model Canvas and get results! http://ow.ly/pgsTG     
    
    
    @oyajimbo @baibbb @Ilotimo @AnaCristinaPrts @llsvldt @RainDeer3 @edmodo @MainwoodDavid @gzicherm @teacherkristina @touqo thnx!    
    
    
    @gruvjunky thanks John! Send us your valuable feedback canvas@gameonlab.com and have a good day!    
    
    
    Design helps businesses grow: Action plan to promote design-driven innovation from European Commission http://ow.ly/pktAA     
    
    
    Lean UX and System Design by @amyjokim http://ow.ly/pktLk     
    
    
    Gamification: remedies the fatigue caused by relentless internal change http://ow.ly/pn3gl  #gamification    
    
    
    @JimHunt thanks Jim!    
    
    
    @Buray22 thanks Christopher!    
    
    
    Gamification: why playing games could be the future of training and e-learning http://ow.ly/pn37F  #gamification    
    
    
    Mobile Gamification is a serious market http://ow.ly/pn3cO  #gamification    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom thanks!    
    
    
    @troymickins thanks Troy!    
    
    
    @giomotivation @AlfredPoor @TatianaKelsh @Jay_Henrickson you too!    
    
    
    @bucharesttutor thanks Vijay! ;)    
    
    
    @Eowathiel Game On!    
    
    
    @GrahamMcCormick @VedRistic @CarolLeaman Game On!    
    
    
    Powerful Workflow Tips, Tools And Tricks For Web Designers http://ow.ly/prVwp     
    
    
    @LPralleKeehn great! good luck and game on!    
    
    
    How Your Product Can Benefit From User Feedback http://ow.ly/prVtQ     
    
    
    What's Next? The evolution of Social Games http://ow.ly/prVHI     
    
    
    Gamification Must Drive Software Ergonomics http://ow.ly/pugqo     
    
    
    @AnnAmandaBee thanks Ann! Have a good day!    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom gracias chic@s! Buen finde!    
    
    
    @tobyberesford thanks Toby!    
    
    
    A lot of people downloaded Gamification Model Canvas, are using it and have helped us to improve it, thank you! http://ow.ly/pySi8     
    
    
    How Gamification Is Going To Change The Workplace http://ow.ly/pB5OZ     
    
    
    Salespeople Thrive off Competition, so Up Their Game http://ow.ly/pB5Ud  #gamification    
    
    
    Why you don't burn out on Candy Crush Saga? http://ow.ly/pB6pS  #psychology #games    
    
    
    10 Examples of Gamification to Influence Employee Behavior http://ow.ly/pDpUQ     
    
    
    A simple, science-backed way to solve the employee-engagement problem http://ow.ly/pDq8B     
    
    
    @openstudy great!    
    
    
    @barbaramcveigh @daverage thanks Barbara! Great article!    
    
    
    @pyramedium @Jalaizdo thanks Gregory!    
    
    
    @LPralleKeehn thanks Leslie! Have a good day!    
    
    
    @cptup thanks Captain!    
    
    
    @nanouk thanks Isabelle for RT! ;)    
    
    
    @gersonbeltran @AntonioVChanal @RuizC_AntJ @eoi @PuroMarketing @sbonet poco a poco! Game On!    
    
    
    @jimbonicholls @TonyVidler thanks Jim!    
    
    
    @TonyVidler thanks Tony!    
    
    
    @playmeapp that looks great! good luck with the project!    
    
    
    @Velocify @mikewatts502 @chazzagarcia @brandtpage @MarketingApes @PaulSlakey @LATechSummit #FF back    
    
    
    @BenWightwick thanks Ben! Send us your most valuable feedback! canvas@gameonlab.com    
    
    
    @boomboxinc thanks for RT! Have a good weekend!    
    
    
    @PPCRocks thanks for RT! :_)    
    
    
    @BahiaJagdeep that's great! Did you check the canvas out?    
    
    
    Incorporating More Quiet Into The UX Design Process http://ow.ly/pQ1bL  #UX    
    
    
    Smart, Effective Strategies To Design Marketing Campaigns http://ow.ly/pQ1Db     
    
    
    Editor in Chief Amy Cosper on Gamification and the Importance of Play http://ow.ly/pQ2QJ  #gamification    
    
    
    Awesome projects have already downloaded and used the #gamification canvas! Great news coming soon, check it out! http://ow.ly/pRpT7     
    
    
    How UX can help us rethink our views of the brain http://ow.ly/pQ1mF  #UX    
    
    
    Less Humble Bundles Are More http://ow.ly/pQ1Xr  #psychology #games    
    
    
    Why Your Mobile Game Failed: Complexity Kills! http://ow.ly/pQ2Dj  #mobile #games    
    
    
    Why Your Business Should Get in on the Gamification Trend http://ow.ly/pQ2Vx  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification Model Canvas has been downloaded in +80 countries around the world! http://ow.ly/pRpZI  #gameon    
    
    
    @Rima_Design @uxmag thanks for mention! =)    
    
    
    @ValeraMariscal @MyriamCarrel @nor7992 @AnaisRG @yukaichou @mherger @imaginateca @virginiog @lramosneira @LourdesLopezRom #FF back!    
    
    
    @AlexBeaussier @mdial thanks for mention Alex! Have a good weekend!    
    
    
    @Hisocialcom thanks for RT my friends!    
    
    
    @daverage yes! Thank you! But I need time to review it! I'll write you soon!    
    
    
    Honor Thy Player’s Time http://ow.ly/pQ2Ju  #games    
    
    
    Design your own game-based solution with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://amzn.to/178RKPS     
    
    
    Download for free the canvas to break down the game design into understandable elements for your project! http://ow.ly/p9pQK     
    
    
    The Developer’s Journey: LeanUX meets the Customer Lifecycle by @amyjokim http://ow.ly/q5zdS     
    
    
    Gamification In Leadership Development: How Companies Use Gaming To Build Their Leader Pipeline http://ow.ly/q5Bnl     
    
    
    Workshop Open Focused sobre #gamification, employee engagement y #RRHH en La Salle Madrid 30/10 ¡plazas limitadas! http://ow.ly/q5CKD     
    
    
    Why you were not wasting your time playing video games http://ow.ly/q5Bsf  #gamification    
    
    
    Design your own game-based solution with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://amzn.to/178RKPS     
    
    
    Five Ways People Adopt And Love Change http://ow.ly/qelKT  #UX    
    
    
    Use Gamification to Effectively Convey Company Goals and Motivate Employees http://ow.ly/qelVa  #gamification    
    
    
    The Nike+ gamification platform delivers valuable big data insights http://ow.ly/qemTb  #gamification #bigdata    
    
    
    Design for Experience: Interactive Component of an Advertising Campaign http://ow.ly/qelOz  #UX    
    
    
    Calculating the ROI of Social Data http://ow.ly/qelYJ     
    
    
    Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://amzn.to/178RKPS     
    
    
    Measuring and Influencing User Behavior with Gamification http://ow.ly/qemPY  #gamification    
    
    
    Four Myths About UX and How to Bust Them http://ow.ly/qelRS  #UX    
    
    
    From Zero to Profitability in the Educational App Market http://ow.ly/qem2v  #game #design    
    
    
    Check it out! The canvas to break down the game design into understandable elements! http://ow.ly/qemoU     
    
    
    Verizon launches its home health platform with EHR support, gamification http://ow.ly/qemVe  #gamification    
    
    
    Fun Times! Work, Games and Culture #TChat Recap http://ow.ly/qen1P     
    
    
    The Myth of Agile Empowerment http://ow.ly/qem5J  #game #design    
    
    
    @kikericart @CM_Madrid @Soulsightmadrid gracias Enrique! :_)    
    
    
    @Leticiaalameda @Soulsightmadrid @CM_Madrid thanks for coming Leticia! Good luck!    
    
    
    @pretavoyager @CM_Madrid @jatubio thanks for coming Anne!    
    
    
    Gamification Punches out Punch Card Programs Everywhere http://ow.ly/qemZb     
    
    
    Innovation Gamified: A Lesson From The XBox Generation http://ow.ly/qen3L     
    
    
    @gamkt sorry! Try this! http://blog.mindjet.com/2013/10/innovation-gamified-xbox/ …    
    
    
    @tobyberesford thanks Toby!    
    
    
    People around the world are running workshops about #gamification with Game On! Toolkit, what are you waiting for? http://ow.ly/qjjuR     
    
    
    The Role of Gamification in the Contact Center and Back Office http://ow.ly/qsqB9     
    
    
    Driving the wrong behaviours with rewards http://ow.ly/qsqG2  #gamification    
    
    
    WoWinSchool: How to use WoW and MMORPGs to Engage Students http://ow.ly/qspzY     
    
    
    Saucy Necromancers And the Psychology of Self-Perception http://ow.ly/qspvG  #psycology #games    
    
    
    Choose a session mode of Game On! Toolkit and build your own game-based solutions! http://ow.ly/qsrYI  #gamification    
    
    
    Design for Experience: Experience that Makes a Difference http://ow.ly/qsqjF  #UX    
    
    
    Safecracking the Brain: What neuroscience is learning from code-breakers and thieves http://ow.ly/qsqLQ     
    
    
    Andrea Kuszewski on The Science of Motivation: Neurology, Psychology, Gamification http://ow.ly/qspE0     
    
    
    Game On! Download for free the Gamification Model Canvas and get results! http://ow.ly/pgsTG     
    
    
    Understanding the Importance of User Research with Steve Portigal http://ow.ly/qsqnX     
    
    
    Google’s Niantic Labs to launch massive augmented reality game on Dec. 14 http://ow.ly/qspNb     
    
    
    Peering into the future of augmented reality games http://ow.ly/qsq85     
    
    
    How Game Based Learning Can Be Used For Training http://ow.ly/qspH0     
    
    
    A New Perspective on Game Writing http://ow.ly/qspVv  #games #storytelling    
    
    
    The Quick Guide for Gamification Model Canvas from UX Magazine http://ow.ly/qsrEh     
    
    
    Five Principles of Writing for Users http://ow.ly/qsqr1     
    
    
    Businessication: Adopting E-Comm Best Practices for Max Player Conversion in Online Games http://ow.ly/qsq35  #games    
    
    
    Gamification Model Canvas, the making of http://ow.ly/qAqL7  Gamasutra Featured Post    
    
    
    Infographic: The Neurology of Gaming http://ow.ly/qsqV7     
    
    
    @chrisnronald yep! It's great!    
    
    
    @rafabillor @VictorManriqueY @kokopus_dark @daverage @gzicherm thanks my friend! #FFback!    
    
    
    @TFOCanada thnx for the mention!    
    
    
    Five Tips for Conducting Scientific Research in the UX World http://ow.ly/qsqv5     
    
    
    What are rewards? Decoding the Game http://ow.ly/qsqeW     
    
    
    Customer Spotlight: KLM’s Meet & Seat Connects Flyers Through Social http://ow.ly/qspJv     
    
    
    Biofeedback and video games: What does the future have in store? http://ow.ly/qsqbD     
    
    
    Vendors should educate users on business gamification http://ow.ly/qsr0k  #gamification    
    
    
    Design your own game-based solution with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://ow.ly/qss0Y  #gamification    
    
    
    9 trends for the next decade of video games: gamification http://ow.ly/qGGxK     
    
    
    Gamification Model Canvas: Game and Business Perspective http://ow.ly/qGI55     
    
    
    The Quest for Honest Feedback http://ow.ly/qGGMd  #game #design #tips    
    
    
    Choose a session mode of Game On! Toolkit and build your own game-based solutions! http://ow.ly/qsrYI  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification as a Content Marketing Tactic, How Brands Are Engaging Consumers http://ow.ly/qIa2P     
    
    
    With the luster of social games gone, what now? http://ow.ly/qGGes  #social #games    
    
    
    Jesse Schell: Games Will Lead the Future of Engagement with Pleasure http://ow.ly/qGHXL     
    
    
    Predicting Behavior: Dissecting rewards http://ow.ly/qGGQk  #gamification    
    
    
    Accenture improves effectiveness and efficiency of Recruiting for Semiconductors through Gamification techniques http://ow.ly/qIaaL     
    
    
    All work and all play, are you doing what you love right now? So, start! http://ow.ly/qLRpI     
    
    
    Balfour Beatty CIO on improving safety with drones and gamification http://ow.ly/qIao4     
    
    
    Mid-Core Success: Players Retention http://ow.ly/qGGnm  #game #design #tips    
    
    
    Five Tips to Keep People Playing Your Game http://ow.ly/qGH17     
    
    
    People around the world are running workshops about #gamification with Game On! Toolkit, what are you waiting for? http://ow.ly/qjjuR     
    
    
    The Psychology of Video Game Nostalgia http://ow.ly/qGHT6     
    
    
    The Way We Work Now http://ow.ly/qGHKo     
    
    
    @applicantes @kwerb the link is broken :(    
    
    
    Design your own game-based solutions with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon! http://ow.ly/qSNua  #gamification    
    
    
    The 'Internet of Toys': Toymail Connects Kids to Their Loved Ones http://ow.ly/qV6eW  #UX    
    
    
    How Not to Compare the Xbox One and Playstation 4 http://ow.ly/qV6ml  #psycology #game #sales    
    
    
    Designing a simple “Thin Layer” gamified system http://ow.ly/qV6z2  #gamification    
    
    
    Game Play Has No Negative Impact on Kids, UK Study Finds http://ow.ly/qV6EL     
    
    
    Run your own #gamification workshop with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon to Europe. http://ow.ly/qV9Wf     
    
    
    Experience Design is a Perspective, not a Discipline http://ow.ly/qV6Pw  #UX    
    
    
    Swinburne University of Technology free course: Concepts in Game Development http://ow.ly/qV6SV     
    
    
    BB&T is Training Leaders Through their Mobile Legacy Game http://ow.ly/qV73X     
    
    
    @MrVecino @ashmaurya @TheHeroPlan that’s great! congrats!    
    
    
    Del CRM al PRM, Player Relationship Management http://ow.ly/qV7ia  #gamification    
    
    
    Check it out! Gamification Model Canvas is now available for your project! http://ow.ly/qV7dF     
    
    
    Empathy in Game Design, or Why Some People Like Beyond: Two Souls http://ow.ly/qV7oq  #game #design    
    
    
    Four Steps to Customer Experience Maturity http://ow.ly/qV7AS  #UX    
    
    
    Cost-per-engagement y #gamification http://ow.ly/qV7IA     
    
    
    Four factors driving gamification in healthcare http://ow.ly/qV7N8  #gamification    
    
    
    Bored with reading #gamification benefits? Let's do it! Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/qVa5q     
    
    
    Can chaos empower the user experience? http://ow.ly/qV7Wj  #UX #game #design    
    
    
    Hi Uxers! Check it out! Build your own gamified user experience with Gamification Model Canvas! http://ow.ly/qV84Z     
    
    
    Getting Your Gamification On: Four Tips for Financial Services Companieshttp://ow.ly/qV8tZ    
    
    
    The Habits Of Successful New Web Professionals http://ow.ly/qV8xw     
    
    
    Check this project! They are mapping the 3D structure of neurons and over 80K people from 130 countries already do http://ow.ly/qV8Up     
    
    
    Check out "Barcelona - Gamification Model Canvas Workshop" http://gameonlab-barcelona.eventbrite.com/?aff=estw  vía @eventbrite    
    
    
    Five Principles for Accommodating User Needs In Developer-Led Projects http://ow.ly/qV8Ye  #UX    
    
    
    Designing a game that breaks friendships http://ow.ly/qV93i  #game #design    
    
    
    Learn and practice gamiﬁcation by designing your own game-based solutions with Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/qVawj     
    
    
    Design for Experience: Work Environment for Digital Practitioners http://ow.ly/r93h4  #UX    
    
    
    Educators! Check it out! A game-based classroom response system http://ow.ly/r93m4  #gamification    
    
    
    Game design experts explain the essential skills to keep players engaged http://ow.ly/r93bb  #gamification    
    
    
    Designing Without Words http://ow.ly/r940O  #game #design    
    
    
    Now you can integrate the game and business perspective with our free #gamification canvas! Check it out! http://ow.ly/r94bc     
    
    
    Want to bake in an engaged user experience? It’s a piece of cake http://ow.ly/r93oi  #UX    
    
    
    The 5 Hidden Superpowers of Balanced Creative Teams http://ow.ly/r93rS     
    
    
    What Is The Legal Status Of Virtual Goods? http://ow.ly/r93ur     
    
    
    Gamification Roundup: Google Glass App, Candy Campaigns, and Healthcare http://ow.ly/r945z     
    
    
    Gaming to Engage the Healthcare Consumer http://ow.ly/r93wT  #gamification #report    
    
    
    Integrating individual rewards with community engagement (future of retail) http://ow.ly/r93Cp     
    
    
    What Neuroscience Says About The Link Between Creativity And Madness http://ow.ly/r93GB     
    
    
    Talks from Gamification World Congress now available for everyone! Game On! http://ow.ly/rdNBV     
    
    
    In narrative games, self-expression doesn't mean 'empowerment' http://ow.ly/r93Jz  #game #design    
    
    
    How to Power Marketing Campaigns with Social Data http://ow.ly/r93M6     
    
    
    Screen play thoughts: A speculative look at trends in video game addiction http://ow.ly/r93OW     
    
    
    Game On! Lab Workshop en el Mobile World Centre de Barcelona! 10/12 @MW_Centre http://ow.ly/rh9fB  Game On!    
    
    
    "You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else" - Albert Einstein pic.twitter.com/ANV1Hbxz9M    
    
    
    Embracing Paradoxes and Narratives in Education http://ow.ly/r93Ru  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification User Types 2.0 by @daverage http://ow.ly/r93V3     
    
    
    Meaningful Choice in Games: Practical Guide & Case Studies http://ow.ly/r93XT  #game #design    
    
    
    Última oportunidad! Reserva tu sitio a precio early bird para el workshop de #gamification en Barcelona http://ow.ly/rgTyG  Game On!    
    
    
    Happy Half Year! http://gamificationmodelcanvas.com  #gamification pic.twitter.com/bDGxjSwsxY    
    
    
    Great article! The Psychology of Video Game Avatars http://ow.ly/rlFZC     
    
    
    4 effective strategies Candy Crush teaches us about Gamification for Corporate Training http://ow.ly/rlGlL     
    
    
    The best christmas gift for marketers, HR managers, innovators and educators this year: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rlGW3     
    
    
    This is not a game: Why #gamification is becoming a multi-billion dollar way to motivate people http://ow.ly/rmHB3     
    
    
    Candy Crush-style game helps scientists fight tree disease http://ow.ly/rmKPg  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification: 5 Cosas Serias que Aprendí Jugando al Angry Birds http://ow.ly/rmSbw     
    
    
    Emotional Monetization - Driving Revenues Through Emotion http://ow.ly/rmPV8  #game #design    
    
    
    Watch BitCoins transactions happen across the world http://ow.ly/rmPnL     
    
    
    Check it out! The ultimate gamification design kit: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rmSQX     
    
    
    The Secret to Implementing Serious Learning Games http://ow.ly/rmJJg     
    
    
    The Top 20 Companies with Employees That Have Gamification in Their LinkedIn Profile http://ow.ly/rmPB4     
    
    
    Play Nice: Building the Well-Behaved Game http://ow.ly/rmQ4k     
    
    
    The power of feedback mechanisms http://ow.ly/rmKct  #gamification    
    
    
    Gamification: Quests, Objectives, Goals and more by @daverage http://ow.ly/rmPJU     
    
    
    @daverage you’re the best!    
    
    
    Beyond the Buzz: Combining Big Data Analytics & Gamification in Recruiting & Hiring http://ow.ly/rmKzB     
    
    
    Levels of Abstraction in Game Design http://ow.ly/rmQsR     
    
    
    @David_Mullich thnx David! #FF back! Have a good weekend    
    
    
    Will gamification stay relevant? http://ow.ly/rA1Cd  #gamification    
    
    
    These 3 Trends will drive Enterprise Software Development in 2014 http://ow.ly/rA1Kk  #gamification    
    
    
    In The Hospital Of The Future, Big Data Is One Of Your Doctors http://ow.ly/rA1TM  #bigdata    
    
    
    Ouch! New link! Game On! In The Hospital of The Future, Big Data is One of Your Doctors http://bit.ly/1bjD19h     
    
    
    @extremezealand thnx! New link posted!    
    
    
    @mogarick thnx! link re-posted!    
    
    
    Gamification Model Canvas World Tour starts now! pic.twitter.com/TTNi0ZlZ9w    
    
    
    Thanks for the feedback! Some minor changes has been applied to Gamification Model Canvas! Check it out! http://ow.ly/rHfc3     
    
    
    Gamification Trends To Watch in 2014 http://ow.ly/rNiZN  #gamification    
    
    
    Three key rules of gamification of the workplace http://ow.ly/rNjp7     
    
    
    Five UX Lessons from Hollywood http://ow.ly/rNiqz  #UX    
    
    
    The Slow Gamification of K-12 Classrooms http://ow.ly/rNkm0     
    
    
    Check it out! The ultimate gamification design kit: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rmSQX     
    
    
    The best christmas gift for marketers, HR managers, innovators and educators this year: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rlGW3     
    
    
    How Social Learning and Feedback Ensures Successful Employee Training http://ow.ly/rNj2T     
    
    
    Trip Hawkins’ new game helps kids learn about their feelings http://ow.ly/rNjlt     
    
    
    Thematic Storytelling Through Menu Design http://ow.ly/rNjIQ     
    
    
    How Your Game Can Change the World http://ow.ly/rNjNV     
    
    
    Build your concept with Gamification Model Canvas, check it out! http://ow.ly/rNTRH     
    
    
    How Your Game Can Change the World (part 2) http://ow.ly/rNj4P     
    
    
    Learn and practice gamification by designing your own game-based solutions with Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/rNmw0     
    
    
    The Psychology Behind Information Dashboards http://ow.ly/rNisd  #UX    
    
    
    Why government health departments are spending millions on mobile gaming http://ow.ly/rNkHz     
    
    
    Who Needs Interactivity? http://ow.ly/rNjTf     
    
    
    Using the Gamification User Types in the Real World by @daverage http://ow.ly/rNj93     
    
    
    Will Rovio recapture its glory as Angry Birds Go! debuts on a global stage? http://ow.ly/rNjn8     
    
    
    Gartner Sticks to its Failing Gamification Prediction http://ow.ly/rNktk     
    
    
    Now you can download for free the most used tool: Gamification Model Canvas http://ow.ly/rNUBm  Game On!    
    
    
    4 Ways Gamification Can Help Your Business http://ow.ly/rNkBI     
    
    
    Using Gamification in Business for Customer Engagement http://ow.ly/rNkFn     
    
    
    The 5 trends that defined the game industry in 2013 http://ow.ly/rNjCL     
    
    
    Run your own #gamification workshop with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon to Europe. http://ow.ly/qV9Wf     
    
    
    Mechanics are the Message: Designing a Game for Change in 3 Months http://ow.ly/s0tQJ     
    
    
    The processes behind King's Candy Crush http://ow.ly/s0tMa  #game #design    
    
    
    Turning Customer Support Into a Game http://ow.ly/s0tWQ  #gamification    
    
    
    You Don't "Always Lose" in Tetris: The Real Nature of Single-Player Competition http://ow.ly/s0tL5  #game #design    
    
    
    Using Gamification in Business for Customer Engagement http://ow.ly/s0tYP     
    
    
    Play at Work: Increase Employee Engagement through Gamification http://ow.ly/s0u4P     
    
    
    Reserva tu sitio en México DF: Gamification Model Canvas Workshop 29/01. Gamification, Networking & Business http://ow.ly/s0uc9     
    
    
    Game Design Theory Applied: A Layered Rewards System http://ow.ly/s4lyw     
    
    
    50 Something Gaming Academics on Twitter http://ow.ly/s4lB3     
    
    
    2014 Forecast: Gamification and the Year Ahead in Banking http://ow.ly/s4lSK     
    
    
    Using Brainwriting For Rapid Idea Generation http://ow.ly/s4lHq     
    
    
    The Top UX Predictions for 2014 http://ow.ly/s4lKX     
    
    
    Who Goes to Work to Have Fun? It Depends On What You Mean By "Fun" http://ow.ly/s4lO9     
    
    
    Playing with Gamification: Employee and Consumer Perspectives http://ow.ly/s4lYT     
    
    
    Highlights from Neuroscience 2013 http://ow.ly/s4m35     
    
    
    @devegape @Humannova @MJohnsonLoyalty @delaossaandres @clubpaul @TheMediaBag @plandenegociosb @AbelFernndezCal #FF back ;)    
    
    
    Battleship: The Ultimate Chocolate Combat Game LOL pic.twitter.com/jI4ZB6liiH    
    
    
    @David_Mullich thanks David! Merry Xmas and gamified new year! =)    
    
    
    Check it out! The ultimate gamification design kit: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/s4n8X     
    
    
    Run your own #gamification workshop with Game On! Toolkit. Now available from Amazon to Europe. http://ow.ly/s4nJb     
    
    
    The Potential of Gamification for Student Recruitment http://ow.ly/s4mek     
    
    
    Messification: Why Games Should Be Designed to Be Games First http://ow.ly/s4m9f     
    
    
    Infographic: The Most Popular Toys Of The Past 50 Years http://ow.ly/s4mjo     
    
    
    How online gamers organize themselves and what organizations can learn from them http://ow.ly/s4mtJ     
    
    
    Merck turns to gamification in diabetes http://ow.ly/s4mJU     
    
    
    6 Exciting Gaming Trends to Watch in 2014 http://ow.ly/s4mAT     
    
    
    The Best Board Games of 2013 http://ow.ly/s4mGq     
    
    
    Happy New Year! Game On 2014!    
    
    
    Remember from now on we’re in 2014!    
    
    
    The Platform and the Player: exploring the (hi)stories of Elite http://ow.ly/scFx5     
    
    
    How Your Game Can Change the World http://ow.ly/scFzX     
    
    
    Psycology of Games: Fake Feels and Free Passes http://ow.ly/scFGL     
    
    
    Increased productivity, the real reason for introducing gamification http://ow.ly/scG4R     
    
    
    Gamification Comes to the Contact Center http://ow.ly/scFEb     
    
    
    Design Microsoft's Surface Into the Classroom Experience http://ow.ly/scFLP     
    
    
    Great compilation by @yukaichou: A Comprehensive List of 90+ Gamification Cases with ROI Stats http://ow.ly/scGru     
    
    
    29/01 México DF - Gamification Model Canvas Workshop http://www.eventbrite.com/e/entradas-mexico-df-gamification-model-canvas-workshop-9628042735?aff=estw … vía @eventbrite    
    
    
    Great article about Multiplayer Logistics http://ow.ly/scFRQ     
    
    
    J.J. Rosen: Gamification helps make learning, earning more fun http://ow.ly/scGwR     
    
    
    Is gamification an insult to our humanity? http://ow.ly/scFWQ     
    
    
    Three Retailers Using Gamification to Engage Employees http://ow.ly/scG27     
    
    
    Top Instructional Design Trends and Outlook for 2014 http://ow.ly/scG8N     
    
    
    Check it out! The ultimate gamification design kit: Game On! Toolkit http://ow.ly/sdxqc     
    
    
    Game Design Theory Applied: Endogenous Value http://ow.ly/scGgG     
    
    
    Shocking Grasps: An Archaeology of Electrotactile Game Mechanics http://ow.ly/scGdI     
    
    
    Become a game designer with Game On! Toolkit. Check it out! http://ow.ly/sdwpq     
    
    
    