Finally see mmm cupcake and can't have any.  #Awesome    
    
    
    Suburbans have huge gas tanks.    
    
    
    It starts #nolo #fb http://ow.ly/i/fFP3     
    
    
    My Jesus shirt just got the whole table free beignets.  #thanksjesus    
    
    
    Amazing breakfast @ Mother's #Nola    
    
    
    I drove my chevy to the levee but the levee was gone #Nola http://ow.ly/i/fL5w     
    
    
    NOLA Flea Market! (@ French Market) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw     
    
    
    Swinging chairs at margaritaville are awesome!!  http://ow.ly/i/fL9i     
    
    
    The best bartender in NO @ Margaritaville.  #Nola    
    
    
    @GoNOLA504 I had eggs and smoked sausage.   Mmmm good!    
    
    
    Wow, #WellsFargo just emailed me an ATM receipt +1 for #wells but @perkstreet is still will be my primary bank (when my deposit amt is up'd)    
    
    
    Seattle Bound! (@ George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH)) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw     
    
    
    iPad Web App being demo'd in Seattle at Microsoft GameFest.  #awesome    
    
    
    Jazz, alcohol, sushi, burgers, and kinect.  That's how #gamefest rolls.    
    
    
    "Don't have your mum hoovering [vacuuming] and end up having to defend the empire" #gamefest on activating the Kinect #fb    
    
    
    I just used #Shazam to discover In The Dark by Dev Feat. Flo Rida. http://shz.am/t53711858     
    
    
    Did Facebook pretty much copy G+?  #blasphemy #awesome    
    
    
    Spotify finally got the Dev - In the Dark - remix
http://open.spotify.com/local/Dev//In+The+Dark+%28Remix%29+feat.+50+Cent/220 …    
    
    
    Now for the Kanye Remix - Dev - In the Dark - http://open.spotify.com/local/DEV//In+the+dark%28remix%29%5bfeat.+Kanye+west%5d/221 …    
    
    
    Hey @monicaortiz, Facebook just reminded me that today would be 1 year engaged #win http://ow.ly/i/gIVz     
    
    
    @monicaortiz It was begging to be used    
    
    
    The lights went out on the orchestra and they kept playing.  #professional #hardcore    
    
    
    And for a second time! Someone forgot to pay Reliant    
    
    
    @eloy I'll take you up on that offer #stalking    
    
    
    @eloy yay! Another pandora business user.    
    
    
    "Sir, the reason for this stop is your speed. When I clocked you, your speed was 86 mph" - Officer outside of Austin #fb    
    
    
    Drink Specials all around houston (or other cities): http://ow.ly/6qI36    
    
    
    Spotify says I'm done listening to music for the month :( http://ow.ly/i/h63c     
    
    
    Hey @jman2k3, How'd you do this week? #FantasyFootball http://ow.ly/6sDza #fb    
    
    
    #UH is apparently on ABC news tonight #vanoutsidebuilding    
    
    
    Listen to T-Pain - 5 O\'clock (feat. Wiz Khalifa  Lily A... on The Hype Machine http://awe.sm/5T6w5     
    
    
    Require payment by mail, but refuses check. All options all say "No trial", but you ask if I want a trial.  Requires Notary. #modernizeplz    
    
    
    Hey @target, I'm going out on a limb and saying you lost data when you migrated to the new site. No one can find my wedding registry anymore    
    
    
    @eloy is it better than mint?    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 today is nearly over!    
    
    
    @spotify So I'm required to post what I'm listening to on my timeline in order to use Facebook integration now?    
    
    
    @monicaortiz Pro's and Con's list time! :D    
    
    
    @monicaortiz Very True.  I'll support you wherever you want to go :)    
    
    
    OLF bought us Pappa's BBQ for working hard.  #yum    
    
    
    USPS on lawndale was awesome today!!  She corrected my mistakes (filled it out too fast) and took me in after hours..  Smply Great service    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 who is this "we"    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 I wad afraid you were going to say that! J/k @MonicaOrtiz    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 I was thinking MooYah, but I could always do a stuffed crust @ pizzahut. Although I think you had something else in mind :)    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 win! Then its all up to my better half    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 Nice Sample, minus the no words part. :)    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 LIKE!    
    
    
    @kalebdf mmm, #tasty.  what's in the Captain Crunch?    
    
    
    I wish every morning in Houston was like this morning    
    
    
    I LOVE Helvetica Playing Cards: http://ow.ly/6Kx8H  Currently on sale @ Fab.com    
    
    
    How did I not know about "How to make it in America"?  Oh I don't have HBO.  #sadness    
    
    
    Work loves us  http://ow.ly/i/it2k     
    
    
    @MonicaOrtiz @Rebecca_88 I see a big sign saying http://barkitecturehouston.com/.  Check it out!    
    
    
    I just entered to win Dropbox Pro For Life FREE http://appsumo.com/~Tcim  via @appsumo    
    
    
    @eloy I'm genuinely sad :/    
    
    
    Excited about #schipulcon tomorrow!  (Thanks @eloy)    
    
    
    My Intel SSD on my MacBook Pro just started reporting SMART errors and fails to boot.  #fb    
    
    
    Matt & Dries on one stage #schipulcon #wordpress #drupal    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 I don't personally know if it is good, but there is a popular one in Rice Village    
    
    
    @babackpacker Side Note: I'm still jealous of your trip!  Enjoy! :)    
    
    
    It's been entirely too long, but inbox(0) again. :)    
    
    
    So @eloy knows how to put on makeup with an awkward amount of professionalism.  http://ow.ly/i/iOSh     
    
    
    @Jman2k3 you haven't found anyone to do it yet?    
    
    
    @glenbot Heh, just got it!    
    
    
    Got iOS 5 installed.  Makes my iPhone 4 sooooo much faster :)    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 *gasp*    
    
    
    @eloy @apoc5392 @heavymetalguru @jman2k3 wigglewigglewigglewigglewiggle HEY! (HT: @apoc5392)    
    
    
    Playing with pre-alpha Windows 8 tablets. Eat your heart out @philt5252 http://ow.ly/i/j7Tv  #fb    
    
    
    It's amazing how many Big Moe songs I grew up with. #979thebox    
    
    
    @trostmann What kind of mac?    
    
    
    @trostmann I approve!  Side note: I have one albeit 2 years old. #notbiased    
    
    
    @flykrystin That's something you don't hear everyday    
    
    
    50GB Free from http://Box.net  for use with iCloud http://ow.ly/6XGUB   (HT: @Phank) #awesome    
    
    
    @eloy @trostmann Strictly technically speaking, @trostmann speaks (types) the truth.    
    
    
    There are way too many awesome dogs at #barkitecture #houston right now.  I want!    
    
    
    The Find Friends app.  Giving every man a tracking anklet.  If you want to be a playa now, you have to get creative. #applehatesthegame    
    
    
    Rocking' the #behappyyoureloved bag I customized at their 1 year anniversary party last night. @Rebecca_88 http://ow.ly/i/jt4Z     
    
    
    OMG! Evernote Premium FREE FOR LIFE! I need to win this! :) http://appsumo.com/~BsSv  via @appsumo    
    
    
    Hey @rebecca_88,  Where is @behappyyoureloved? :)    
    
    
    My love (@monicaortiz) modeling for my new Camera+ app http://campl.us/ghxR     
    
    
    @eloy http://shitthatsirisays.tumblr.com  #awesome    
    
    
    @monicaortiz @eloy This is awesome for a home: http://ow.ly/786YI  #energysaver    
    
    
    I loved the random dance session to @sheandhim's new Christmas album with @MonicaOrtiz #love #favoritetimeoftheyear    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Paul! – at Avant Garden http://gowalla.com/stories/5bpMA     
    
    
    I'm in line for @everlane - Designer-quality goods under $100. Join today. http://www.everlane.com/i/r0n8v3     
    
    
    It's real ladies. @MonicaOrtiz just bought me a wedding band. #offthemarket    
    
    
    Abuelita chocolate cake from Ninfa's = #amazing    
    
    
    I like Google Reader's new Google+ -like design    
    
    
    Payment by saying "Put it on Will's Tab".  Amazing @square, simply amazing. http://ow.ly/7hkXh     
    
    
    @monicaortiz <3    
    
    
    @kalebdf That sucks man.  I hate there are people who think its OK to leave a car with a dent.    
    
    
    Hey, @monicaortiz, your daddy must have been a drug dealer.  Cause you're dope. #cataracts    
    
    
    Beautiful day in #houston.  Programming outside with #Chloe #thegoodlife    
    
    
    @bandnerd330 Like a boss    
    
    
    @karaet that looks delicious    
    
    
    .@perkstreet makes my international travel happy. #london #paris #honeymoon    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 we're in London!    
    
    
    Mind the Gap! http://campl.us/gREr     
    
    
    Wow @simplify looks very nice.  @perkstreet better watch out.  I can't wait to see the win for consumers with this friendly competition.    
    
    
    @bandnerd330 #like    
    
    
    @sprintcare I missed that small "notice" in my online bill. Now I have $500 in overages after you removed unlimited data from my "contract"    
    
    
    @sprintcare email sent!    
    
    
    @comcastcares If I buy my own SurfBoard modem, does Comcast still have to come out for setup? Or just phone activation. Note: New Customer    
    
    
    I just entered Win a Paid GitHub Account for Life (worth $8,000!!)! http://appsumoforlife.com/~O6US  via @appsumo    
    
    
    @comcastcares Signed up for service online, but you can't find my address.If my line/modem are fine, can I call to get setup without waiting    
    
    
    @comcastmichael Email sent! Pre-thanks for your help!    
    
    
    @Trostmann sorry I'm taken :(    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 Doctor Who Lenticular Animated Chess Set http://www.neatorama.com/2011/12/16/doctor-who-lenticular-animated-chess-set/ …    
    
    
    I'm praying to the TD gods for Mike Wallace to do his thing. #ff #fb    
    
    
    My Rdio free trial is up. It might just be better than Spotify.    
    
    
    Wow, these Beats by Dre are amazing. Thanks @monicaortiz #productivitywin    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 You might be interested in this: https://www.moviepass.com/?mlu=44390     
    
    
    @trostmann cornfields in Houston?    
    
    
    @trostmann I don't know of any.  Does @eloy?    
    
    
    @jman2k3 That's what you get for whipping up on everyone this year Champ. #FF    
    
    
    @eloy Hopefully this doesn't affect you @ATDMoney: Verizon Introduces "Convenience Fee" for Some Online, Phone Payments http://dthin.gs/sXECQV     
    
    
    @monicaortiz happy new years love!    
    
    
    "Fantasy. Trucks can't snowboard or do barrel rolls"  -Toyota Commercial #awesome #fineprint    
    
    
    If I had more money, I'd be a @fab buying fiend. #greatstuff    
    
    
    @eloy Perhaps you'd enjoy this: https://github.com/DanielRapp/twss.js …    
    
    
    Woop! Game starts at 12:30, not 11:30 like I thought.  So not late :)    
    
    
    @Trostmann I think TV coverage starts at noon    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 RT @CNBCWorld: Macy's Sues Martha Stewart for Breach of Contract http://bit.ly/wK2M9x     
    
    
    Next Spotify goal: obscure, anti-mainstream rap/hip-hop playlist    
    
    
    I'm pumped to watch the State of the Union.  What kind of person does that make me?    
    
    
    She wouldn't let me write my paper, so I set her up in front of an open window. #distractions http://ow.ly/i/qX7c     
    
    
    Congrats to the newlyweds.  #awesome #fb http://campl.us/hDai     
    
    
    Send someone a message letting them know you arrived safely by adding #mom to your @foursquare checkin: http://hashtagmom.com  #awesome    
    
    
    @rsotelo1 Agreed!    
    
    
    TedTalk: Positive Psychology  http://ow.ly/98BMV  #lovedit    
    
    
    @comcastcares I contacted chat support about voice outage. Reset my modem. Voice is still down and I can't access chat http://bit.ly/wRDsTk     
    
    
    @ComcastWill It says I can't DM you without you following me.    
    
    
    @ComcastWill Thanks for the help!    
    
    
    Playing with Windows 8 at work.  Microsoft says: people cant share.   http://ow.ly/i/uiH4     
    
    
    Just nabbed a free copy of Cassandre posters. Download it for free: http://cassannet.net     
    
    
    Why Ruby isn't Python - Solid talk by @wycats http://ow.ly/9OfSK     
    
    
    Thanks to all who helped me with the experiment a few months ago.  My 2nd publication is in the books! #fb    
    
    
    @Jman2k3 but I drink dr pepper.    
    
    
    Want! RT @designtaxi: #Recap - Yes, a box of 'Scrabble Typography' please. http://ow.ly/9QTUr     
    
    
    Wow, I just put myself in debt.  Oh right, also, I'm a home owner #fb    
    
    
    @kalebdf Thanks!  Just got internet (finally).    
    
    
    @eloy Thanks!    
    
    
    Wife's first lawn mowing experience.  http://ow.ly/i/zdPX  #proud #fb    
    
    
    @jman2k3 Like    
    
    
    Hello Austin (@ City of Austin, TX w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/JptT6l     
    
    
    @Simplify Any idea when I'll get an invite [holtkampw at gmail]?  I have Wells and they are.. well.. Wells Fargo.    
    
    
    Stylish shirts, blazers, accessories for guys all under $50 – I have 2 exclusive invites here: http://foak.co/hwnh/gfc2  via @FrankAndOak    
    
    
    @eloy I think invite is a relative word.  It was an auto share tweet.  You will get access after you share and two friends join.  #ponzilike    
    
    
    About to fire @Uverse.  Third outage in less than a month.  Oh, and they won't fix it today.  Have to wait until tomorrow afternoon.    
    
    
    @Simplify Any idea if I'm a spring or summer invitee? (holtkampw at gmail)    
    
    
    Dynamo!!!! (@ BBVA Compass Stadium w/ 26 others) http://4sq.com/ILwadf     
    
    
    We are officially Houston #Dynamo season ticket holders #fb    
    
    
    Looks like @MonicaOrtiz is already giving me grey hair! #whatwedoforlove    
    
    
    @eloy In other news: just got a sonos speaker. So far: highly recommend.    
    
    
    @Trostmann you don't consider that a successful attempt?    
    
    
    Wow, @AmericanExpress now has #hashtag based deals that you can load to your card.  Just sync'd up #awesome    
    
    
    I REALLY want Simple now #impatient -- Announcing the Simple iPhone App | Simple Blog https://simple.com/blog/Simple/announcing-the-simple-iphone-app/ … via @simplify    
    
    
    So, @comcast #blast.  First Impression: FAST.  I don't miss @uverse.    
    
    
    Congrats Laura! (@ William R. Johnson Coliseum w/ 11 others) http://4sq.com/M6M4yG     
    
    
    @simplify Any plans for savings accounts?  Also, I see someone else mentioning joint accounts.  When available, would the switch be easy?    
    
    
    @simplify 1. Awesome! 2. To clarify, I should apply for an invite for my wife? We can sync my account with hers (into a shared account)?    
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium for Portland Timbers vs. Houston (Houston, TX) w/ 106 others http://4sq.com/Ji0p5f     
    
    
    @apoc5392 FYIF    
    
    
    @trostmann Agreed    
    
    
    @trostmann The Freebirds tortilla is better than chipotle, however, the Chipotle Steak is much better than Freebirds #meatlover #carnivore    
    
    
    @Trostmann Ahhh see we just care about different things.  If I goto one of those spots it's always a steak burrito for me.    
    
    
    Thinking about rebuilding all of my Twitter lists. I'm finding that I get tons of noise in certain lists. Have any favored grouping methods?    
    
    
    Anyone making a go at the Facebook IPO?    
    
    
    Brewing up a surprise tomorrow #holtkamps    
    
    
    Can't wait for the festivities to begin #holtkamps    
    
    
    A quick preview of the #holtkamps http://ow.ly/i/DBci  #fb    
    
    
    Just saw a rabbit at the lake. #awesome    
    
    
    @simplify Soooo when you say summer.. do you mean june, july, or august??  #anxious #wantingtodumpwellsfargo    
    
    
    @trostmann I have you address now.  #identitytheft    
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium for Los Angeles vs. Houston (Houston, TX) w/ 56 others http://4sq.com/L2ZKHe     
    
    
    @trostmann Vampire Weekend does.    
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium (Houston, TX) w/ 24 others http://4sq.com/L1K2vz     
    
    
    Valencia #3 in La Liga looks good in practice #houstondynamo    
    
    
    Kallie's graduation from Pearland High (@ Reliant Stadium w/ 15 others) http://4sq.com/KyEJXr     
    
    
    I'm at Gristmill River Restaurant & Bar (Gruene, TX) http://4sq.com/K28TEC     
    
    
    I'm at BJ's Restaurant & Brewhouse (Webster, TX) w/ 7 others [pic]: http://4sq.com/KD7ZO8     
    
    
    @jman2k3 Yeah I saw that a month or so ago.  Pretty solid song.  Like it.    
    
    
    Great Read: McSweeney’s Internet Tendency: Prospectus for Silicon Valley’s Next Hot Tech IPO http://bit.ly/M8rOby  #humor    
    
    
    #PayWithATweet bariol, a new rounded font designed by atipo. download it for free: http://www.bariol.com/     
    
    
    @eloy association!    
    
    
    Date Night! (@ Churrascos) http://4sq.com/LC2wWa     
    
    
    I'm at Stadia Sports Grill (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/LEU8p1     
    
    
    @Simplify Ahhhh! Wells Fargo just hit me with a fee to have the account open.  Any chance that "Summer" is now?    
    
    
    Meebo is dead! #sadday RT @newsycombinator: Meebo discontinued: shutting down on July 11, 2012 http://j.mp/Nor877     
    
    
    Lunch in Wisconsin (@ Takara Japanese Restaurant) http://4sq.com/MpPawo     
    
    
    I'm at The Old Fashioned (Madison, WI) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/L3OehO     
    
    
    Games + Learning + Society (@ Memorial Union w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/LVSBuM     
    
    
    I'm at Ian's Pizza by the Slice (Madison, WI) http://4sq.com/LF6DjT     
    
    
    Bikini girls laying out in the grass in front of a parking lot.  Stay classy Madison.    
    
    
    Pre-Presentation http://campl.us/kacg     
    
    
    I'm at Dotty Dumpling's Dowry (Madison, WI) http://4sq.com/KAso7I     
    
    
    I'm at Jason's Deli (Webster, Texas) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/NCPCe2     
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium for Toronto FC vs. Houston (Houston, TX) w/ 166 others http://4sq.com/MzvAtR     
    
    
    @trostmann Where are you going?    
    
    
    Pho for my sick Monica (@ Pho 518) http://4sq.com/Mx328D     
    
    
    Inbox 0 feels oh so good.    
    
    
    Woah Woah Woah @spotify, why did I just get 10 more playlists that I never subscribed to?  Especially the lame ones.  #nobueno    
    
    
    @trostmann Tweeting and driving?  #slaponthewrist    
    
    
    @trostmann My tweet was a trap.  You just did it again to answer me.  #anotherslaponthewrist    
    
    
    @trostmann And now you're tweeting me without @ing my name!  #thirdslaponthewrist    
    
    
    Just finished getting my new work lappy setup.  Thanks #OLF  Not an i7, but an i5 will do.    
    
    
    Creativity time http://ow.ly/i/JIbV     
    
    
    Spain v Italy (@ Stadia Sports Grill) http://4sq.com/KUOIb3     
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium (Houston, TX) w/ 46 others http://4sq.com/N7qtVR     
    
    
    @Trostmann lame! Come over!!!    
    
    
    @Trostmann you bring red & blue paint and I'll give you $5 gas money! :P    
    
    
    @Trostmann Erika said I you bring red and blue texans paint the she'll pay you $20 as money    
    
    
    @Trostmann Ricky and Erika wants you specifically to do it.  Really bad :). That's $25 if you come over and paint :)    
    
    
    Ricky says home depot is open!    
    
    
    Sneak Peak - The Holtkamp's new website: http://bit.ly/PxcI72     
    
    
    @StealthMountain haha yes you are correct!    
    
    
    Fire up Google Reader, it's my FIRST blog.  I feel like I accomplished something and I just posted once: http://bit.ly/RQXmYr     
    
    
    Freshly grilled steak dinner! #cafedeholtkamp http://ow.ly/i/LPtB     
    
    
    I'm at Buca di Beppo (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/M4vGvT     
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium for Kansas City vs. Houston (Houston, TX) w/ 83 others http://4sq.com/Oo1TRp     
    
    
    Sparrow acquired by Google.  Does this mean no more Sparrow hottness? #mixedemotions    
    
    
    Rocking the @pearlandcoffee this morning  http://ow.ly/i/MSCA  #tasty    
    
    
    @eloy Going EC2?    
    
    
    Well @comcastcares never came to bury my cable line after several months, so I did it myself.  Finished it up tonight.  #lame    
    
    
    @Simplify The previous quote for me was summer and it's almost over.  I'm like a kid staring through a candy store window.  Any news?    
    
    
    @simplify That was quick! Just got the invitation notice. To Confirm: There will be no way for my wife to join my account just yet? #excited    
    
    
    @simplify Is there any way to get her an account so I can transfer funds to her? We wouldn't be able to use Simple full-time without 2 cards    
    
    
    @simplify As a side note, she registered a few months ago (monicaortiz7[at]gmail).  I assume she'd be a late fall invite?    
    
    
    @simplify Thanks for all the help!  I just contacted support.    
    
    
    @trostmann Once in SD: skype attendance to Guy's Night?    
    
    
    @trostmann I'm not sure how you can play pinball remotely though.  I'm looking forward to solving that challenge :)    
    
    
    @kalebdf #like!!  (Congrats on giving presentations by the way.  That's awesome.    
    
    
    Help bring amazing internet to Houston.  Pre-register now: http://fiber.google.com     
    
    
    Season ticket holder event.  Free Budweiser, free food, free shirt. #Awesome (@ BBVA Compass Stadium) http://4sq.com/MosDyI     
    
    
    I'm at Brio Tuscan Grille (Houston, Texas) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/LWT1hH     
    
    
    Bachata! (@ Flora & Muse) http://4sq.com/MRmNqB     
    
    
    @mattgillooly @simplify It has been since last Tuesday for me.  #patientlywaiting    
    
    
    I'm at Which Wich (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/NSVxc9     
    
    
    I'm at Tutti Frutti (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/Qu5l0u     
    
    
    Pre-Dynamo Restaurant Week Dining. (@ Hearsay Gastro Lounge) http://4sq.com/OGjBOn     
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium for New York Red Bulls vs. Houston (Houston, TX) w/ 70 others http://4sq.com/OGqVJP     
    
    
    #1 in the East!  Dale @houstondynamo!  I still can't believe I can't get a @calencarr3 jersey online.  I guess I need to custom order it #fb    
    
    
    After an amazing 5 1/2 hour game of Catan, I came out victorious over frienenemies like @MonicaOrtiz and Switzerland (@Rebecca_88) #fb    
    
    
    I'm at RA Sushi (Houston, TX) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/PDVbDw     
    
    
    @BAbackpacker Erika says hi.  We're celebrating her new job/car with sushi!    
    
    
    My first @BHYLCrafts purchase #excited http://instagr.am/p/OM2ePsSS2p/     
    
    
    Cooper excited to go see my parents dogs http://instagr.am/p/OO_jddSS-c/     
    
    
    New Blog Post | Design Challenge: @FrontPoint & @AlarmDotCom iPhone App Refresh http://bit.ly/MR8u9E     
    
    
    @frontpoint Thanks for being #awesome. Now we need @AlarmDotCom to get you guys a better looking app (it is functionally awesome already)    
    
    
    Dinner of champions #steak http://instagr.am/p/OU0HqmyS6U/     
    
    
    @apoc5392 I won a tasty steak dinner.    
    
    
    @apoc5392 *whew*  I was worried about that one :)    
    
    
    @trostmann Koopa Troopa = Win    
    
    
    @garyvee Congrats!    
    
    
    Cathy's Birthday! (@ Miyako Sushi) http://4sq.com/PuzckD     
    
    
    I'm at Gloria's Restaurant (Houston, TX) w/ 6 others http://4sq.com/R80wIk     
    
    
    Roller coaster ride for Beto's birthday (@ Boardwalk Bullet) http://4sq.com/P66EgE     
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium (Houston, TX) w/ 84 others http://4sq.com/NR0qlt     
    
    
    @frontpoint Thanks!  I spent roughly an hour a day for a week.  That created 3-4 other design variations until I arrived at the one you see.    
    
    
    Drive by shootings in Mars really kill the property value http://ow.ly/d5sl0  #curiosity    
    
    
    @trostmann LoL?  What is this game the cool kids play?    
    
    
    @trostmann Ah, Yes! My brother plays that.  He hasn't converted me yet.    
    
    
    @frontpoint I made 3-4 iPhone apps while still in graduate school, but since graduation most of my client work has been web-based.    
    
    
    @frontpoint That said, if you're looking to revamp your app I'd be interested.  I've only been focused on the web due to client interest.    
    
    
    @frontpoint mmmm interesting.  I'll check it out!  Thanks!    
    
    
    @trostmann That was on purpose just so you can tweet that word. Admit it!    
    
    
    @trostmann I just teared up a bit    
    
    
    I'm at The Drink Station (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/RARwxQ     
    
    
    @frontpoint I'm definitely interested.  I was going to take this weekend to work on a resume.  My current one is #old and way too #formal    
    
    
    @trostmann So did you call yet?    
    
    
    @kalebdf Sweet find!    
    
    
    Rain rain go away.  Come back at noon when I'm done! (@ Brock Park Golf Course) http://4sq.com/U1hgB6     
    
    
    I'm at Pearwood Skate Center (Pearland, Texas) http://4sq.com/SBDwBy     
    
    
    I'm at Cracker Barrel (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/PQEhpo     
    
    
    @kalebdf I recently started playing around with emberjs.  Did you enjoy the session?    
    
    
    Note to self: @simplify minimalist wallet and my washing machine are not friends #mistake #forgottoremovefrompants    
    
    
    @eloy My current bag is a @moopshop and I love it. http://ow.ly/dgyKA     
    
    
    @trostmann Beer/Schmirnoff pong was awesome.  We should do that again before you leave for Cali    
    
    
    @trostmann @eloy make it happen!    
    
    
    Free Font! I just downloaded Citizen Slab! Check it out! #citizenslab http://bit.ly/Tz5vl1     
    
    
    @kevinrose What about an iPhone/Android app for an HTML5 app store?  An completely alternative app store for Google Play/App Store.    
    
    
    @themariam Amazing how deceptive politicians can be. #morningcommutenpr    
    
    
    @trostmann For the record, I support the California epic journey.  And it is not ONLY because I want an excuse to visit :)    
    
    
    I'm at Gringo's Mexican Kitchen (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/ODi3rp     
    
    
    I'm at Antica Osteria (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/Q8VhaJ     
    
    
    I'm at Chama Gaúcha Brazilian Steakhouse (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/NEyzZV     
    
    
    I'm at Brady's Landing (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/N7vuQu     
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium for Real Salt Lake Real Salt Lake vs Houston Dynamo (Houston, TX) w/ 69 others http://4sq.com/OejNc8     
    
    
    @eloy Phil and I have this theory that Google uses your phone microphone to monitor conversations for keywords to serve ads #conspiracy    
    
    
    Probably the best website I've seen that does event ticket sales: http://seatgeek.com/  #awesome #ui #love    
    
    
    Kanye West, Big Sean & Jay Z - Clique (Prod. Hit Boy) on @hypem http://awe.sm/g4l3V  #inspiration #worknight    
    
    
    Trimming a palm tree sometimes means angering a wasp family.  Wasps 3 - 0 Will.  On a related note: my face hurts. #yardworkdangers    
    
    
    @eloy you'll see me tomorrow.  Besides I'd much rather see a video in slow-motion.  Hmmm, must invest in backyard cameras.    
    
    
    I'm at West Elm (Houston, TX) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/U2fbml     
    
    
    I'm at Restoration Hardware Houston Gallery (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/RL2MFN     
    
    
    Finished off my first propane tank on the grill today.  Apparently a tank lasts me 3 months of grilling satisfaction    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 but customer parking is like 10 spaces... #joy    
    
    
    @bandnerd330 #lame pinterest/twitter hack :)    
    
    
    Hey @42Floors help me find an office in Houston, TX! http://42floors.com     
    
    
    @frontpoint Any word on the interaction designer #job?    
    
    
    @frontpoint Hmm, I sent it to jobs@frontpointsecurity on the 27th. That works out for me though(forgot to add 1 thing). I'll resend tonight!    
    
    
    @frontpoint Sent! :)    
    
    
    @eloy Apple announced iCloud Tabs for Safari syncing to mobile devices #thoughtofyou    
    
    
    @eloy I'll probably stay with chrome anyways.  I like the tabs better    
    
    
    I can't wait for the @railsrumble!  Any app ideas anyone?    
    
    
    @ugmonk Very #Microsoft metro of them (aside from that terrible iPad photo)    
    
    
    @trostmann If it is 7 letters, you can follow it up with an exclamation point    
    
    
    @trostmann Hahah! Preview:  Melissa:(    
    
    
    @Algaenic Haven't seen you in forever.  What's new man?    
    
    
    JD Power gave me a dollar to review the Mini Cooper http://instagr.am/p/Ph7hpvyS2E/     
    
    
    @trostmann Agreed!    
    
    
    @trostmann as it should.  Apparently it isn't a real scentsy thing: http://ow.ly/dIcjQ  but it does exist as a candle: http://ow.ly/dIcm4     
    
    
    "Thank you for placing your order with AT&T.  Your iPhone 5 will be delivered on 9/21/12." #winning #fb    
    
    
    I'm at The Original Ninfa's on Navigation (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/PjP2j1     
    
    
    An hour of traffic on 288 and counting.  Must have been a bad one    
    
    
    It was a poor cow hit by car taking up all but one lane.  #sadrandomcowinthebigcity    
    
    
    @eloy Rethinking the debit card only route?    
    
    
    @eloy No I mean, you personally.  Are you still considering that option?  #livingvicariously    
    
    
    According to Sirius, Psy is a hit! #gangnamstyle http://instagr.am/p/PvMO3bSS3r/     
    
    
    It's Michelada Wednesday! (@ Buffalo Wild Wings) http://4sq.com/PIAeZO     
    
    
    Concacaf! (@ BBVA Compass Stadium w/ 69 others) http://4sq.com/RF8dT4     
    
    
    @eloy RT: @mashable 'Gangnam Style' Sets a Guinness World Record http://on.mash.to/PGKpj4     
    
    
    Just informed that my iPhone 5 (pre-ordered on the 15th) will even be shipped until the 4th.  Should have waited in line #regret    
    
    
    I just downloaded the new signage typeface Wayfinding Sans (by @FontsDotInfo). You can get a free copy here:  http://j.mp/MSIxj5     
    
    
    @trostmann Good Luck sir, have a blast in SD.    
    
    
    @heavymetalguru Congrats!    
    
    
    Brother Ali on NPR? #win    
    
    
    @trostmann Weather nice?    
    
    
    Traffic officer at every intersection downtown.  All lights are working too.  #odd    
    
    
    @mattgillooly @cmeik OoOo, how can I get a copy of those slides?  I've been wanting to give #emberjs a solid go    
    
    
    New Blog Post: Gomez Custom Woodwork http://buff.ly/QoM9j7     
    
    
    I just realized finally have to get rid of my iPhone 3G's armband (iPhone 4 actually fit) #iphone5woes    
    
    
    Any recommendations on an #iPhone5 case?  Bonus points for minimalism    
    
    
    iPhone 5 Status: Speakerphone..Great!  Ring Volume..Great! Headphones..Great!  Handset Volume during call.. muffled/underwater? #fail #fb    
    
    
    @eloy That's actually a true statement: I left the clear plastic protection on the front of the device and that muddled the sound. #fail    
    
    
    @eloy Where's the clone fit? It's the hardest part for me to draw when I explain git to other devs #cloneislikeapullbutnotreally #confusion    
    
    
        
    
    
    @eloy How was Sams?    
    
    
    @trostmann #jealous  Its raining here.    
    
    
    Dynamo game is too wet.  Watching it here instead Monica (@ Buffalo Wild Wings) http://4sq.com/QdgWgZ     
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagr.am/p/QLg4gbySy6/     
    
    
    I'm at Taps House Of Beer w/ @eloy http://4sq.com/QBIeQ3     
    
    
    Why cant Houston always feel this way #weather #love    
    
    
    @trostmann Less tweets means Houston is more interesting. #win    
    
    
    @trostmann I was just hoping there wasn't as much to do/talk about. Who needs perfect weather, rolling hills, and windy beaches. #overrated    
    
    
    @trostmann Now you're just showing off    
    
    
    @Monicaortiz7's phones: new vs old http://instagr.am/p/QTBq40yS7H/     
    
    
    Steak Night + Date Night. Later: politics. #love #win http://instagr.am/p/QVxvg4yS25/     
    
    
    Romney vs Obama, Round 1  #fight    
    
    
    Votizen is pretty awesome: http://live.votizen.com/  #politics    
    
    
    Experiment: cupcake-tin muffalatos #foodie http://instagr.am/p/QYY-V4yS83/     
    
    
    Me: "Have a good weekend" Coworker: "I will. Me, Jack Daniels, and my computer screen"    
    
    
    https://diy.org  is pretty awesome for people with kids #wishitwasaroundwheniwasgrowingup    
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium (Houston, TX) w/ 77 others http://4sq.com/OKFbqc     
    
    
    I'm at The Grove w/ @monicaortiz http://4sq.com/Q6yxr2     
    
    
    Cooper is ready for Monday Night Football #mnf #texans http://instagr.am/p/QiQk1pSSzg/     
    
    
    OH: You can't try to throw it over my head -JJ Watt    
    
    
    Cooper got a much need haircut.  Now he's extra spunky. http://instagr.am/p/Qk_BjHSS-i/     
    
    
    An entire owl aisle. She's in heaven http://instagr.am/p/QlWK--SSxi/     
    
    
    @trostmann I'm sorry but Green Bay will lose to the Texans.  #realtalk    
    
    
    @trostmann Still enjoying Cali?    
    
    
    OH: Their UI was horrible.  Worse than Comic Sans.  It looked worse than a dead dog in a gutter.    
    
    
    Have a friend in a startup competition looking to make store sales more convenient. Help out by liking his video: http://ow.ly/enp6w  #SLGT    
    
    
    The @RailsRumble starts tomorrow, wish us luck!  #excited #anxious #pumped    
    
    
    Heh.  Just realized @TexasSEO stole my alpha logo design for @VosslerPlumber.  #lessonlearned    
    
    
    @eloy 3 strong (Phil/Sara).    
    
    
    @eloy 48 hours and 4 (I think)    
    
    
    @eloy 7PM tomorrow and I expect nothing less!    
    
    
    Date night (@ Emma's Grill w/ @monicaortiz) http://4sq.com/Ta74U6     
    
    
    Defining sprints and whiteboarding with   12 minutes before kickoff http://ow.ly/i/11fpv  #railsrumble    
    
    
    2 hour nap complete.  Back to the grind #railsrumble    
    
    
    Small #railsrumble break for wife time Monica (@ SmashBurger w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/Qbf5ra     
    
    
    It's that time.  Don Omar, Tego Calderon, Shakira.  #spanishmix #railsrumble    
    
    
    @ie_cortex That's how I feel!  #daunting    
    
    
    @ie_cortex Ha! So much left.  The rest of my team is on a power nap.  How are things over there?    
    
    
    Hootsuite just doesn't do it for me anymore, and Tweetdeck isn't much better.  Any suggestions on a cross-platform twitter tool?    
    
    
    @laura_beth9 Tweetbot for iPhone or Mac? I've heard really good things about them but I enjoy seeing multiple lists at once    
    
    
    @laura_beth9 @PhanK Haha, yes but that is definitely non-intuitive.  Still, I use my desktop at work and like the Hootsuite-ish list layout    
    
    
    The Rails Rumble is over!  We had a blast and learned a ton for next year.  http://idkboundaries.com/blog/2012/10/14/rafflin-final-code-freeze/ … #railsrumble    
    
    
    I'm at Spirit Halloween w/ @monicaortiz http://4sq.com/WpBd8q     
    
    
    @phank Do you have a mac?  Being a tapbots fan, I'm curious about your opinion on Tweetbot for Mac being worth $20.    
    
    
    Just got an invite to OST.  Minimal/Epic Web-based twitter/instagram/social client.  https://www.useost.com     
    
    
    Wife just bought a 2nd Sonos unit.  Its pretty epic how they interact together.  #love #fb    
    
    
    @Trostmann So that means you got a job?    
    
    
    Just reorganized my twitter lists.  Should finally have a better breakdown of followers by interests.    
    
    
    @Trostmann 3rd one on the right    
    
    
    Why watch the debate when you have twitter?  You get quotes and biased analysis pretty much just like the news.    
    
    
    @eloy No partaking in the annual Schipul zombie pics?    
    
    
    Harris county closes at 4:30pm (Brazoria at 5pm.  Since my registration didn't get updated (thanks TexasOnline), I must wait until tomorrow    
    
    
    Concacaf! Dale Dynamo!, Monica (@ BBVA Compass Stadium w/ 66 others) http://4sq.com/XbFmLP     
    
    
    I'm at Cork Soakers (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/RjgjTu     
    
    
    Dynamo move on to the quarterfinals.  It took 8 yellows and 1 red to get there. Rough game. Terrible ref. #fb    
    
    
    I voted, did you? (@ Hiram Clark) http://4sq.com/UDRlTc     
    
    
    Html5 Doodle Jump is killing my productivity: http://cssdeck.com/labs/html5-doodle-jump/8 …    
    
    
    Weekend Prep. Here's looking at you @eloy http://instagr.am/p/RQpgM9SS80/     
    
    
    Tasty... http://instagr.am/p/RTJmOnyS9z/     
    
    
    Party Prep http://instagr.am/p/RTQVPeSS1U/     
    
    
    First shot of the night http://instagr.am/p/RTkQ8CyS6-/     
    
    
    @MonicaOrtiz, I love you.  That is all. Good night #love    
    
    
    2012 MLS Cup Playoffs http://buff.ly/Rjso9t     
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 may I have some change?    
    
    
    Date Night! http://instagr.am/p/Rdj6-7yS4W/     
    
    
    Date Night! http://instagr.am/p/RdkDwryS4j/     
    
    
    @Trostmann did she?    
    
    
    @Trostmann lame… next Thursday    
    
    
    My old hangout.  Rebecca's getting an award! With Monica, @rebecca_88 (@ University of Houston-Downtown) http://4sq.com/Yy71Xf     
    
    
    Waiting for the Kappa Delta Pi Honor Society Ceremony to start http://instagr.am/p/Ri3OqZyS-H/     
    
    
    Rebecca getting the invocation certificate! http://instagr.am/p/Ri9s3HSS01/     
    
    
    @eloy Dangit! I vow to one day go to Ted and SXSW    
    
    
    Is it just me or is OSX's integration with HP printers getting worse and worse?    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker must have been one epic night!    
    
    
    Dynamo Slams for playoffs with Monica (@ Denny's) http://4sq.com/R57TQ2     
    
    
    Playoffs!!!! With Monica (@ BBVA Compass Stadium for Kansas City Sporting vs Houston Dynamo w/ @monicaortiz) http://4sq.com/U2uxXp     
    
    
    @BAbackpacker Great!  Having a great time with the wife and new house.  Dynamo are in the playoffs, so we’re pumped for that too    
    
    
    Hmm.. Thanks for the odd tweet random hack.  Password changed, reviewing app access.  Thanks for the heads up @eloy!    
    
    
    Voting Machine Fraud already? http://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/12q6wu/2012_voting_machine_altering_votes/c6x8sbi … #lameiftrue    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker just got your postcard! Thanks, you rock!    
    
    
    with Monica (@ Chipotle Mexican Grill w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/Um4NLQ     
    
    
    Company Lunch (@ Lupe Tortilla Mexican Restaurant) http://4sq.com/TaaUi4     
    
    
    Date Night with Daniel Craig and Bond Girls. Fun for the whole family with Monica (@ Cinemark for Skyfall) http://4sq.com/SVVAb0     
    
    
    New place. $2 margaritas are a good start. With Monica (@ Bogie's Pub & Grill) http://4sq.com/RqtBOw     
    
    
    Playoffs! (With Monica) (@ BBVA Compass Stadium for DC United vs Houston Dynamo w/ 110 others) http://4sq.com/WV3EML     
    
    
    Martha Stewart's Dark Chocolate Hot Cocoa recipe is simply amazing.  Eat your heart out @Rebecca_88! http://instagr.am/p/R_dSXUyS4d/     
    
    
    with Monica (@ Benjy's) http://4sq.com/ZwqsB6     
    
    
    HSA social (with Monica) (@ Los Cucos Mexican Cafe) http://4sq.com/RZUmef     
    
    
    Growing One's Consulting Business (via @Pocket) #longreads http://pocket.co/shs5Q     
    
    
    Ack! Country.   Kara's birthday is worth it. (@ Whiskey River) http://4sq.com/TUvAs6     
    
    
    Chris & Lindsey Wedding! (With Monica) (@ Lake Raven Lodge) http://4sq.com/TmQ2Wo     
    
    
    @Trostmann dinner?    
    
    
    Batch: 300 Icons for Web and User Interface Design by @adamwhitcroft: http://adamwhitcroft.com/batch/     
    
    
    "I'll wear your granddad's clothes.  I'll look incredible" - Macklemore    
    
    
    Christmas tree maybe? (@ Houston Garden Centers) http://4sq.com/TmXXkp     
    
    
    I want to be @Superhuman. Anyone have an invite? http://superhuman.io     
    
    
    @HOUZElabs what is the square foot range of your awesome houses?    
    
    
    Dale dynamo! Monica (@ Buffalo Wild Wings) http://4sq.com/TA22lq     
    
    
    @eloy Spotify vs Rdio: http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/battle-of-the-brands-which-music-service-earns-your-monthly-allowance/#p3n …    
    
    
    @eloy Yep! Desktop: Spotify, Features: Spotify, Mobile: Rdio, Look/Feel: Rdio    
    
    
    @eloy I wish they had a new UI guy    
    
    
    I want to see the jOBS movie.  Hint Hint @MonicaOrtiz (http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/12/ashton-kutcher-as-steve-jobs-premieres-jan-27-at-sundance/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+arstechnica%2Findex+%28Ars+Technica+-+All+content%29 …)    
    
    
    @eloy @MonicaOrtiz agreed but the facial similarities are fairly spot on.  #impressed    
    
    
    @eloy @MonicaOrtiz I’m still in. #fanboy    
    
    
    I thought my name would be bigger/more important looking. #disseration http://instagr.am/p/S36-47SS-W/     
    
    
    DecoNeue Light is a gorgeous #freefont designed by @jonatanxavier. Check it out: http://bit.ly/GGhHej     
    
    
    bariol, a new rounded font designed by atipo. download it for free: http://www.bariol.com/     
    
    
    bariol, now italics versions!! designed by atipo. download regular italic for free:  http://www.bariol.com/     
    
    
    #PayWithATweet rocks my twitter feed when I download fonts    
    
    
    View from on my roof #christmaslights http://instagr.am/p/S9N-U2yS1d/     
    
    
    @monicaortiz RT @hnycombinator: How to Hack Chipotle http://flip.it/BKSRN     
    
    
    with Monica (@ Berryhill Baja Grill) http://4sq.com/TSWq5U     
    
    
    I'm at Lights In The Heights (Houston, TX) w/ 52 others http://4sq.com/TT2FGR     
    
    
    @eloy like!    
    
    
    @eloy Oh yes, I’ve had it since before it was on the App Store. Thanks for the heads up! #goodstuff    
    
    
    @eloy Depends on what you've heard.  My absolute latest: http://www.useost.com , http://thefancy.com     
    
    
    @eloy Also, just found out you can link your AMEX card to your amazon account.  Just bought things on points.  #epicwin    
    
    
    @eloy I have Erika, @rickg0413 & @monicaortiz using it.  Its like pinterest, but.. different.    
    
    
    @eloy she is? I’m not following her. Handle please!    
    
    
    @Landsmanuvqbqmw Not nice.    
    
    
    @eloy ha! I’m still impressed he has a twitter acct but no Facebook cc: @rickg0413    
    
    
    @monicaortiz Check this out: http://www.guardian.co.uk/music/2012/dec/12/paul-mccartney-kurt-cobain-nirvana …    
    
    
    My cat hates the rain http://instagr.am/p/TTin-gSSyu/     
    
    
    When mommy isn't home, daddy is plain boring to the kids. http://instagr.am/p/TXEEWgSS5p/     
    
    
    @Trostmann Welcome home    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 LIKE!    
    
    
    Impromptu road trip with @MonicaOrtiz  begins!    
    
    
    Roadtrip through the countryside pic.twitter.com/E2dUYNSS    
    
    
    Spontaneous road trip with Monica (@ San Marcos, TX) http://4sq.com/YyrRIQ     
    
    
    I don't always eat Mexican, but when I do I drive to Austin for Guero's (w/ Monica) (@ Guero's w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/Tehmqt     
    
    
    Baby bucees  w/ Monica (@ Buc-ees) http://4sq.com/TgssKn     
    
    
    I'm at Spring Creek BBQ (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/Vemhbx     
    
    
    Waiting on Houston’s Finest for an hour now.  I wish they had an ETA service #impatient #fb    
    
    
    @Trostmann guy reversed for two blocks into my car.  Then drove off.  Got his plate though.    
    
    
    @kalebdf thanks! You too man.  I’m just happy it was parked and I wasn’t in it    
    
    
    @eloy @Trostmann at my in-laws    
    
    
    It has now been 3 hours.  Talked to a HPD SGT on the phone.  They filed a report for our address but for a different case.  #stillwaiting    
    
    
    I wish I was home with family instead of waiting to the police to do their job #hpd #fail    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker we’re ok!  Some idiot reversed into our car parked on the road and drove off.  Got his plate number so we’re ok :)    
    
    
    Just got some Vietnam air mail from @BAbackpacker!!  #excited    
    
    
    I'm at Dolce Vita Pizzeria & Enoteca (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/TvjB7A     
    
    
    @OnDaMenu currently eating the calzone and it is great!    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker yes sir!  Thanks for thinking about us!    
    
    
    with Monica, @rebecca_88 (@ Firehouse Subs) http://4sq.com/X8lrzR     
    
    
    I'm at Cracker Barrel (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/WfYd4M     
    
    
    with Monica (@ Barnaby's Cafe) http://4sq.com/10ORhCT     
    
    
    MinuteClinic’s (CVS) data entry touchscreen is intuitive, responsive, and faster than paper for data entry #doingitright    
    
    
    @civisisus bottle of sanitizer is right next to the screen    
    
    
    Love this place.  Paid with square (with Monica) (@ Pearland Coffee Roasters) [pic]: http://4sq.com/134QaOR     
    
    
    First time with Southwest (@ William P Hobby Airport (HOU) w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/Z6XBjI     
    
    
    I'm at Avant Garden (Houston, TX) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/10uVY4Q     
    
    
    .@MonicaOrtiz is my little craftinista. pic.twitter.com/hXfiX4na    
    
    
    with Monica (@ Hobbit Cafe w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/WwHqfa     
    
    
    I'm at Emma's Grill (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/W1ez5M     
    
    
    I'm at Emma's Grill (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/V62vy7     
    
    
    I'm at Vic & Anthony's Steakhouse (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/WEhG2Z     
    
    
    @JohnathanKuskos my favorite language.  Hope you enjoy it!    
    
    
    Enjoying Netflix’s House of Cards. If you dig politics and suspenseful drama, get a Netflix account and watch #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Post Oak Grill - Downtown (Houston, Texas) http://4sq.com/XU1qHo     
    
    
    I'm at Bombay Pizza Co. (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/X4zioD     
    
    
    I'm at Center Court Pizza & Brew (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/12zZEmB     
    
    
    @kalebdf congrats! That’s awesome!    
    
    
    Used passbook for the first time with Monica (@ Cinemark for Side Effects) http://4sq.com/XmI1Tl     
    
    
    with Monica, Erika (@ Emma's Grill) http://4sq.com/12EpaHt     
    
    
    Who’ hosting a State of the union party?  Here’s look at you @eloy!    
    
    
    @eloy for sure! I’m no grandma.  #scotch #sotu    
    
    
    Tim Cook on #SOTU. #fanboy    
    
    
    @Trostmann looks like fun #epic    
    
    
    @eloy free I really need to build up a portfolio!    
    
    
    @eloy AMEX now supports twitter purchases. #win    
    
    
    @eloy Yep! They can’t lose.    
    
    
    I'm at Spring Creek BBQ (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/VceJc0     
    
    
    with Monica (@ Rosarios Mexican Cafe Y Cantina) http://4sq.com/12M5SeV     
    
    
    .@sheratonhotels I booked, got charged a day later. Now that I’m here, you say you never charged me and have to recharge #ValentinesFail    
    
    
    @sheratonhotels thanks for the quick response.  I just finished sending the email.    
    
    
    Lovely day http://vine.co/v/brtzp3ZmmZZ     
    
    
    Lovely day http://vine.co/v/brtaMh2rzgX     
    
    
    Day 1: loving @mailbox pic.twitter.com/Sj1YY2S9    
    
    
    @mailbox I know you're busy with this little thing called a launch and all, but Google Chrome Integration plz! #featurerequest #awesomeapp    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker like!    
    
    
    9 days left of Macy’s in downtown Houston.  Everything is 70-80% off.    
    
    
    Dale dale dale dynamo! #gameday #fb    
    
    
    @eloy wow. Just wow.    
    
    
    Fighting for the best position #sunbathing pic.twitter.com/LQ8Gt2NVaX    
    
    
    with @monicaortiz (at @bbvacompassstdm for DC United vs Houston Dynamo w/ 65 others) http://4sq.com/15Zwa1r     
    
    
    .@thetontons sang the national anthem! #supportlocalartists #fb    
    
    
    First win of the season and my first new jersey since the inaugural season.  #houstondynamo #fb    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker yes sir!  What’s up?    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker hmm bring it and we’ll see what we can do!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm at @bbvacompassstdm for Houston Dynamo vs. Santos Laguna (Houston, TX) w/ 100 others http://4sq.com/W3IERL     
    
    
    with Monica (@ Baby Barnaby's) http://4sq.com/15E7eLP     
    
    
    Macy’s in downtown Houston is crazy!!    
    
    
    Note: @MarbleSlab doesn’t take @AmericanExpress.  #shame    
    
    
    Not going to lie, just started giving @spotify's radio a chance.  I thought it was a gimmick.  Nope, its legit.  #impressed    
    
    
    The @HoustonDynamo lose to @ClubSantosLagun.  Sad day.  #concacaf #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Himalaya Restaurant (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/Xd9lRj     
    
    
    Good times http://vine.co/v/bdLQ9nB1t3T     
    
    
    The Holtkamps will be on the fan wall at BBVA Compass (@HoustonDynamo) stadium.  How epic is that!! #seasonticketholder #perk    
    
    
    @LenKendall sweet! Congrats on the good press!    
    
    
    Proud if @MonicaOrtiz for being in a 5K today! #colorrun    
    
    
    Going to bed at 9pm.  #grandpa    
    
    
    Limbo! https://vine.co/v/bIb357Qx2BT     
    
    
    Coming home late has its advantages.just discovered TED hour on NPR #impressed    
    
    
    @JohnathanKuskos TED by itself is awesome, but it seems NPR brings in extra commentary to go with the speech.    
    
    
    @eloy sadness. At work or home?  How long did she last?  #sadday    
    
    
    @eloy is this enough to make you switch?  It is enticing to me.  Although if like to now how much each rental costs.
http://blog.rdio.com/us/2013/04/introducing-vdio.html …    
    
    
    @eloy Only if you want VDIO.  I mean, you could pay for both premium memberships right? If the price matches amazon/vudu then i won’t switch    
    
    
    @jrzapata wow. Agreed!    
    
    
    Awesome.  http://www.distancetomars.com     
    
    
    @NewLeafEnergy Do you guys have a screenshot of your admin section?    
    
    
    Just found a left over Easter egg in my back yard.  #winning http://instagram.com/p/X5ycxESS7p/     
    
    
    Guy's night! http://instagram.com/p/X-9AfKyS5_/     
    
    
    Dear bird who just pooped on my arm, I congratulate you on your accuracy.  Sincerely, Will #fb    
    
    
    @aguilarll - @MonicaOrtiz just told me “you did this to me!”  You called it!    
    
    
    So Shell rented out Minute Maid park for a meeting today.  These allow me to play softball on the field. http://instagram.com/p/YNYDodSS8R/     
    
    
    Diamond club at Shell's private game http://instagram.com/p/YOTs_FSS2f/     
    
    
    https://vine.co/v/bUahiK3gbjE     
    
    
    @aguilarll What kind of game? Board Game: Settlers of Catan!  Long but fun.    
    
    
    @aguilarll Well that’s a whole other story.  Cut the rope, maybe?    
    
    
    Beautiful day pic.twitter.com/bAAH89eHSU    
    
    
    @rsotelo1 @eloy Agreed! Home is best. Barnaby’s is a distant second.    
    
    
    Seems like Bing doesn't know anything about code #bingiton #fail pic.twitter.com/iO0cp2esIN    
    
    
    I was just Google mapped!    
    
    
    Come support children learning about entrepreneurship by selling lemonade!  At Mason Park until 1:30pm… http://instagram.com/p/Y7-L-8yS5p/     
    
    
    My tC is getting old http://instagram.com/p/ZEXbt-ySyc/     
    
    
    @MonicaOrtiz this is for you:  if Mom got paid for being Mom? http://blocktalk.wpengine.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/HRB_IG_MothersDay_Final-1.jpg … Via @KatieS    
    
    
    @Jman2k3 congrats!    
    
    
    Proud of how far social media has come! @newsycombinator: American Airlines offer lounge access Klout score over 55 http://j.mp/11Qin9N     
    
    
    @MCpipster congrats sir!    
    
    
    Congrats Brian Holtkamp on graduation! We’re proud of you @uhdowntown    
    
    
    Congrats Jerry Berry!  @JerryoTheGreat @uhdowntown    
    
    
    UHD Graduation with @monicaortiz, Jerryo, Jessica, Brian, Kara, @eloy (@ Minute Maid Park - @mlb w/ 23 others) http://4sq.com/YQKW8c     
    
    
    Graduation Lunch @monicaortiz, Brian (at @BucadiBeppo) http://4sq.com/10MqjHQ     
    
    
    Thanks @WellsFargo for changing your password requirements.  Mine had an ! in it and now that is an illegal character.  #forcedpassreset    
    
    
    with Alyssa, Laura, @monicaortiz, @rebecca_88 (@ Barnaby's Cafe Downtown) http://4sq.com/146VC4A     
    
    
    with Laura, Alyssa, @monicaortiz, @rebecca_88 (@ Free Press Summer Fest w/ 255 others) http://4sq.com/19x8pQ6     
    
    
    Excited about the Geto Boys #fpsf #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Free Press Summer Fest (Houston, TX) w/ 200 others http://4sq.com/10JWL19     
    
    
    Upcoming: Matt & Kim, Of Monsters & Men, and Macklemore/Ryan Lewis. #fpsf #sundayfunday #fb    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm at Cafe Brasil (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/10Ue93x     
    
    
    I'm at Pearland Old Townsite Farmers Market (Pearland, TX) http://4sq.com/13lTXpb     
    
    
    We came back from the Pearland Farmers market with this! http://instagram.com/p/aTlevHyS9J/     
    
    
    Baby room preparation with the help of Sherwin Williams http://instagram.com/p/aTmfloyS-h/     
    
    
    I'm at IKEA - @designbyikea (Houston, TX) w/ 7 others http://4sq.com/14ogHHS     
    
    
    Solid competition, but I struggling for the full 90 minutes.  #soccer (@ Houston Amateur Sports Park) http://4sq.com/ZN4UBn     
    
    
    In the kitchen at Le Mistral while they prepare our food #awesome https://vine.co/v/hBbuZ7tjjv2     
    
    
    Happy birthday Sara! https://vine.co/v/hBb5JBv1jFV     
    
    
    Father's Day! (at @RedLobster) http://4sq.com/12B1ep0     
    
    
    Shell bought us ice cream two days in a row http://instagram.com/p/ayvU6CSS73/     
    
    
    @destroytoday congrats!    
    
    
    I'm at TopGolf Houston - @topgolfusa (Houston, TX) w/ 6 others http://4sq.com/11vp6J6     
    
    
    So Golf Channel is at Top Golf recording.  If you watch golf channel, be sure to let me know if you see me. #golf #fun    
    
    
    with @monicaortiz (@ BBVA Compass Stadium - @bbvacompassstdm for @torontofc vs @HoustonDynamo w/ @chidovic1612) http://4sq.com/141n1Ei     
    
    
    Don't forget your dollar bills for the gender reveal game! #babyh http://instagram.com/p/bJhg66ySwT/     
    
    
    Cornhole scores (me vs @MonicaOrtiz): 24-18, 23-16, 23-16, 23-18, 22-15.  She beat me every game tonight  #ashamed and #proud    
    
    
    Sad that @FrontPoint has moved to an automated system.  My alarm went off and the robot hung up on me.  #missingrealpeople #falsealarm    
    
    
    Big thanks to @FrontPoint for calling me to clarify about the automated call only being for tamper signals #great #customerservice    
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium - @bbvacompassstdm for @PhilaUnion vs @HoustonDynamo w/ @monicaortiz http://4sq.com/129TTIi     
    
    
    Davis is watching the game. http://instagram.com/p/bcmvzxyS9u/     
    
    
    Dynamo fireworks night http://instagram.com/p/bcwB9tSS9d/     
    
    
    Do they have dosants, maybe? (@ Pena's Donut Heaven & Grill @ Shadow Creek) http://4sq.com/1d65dKt     
    
    
    Does this mean I need a new laptop soon? #macbookpro #dying #slowly pic.twitter.com/sHuQ7COy2e    
    
    
    I'm at Buc-ee's w/ @monicaortiz http://4sq.com/16y79rp     
    
    
    Hello Bambi http://instagram.com/p/br1ZJCyS0C/     
    
    
    Eating out of her hands #spoiled http://instagram.com/p/br1f52SS0V/     
    
    
    Tiny & Jason's Wedding!! (@ The Hall at The Rail House w/ @monicaortiz) http://4sq.com/17c0BAU     
    
    
    On our way home (@ Buc-ee's w/ @monicaortiz) http://4sq.com/141WU2I     
    
    
    @spendeeapp it’s looking great! Feature request: sync between multiple users for married couples who want to log finances together.    
    
    
    I'm at Jimmy Changas (League City, TX) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/18uUNHn     
    
    
    @eloy @fitbit what a harsh joke!  I love it.  #goodstuff #unintentionalhumor    
    
    
    I'm at @OliveGarden w/ @monicaortiz http://4sq.com/15XvrhC     
    
    
    Freshly squeezed limeade http://instagram.com/p/cC6XXoSS7O/     
    
    
    Stoke City! (@ BBVA Compass Stadium - @bbvacompassstdm w/ @monicaortiz) http://4sq.com/15Ku3x3     
    
    
    @BAbackpacker I thought you might like this interview with Bob Bradley about Egyptian football: http://www.thedailyshow.com/watch/thu-july-25-2013/bob-bradley …    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker did you see the extended interview?  That video was all that aired but they have 10 more minutes on their website    
    
    
    @chidovic1612  oh yeah? Awesome!  This ref has had a terrible game.  We’ve been attacking well so hopefully one goes through before the half    
    
    
    @KuhlLinscomb Hey guys, what is your phone number?  I keep calling 713.526.6000 and it says that it is disconnected.    
    
    
    I'm at @BabiesRUs w/ @monicaortiz http://4sq.com/14qCGBb     
    
    
    I felt the baby kick for the first time today. #amazing #fb    
    
    
    I hate it when my @fitbit flex battery dies during the night and my alarm doesn't go off. #setremindertocharge #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    When there's no power in Pearland, we play Settler's with candlelight. #storm #poweroutage pic.twitter.com/IqKXegnY39    
    
    
    This might be the most epic thing Amazon has done. http://www.amazon.com/gp/feature.html/ref=amb_link_379213722_2?ie=UTF8&docId=1001250201&nav_sdd=aps&pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER&pf_rd_s=center-B2&pf_rd_r=08ACQX675J552B5VWZM8&pf_rd_t=101&pf_rd_p=1608869682&pf_rd_i=507846 … #fb    
    
    
    Ozil joined Podolski at Arsenal?  I might have to become a fan. #fb    
    
    
    First timers! (@ Killen's BBQ w/ @eloy @monicaortiz) http://4sq.com/18GbnzI     
    
    
    I'm proud of @MonicaOrtiz for passing her certification exam!    
    
    
    Erika's Bingo Birthday! http://instagram.com/p/edrAdjyS4G/     
    
    
    @Trostmann where’d that kid in front of you go?  That looks epic.    
    
    
    The old Macy's in downtown Houston.  #destroyed http://instagram.com/p/emiQUbyS0g/     
    
    
    I'm at BBVA Compass Stadium - @bbvacompassstdm for W Connection FC vs Houston w/ @monicaortiz http://4sq.com/1fF1JCI     
    
    
    Pregnancy says: Taco Tuesday (@ Chipotle Mexican Grill w/ @monicaortiz) http://4sq.com/15JGDvG     
    
    
    @MCpipster 5S :)    
    
    
    I'm at @FairPark for The State Fair of Texas w/ @eloy @monicaortiz http://4sq.com/1gdPuxg     
    
    
    Kelly Rowland live on the main stage #win #texasstatefair #fb    
    
    
    @SusuLiao hey!    
    
    
    This is epic! https://square.com/cash     
    
    
    @ComcastMattV My friend @SusuLiao (new to twitter) has been having internet troubles in 77459 for hours.  Would you mind helping her out?    
    
    
    @tomdale yes please!    
    
    
    Thanks for the great season @HoustonDynamo #fb    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker @MonicaOrtiz I can't read it :(  Do I have to have a subscription?  It just seems like the page doesn't load.    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker @MonicaOrtiz It works now!  Interesting read.  Those fees are outrageous!  Luckily, I have awesome insurance!    
    
    
    @comcastcares any ETA on the outage in 77584?    
    
    
    @ComcastPete it seemed to be working this morning.  Thanks!    
    
    
    Dale Dynamo!  Check the game out on NBC.  It’s our last game of the regular season! #fb    
    
    
    The @HoustonDynamo make the playoffs!  #excited #clutch #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Lake House Waterside Café (Houston, TX) http://4sq.com/16YWRSc     
    
    
    Baby Owen officially has 64 articles of clothing.  #spoiled #fb    
    
    
    “Your daddy must have been a drug dealer.”  “Why?”  “‘Cause you’re dope.”  - @thecataracs    
    
    
    .@houstonhospital just upgraded our room to a suite for free since they were overbooked.  Amazing customer service #impressed #recommended    
    
    
    Don’t run out of diapers on Black Friday.  The Baby section at @Walmart looks like this.  #parentingfail pic.twitter.com/jWsIFcPArC    
    
    
    I think my @fitbit flex band has died. #rip pic.twitter.com/OckRWWjxK6    
    
    
    @JohnathanKuskos kudos!    
    
    
    @JohnathanKuskos everything is great! Looks like you’re having a blast in the white hat community.    
    
    
    @oscarhealth any plans on coming to Texas?  Perhaps a small town called Houston? #interested    
    
    
    @Trostmann Happy birthday sir.  Guys night and Houston misses you.    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker a merry Christmas to you too sir!    
    
    
    My @fitbit flex band has finally died.  No more tracking for a bit #sad pic.twitter.com/WpZEVtQM5E    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker agreed!    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker all of it.  #guiltypleasure    
    
    
    @eloy yay!  That’ll save me monies    
    
    
    @eloy oriented?    
    
    
    @bandnerd330 +1    
    
    
    Teaching Owen a little something about programming #emberjs #bonding http://instagram.com/p/jAi-WlyS35/     
    
    
    @BAbackpacker that would be awesome.  Naked, watching titanic, and ordering scotch. #greatnight    
    
    
    @eloy no contract parking available?  That’s what I had to do.    
    
    
    @eloy haha welcome to working near downtown!  I got lucky and mine is now company expensed.    
    
    
    @Xero I'm considering switching from Quickbooks.  Is there any ETA on payroll implementation in the state of Texas?    
    
    
    @eloy @BAbackpacker  I like this definition: “Kara Eloy”    
    
    
    Beats Music is slick.  @spotify might lose a customer.    
    
    
    @localbyproxy @beatsmusic do you guys scrobble? #lastfm    
    
    
    @MSTechStudent Vote #STC!  We built an XBOX360 tower-defense game that is not only fun, but tackles real-world issues. http://bit.ly/STCTEAM    
    
    
    Checking in with @eightbit reminds me of the NES days. #nostalgia    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 b-a-n-a-n-a-s!    
    
    
    Who's interested in hitting up the Yelp Happy Hour next week?  Pick any day before Thursday (leave for Seattle), please!  http://ow.ly/4rNto    
    
    
    .@monicaortiz Just got admitted into Grad School!  She's a future Social Worker :) #proudhusband #fb    
    
    
    @eloy are you doing the complaining?    
    
    
    2 year anniversay! (@ Shade) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw    
    
    
    @shawnhargreaves  Hey Shawn!  My team is in the @imaginecup National Finals.  Can you  give us some feedback?  http://bit.ly/STCPreview    
    
    
    @nickgravelyn Hey Nick!  My team is in the @imaginecup finals and I was hoping you might give us some feedback.  http://bit.ly/STCPreview    
    
    
    There's a new race in town: Finish your task and save before premiere pro decides it wants to crash.  #5minuteiterations    
    
    
    @mstechstudent Come join us for a live stream playtesting of our @imaginecup game tonight at 9PM Central http://bit.ly/STCPreview Please RT!    
    
    
    All are invited to come view a live demo of our game online!  The fun starts tonight at 9PM Central.  http://bit.ly/STCPreview #fb    
    
    
    @mstechstudent Suggestions: There are a ton of cool things you can do, but won't have the time for.  Focus on making everything great!    
    
    
    @mstechstudent I can't wait!  Thanks, we're going to need the luck.  There's some tough competition out there!    
    
    
    @mstechstudent First round is Saturday.  If make the cut, the final four will be Monday.  Are you going to be in Seattle?    
    
    
    Houston ✈ Seattle imagine cup nationals! @ IAH George Bush Intercontinental http://gowal.la/c/3X4cJ    
    
    
    Hello Seattle! @ SEA Seattle-Tacoma International http://gowal.la/c/3Xbnf    
    
    
    Macs on Microsoft campus #victory http://ow.ly/i/a7LS    
    
    
    :) @ Original Starbucks http://gowal.la/c/3XLmW    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 false, I'm a coffee fanboy    
    
    
    The Land of Pines rocking at @imaginecup's concert    
    
    
    Playing Kinect games before launch.  Everyone go get the Michael Jackson experience.  It's off the chain!    
    
    
    Local place with local food and local microbrews.  #Awesome @ Munchbar http://gowal.la/c/3Ymws    
    
    
    "the opposite of play isn't work - it's depression" - quoted by #imaginecup keynote    
    
    
    Didn't win but we had a blast at @imaginecup.  Thanks for the support everyone #fb    
    
    
    @munchbellevue Yeah, the only problem is that I live in Houston!  Thinking of branching off there? It'd be awesome!    
    
    
    @jman2k3 I'm not feeling it. Sorry bro    
    
    
    This is a cruel joke.  My macbook won't charge anymore.  #lifeflashingbeforemyeyes http://yfrog.com/h7a0stp     
    
    
    Hey #Houston, Skeeters is closed!!!! #sadness    
    
    
    New charger = happy laptop! Luckily it was just erratic behavior due to a faulty charger.  Too bad chargers are $80! #outrageous    
    
    
    @eloy apple and not iTunes? Interesting!    
    
    
    @monicaortiz Check out the new bettle: http://ow.ly/4DiqD    
    
    
    @Jman2k3 yeah they really are    
    
    
    @kalebdf sweet! Congrats    
    
    
    Free Webinar, Social Media Marketing for small business, starts in 30 minutes.  Sign up now! http://bit.ly/fPzqBu    
    
    
    @nickgravelyn I want to say its more of a licensing issue.    
    
    
    @nickgravelyn Haha, now that is something I'll join you in!    
    
    
    Sorry about that: make that webinar a WEEK and 30 minutes.  #gottooexcited    
    
    
    @monicaortiz Check this out (on a computer) and show your parents! http://ow.ly/4F4xj    
    
    
    @rsotelo1 Agreed!    
    
    
    In #galveston but thinking about #appsterdam    
    
    
    @oudeholt theholtkamps.com?  Yeah it's mine but I don't have any access problems.... Why?    
    
    
    Beautiful day in #houston.  Time to do some coding outdoors    
    
    
    I've been researching #Appsterdam http://mur.mu.rs/    
    
    
    @trostmann Without a helmet?  That makes it even better.    
    
    
    Just started #ios dev (again), and I haven't even opened the Interface Builder. Is it really that pointless or am I just not doing it right?    
    
    
    @eloy They are my primary document suite.    
    
    
    Getting a #phd?  Apparently we're overwhelming the market http://ow.ly/4I5hu #fb    
    
    
    @eloy I like! $27 an issue though? #crazy    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 I didn't realize you were at school today.  I would have said Hi.  I just got home from there    
    
    
    @oneforty @constantcontact Is the #smmsb already over!?  All the emails I got said 1:00 PM - 2:00 PM CDT (which is now).    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 Whoa!  Rebecca Black in the Galleria and we're that for Arcade Fire!? #pfftt    
    
    
    Yay @aptana says java.lang.StackOverflowError on copy/paste. Latest update ruined quick code edits :/    
    
    
    Thanks Hot 95.7.  Baby Got Back on the commute to my pre-defense.  #bumpin    
    
    
    So I'm a doctoral candidate now.  One step closer to the goal #yay #fb    
    
    
    Mmm steak! (@ Del Frisco's Double Eagle Steakhouse) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw    
    
    
    First impression: margarita is absolutely amazing! #delfriscos    
    
    
    @eloy too bad they suck :/ 5-0 #fail    
    
    
    Best steak ever.  Thanks @MonicaOrtiz #delfriscos    
    
    
    Come join me at @ifest today.  I'll be volunteering between 11:30 and 3:30 at the drinks booth #fb    
    
    
    @eloy Check this out: http://ow.ly/4KsXf    
    
    
    After watching Jon Stewart's interview with Elizabeth Warren, it makes me want a political career.  Just so we aren't so screwed.    
    
    
    With Bin Laden dead, will Torreto and O'Connor be America's most wanted? #fastfive    
    
    
    Obama's Live!    
    
    
    Pretty much every movie comedian made a 30 minute short about the Beastie Boys (directed by the Beastie Boys) http://ow.ly/4LqLd #amazing    
    
    
    .@rebecca_88 just installed @Aptana.  She's officially a coder/designer.  #awesome    
    
    
    Anyone hiring a web dev (i know HTML/CSS/jquery/rails) in Houston for the summer? Looks like I'm a free agent until grad school in September    
    
    
        
    
    
    @rebecca_88 Party in the back!    
    
    
    Arcade Fire! (@ Cynthia Woods Pavilion For The Arts) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw    
    
    
    @karaet No Bueno!!!!    
    
    
    #SaturTuesday is #awesome    
    
    
    I'm a post-modern. #fairlyaccurrate Where Do You Fit? Take the @pewresearch Political Typology Quiz http://pewrsr.ch/mm8OuG    
    
    
    .@bustedtees Could you please make me this shirt: "Osama Bin Laden.  Hide and seek champion 2001-2011"? Thanks!    
    
    
    @eloy theres got to be a frogger joke there somewhere    
    
    
    Look ma, I got a MemoLane. http://memolane.com/holtkampw    
    
    
    Got a #mac?  Running #rails?  Check out @37signals awesome new local server: http://pow.cx/    
    
    
    "From Prada to Nada" is on TV right now.  #ack    
    
    
    @quentinroyce We should probably meet and go over things again    
    
    
    Hey #CraftyHoustonistas, have you seen this site? http://heartsy.me/  @monicaortiz @karaet @rebecca_88 @rsotelo1 @themariam @orangejulius    
    
    
        
    
    
    A guy just jumped two fences and started running away from a house.  Did I just witness a break-in getaway?  #interesting    
    
    
    @monicaortiz Naw, he was coming from the house behind our non-apartment neighbors    
    
    
    @jerrigirl but Armageddon makes for such a better story!    
    
    
    @craftinistas Where's the Craftinista's tumblr/blog? :)    
    
    
    @Trostmann @karaet @eloy you guys are crazy tweeting eachother.  Why doesn't Daniel have a twitter account!?    
    
    
    I know I've tweeted the song, but the video isn't too shabby either: Ninjasonik - Daylight http://youtu.be/b2vO65MP0lc #ninjasonik #matt&kim    
    
    
    @eloy I've seen this story.  You get killed last.    
    
    
    My #toptuesday is out on @goscoville ★ Top places this week ★ Hermann Park, BJ's Restaurant and Brewhouse http://bit.ly/iKzfq7    
    
    
    @destroytoday congrats!    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 #NAACP    
    
    
    @eloy Don't forget the gun's follow through    
    
    
    First time to watch #Anchorman.  Quite a few T-shirts that make sense now.    
    
    
    @eloy Wow, that's awesome! I want some #bitcoins    
    
    
    While @eloy is shooting things, I'm looking at crafts    
    
    
    .@Rebecca_88 is listening to a song that says "I want those titties to bounce, I want to see those titties shake"    
    
    
    It's 6PM, do you know where your rapture is?    
    
    
    @glenbot congrats!!!!    
    
    
    Fortune cookie man needs to learn more English  http://ow.ly/i/bTvn    
    
    
    @eloy command + z    
    
    
    The rapture didn't take me but it sure  did take my @sprint overdrive.  @bestbuy here I come! http://ow.ly/i/bULS    
    
    
    Looking for #checking account replacement.  @perkstreet looks great.  @banksimple might be cool (if it were open).  Any recommendations?    
    
    
    @skipgienapp I'm with Wells Fargo right now and they are disc their rewards program.  I'm grandfathered in, but who knows for how long #lame    
    
    
    @crondavid Do you have Perkstreet?  If so, why PerkStreet over Ally?    
    
    
    @perkstreet Clearly, your customer service is amazing.  Out of sheer curiosity, who do you consider to be your biggest competitor?    
    
    
    @theitbros Did you ever have to overcome the withdrawal limits from @perkstreet (at ATMs)?  If so, what options did you use?    
    
    
    @gameopen My wife has Smart Financial CU and we've had so many problems.  She's had debit cards disabled (hacking), random bill payments,etc    
    
    
    @allybank Great advantage!  Rewards: with 5K in the bank and 2K monthly spending, I calculate yearly savings at $250 vs Perkstreet's $480    
    
    
    @allybank @perkstreet picks up the phone within 30 seconds(on average).  Do you have a figure for average time? Cust Service is king for me!    
    
    
    @BAbackpacker Check out this link: http://ow.ly/51aOl It involves Kelly Clarkson and VIP tickets to meet her in Houston.    
    
    
    @karaet How'd your kids do!?    
    
    
    .@rebecca_88 @eloy I call it, the "Late Night Munchies Picnic table" plank    
    
    
    @babackpacker Congrats!  I think.. haha!    
    
    
    Is the really how early the normal working force wakes up?  #ridiculous    
    
    
    "No one is going to be the asshole who throws trash code on a clean codebase" - DHH    
    
    
    @kalebdf I'm torn if I like this platform better than the online version.  What's your thoughts?    
    
    
    @Aunistics simplicity and clever designs.  Jeff's stuff is great    
    
    
    Sad ManU lost, but big props to Barca.  They truly are a powerhouse of talent.  #fb    
    
    
    @Trostmann look at your spot near Leon's http://ow.ly/i/cdQp    
    
    
    Shower - 1. Holtkamp - 0.  You might have won the battle but I'll win the war.    
    
    
    @jman2k3 Just a clogged drain    
    
    
    It was between @allybank and @perkstreet, and I chose @perkstreet.  Both are amazing.  I don't really use ATMs, so the rewards pulled me in.    
    
    
    @kalebdf About a month ago I thought about making an app for that, but don't have the time.   I did find one api: http://api.eventful.com/    
    
    
        
    
    
    @rebecca_88 http://chromeo.net/videos/ #summerfest    
    
    
    Summerfest! (@ Eleanor Tinsley Park) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw    
    
    
    Just played the Playstation Move @ #summerfest.  Kinect - 1, Move - 0    
    
    
    Anyone at #summerfest today? #fb    
    
    
    I just ran a bobble and the bobble won #summerfest    
    
    
    @Trostmann still around?    
    
    
    @Trostmann awesome. @eloy, this is your invitation    
    
    
    I love "official merchandise" places at events.  Can I open an "unofficial merchandise" venue to compete?  Everyone would buy from me.    
    
    
    @MonicaOrtiz *yawn*    
    
    
    @karaet easy solution: call him.  He can't talk and play with apps at the same time on Verizon.    
    
    
    @eloy ignoring significant others is frowned upon #hasexperience    
    
    
    @eloy touché    
    
    
    Big Boi is at Fitzgeralds tonight. Surprise concert just announced at #summerfest    
    
    
    At #summerfest: "thanks for supporting your local artists & musicians (and their illegal mexican cockfight rings)"    
    
    
    @Trostmann day 2!!    
    
    
    @Trostmann yeah we're @ featherface    
    
    
    @Trostmann I'm stalking you @ stage 2    
    
    
    @karaet @Trostmann We just happen to be at the same place at the same time.  That's not a bromance, that's fate.    
    
    
    #summerfest sees rain #rockon    
    
    
    I'm excited for #chromeo #summerfest    
    
    
    Chromeo rocked! #summerfest    
    
    
    @Trostmann tell Daniel his hat is highly recognizable among the masses    
    
    
    Blackie kinda sucks. #summerfest    
    
    
    @Trostmann the beach balls are clean.  Fix that please ;)    
    
    
    Hoola hoop lady is back and still off the chain #summerfest    
    
    
    @Trostmann we can fit you    
    
    
    .@MonicaOrtiz beat me at thumb war and is the undisputed champion.  I approve this message.    
    
    
    @trostmann Play Google's Guitar.  It'll make you feel better.    
    
    
    @trostmann You can even record what you played and share with others.    
    
    
    @HtownBeerFest Do you accept credit or are tickets going to be cash only?  Also, is it 10 tickets for $10? or what's the price?    
    
    
    @eloy What's with the instagram love lately?  is it really that much better?    
    
    
    @eloy than.. twitpic, yfrog, smugmug, flickr, posterous, twitgoo?    
    
    
    Shout out to the guys @ #guysnight  http://ow.ly/i/cJDY    
    
    
    I just realized @SoundCloud has a desktop app that syncs to the iPhone app.  #eatyourheartoutgrooveshark    
    
    
    Trying to cheat the system so I can check out my geek cred http://coderwall.com/holtkampw  via @coderwall    
    
    
    Tom Tom is mapping the world  http://ow.ly/i/cM7u    
    
    
    @monicaortiz You and I baby, we go side to side    
    
    
    It seems everyone in Houston bought a groupon #beerfest    
    
    
    1 hour later: in line. #beerfest    
    
    
        
    
    
    @HtownBeerFest I had $40 worth of tickets that I couldn't use because everyone ran out of beer.    
    
    
    @eloy #spoiled!    
    
    
    @Trostmann Vespa gangs are cooler    
    
    
    I just bought a Kate Spade purse. #sucka    
    
    
    @Trostmann let's start a Prius gang.  #priusgoeshard    
    
    
    @Trostmann yes, mission accomplished!  If I do this every week, can I have a guys night intervention every week?    
    
    
    @eloy root for USA!!    
    
    
    @karaet We're having Lenoir from Rosemary    
    
    
    @karaet #thatshowweroll    
    
    
        
    
    
    At the Garfias pre-union.  I can't wait! #erikarickywedding    
    
    
    @comcastcares Voice is out at a friends. I tried to reset on the modem but that didn't work. Any ideas?    
    
    
    @comcastwill Nope.  Did the reset + wait 5 minutes.  It took 3-4 tries but it eventually came back up.  Thanks!    
    
    
    Congrats #erikanricky    
    
    
    #erikanricky we love you guys!    
    
    
    Congrats #erikanricky , the newlyweds!!!  (please RT)    
    
    
    Note to self: learn Spanish.    
    
    
    @Trostmann For sure!  I can't understand the fast speakers.    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 what did you win?    
    
    
    Beautiful day in McAllen TX.  Wind blowing/overcast.    
    
    
    @karaet  did you ever get an invite to google+?    
    
    
    @Trostmann I unfortunately have a date with #work    
    
    
    @kalebdf I'm butting in, but look up the delayed_job gem.  I use it from time to time or background tasks/events    
    
    
        
    
    
    Eating. Missing @eloy's nerd talk. (@ Onion Creek Coffee House) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw    
    
    
    @eloy how'd scrum go?    
    
    
    @eloy the word agile is taboo here. We do have daily stand up meetings but never planning for incremental releases    
    
    
    @trostmann Just watched Pulp Fiction for the first time. #goodstuff    
    
    
    Its #micholata wednesday! yay!    
    
    
    @karaet Agreed! She rocks!    
    
    
    "You call it murder.  I call it the market regulating the brother supply" - Wyatt Cenac    
    
    
    Harry Potter gives pedophiles with cloaks a reason to leave the house.    
    
    
    This is why you don't use windows  http://ow.ly/i/elPo    
    
    
    Omfg, Harry potter is dead!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Happy 1 year @craftinistas (@ Pearl Bar) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw    
    
    
        
    
    
    @monicaortiz DIY | greenUPGRADER http://greenupgrader.com/category/diy-green/    
    
    
    @eloy Look at this pic.  Isn't that the setup you wanted? http://ow.ly/5JCEX    
    
    
    @eloy thunderbolt :)    
    
    
    @eloy Brand new thunderbolt monitor released today: http://ow.ly/5JEmi    
    
    
    @eloy I'm not 100% sure, but I think your current lappy has to support Thunderbolt.  #upgradetime    
    
    
    @eloy Shame! I haven't upgraded... yet.    
    
    
    @eloy Yes, they DID reverse the finger scroll.  Crazy-ness    
    
    
    @eloy @rebecca_88 @karaet @monicaortiz Check out these cards (just like apples to apples).  How awesome are they!? http://ow.ly/5LKfa    
    
    
    Good Bye Amy Winehouse.  #RIP    
    
    
    I love me some Chiddy Bang.  http://open.spotify.com/track/15Nr0veB5floYCjdtjgZ7U … Chiddy Bang – Mind Your Manners (feat. Icona Pop) #awesome    
    
    
    Happy #Micholata Wednesday everyone! #fb    
    
    
    @eloy at home :) #thatshowweroll    
    
    
    @eloy I'm actually drinking wine.  my boss just calls it #micholata Wednesday.  Any excuse, right?  #dietintact    
    
    
    @eloy my boss at openlink    
    
    
        
    
    
    @eloy nope, left openlink @ 6p today    
    
    
    @eloy I get to work everyday @ 6:30am. Mon and Tuesday, I left at 9pm (30 min lunch = 14 hrs    
    
    
    @eloy soon my friend.  Soon    
    
    
    I just ran out of Spotify for the month. #gameover    
    
    
    @eloy What are you and @glenbot building? #djangodash    
    
    
    Screw mojitos, it's all about the caipiroska #amazing @piolahouston    
    
    
        
    
    
    I might as well take a minute or two to talk about the perks Cause you can't compete with a man like me And that's just how it works -Chomeo    
    
    
    @Jman2k3 have you tried a caiproski?    
    
    
    @Jman2k3 the ingredients :)    
    
    
    Finally see mmm cupcake and can't have any.  #Awesome    
    
    
    Suburbans have huge gas tanks.    
    
    
    It starts #nolo #fb http://ow.ly/i/fFP3     
    
    
    My Jesus shirt just got the whole table free beignets.  #thanksjesus    
    
    
    Amazing breakfast @ Mother's #Nola    
    
    
    I drove my chevy to the levee but the levee was gone #Nola http://ow.ly/i/fL5w     
    
    
    NOLA Flea Market! (@ French Market) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw     
    
    
    Swinging chairs at margaritaville are awesome!!  http://ow.ly/i/fL9i     
    
    
    The best bartender in NO @ Margaritaville.  #Nola    
    
    
    @GoNOLA504 I had eggs and smoked sausage.   Mmmm good!    
    
    
    Wow, #WellsFargo just emailed me an ATM receipt +1 for #wells but @perkstreet is still will be my primary bank (when my deposit amt is up'd)    
    
    
    Seattle Bound! (@ George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH)) http://eightbit.me/holtkampw     
    
    
    iPad Web App being demo'd in Seattle at Microsoft GameFest.  #awesome    
    
    
    Jazz, alcohol, sushi, burgers, and kinect.  That's how #gamefest rolls.    
    
    
    "Don't have your mum hoovering [vacuuming] and end up having to defend the empire" #gamefest on activating the Kinect #fb    
    
    
    I just used #Shazam to discover In The Dark by Dev Feat. Flo Rida. http://shz.am/t53711858     
    
    
    Did Facebook pretty much copy G+?  #blasphemy #awesome    
    
    
    Spotify finally got the Dev - In the Dark - remix
http://open.spotify.com/local/Dev//In+The+Dark+%28Remix%29+feat.+50+Cent/220 …    
    
    
    Now for the Kanye Remix - Dev - In the Dark - http://open.spotify.com/local/DEV//In+the+dark%28remix%29%5bfeat.+Kanye+west%5d/221 …    
    
    
    Hey @monicaortiz, Facebook just reminded me that today would be 1 year engaged #win http://ow.ly/i/gIVz     
    
    
    @monicaortiz It was begging to be used    
    
    
    The lights went out on the orchestra and they kept playing.  #professional #hardcore    
    
    
    And for a second time! Someone forgot to pay Reliant    
    
    
    @eloy I'll take you up on that offer #stalking    
    
    
    @eloy yay! Another pandora business user.    
    
    
    "Sir, the reason for this stop is your speed. When I clocked you, your speed was 86 mph" - Officer outside of Austin #fb    
    
    
    Drink Specials all around houston (or other cities): http://ow.ly/6qI36    
    
    
    Spotify says I'm done listening to music for the month :( http://ow.ly/i/h63c     
    
    
    Hey @jman2k3, How'd you do this week? #FantasyFootball http://ow.ly/6sDza #fb    
    
    
    #UH is apparently on ABC news tonight #vanoutsidebuilding    
    
    
    Listen to T-Pain - 5 O\'clock (feat. Wiz Khalifa  Lily A... on The Hype Machine http://awe.sm/5T6w5     
    
    
    Require payment by mail, but refuses check. All options all say "No trial", but you ask if I want a trial.  Requires Notary. #modernizeplz    
    
    
    Hey @target, I'm going out on a limb and saying you lost data when you migrated to the new site. No one can find my wedding registry anymore    
    
    
    @eloy is it better than mint?    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 today is nearly over!    
    
    
    @spotify So I'm required to post what I'm listening to on my timeline in order to use Facebook integration now?    
    
    
    @monicaortiz Pro's and Con's list time! :D    
    
    
    @monicaortiz Very True.  I'll support you wherever you want to go :)    
    
    
    OLF bought us Pappa's BBQ for working hard.  #yum    
    
    
    USPS on lawndale was awesome today!!  She corrected my mistakes (filled it out too fast) and took me in after hours..  Smply Great service    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 who is this "we"    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 I wad afraid you were going to say that! J/k @MonicaOrtiz    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 I was thinking MooYah, but I could always do a stuffed crust @ pizzahut. Although I think you had something else in mind :)    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 win! Then its all up to my better half    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 Nice Sample, minus the no words part. :)    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 LIKE!    
    
    
    @kalebdf mmm, #tasty.  what's in the Captain Crunch?    
    
    
    I wish every morning in Houston was like this morning    
    
    
    I LOVE Helvetica Playing Cards: http://ow.ly/6Kx8H  Currently on sale @ Fab.com    
    
    
    How did I not know about "How to make it in America"?  Oh I don't have HBO.  #sadness    
    
    
    Work loves us  http://ow.ly/i/it2k     
    
    
    @MonicaOrtiz @Rebecca_88 I see a big sign saying http://barkitecturehouston.com/.  Check it out!    
    
    
    I just entered to win Dropbox Pro For Life FREE http://appsumo.com/~Tcim  via @appsumo    
    
    
    @eloy I'm genuinely sad :/    
    
    
    Excited about #schipulcon tomorrow!  (Thanks @eloy)    
    
    
    My Intel SSD on my MacBook Pro just started reporting SMART errors and fails to boot.  #fb    
    
    
    Matt & Dries on one stage #schipulcon #wordpress #drupal    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 I don't personally know if it is good, but there is a popular one in Rice Village    
    
    
    @babackpacker Side Note: I'm still jealous of your trip!  Enjoy! :)    
    
    
    It's been entirely too long, but inbox(0) again. :)    
    
    
    So @eloy knows how to put on makeup with an awkward amount of professionalism.  http://ow.ly/i/iOSh     
    
    
    @Jman2k3 you haven't found anyone to do it yet?    
    
    
    @glenbot Heh, just got it!    
    
    
    Got iOS 5 installed.  Makes my iPhone 4 sooooo much faster :)    
    
    
    @rebecca_88 *gasp*    
    
    
    @eloy @apoc5392 @heavymetalguru @jman2k3 wigglewigglewigglewigglewiggle HEY! (HT: @apoc5392)    
    
    
    Playing with pre-alpha Windows 8 tablets. Eat your heart out @philt5252 http://ow.ly/i/j7Tv  #fb    
    
    
    It's amazing how many Big Moe songs I grew up with. #979thebox    
    
    
    @trostmann What kind of mac?    
    
    
    @trostmann I approve!  Side note: I have one albeit 2 years old. #notbiased    
    
    
    @flykrystin That's something you don't hear everyday    
    
    
    50GB Free from http://Box.net  for use with iCloud http://ow.ly/6XGUB   (HT: @Phank) #awesome    
    
    
    @eloy @trostmann Strictly technically speaking, @trostmann speaks (types) the truth.    
    
    
    There are way too many awesome dogs at #barkitecture #houston right now.  I want!    
    
    
    The Find Friends app.  Giving every man a tracking anklet.  If you want to be a playa now, you have to get creative. #applehatesthegame    
    
    
    Rocking' the #behappyyoureloved bag I customized at their 1 year anniversary party last night. @Rebecca_88 http://ow.ly/i/jt4Z     
    
    
    OMG! Evernote Premium FREE FOR LIFE! I need to win this! :) http://appsumo.com/~BsSv  via @appsumo    
    
    
    Hey @rebecca_88,  Where is @behappyyoureloved? :)    
    
    
    My love (@monicaortiz) modeling for my new Camera+ app http://campl.us/ghxR     
    
    
    @eloy http://shitthatsirisays.tumblr.com  #awesome    
    
    
    @monicaortiz @eloy This is awesome for a home: http://ow.ly/786YI  #energysaver    
    
    
    I loved the random dance session to @sheandhim's new Christmas album with @MonicaOrtiz #love #favoritetimeoftheyear    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Paul! – at Avant Garden http://gowalla.com/stories/5bpMA     
    
    
    I'm in line for @everlane - Designer-quality goods under $100. Join today. http://www.everlane.com/i/r0n8v3     
    
    
    It's real ladies. @MonicaOrtiz just bought me a wedding band. #offthemarket    
    
    
    Abuelita chocolate cake from Ninfa's = #amazing    
    
    
    I like Google Reader's new Google+ -like design    
    
    
    Payment by saying "Put it on Will's Tab".  Amazing @square, simply amazing. http://ow.ly/7hkXh     
    
    
    @monicaortiz <3    
    
    
    @kalebdf That sucks man.  I hate there are people who think its OK to leave a car with a dent.    
    
    
    Hey, @monicaortiz, your daddy must have been a drug dealer.  Cause you're dope. #cataracts    
    
    
    Beautiful day in #houston.  Programming outside with #Chloe #thegoodlife    
    
    
    @bandnerd330 Like a boss    
    
    
    @karaet that looks delicious    
    
    
    .@perkstreet makes my international travel happy. #london #paris #honeymoon    
    
    
    @Rebecca_88 we're in London!    
    
    
    Mind the Gap! http://campl.us/gREr     
    
    
    Wow @simplify looks very nice.  @perkstreet better watch out.  I can't wait to see the win for consumers with this friendly competition.    
    
    
    @bandnerd330 #like    
    
    
    @sprintcare I missed that small "notice" in my online bill. Now I have $500 in overages after you removed unlimited data from my "contract"    
    
    
    @sprintcare email sent!    
    
    
    @comcastcares If I buy my own SurfBoard modem, does Comcast still have to come out for setup? Or just phone activation. Note: New Customer    
    
    
    I just entered Win a Paid GitHub Account for Life (worth $8,000!!)! http://appsumoforlife.com/~O6US  via @appsumo    
    
    
    @comcastcares Signed up for service online, but you can't find my address.If my line/modem are fine, can I call to get setup without waiting    
    
    
    @comcastmichael Email sent! Pre-thanks for your help!    
    
    
    @Trostmann sorry I'm taken :(    
    
    
    