    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Rad!! Real life intro to the Simpsons http://fb.me/IPJUE7c9     
    
    
    According to this kook, sweaters from the Goodwill could come with demons attached. http://fb.me/1xRJoPKoP     
    
    
    Eyes hurting from being glued to my computer all day. All good and thankful I get to do what I like full time now    
    
    
    When that one shot you need is so hard to get http://fb.me/1UvlySz0Q     
    
    
    Apparently its not such a good idea for someone my size to be jumping off of ledges. 4 feet isnt that high, but... http://fb.me/2AF2RLKYF     
    
    
    This and the iPhone are the best phones ever made. http://fb.me/wrD9bT7L     
    
    
    Pro Tranny MMA fighter http://fb.me/GtDrGoyu     
    
    
    Forever rad http://fb.me/1d9rSCM6N     
    
    
    I'd like to thank Time Warner Cable for allowing me to lose 2 hours worth of work and then completely losing My... http://fb.me/23BgqCili     
    
    
    RAD!!! Repurposed Skateboard decks, turned into guitars!! They look awesome and if you look at their post from... http://fb.me/ASeUAicc     
    
    
    I write content for blogs daily. Yet I feel I need to start writing more personal stuff also. Maybe ill get back to those #blogs I started    
    
    
    Whos taking the train to San Diego tomorrow? This guy!    
    
    
    So I wasn't able to take the Amtrak to San Diego after all. I came to the greyhound in North Hollywood and the guy... http://fb.me/CsRg0Rwp     
    
    
    1 whole day without my laptop and Im using our desktop PC to get some work done. Clearly remember why I stopped... http://fb.me/GzwbjBpv     
    
    
    Hashtags May Be Coming to Facebook. HA! All the confused people who use hashtags on Facebook, will be justified... http://fb.me/2jvx1EHTH     
    
    
    New Law Could Keep L.A. Bars Open Till 4 A.M http://fb.me/LRisUKG5     
    
    
    Inspiration for customization http://dimagec.com/  http://fb.me/D6l9GXvq     
    
    
    The original pledge of allegiance http://fb.me/1VvOidLR6     
    
    
    "Stop trying to pretend like youre dangerous, before you get hurt."    
    
    
    This coming Saturday, March 23 were back on stages after a long, long time at The Ruby Room for TOOTHLESS GEORGE... http://fb.me/1pglWa5qX     
    
    
    Hey San Diego peeps. I'm gonna be all up in ya at 5pm today. I lagged on reaching out last week. Who wants to get lunch?    
    
    
    Kitty wants some #RockNRoll style. Was #Lemmy the first person to rock a #bulletbelt ? http://instagram.com/p/XK-mVwLNBI/     
    
    
    Egocentrism

Egocentrism is characterized by preoccupation with one's own internal world. Egocentrics regard... http://fb.me/1ZCNY2yxS     
    
    
    According to #Goodyear blimp, #IceCube is a #pimp http://instagram.com/p/XQoTG4rNOx/     
    
    
    Photo: For the #Monday whine crowd #GrumpyCat puts you in check http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wh6NguM     
    
    
    Photo: #Sherbet ice cream, you’re my only friend today. You’re sugary, fruity goodness will scare this... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wh8loun     
    
    
    Apparently I smell like Sulfur. Ill take that as a compliment \m/    
    
    
    #Sulfur #Brimstone http://instagram.com/p/XT9NuArNLI/     
    
    
    Personal understatement for today. "Ill edit that website afterwards, it shouldn't take me that long." DARN!    
    
    
    Photo: I gotta say this is encouraging on different levels. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whEL6-z     
    
    
    Photo: What can’t it just #SanDiego weather here in #LosAngeles all the time!? It’s perfectly cloudy &... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whG8EA0     
    
    
    Photo: The band I’ve put the most work in & traveled the country with. Still going! #Cowpunk #SanDiego... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whJ7tpi     
    
    
    The Screamin Yeehaws | Rock from San Diego, CA http://fb.me/2kahh6mDH     
    
    
    Further words to live by. #business #hustle #pma http://instagram.com/p/XgKuxPLNPl/     
    
    
    Officially the best #easter pic you'll see today. #Lemmy makes everything cool. #Motorhead http://instagram.com/p/XiXhS3LNGG/     
    
    
    Photo: Officially the best #easter pic you’ll see today. #Lemmy makes everything cool. #Motorhead http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whav1zD     
    
    
    The need to create n perform will never die. I'm interested in starting a Vlog and/or podcast. Topical n comedic... http://fb.me/298jrFmRa     
    
    
    http://fb.me/F6HZfuwp     
    
    
    In case you ever feel like the most #intelligent person to ever walk your block; try reading & fully understanding #TheNewYorker    
    
    
    I really do live by this, every single day of my life. #WayGooder @ Flair Cleaners - Studio City http://instagram.com/p/XqNHs6LNAG/     
    
    
    I really do wanna get one of these, if for nothing else other than decorative and nostalgic purposes.… http://instagram.com/p/XrZv45LNMv/     
    
    
    Photo: I really do wanna get one of these, if for nothing else other than decorative and nostalgic purposes.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whtFfgA     
    
    
    Hey Cinderella, go find yourself a fella. You're on the clock, bitch and midnight is coming."… http://instagram.com/p/XsxHZ0rNJV/     
    
    
    Photo: Hey Cinderella, go find yourself a fella. You’re on the clock, bitch and midnight is coming.”... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whvlvQJ     
    
    
    Photo: A lot of people put in some serious work with these #hashtags ; Use Em, don’t abuse them.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whyBIva     
    
    
    New Mad Sin video is awesome as expected http://fb.me/2U2jWeCl4     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1H5z0H9Pj     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2xlCjRfkA     
    
    
    Feel like I need this guy for my wit to be properly appreciated. Yeah that's what it is :) #Jokes #Wit… http://instagram.com/p/XvjX7ZLNLu/     
    
    
    The decadence of this place is one of the things I also miss about San Diego http://fb.me/MrGosmbG     
    
    
    Had to share this. Ive been trying this out for about a week now. Every night it helps with my upper back and... http://fb.me/2z61P1XuS     
    
    
    Photo: This applies to all areas of #business including musicians. #DoWork #Hustle (at Chateau De Beelzebub... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wi3QAqG     
    
    
    Photo: And that’s how your hats end up on the floor. #drunk #shenanigans http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wi5dTCp     
    
    
    Photo: Gonna give video games a shot. Again. #RedDeadRedemption won a bunch of awards & came highly... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wiFJ-Px     
    
    
    Got a lot accomplished today. Feeling tired, but relieved    
    
    
    Photo: Found DVD in a drawer. Been over 3 years and just watched it today. A cd release party we had at the... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wjLRMKP     
    
    
    Photo: Oh that’s right! That’s another reason I left; I needed a quick reminder. #instacollage #Calecia... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wjgt4pc     
    
    
    Photo: The DVD logo hit the corner right after, I swear. #greyhound #losangeles #SanDiego http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wk4KFxC     
    
    
    Bands like this are what makes my nerves settle.  ♫ The Slackers http://spoti.fi/ZSvsmx  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Photo: The EBay sniper strikes again! Just got these in the mail and got a great deal. Stoked. #FredPerry... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wkvccKJ     
    
    
    Photo: Feeling it. #Trojan #spiritof69 #SkinheadReggae http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wlEiCTM     
    
    
    Photo: One of these will hopefully be happening soon. #vespa #vespa1966 (at Chateau De Beelzebub ) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wldhCBW     
    
    
    Photo: This is me. Often. #SerenityNow #Seinfeld #InsanityLater (at Chateau De Beelzebub ) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wllWYo4     
    
    
    Photo: Seriously? There was a demand large enough that there had to be a run of these #DrMartens made? Who... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wln90NV     
    
    
    Photo: Finally got an #Apple #magicmouse & geeking out on it. In theory, this should make me more... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wlpoitc     
    
    
    Photo: I keep it #oldschool #otterpops #MassSnacks (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wlrRkCc     
    
    
    Photo: I’ve decided that I want a #StellaScooter & get the sidecar. P-series #Vespa w/ modern reliability.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wlx7CPc     
    
    
    Photo: This is what’s up for next Friday in #LA #TrojanLounge at the #FaisDoDo #SkinheadReggae #Rocksteady... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wl-PG2p     
    
    
    Photo: I grew up in a predominately Mexican town & was made to watch this movie many times during school.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wmARM91     
    
    
    Photo: #TrojanRecords collection is coming along. Almost have all of my first choices. #SkinheadReggae... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wmF6gP5     
    
    
    Photo: Sir, we have a zero tolerance rule for lightweights. Beat it, nerd! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wm_4mGt     
    
    
    Photo: #SanYsidro border crossing. How come the word on top isn’t translated? Always get into arguments with... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wn56cFO     
    
    
    Photo: #TheMoreYouKnow #Facts #CowsAreGood (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wn9Ib8H     
    
    
    Feeling calm and prosperous    
    
    
    Need coffee ASAP.... #makeithappen    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 Don't tell me what to do    
    
    
    That's awkward moment when you make #coffee and realize you're out of milk #DarnItToHeck    
    
    
    How come #Elvis impersonators generally tend to go for the fat Elvis?    
    
    
    @StuForReal As long as you don't feel like 2 of them.    
    
    
    @StuForReal just as well; I'm not here to judge ;)    
    
    
    Photo: This is close enough to me…if I was thin…and white….and nice to people. #TrojanRecords #Spiritof69... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnDAPRq     
    
    
    Finally gonna make time to tweet more. Now I'm looking for interesting people to follow with similar interests    
    
    
    @apogeepiercing wouldn't that be more like rubbing up against you?    
    
    
    Pharmacy taking hours. My frozen stuff isn't gonna keep much longer Hayley (@ Costco) http://4sq.com/11DmHbx     
    
    
    My brain refuses to wake up. Like other problems, I'll throw coffee at it and hope for the best    
    
    
    Photo: A lot of #BouncingSouls songs still strike a nerve years & years later. This hook from one of their... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnQDBcK     
    
    
    Photo: Not sure if it’s for the band #Suedehead or not, but this is awesome. (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnRca0c     
    
    
    Photo: Guilty pleasure confession. I’ve always liked #ArchieComics (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnWFta_     
    
    
    Photo: I’ve been through a few pairs of #DrMartens in my life. My shoe disease will never be cured and... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnXpJYb     
    
    
    #NoSoupForYou    
    
    
    Photo: A good friend of mine, whom I grew up with, just gave me this. A custom 7 string bass he had lying... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wng_H28     
    
    
    @Suedehead_Korey I'd totally try to abuse it and see how much #Hova could get away with.    
    
    
    Photo: You always have that uneasy feeling when using an establishments bathroom for the first time.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnhuytW     
    
    
    Photo: James Gandolfini is no longer around. I’ll always be a fan of #TonySoprano and all of his roles. (at... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnkrAME     
    
    
    I don't get what the appeal of that wipeout tv show is. I get it, they fall on padded surfaces and pools. Not that interesting    
    
    
    Photo: Why hello there Mr Rocko Bama http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnr3Ws8     
    
    
    Photo: My first video on here. #Deathmetal rooster actually makes me laugh out loud every time. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnzX4SY     
    
    
    Why do most Craigslist job ads from "startups" claim to be successful. Yet, always wanna hire unpaid interns to do all the work for them?    
    
    
    Photo: Had this tasty soda today. Mostly for the novelty label, but tasty nonetheless. Taste the revolution.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wo7G41h     
    
    
    @HollywoodCimmy I've gone for 2 internships already to build my resume. #DuesPaid #PayMe    
    
    
    Photo: Found the perfect #coffee tumbler for myself. I love coffee and all of its great side effects. (at... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wo8OXKI     
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 Ready by 6am then? No bugs!    
    
    
    Photo: Did you know: #Coolio has a #juggalotattoo and also the words “Juggalo Cool” underneath it? He also... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woCUFLJ     
    
    
    Just noticed that #Zeitgeist is a trilogy    
    
    
    I love my MacBook Pro. There I said it    
    
    
    I think I've come to a point in my life where I now think every #conspiracytheory is bullshit.    
    
    
    Photo: #NoMames #Calma (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woDsed4     
    
    
    Photo: I need to shave, but I like my hair today #tuff (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woGrMbj     
    
    
    Photo: Part of the reason working from home is is both awesome and horrible. Found this particularly funny.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woO35Qe     
    
    
    That terrible Saturday morning feeling of being hungover & I didn't even drink last night #thatsthatshitidontlike    
    
    
    Photo: Realized I haven’t listened to #Sublime in a good while. The summer time heat always reminds me of... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woUJ5HM     
    
    
    Photo: Paper towel #coffee filter. #FTW #DIY #TheStruggle http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woUPIa1     
    
    
    I have nothing against #beerpong AKA #beirut but my neighbors play it damn near everyday. Does it never get old?...sidenote, I'm in my 30s    
    
    
    @HLove19 I've played a bit. I can't find the appeal of drinking games. Why do people drink in a hurry? Also, hangover are far worse after 25    
    
    
    @HLove19 Totally! #OldPeopleProbs    
    
    
    Multi vitamin & coffee are now in my body. Now I can think straight    
    
    
    @NeverWanderer discharged?    
    
    
    I'm finally getting into #snapchat add me - ErnieVelas    
    
    
    I want some turntables    
    
    
    Actually I need a #mancave or workspace area. To house all my music stuff & business related things    
    
    
    Photo: #Morrissey repping classic #skinhead imagery. #suedehead #subculture (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woXI0DF     
    
    
    Finally made the switch from disposable to grown up razors. Got a 1960s safety razor & it's the best shave I've ever had. #babybottom    
    
    
    Photo: Strange how overlooking through spreadsheets is what I’ve been looking forward to doing. People find... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wobny4W     
    
    
    Photo: Apparently July 1st is international #reggae day. Let us dance & stomp. (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wocRLwi     
    
    
    I want ceviche    
    
    
    I wanna move to Silverlake. There, I said it    
    
    
    Soooooo huuuunngry #FeedMe    
    
    
    If a company is looking for an intern and there's nobody with a similar role; how & what are you gonna learn? Don't fall for it.    
    
    
    #LA - The land of 1,000,0000 #startups    
    
    
    Photo: #fact #truthiness http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wof6-Z8     
    
    
    Photo: Another one for #InternationalReggaeDay #SkinheadReggae for days (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wof86ig     
    
    
    Photo: Next time I have a birthday party, I wanna hire a face painter and have them paint everyone’s face... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wognyd-     
    
    
    Sick of being tired, far & lazy    
    
    
    Photo: I Googled “Hepcat" to look for the bands main website and noticed that a Tribute band has the highest... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wol3nEs     
    
    
    Photo: Watching #Swingers and forgot this was an all around rad cast. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wopunbi     
    
    
    Photo: I was very spoiled having a gigantic #craftbeer selection at a lot of places in #SanDiego. #LA kinda... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woqpjdj     
    
    
    Photo: Happy #4thofJuly #Merica!! (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0worFweC     
    
    
    Photo: Yep, that’s a fried dollar. Cus #Merica! That’s why! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0worJ7m5     
    
    
    I really wanna start a vinyl collection started. Always on the hunt for more stuff to do at home    
    
    
    Photo: …and that’s why he’ll always be a national hero. #Merica! (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wosmnNe     
    
    
    Photo: I’m sorry I can’t hear you over all this freedom! Happy 4th! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wos_AX_     
    
    
    Photo: Another American hero on this great 4th of July. As seen here taking a victory lap after winning the... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wotHMG5     
    
    
    Photo: That feeling you get when all of your shirts and shoes are clean & organized. (at Chateau De... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wo_5vce     
    
    
    Photo: Saw this at a parking lot in #NorthHollywood…wtf is #loafing!? (at Chateau De Beelzebub ) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wp33n_C     
    
    
    Photo: How many jokes can you think of between these 2 businesses and the connection between them? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wp34JBe     
    
    
    I want some #sweettea    
    
    
    Manipulative people play the victim to justify themselves – being diluted in how they treat others & what they believe about themselves    
    
    
    #LosAngeles really needs to step up its #craftbeer game.    
    
    
    Finally found a place that offers my favorite spicy junk food. Frozen yogurt is good here also. Plan on trying every… http://www.yelp.com/biz/slusheeland-north-hollywood?pt=quick_tip&ref=twitter&v=5a …    
    
    
    Photo: Trying to figure out what all I can do with this 7 string beast. I was getting cocky with 4 strings... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpCVDVA     
    
    
    I like a lot of bands. I like certain bands a shitload. I like playing music, I love playing shows. No urge to start a "tribute" band,at all    
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/vbUrEp  #in    
    
    
    Watching anything on YouTube with an #iphone5 using wifi is fucking impossible.    
    
    
    I'm gonna switch one of my basses to flatwound strings. Get some thumping going on    
    
    
    Photo: If you claim it. #BeAboutIt #BoutThatLife #MyAss ha #GetSome (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpNe5pq     
    
    
    Photo: Finally got to sit down and play one of these. I want one. I still love my #Fender p-bass special &... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpNuF3w     
    
    
    Photo: Newest acquisition for my #FredPerry collection. Not sure if I can call it a collection, because... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpPxGxC     
    
    
    Easy Rider| Tosh.0 | Comedy Central http://tosh.comedycentral.com/blog/2013/07/11/easy-rider/ …    
    
    
    Photo: Carne Asada tortas with refried beans w chorizo. All kinds of Mexican stuff is happening.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpSO8yc     
    
    
    Photo: "It’s a fool that looks for logic in the chambers of the human heart." One of my favorite quotes from... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpSt-bv     
    
    
    Photo: Because #HomerSkin was a badass. #Woohoo (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpW5CLT     
    
    
    I think it might be safe to wear a fedora again    
    
    
    Photo: I’d rip that #Pendleton off a #hipster #battlestargalactica http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpbRa7r     
    
    
    Photo: #UruapanMexicanLoqui (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpcYHHx     
    
    
    Photo: Part of the birthday gifts @hayleywilcox84 got me today. A custom beer pilsner flute that reads... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpccheu     
    
    
    Video: Late night, classic Mexican drinking tunes. #Tucanes #3Animales (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpchh4H     
    
    
    I want a pair of brown Dickies    
    
    
    Now accepting get rich quick schemes    
    
    
    When your head receives a landslide of insults you could've said during an argument you had a week ago    
    
    
    Can a 3d printer printer a 3d printer?    
    
    
    How low does a lowlow have to go?    
    
    
    An I the only one whose got #LAriots nostalgia?    
    
    
    #LAPD putting in work. Maybe they needed a change from pushin around bums & tickets for not tapping your card    
    
    
    Riot gear is on and it's getting real over on Crenshaw.    
    
    
    How is the winner decided in these things? The ratio of convenience stores that were stolen over the the norm? Do you compare it to 1992?    
    
    
    @Hollywood_WOF @TheLAScene oh shit it got all granola!    
    
    
    Top 5 places you'd love to loot during a riot......and go!!    
    
    
    @TheLAScene These granola munchers are gonna take the credit and claim this to have been successful #DarnThem    
    
    
    I really gotta play some music. Going stir crazy    
    
    
    Any time is a good time to exercise I suppose    
    
    
    Learned to edit some stuff on #imovie, what's the long way to say that, so it'll go on a resume?    
    
    
    #TalkAboutYourCrush  ok, fine; it's mostly #SugarWaterPurple pic.twitter.com/AlsFWReznm    
    
    
    These beautiful @DelJunction #rudeboy shoes need to be mine ASAP pic.twitter.com/IH2hgLXUQl    
    
    
    British Style Genius - The Street Look - Part 3 http://youtu.be/Pbm6_FqjEHA     
    
    
    I've got a hater who is pathetically not subtle. I'll take it as a compliment, because you'll always be lame. No matter what stories make up    
    
    
    Photo: This is one of those records that’ll never get old for me. I had the first 2 #CypressHill albums on... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpl0uY6     
    
    
    There's nothing wrong with being proud of your culture. But posting about it every single day w/ tons of hashtags is annoying.    
    
    
    Overly boasting your ethnicity on social networks can become annoying. Especially, if you've never been to the country you rant & rave about    
    
    
    Just finished watching #SharkNado. It's exactly what I thought it'd be and a few steps more. A golden thumbs down, for #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    What if I make #TerribleAwesomeness my signature hashtag for a while?    
    
    
    @jwoodham You had a good run. I'd suggest a TV movie about your twitter career.    
    
    
    That moment you get the spins from so much sugar from that fistful of taffy you had #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    That moment when the condom breaks and she doesn't care #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    Long pointy boots, white denim and a curly mullet? #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    #Celebrity #SexTape!? But it's #HulkHogan ~ #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    Seriously #WantNewCar from @Honda~it'd be so life changing I'd work it into every convo I ever have "Hey did I tell you when...YES YOU DID!"    
    
    
    I need a haircut so bad    
    
    
    #Instagram has helped launch a ridiculous amount of imaginary #modeling careers.    
    
    
    The #hustle is getting stronger #stoked    
    
    
    My stuff is finally coming together. Had to separate myself from the charlatans & positively gravitate towards like minded individuals #RAD    
    
    
    Photo: I’m gonna have to get all of these. #TMNT #80s http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wprUSjV     
    
    
    Is #tofu #pho any good?    
    
    
    Photo: Have to stay looking sharp. @socalkutz #barbers always deliver rad results. #TrojanLounge (at Chateau... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpwEBp4     
    
    
    #ProjectBadass    
    
    
    Photo: #SnoopDogg medicated #bbq sauce is happening. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpwL57Z     
    
    
    How does my dog always find that perfect angle, where he uses up most of the bed?    
    
    
    The older you get, the less you can trust a fart to be just that    
    
    
    Every morning I play a game called "Lets see how many parts of my body crack as I get out of bed"    
    
    
    Why does 2% milk cost the same as whole milk? #Shenanigans    
    
    
    How old is too old to have a pimple?    
    
    
    Why do you look before you flush?    
    
    
    Most towns across the country, people get out of my way & strangers dont aske shit. In #LA I get asked what ingredients are needed for tacos    
    
    
    @fingerbangs Most awkward ending to a #Scrabble game, ever!    
    
    
    Do people still have penpals that aren't in prison?    
    
    
    A deleted Instagram account is now referred to as a "formal modeling career"    
    
    
    My eyebrows grow so ferociously, that I could easily be mistaken for Persian dude, if I wore a ski mask    
    
    
    My lottery ticket retirement plan is a pre capital venture at the moment. Stay tuned for updates.    
    
    
    That awkward moment when you're waiting for the sleep medicine to kick in & don't know if you have time for a movie    
    
    
    @tonejonzz Keep hope alive; you will get past this!    
    
    
    I'm thinking of doing consulting work for companies. What's the average salary for a de-motivational speaker?    
    
    
    #UPGRADDE ~  Why two D's?  So we can get a double dose of dis pimpin'!    
    
    
    What are Canadian only curse words?    
    
    
    I never know how to compliment women that have nicer sideburns than me    
    
    
    Ever give someone the wrong directions on purpose?    
    
    
    Is there a way to make deli meat a dessert?    
    
    
    #Fact - Your penis grows 1/2 inch every time you peel out of a driveway    
    
    
    Is there a way to make multi level parking not make everyone sound like a formula 1 racer?    
    
    
    Do I have to have a playlist before I start going to a gym? Sidenote- Is that why everyone is a #DJ now?    
    
    
    Waking up early for no reason is not as awesome as Id hoped.    
    
    
    Photo: Side effects may include a happier, satisfying life. (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wp-q4rh     
    
    
    Photo: Seeing what an IPA in a can tastes like. Doing a self guided tour of #LA #craftbeer - so far, so good... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wq0qOPz     
    
    
    The first time I went to #Texas, I expected to bump into Hank Hill    
    
    
    Any burrito worth more than $7 better be like a carne asada money shot in my mouth    
    
    
    There's a layer of filth, that'll never wash off    
    
    
    How often do "jumping jacks" just turn into "hopping and flailing"?    
    
    
    Maybe it was a bad idea to drink beers while laying on the couch. For a Homer Simpson thing going on #Doh    
    
    
    Photo: #AmericanAsylum #AmericanHorrorStory for the sake of #meme (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wq12loN     
    
    
    @ikunsaurus Good to meet you man    
    
    
    Puns will always be funny to me    
    
    
    Need to start playing shows more often. Playing once next month. Any good traditional #ska or #reggae bands in #LA need a good #bass player?    
    
    
    @pdxcreep Ha! Thanks for the RT #grateful    
    
    
    @shesananteater The back of women's knees is like men's  5th favorite erotic zone. Right after armpits.    
    
    
    The next marketing campaign for @RollingStone is just going to be called #OurBad    
    
    
    Eyebrow shaping is a constant struggle with an inevitable loss. To them.    
    
    
    Apparently I already had a KIK account. Add me now ~ ErnieVelas    
    
    
    I'm to old to know people who claim to hate shit they were doing last week.    
    
    
    Older video & the sound isnt the best. Still awesome. #SkinheadReggae The Aggrolites "Funky Fire" http://youtu.be/hi4Ys9CgSfE     
    
    
    @Ernycakes It's always a beautiful city. #ComicCon just gums up commuting & bars for a few days    
    
    
    @Angeleyes_619 Great fucking band. My neighbors might hate by now. Haven't met them yet, have a few friends in common w/ those dudes    
    
    
    @Ernycakes I wanna go to this    
    
    
    That angry/vengeful/satisfying feeling when a mosquito goes up your nose. You're angry it happened, and he got what he deserved    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 [maybe] written in crayon    
    
    
    @Angeleyes_619 No prob. Are you from #SanDiego?    
    
    
    @Angeleyes_619 I asked cause you have 619 in your handle and I lived in San Diego a few years. I live in #NorthHollywood now    
    
    
    @Ernycakes Dope. I'm there    
    
    
    @CackleClub The DMV might take issue to a name that long    
    
    
    Add me on @Kik: ErnieVelas http://kik.com/u/ErnieVelas     
    
    
    Video: Din din http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wq5cbg5     
    
    
    Photo: "Be as a lion in the path. Be dangerous even in defeat." —Anton Szandor LaVey #COS #HS #LaVeyQuote... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wq6fIa6     
    
    
    Why do stupid people love to give advice?    
    
    
    Maybe I will start my own business after all. Everyone else in this city is doing it    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 I'm already selling this video to food fetish sites    
    
    
    The Old Firm Casuals live at Pieffe Factory 2012 (full show) HD http://youtu.be/nYsN2XQTdBE     
    
    
    @uladhexile He had a big closet cleaning sale on eBay w/ his punk rock gear & became a freshcut at 40. I still like his bands n all. Thanks!    
    
    
    How does one go stir crazy?    
    
    
    Checking my temperature for cabin fever    
    
    
    How good were you at #Monopoly? Did you feel bad when you took other people's money?    
    
    
    Photo: I quite possibly may now have the coolest twitter header ever. #Bootleg verification check mark and a... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqHR0ep     
    
    
    Don't let anyone tell you how dumb you are. You should already be aware, after a lifetime of stupid decisions.    
    
    
    They should make a #LemonySnicket remake & have it take place in the ghetto,where an entirely different series of unfortunate events happen    
    
    
    Ever feel that street signs come off as being pushy?    
    
    
    @ErnieVelas: Do they have a refrigerated pillow yet? If not @thesharperimage needs to step up their game    
    
    
    When is #hypercolor clothing gonna make a comeback?    
    
    
    I wonder if all of my old @McDonalds #HappyMeal toys are together somewhere & playing w/ my lost socks, talking about how they don't need me    
    
    
    #SanDiego #craftbeer --- I miss you. Do you think about me also?    
    
    
    Photo: I’ve actually been looking for a chart like this. Wanna start cooking and never know what’s in... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqHuUbw     
    
    
    Somebody needs to talk me out of buying these boots on eBay    
    
    
    @LisaMariaOrtiz You're to far to be throwing down challenges like that, lady :)    
    
    
    @HLove19 Thank you. Cooler heads prevailed and I chose to hold off. eBay is my cryptonite    
    
    
    @LisaMariaOrtiz Ha! I'm a musician, so I flail around on the beat    
    
    
    @LisaMariaOrtiz I guess that's what I was trying to say :p    
    
    
    This country fought for independence so we wouldn't have to care about the #RoyalBaby pic.twitter.com/8BL8RAvlgP    
    
    
    @radiomaru parallels for Mac    
    
    
    The Kids in the Hall are Reuniting Again – IFC http://www.ifc.com/fix/2013/07/the-kids-in-the-hall-reuniting …    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 pic.twitter.com/X2XwKdtzqu    
    
    
    Photo: This freakin guy :) (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqNKdAe     
    
    
    Boots with the furrrrrrr    
    
    
    Melatonin you're my only fr.......    
    
    
    How many super moons are we gonna have?    
    
    
    Boom, boom pow    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 bad grammar. Disgusting    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 Digusting    
    
    
    You wouldn't think it'd be this hard to find good musicians in LA    
    
    
    Why do white denim jeans exist?    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 I'd Does flinging these at you with a slingshot count? pic.twitter.com/A60diRWbxW    
    
    
    Netflix needs a late night section. Not softcore, something like infomercials    
    
    
    @SunsetSherry tweeting about it counts as soliciting    
    
    
    @SunsetSherry Let me know if you need "management" I have a snazzy outfit & a fucking fish bowl I've been wanting to drink out of in public    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 A true romantic :)    
    
    
    @shesananteater Yes. We should split a pizza    
    
    
    @DIDUSAYCHEESE It learned to tweet.    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 Tell me more about the Taco Bell    
    
    
    #KanyeWestIsTheKindOfGuyThatWill RT one of his own tweets and star that one as well.  @kanyewest likes that about @kanyewest    
    
    
    Wtf is a #bumgun!?    
    
    
    Those fake friend requests are extremely obvious there guy. Wouldn't expect anything creative though.    
    
    
    Keep on truckin, nerd :)    
    
    
    Photo: Randomly found this. Ead designer. #TradSkin #Spiritof69 #HardMod #Skinhead #Suedehead #subculture http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqYCFAK     
    
    
    Photo: Has anyone played #BovverBoysoftheDead? You play as a skin, listen to ska, and kill zombies. It’s... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqYIFxc     
    
    
    "I'm a full-on-rapist. Y'know? Africans. Dyslexics. Children. That sorta thing."    
    
    
    Can I offer you a nice egg in these trying times?    
    
    
    I find it weird and complimentary that I have to block as many people as I do    
    
    
    I hate the word "epic" and I hate the word "fail". I loathe the term "epic fail"    
    
    
    What collective actions do you feel we should be taking as an American society to combat self entitlement?    
    
    
    Participation ribbons, should be destroyed.    
    
    
    Photo: Found this randomly at #Bevmo. Probably gonna be the last time I buy this. Bought some stuff as a... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqhFD0D     
    
    
    Photo: Got this #IslanderIPA from #CoronadoBrewing as a backup. Proving once again that #SanDiego #craftbeer... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqhOF42     
    
    
    Photo: The truth hurts http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqnGdCN     
    
    
    Photo: I definitely am gonna get a #Condorito #tattoo http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqneqtH     
    
    
    Photo: Children’s literature. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqxgnCl     
    
    
    Photo: Steven #Urkel opens up the pit! #DidIDoThat http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqyTscI     
    
    
    Photo: Out of Step and on point! Yeahhh Booyyyyyyyyyyy! #MinorThreat #PublicEnemy #ChuckD and #FlavorFlav... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wr2X27b     
    
    
    My laptop froze for a bit. Weird! It's only happened 2-3 times since I've owned it. So rare I had to document it via twitter. #macbookpro    
    
    
    Photo: I wonder what card game they’d be playing? #SuicidalTendencies #IronMaiden #Megadeth #Motorhead... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wr5vfK_     
    
    
    Photo: I got your romantic quote right heeeah!! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wr8FdN7     
    
    
    Photo: Got a few booboos today http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrCka3X     
    
    
    Photo: Checking to see if I really need to shave. Pretty sure I’m using the hidef capabilities on my phone... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrD6FSr     
    
    
    Getting shit handled! That's what's up!    
    
    
    Photo: Do all dogs sleep like this? He’s been doing it a couple years now http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrJVEJw     
    
    
    I feel like such an old person every time I write a check    
    
    
    How do I never get tired of watching #Frasier? Probably been through the whole series a few times    
    
    
    #FearAndLoathing is #LostWages AKA #LasVegas #RenAndStimpy like to party too http://fb.me/CJHX8JZp     
    
    
    No, no no Meester Griffin #Consuela http://fb.me/2RRcFGKy0     
    
    
    I'm on fiyaaaa today. Can't stop, won't stop #uhuh    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1YGrgSKyG     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2fFbivFpT     
    
    
    Photo: Yet another thing I need to get for my future office/man cave. #Seinfeld #Costanza #seduction http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrWORiZ     
    
    
    #bowls #blunts or #dabs http://fb.me/PM46QB8Y     
    
    
    Everyday http://fb.me/2X0jgqE8m     
    
    
    Photo: The answer to all your financial woes. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrZlNO_     
    
    
    Photo: The #Kramer http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrf6cBH     
    
    
    Photo: I feel this being sent to me was no accident. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrsrgi8     
    
    
    Photo: #PeeWee dancing on a bar with bikers while wearing platform shows, never gets old for me. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wr_ZPIg     
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 @there_she_goz I liked his segments. Made me feel grown up, because he was so serious & talked about stuff I was interested    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 looks awesome    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 #DickJoke    
    
    
    Photo: #KanyeWest is a dipshit. I know that’s old news, but his record company, PR and marketing people... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0ws2HLGF     
    
    
    Photo: WTF does that even mean!!!!!?? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0ws7NAPQ     
    
    
    Photo: No one was allowed to touch the TV when this dude came on the screen. #ChavoDel8 #Chespirito #pipipi... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0ws9OXps     
    
    
    Photo: Abandoned at the #Greyhound station in #DowntownLA http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsK-GO4     
    
    
    Photo: #MovieQuote #RomperStomper http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsl9lQl     
    
    
    Are more pictures taken in female restrooms, teenage girl bedrooms or gyms?    
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxRD-c     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxRLIJ     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxRSsM     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxRwAK     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxSOJl     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxTPDa     
    
    
    Video: #KnickKnackPaddyWhack http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsyG0wb     
    
    
    Photo: Real life #DaleGribble AKA #RustyShackleford #KingOfTheHill #ShiShaw http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wt0F7Xi     
    
    
    Photo: He stole my pillow again. #Jerk http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wt2AJAi     
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 don't tell me what to do    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 #DickJoke    
    
    
    Photo: Not gonna mention any names, but if your gear doesn’t resemble this. Don’t fucking talk to me about... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtB2EIK     
    
    
    Photo: How many lives have these 3 dudes changed? #CircleJerks #MinorThreat #BlackFlag http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtCFmik     
    
    
    Photo: I was attending jr high in Calexico when a new kid transferred in from LA and let me borrow a... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtCNO_E     
    
    
    Photo: This is what my Saturday night is looking like. I’m a wild man. Don’t judge me. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtD6wYY     
    
    
    Saddest article ever http://fb.me/2i5XPbjeB     
    
    
    Photo: I’m pretty sure my desktop is cooler than yours. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtGrCw8     
    
    
    Photo: All of a sudden he wants to cuddle. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtN9iC9     
    
    
    @pdxcreep I see what you did there    
    
    
    Photo: #Naptime 2.0 http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtYUF3U     
    
    
    Photo: This is unacceptable! It’s hotter here than in #Calexico #bullcrap http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtiWIVj     
    
    
    Photo: This horrible heat called for a fresh cut. Loathing this weather http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtj27OQ     
    
    
    Pregaming with these tunes ♫ Banana – E. K. Bunch http://spoti.fi/147vadO  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    #Christmas movie binge for #LaborDay weekend http://fb.me/2jVREKX7I     
    
    
    Photo: #RedHook beer bottle caps http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtrGNNr     
    
    
    Photo: #MileyCyrus #twerk jams 2013 http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wtwbPAh     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2AzZPImIS     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wu7O3oZ     
    
    
    Photo: If you don’t know, now you know. H.S. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wuC_4qT     
    
    
    Photo: Had to share this rad #Cantinflas image. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wuC_kHn     
    
    
    Drained. Just mentally drained. I'll make tomorrow better.    
    
    
    I'm ok with you thinking that about me.    
    
    
    Lets burn this motherfucker down pookie!    
    
    
    Photo: Who wants free donuts from Krispy Kreme? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wuHacOA     
    
    
    Photo: So this is happening. #Mass #Pizza 36” In ya face http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wuN25eH     
    
    
    Photo: Anybody interested in a free and fake Fred Perry? I got it on eBay and was described as being made in... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wuRTC3f     
    
    
    Photo: I’m not the only one who’s had this happen on #CandyCrush right? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wuYegYg     
    
    
    Photo: What are you looking at? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wukrJ9g     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wukxyhX     
    
    
    Photo: Little dagger #tattoo for #FridayThe13th (at True Tattoo) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wuz5q9l     
    
    
    Check out Speech Jammer by @dwightpro on the App Store! http://dwightd.com/speech.html     
    
    
    Photo: Spotify isn’t always enough and you just have to own some of these albums. #Hepcat http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wv1G099     
    
    
    Photo: I want #iOS7 now!! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wvNcnAA     
    
    
    Photo: Yay! Now this is happening #ios7 shall be mine http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wvNdvkC     
    
    
    Photo: Yessss! Guess who’s got ios7!?? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wvNvTan     
    
    
    Photo: Pardon the grammar. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wvR3uqS     
    
    
    Photo: He’s got human eyes http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wvR5ItT     
    
    
    Photo: These are just facts. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wvbMu-4     
    
    
    Photo: Greatest name for a liquor store, ever!! #LiquorBox http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wvh3b8E     
    
    
    ♫ Roll 'Em Up – Vanilla Ice http://spoti.fi/11P6GDd  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    @Suedehead_Korey Your account has been hacked    
    
    
    @Suedehead_Korey pic.twitter.com/ngrlauRbri    
    
    
    @Suedehead_Korey sent you a screenshot. Unless you're pimping out those promotions on purpose. In which case, I understand #TheStruggle LOL    
    
    
    Photo: Got a new tiny toy today. #SkilletTools #MrsDabalina http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wwHupTt     
    
    
    Photo: Plans for the evening. I watched it on YouTube a while back and downloaded it. Just ordered a DVD... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wwIA72e     
    
    
    Kramer Lesson #44 - How to Make Sausages http://fb.me/1Lruxysa5     
    
    
    Photo: Decided to start a childhood dream toy collection and startIing with #PeeWee’s playhouse. I grew up... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wwS76Hi     
    
    
    Photo: I’ve posted this before, but this is totally me right now. Feeling frustrated and agitated. The... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wwT3DoF     
    
    
    Photo: Just arrived in the mail! #PeeWee figure w/ matching scooter and helmet. Chairry is happy as well http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wwhirv4     
    
    
    Photo: We’re down for each other. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wxK5sw1     
    
    
    Video: It was actually 2 different possums chilling on the fence. I stopped recording before they attacked http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wxLLGfT     
    
    
    Photo: I use my MacBook Pro everyday and still love it. Apple changed my opinion on computers as a whole!... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wxLtX8o     
    
    
    Photo: Guess who came up on a #BenSherman at the goodwill for $6? Weird how there was only 1 and it happened... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wxQ7SWI     
    
    
    Photo: Even though we’re going nowhere tonight. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wxQEehB     
    
    
    All kinds of awesome http://fb.me/6mhSh0GmR     
    
    
    Photo: That awkward feeling when you find something in the cupboard that you should’ve used years ago.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wxwxD9t     
    
    
    Photo: Now I really wanna carve a #FredPerry pumpkin myself http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wyjEbQ1     
    
    
    Photo: When #Halloween was scary http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wyoW7fq     
    
    
    Photo: Who got a new addition to his #PeeWeeHerman collection? I’m gonna take it out of the box when I get... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wywwaxW     
    
    
    Photo: I figure a proper gentlemen needs a shine box right? Maybe I’ll hunt down a vintage one. #Goodfellas http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wz0HpCx     
    
    
    Photo: Does anyone one where I can get either of these 2 eyeglass frames? Maybe some of my English friends... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wz5aNNB     
    
    
    Photo: Nap time for Mr Bama http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wzQsBgJ     
    
    
    Photo: I’d never seen a #mazapan that’s the size of a hockey puck!! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wzdzzKR     
    
    
    Photo: #BrickbyBrick tomorrow!!! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w_PoL_z     
    
    
    Photo: Why did I not have coffee today? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w-5Ig3s     
    
    
    Photo: These are the gangsters in the Mexican movie I’m watching. Pretty sure the dude on the far left is... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w-BLGVb     
    
    
    Photo: These are the types of things you end up with when you go to #Costco when you’re hungry. #regrets http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w-GYm88     
    
    
    Photo: Fresh dye and polish, toothbrushed the stitching and added new laces. #DrMartens are looking a bit... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w-TaTPW     
    
    
    Photo: Watching a Hispanic version of Jerry Springer - Uncensored. It’s a horrible rip off, with the same... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w-TvHW9     
    
    
    Photo: I was told I have a plaid shirt problem. I don’t see what the problem is. When all shirts are clean... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w-Z_paF     
    
    
    Our 1st run of the #Butchers Stash is being packed now!! Gotta keep our #SanDiego peeps fed proper. http://instagram.com/p/hOxNRanGkc/     
    
    
    Photo: I think this is what I’d look like if I was on a real soapbox giving my 8 cents http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w-pHgFI     
    
    
    Photo: Does anybody have any version of the #Maschine sampling hardware they wanna get rid of? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w100JRYV     
    
    
    Make sure to order your cut of the Butchers Stash this week! http://www.theheartandtrotter.com/services/  http://instagram.com/p/hb_AH-nGs3/     
    
    
    Photo: This is what #TheFonz thinks about insomnia. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w108olR6     
    
    
    Photo: Greyhound trip back to LA from Calexico. Riverside is like the 8th fucking stop so far. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w10ncY5g     
    
    
    Photo: Shaking the cobwebs off the old jackets. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w10y0EEc     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w10-Ccem     
    
    
    Photoset: "She’s in a little bit of a mood because her cat got stuck in the wall". http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w113pAr6     
    
    
    Photoset: twerkingderp: thecoffeeisntstrongenough: benthebum: violence-of-action: That’s cool as shit…… The... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w113q8aL     
    
    
    Photo: Got another #Fridaythe13th tattoo today http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w119KW3-     
    
    
    Photo: Friday night jams. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w119NnBN     
    
    
    Photo: I can probably make one of these right!? #baphomet http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11FmDjT     
    
    
    Photo: Words & junk. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11KabDR     
    
    
    Photo: My trusty old iPod is on its last leg. I can listen to music on my iPhone 5 for longer and still... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11Rgf2Q     
    
    
    Photo: This is how we roll http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11Ygady     
    
    
    Photo: Need a haircut sooooo bad. I got that 1970s microphone wind screen look going. Gonna have to hit up... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11Yi-hd     
    
    
    Photo: The gospel http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11eBRWU     
    
    
    asd http://fb.me/3mMP51Sce     
    
    
    Photo: Better late than never. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11pV5FA     
    
    
    Photo: If you hear boots stomping on your roof. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11pfCki     
    
    
    Video: Sometimes we just listen to music together. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11ps6iK     
    
    
    Video: #ReggaeFever http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11puDOc     
    
    
    Photo: #DiversifyYourBonds👐👐http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11pw31s     
    
    
    Photo: Gifts. Now I wanna put gifts under there. Gifts. I want gifts. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11vnpAb     
    
    
    Photo: #GilligansIsland #PoopDeck http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w11v__KZ     
    
    
    Photo: All kinds of awesome! #Griswold #ChristmasVacation http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w12C6d6t     
    
    
    Photo: I normally don’t watch mma fights or anything, but damn. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w12cEwFo     
    
    
    Video: Anybody wanna barter for the sake of bartering? This tiki lamp, flame thingie works and I’m not... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w12hOS1f     
    
    
    Photo: Thug shit, homie. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w12uNsv3     
    
    
    Photo: 1st selfie of 2014 http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0w12zOOZC     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Rad!! Real life intro to the Simpsons http://fb.me/IPJUE7c9     
    
    
    According to this kook, sweaters from the Goodwill could come with demons attached. http://fb.me/1xRJoPKoP     
    
    
    Eyes hurting from being glued to my computer all day. All good and thankful I get to do what I like full time now    
    
    
    When that one shot you need is so hard to get http://fb.me/1UvlySz0Q     
    
    
    Apparently its not such a good idea for someone my size to be jumping off of ledges. 4 feet isnt that high, but... http://fb.me/2AF2RLKYF     
    
    
    This and the iPhone are the best phones ever made. http://fb.me/wrD9bT7L     
    
    
    Pro Tranny MMA fighter http://fb.me/GtDrGoyu     
    
    
    Forever rad http://fb.me/1d9rSCM6N     
    
    
    I'd like to thank Time Warner Cable for allowing me to lose 2 hours worth of work and then completely losing My... http://fb.me/23BgqCili     
    
    
    RAD!!! Repurposed Skateboard decks, turned into guitars!! They look awesome and if you look at their post from... http://fb.me/ASeUAicc     
    
    
    I write content for blogs daily. Yet I feel I need to start writing more personal stuff also. Maybe ill get back to those #blogs I started    
    
    
    Whos taking the train to San Diego tomorrow? This guy!    
    
    
    So I wasn't able to take the Amtrak to San Diego after all. I came to the greyhound in North Hollywood and the guy... http://fb.me/CsRg0Rwp     
    
    
    1 whole day without my laptop and Im using our desktop PC to get some work done. Clearly remember why I stopped... http://fb.me/GzwbjBpv     
    
    
    Hashtags May Be Coming to Facebook. HA! All the confused people who use hashtags on Facebook, will be justified... http://fb.me/2jvx1EHTH     
    
    
    New Law Could Keep L.A. Bars Open Till 4 A.M http://fb.me/LRisUKG5     
    
    
    Inspiration for customization http://dimagec.com/  http://fb.me/D6l9GXvq     
    
    
    The original pledge of allegiance http://fb.me/1VvOidLR6     
    
    
    "Stop trying to pretend like youre dangerous, before you get hurt."    
    
    
    This coming Saturday, March 23 were back on stages after a long, long time at The Ruby Room for TOOTHLESS GEORGE... http://fb.me/1pglWa5qX     
    
    
    Hey San Diego peeps. I'm gonna be all up in ya at 5pm today. I lagged on reaching out last week. Who wants to get lunch?    
    
    
    Kitty wants some #RockNRoll style. Was #Lemmy the first person to rock a #bulletbelt ? http://instagram.com/p/XK-mVwLNBI/     
    
    
    Egocentrism

Egocentrism is characterized by preoccupation with one's own internal world. Egocentrics regard... http://fb.me/1ZCNY2yxS     
    
    
    According to #Goodyear blimp, #IceCube is a #pimp http://instagram.com/p/XQoTG4rNOx/     
    
    
    Photo: For the #Monday whine crowd #GrumpyCat puts you in check http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wh6NguM     
    
    
    Photo: #Sherbet ice cream, you’re my only friend today. You’re sugary, fruity goodness will scare this... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wh8loun     
    
    
    Apparently I smell like Sulfur. Ill take that as a compliment \m/    
    
    
    #Sulfur #Brimstone http://instagram.com/p/XT9NuArNLI/     
    
    
    Personal understatement for today. "Ill edit that website afterwards, it shouldn't take me that long." DARN!    
    
    
    Photo: I gotta say this is encouraging on different levels. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whEL6-z     
    
    
    Photo: What can’t it just #SanDiego weather here in #LosAngeles all the time!? It’s perfectly cloudy &... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whG8EA0     
    
    
    Photo: The band I’ve put the most work in & traveled the country with. Still going! #Cowpunk #SanDiego... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whJ7tpi     
    
    
    The Screamin Yeehaws | Rock from San Diego, CA http://fb.me/2kahh6mDH     
    
    
    Further words to live by. #business #hustle #pma http://instagram.com/p/XgKuxPLNPl/     
    
    
    Officially the best #easter pic you'll see today. #Lemmy makes everything cool. #Motorhead http://instagram.com/p/XiXhS3LNGG/     
    
    
    Photo: Officially the best #easter pic you’ll see today. #Lemmy makes everything cool. #Motorhead http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whav1zD     
    
    
    The need to create n perform will never die. I'm interested in starting a Vlog and/or podcast. Topical n comedic... http://fb.me/298jrFmRa     
    
    
    http://fb.me/F6HZfuwp     
    
    
    In case you ever feel like the most #intelligent person to ever walk your block; try reading & fully understanding #TheNewYorker    
    
    
    I really do live by this, every single day of my life. #WayGooder @ Flair Cleaners - Studio City http://instagram.com/p/XqNHs6LNAG/     
    
    
    I really do wanna get one of these, if for nothing else other than decorative and nostalgic purposes.… http://instagram.com/p/XrZv45LNMv/     
    
    
    Photo: I really do wanna get one of these, if for nothing else other than decorative and nostalgic purposes.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whtFfgA     
    
    
    Hey Cinderella, go find yourself a fella. You're on the clock, bitch and midnight is coming."… http://instagram.com/p/XsxHZ0rNJV/     
    
    
    Photo: Hey Cinderella, go find yourself a fella. You’re on the clock, bitch and midnight is coming.”... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whvlvQJ     
    
    
    Photo: A lot of people put in some serious work with these #hashtags ; Use Em, don’t abuse them.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0whyBIva     
    
    
    New Mad Sin video is awesome as expected http://fb.me/2U2jWeCl4     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1H5z0H9Pj     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2xlCjRfkA     
    
    
    Feel like I need this guy for my wit to be properly appreciated. Yeah that's what it is :) #Jokes #Wit… http://instagram.com/p/XvjX7ZLNLu/     
    
    
    The decadence of this place is one of the things I also miss about San Diego http://fb.me/MrGosmbG     
    
    
    Had to share this. Ive been trying this out for about a week now. Every night it helps with my upper back and... http://fb.me/2z61P1XuS     
    
    
    Photo: This applies to all areas of #business including musicians. #DoWork #Hustle (at Chateau De Beelzebub... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wi3QAqG     
    
    
    Photo: And that’s how your hats end up on the floor. #drunk #shenanigans http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wi5dTCp     
    
    
    Photo: Gonna give video games a shot. Again. #RedDeadRedemption won a bunch of awards & came highly... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wiFJ-Px     
    
    
    Got a lot accomplished today. Feeling tired, but relieved    
    
    
    Photo: Found DVD in a drawer. Been over 3 years and just watched it today. A cd release party we had at the... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wjLRMKP     
    
    
    Photo: Oh that’s right! That’s another reason I left; I needed a quick reminder. #instacollage #Calecia... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wjgt4pc     
    
    
    Photo: The DVD logo hit the corner right after, I swear. #greyhound #losangeles #SanDiego http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wk4KFxC     
    
    
    Bands like this are what makes my nerves settle.  ♫ The Slackers http://spoti.fi/ZSvsmx  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Photo: The EBay sniper strikes again! Just got these in the mail and got a great deal. Stoked. #FredPerry... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wkvccKJ     
    
    
    Photo: Feeling it. #Trojan #spiritof69 #SkinheadReggae http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wlEiCTM     
    
    
    Photo: One of these will hopefully be happening soon. #vespa #vespa1966 (at Chateau De Beelzebub ) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wldhCBW     
    
    
    Photo: This is me. Often. #SerenityNow #Seinfeld #InsanityLater (at Chateau De Beelzebub ) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wllWYo4     
    
    
    Photo: Seriously? There was a demand large enough that there had to be a run of these #DrMartens made? Who... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wln90NV     
    
    
    Photo: Finally got an #Apple #magicmouse & geeking out on it. In theory, this should make me more... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wlpoitc     
    
    
    Photo: I keep it #oldschool #otterpops #MassSnacks (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wlrRkCc     
    
    
    Photo: I’ve decided that I want a #StellaScooter & get the sidecar. P-series #Vespa w/ modern reliability.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wlx7CPc     
    
    
    Photo: This is what’s up for next Friday in #LA #TrojanLounge at the #FaisDoDo #SkinheadReggae #Rocksteady... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wl-PG2p     
    
    
    Photo: I grew up in a predominately Mexican town & was made to watch this movie many times during school.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wmARM91     
    
    
    Photo: #TrojanRecords collection is coming along. Almost have all of my first choices. #SkinheadReggae... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wmF6gP5     
    
    
    Photo: Sir, we have a zero tolerance rule for lightweights. Beat it, nerd! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wm_4mGt     
    
    
    Photo: #SanYsidro border crossing. How come the word on top isn’t translated? Always get into arguments with... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wn56cFO     
    
    
    Photo: #TheMoreYouKnow #Facts #CowsAreGood (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wn9Ib8H     
    
    
    Feeling calm and prosperous    
    
    
    Need coffee ASAP.... #makeithappen    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 Don't tell me what to do    
    
    
    That's awkward moment when you make #coffee and realize you're out of milk #DarnItToHeck    
    
    
    How come #Elvis impersonators generally tend to go for the fat Elvis?    
    
    
    @StuForReal As long as you don't feel like 2 of them.    
    
    
    @StuForReal just as well; I'm not here to judge ;)    
    
    
    Photo: This is close enough to me…if I was thin…and white….and nice to people. #TrojanRecords #Spiritof69... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnDAPRq     
    
    
    Finally gonna make time to tweet more. Now I'm looking for interesting people to follow with similar interests    
    
    
    @apogeepiercing wouldn't that be more like rubbing up against you?    
    
    
    Pharmacy taking hours. My frozen stuff isn't gonna keep much longer Hayley (@ Costco) http://4sq.com/11DmHbx     
    
    
    My brain refuses to wake up. Like other problems, I'll throw coffee at it and hope for the best    
    
    
    Photo: A lot of #BouncingSouls songs still strike a nerve years & years later. This hook from one of their... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnQDBcK     
    
    
    Photo: Not sure if it’s for the band #Suedehead or not, but this is awesome. (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnRca0c     
    
    
    Photo: Guilty pleasure confession. I’ve always liked #ArchieComics (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnWFta_     
    
    
    Photo: I’ve been through a few pairs of #DrMartens in my life. My shoe disease will never be cured and... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnXpJYb     
    
    
    #NoSoupForYou    
    
    
    Photo: A good friend of mine, whom I grew up with, just gave me this. A custom 7 string bass he had lying... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wng_H28     
    
    
    @Suedehead_Korey I'd totally try to abuse it and see how much #Hova could get away with.    
    
    
    Photo: You always have that uneasy feeling when using an establishments bathroom for the first time.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnhuytW     
    
    
    Photo: James Gandolfini is no longer around. I’ll always be a fan of #TonySoprano and all of his roles. (at... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnkrAME     
    
    
    I don't get what the appeal of that wipeout tv show is. I get it, they fall on padded surfaces and pools. Not that interesting    
    
    
    Photo: Why hello there Mr Rocko Bama http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnr3Ws8     
    
    
    Photo: My first video on here. #Deathmetal rooster actually makes me laugh out loud every time. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wnzX4SY     
    
    
    Why do most Craigslist job ads from "startups" claim to be successful. Yet, always wanna hire unpaid interns to do all the work for them?    
    
    
    Photo: Had this tasty soda today. Mostly for the novelty label, but tasty nonetheless. Taste the revolution.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wo7G41h     
    
    
    @HollywoodCimmy I've gone for 2 internships already to build my resume. #DuesPaid #PayMe    
    
    
    Photo: Found the perfect #coffee tumbler for myself. I love coffee and all of its great side effects. (at... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wo8OXKI     
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 Ready by 6am then? No bugs!    
    
    
    Photo: Did you know: #Coolio has a #juggalotattoo and also the words “Juggalo Cool” underneath it? He also... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woCUFLJ     
    
    
    Just noticed that #Zeitgeist is a trilogy    
    
    
    I love my MacBook Pro. There I said it    
    
    
    I think I've come to a point in my life where I now think every #conspiracytheory is bullshit.    
    
    
    Photo: #NoMames #Calma (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woDsed4     
    
    
    Photo: I need to shave, but I like my hair today #tuff (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woGrMbj     
    
    
    Photo: Part of the reason working from home is is both awesome and horrible. Found this particularly funny.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woO35Qe     
    
    
    That terrible Saturday morning feeling of being hungover & I didn't even drink last night #thatsthatshitidontlike    
    
    
    Photo: Realized I haven’t listened to #Sublime in a good while. The summer time heat always reminds me of... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woUJ5HM     
    
    
    Photo: Paper towel #coffee filter. #FTW #DIY #TheStruggle http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woUPIa1     
    
    
    I have nothing against #beerpong AKA #beirut but my neighbors play it damn near everyday. Does it never get old?...sidenote, I'm in my 30s    
    
    
    @HLove19 I've played a bit. I can't find the appeal of drinking games. Why do people drink in a hurry? Also, hangover are far worse after 25    
    
    
    @HLove19 Totally! #OldPeopleProbs    
    
    
    Multi vitamin & coffee are now in my body. Now I can think straight    
    
    
    @NeverWanderer discharged?    
    
    
    I'm finally getting into #snapchat add me - ErnieVelas    
    
    
    I want some turntables    
    
    
    Actually I need a #mancave or workspace area. To house all my music stuff & business related things    
    
    
    Photo: #Morrissey repping classic #skinhead imagery. #suedehead #subculture (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woXI0DF     
    
    
    Finally made the switch from disposable to grown up razors. Got a 1960s safety razor & it's the best shave I've ever had. #babybottom    
    
    
    Photo: Strange how overlooking through spreadsheets is what I’ve been looking forward to doing. People find... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wobny4W     
    
    
    Photo: Apparently July 1st is international #reggae day. Let us dance & stomp. (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wocRLwi     
    
    
    I want ceviche    
    
    
    I wanna move to Silverlake. There, I said it    
    
    
    Soooooo huuuunngry #FeedMe    
    
    
    If a company is looking for an intern and there's nobody with a similar role; how & what are you gonna learn? Don't fall for it.    
    
    
    #LA - The land of 1,000,0000 #startups    
    
    
    Photo: #fact #truthiness http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wof6-Z8     
    
    
    Photo: Another one for #InternationalReggaeDay #SkinheadReggae for days (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wof86ig     
    
    
    Photo: Next time I have a birthday party, I wanna hire a face painter and have them paint everyone’s face... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wognyd-     
    
    
    Sick of being tired, far & lazy    
    
    
    Photo: I Googled “Hepcat" to look for the bands main website and noticed that a Tribute band has the highest... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wol3nEs     
    
    
    Photo: Watching #Swingers and forgot this was an all around rad cast. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wopunbi     
    
    
    Photo: I was very spoiled having a gigantic #craftbeer selection at a lot of places in #SanDiego. #LA kinda... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0woqpjdj     
    
    
    Photo: Happy #4thofJuly #Merica!! (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0worFweC     
    
    
    Photo: Yep, that’s a fried dollar. Cus #Merica! That’s why! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0worJ7m5     
    
    
    I really wanna start a vinyl collection started. Always on the hunt for more stuff to do at home    
    
    
    Photo: …and that’s why he’ll always be a national hero. #Merica! (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wosmnNe     
    
    
    Photo: I’m sorry I can’t hear you over all this freedom! Happy 4th! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wos_AX_     
    
    
    Photo: Another American hero on this great 4th of July. As seen here taking a victory lap after winning the... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wotHMG5     
    
    
    Photo: That feeling you get when all of your shirts and shoes are clean & organized. (at Chateau De... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wo_5vce     
    
    
    Photo: Saw this at a parking lot in #NorthHollywood…wtf is #loafing!? (at Chateau De Beelzebub ) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wp33n_C     
    
    
    Photo: How many jokes can you think of between these 2 businesses and the connection between them? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wp34JBe     
    
    
    I want some #sweettea    
    
    
    Manipulative people play the victim to justify themselves – being diluted in how they treat others & what they believe about themselves    
    
    
    #LosAngeles really needs to step up its #craftbeer game.    
    
    
    Finally found a place that offers my favorite spicy junk food. Frozen yogurt is good here also. Plan on trying every… http://www.yelp.com/biz/slusheeland-north-hollywood?pt=quick_tip&ref=twitter&v=5a …    
    
    
    Photo: Trying to figure out what all I can do with this 7 string beast. I was getting cocky with 4 strings... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpCVDVA     
    
    
    I like a lot of bands. I like certain bands a shitload. I like playing music, I love playing shows. No urge to start a "tribute" band,at all    
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/vbUrEp  #in    
    
    
    Watching anything on YouTube with an #iphone5 using wifi is fucking impossible.    
    
    
    I'm gonna switch one of my basses to flatwound strings. Get some thumping going on    
    
    
    Photo: If you claim it. #BeAboutIt #BoutThatLife #MyAss ha #GetSome (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpNe5pq     
    
    
    Photo: Finally got to sit down and play one of these. I want one. I still love my #Fender p-bass special &... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpNuF3w     
    
    
    Photo: Newest acquisition for my #FredPerry collection. Not sure if I can call it a collection, because... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpPxGxC     
    
    
    Easy Rider| Tosh.0 | Comedy Central http://tosh.comedycentral.com/blog/2013/07/11/easy-rider/ …    
    
    
    Photo: Carne Asada tortas with refried beans w chorizo. All kinds of Mexican stuff is happening.... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpSO8yc     
    
    
    Photo: "It’s a fool that looks for logic in the chambers of the human heart." One of my favorite quotes from... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpSt-bv     
    
    
    Photo: Because #HomerSkin was a badass. #Woohoo (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpW5CLT     
    
    
    I think it might be safe to wear a fedora again    
    
    
    Photo: I’d rip that #Pendleton off a #hipster #battlestargalactica http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpbRa7r     
    
    
    Photo: #UruapanMexicanLoqui (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpcYHHx     
    
    
    Photo: Part of the birthday gifts @hayleywilcox84 got me today. A custom beer pilsner flute that reads... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpccheu     
    
    
    Video: Late night, classic Mexican drinking tunes. #Tucanes #3Animales (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpchh4H     
    
    
    I want a pair of brown Dickies    
    
    
    Now accepting get rich quick schemes    
    
    
    When your head receives a landslide of insults you could've said during an argument you had a week ago    
    
    
    Can a 3d printer printer a 3d printer?    
    
    
    How low does a lowlow have to go?    
    
    
    An I the only one whose got #LAriots nostalgia?    
    
    
    #LAPD putting in work. Maybe they needed a change from pushin around bums & tickets for not tapping your card    
    
    
    Riot gear is on and it's getting real over on Crenshaw.    
    
    
    How is the winner decided in these things? The ratio of convenience stores that were stolen over the the norm? Do you compare it to 1992?    
    
    
    @Hollywood_WOF @TheLAScene oh shit it got all granola!    
    
    
    Top 5 places you'd love to loot during a riot......and go!!    
    
    
    @TheLAScene These granola munchers are gonna take the credit and claim this to have been successful #DarnThem    
    
    
    I really gotta play some music. Going stir crazy    
    
    
    Any time is a good time to exercise I suppose    
    
    
    Learned to edit some stuff on #imovie, what's the long way to say that, so it'll go on a resume?    
    
    
    #TalkAboutYourCrush  ok, fine; it's mostly #SugarWaterPurple pic.twitter.com/AlsFWReznm    
    
    
    These beautiful @DelJunction #rudeboy shoes need to be mine ASAP pic.twitter.com/IH2hgLXUQl    
    
    
    British Style Genius - The Street Look - Part 3 http://youtu.be/Pbm6_FqjEHA     
    
    
    I've got a hater who is pathetically not subtle. I'll take it as a compliment, because you'll always be lame. No matter what stories make up    
    
    
    Photo: This is one of those records that’ll never get old for me. I had the first 2 #CypressHill albums on... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpl0uY6     
    
    
    There's nothing wrong with being proud of your culture. But posting about it every single day w/ tons of hashtags is annoying.    
    
    
    Overly boasting your ethnicity on social networks can become annoying. Especially, if you've never been to the country you rant & rave about    
    
    
    Just finished watching #SharkNado. It's exactly what I thought it'd be and a few steps more. A golden thumbs down, for #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    What if I make #TerribleAwesomeness my signature hashtag for a while?    
    
    
    @jwoodham You had a good run. I'd suggest a TV movie about your twitter career.    
    
    
    That moment you get the spins from so much sugar from that fistful of taffy you had #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    That moment when the condom breaks and she doesn't care #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    Long pointy boots, white denim and a curly mullet? #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    #Celebrity #SexTape!? But it's #HulkHogan ~ #TerribleAwesomeness    
    
    
    Seriously #WantNewCar from @Honda~it'd be so life changing I'd work it into every convo I ever have "Hey did I tell you when...YES YOU DID!"    
    
    
    I need a haircut so bad    
    
    
    #Instagram has helped launch a ridiculous amount of imaginary #modeling careers.    
    
    
    The #hustle is getting stronger #stoked    
    
    
    My stuff is finally coming together. Had to separate myself from the charlatans & positively gravitate towards like minded individuals #RAD    
    
    
    Photo: I’m gonna have to get all of these. #TMNT #80s http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wprUSjV     
    
    
    Is #tofu #pho any good?    
    
    
    Photo: Have to stay looking sharp. @socalkutz #barbers always deliver rad results. #TrojanLounge (at Chateau... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpwEBp4     
    
    
    #ProjectBadass    
    
    
    Photo: #SnoopDogg medicated #bbq sauce is happening. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wpwL57Z     
    
    
    How does my dog always find that perfect angle, where he uses up most of the bed?    
    
    
    The older you get, the less you can trust a fart to be just that    
    
    
    Every morning I play a game called "Lets see how many parts of my body crack as I get out of bed"    
    
    
    Why does 2% milk cost the same as whole milk? #Shenanigans    
    
    
    How old is too old to have a pimple?    
    
    
    Why do you look before you flush?    
    
    
    Most towns across the country, people get out of my way & strangers dont aske shit. In #LA I get asked what ingredients are needed for tacos    
    
    
    @fingerbangs Most awkward ending to a #Scrabble game, ever!    
    
    
    Do people still have penpals that aren't in prison?    
    
    
    A deleted Instagram account is now referred to as a "formal modeling career"    
    
    
    My eyebrows grow so ferociously, that I could easily be mistaken for Persian dude, if I wore a ski mask    
    
    
    My lottery ticket retirement plan is a pre capital venture at the moment. Stay tuned for updates.    
    
    
    That awkward moment when you're waiting for the sleep medicine to kick in & don't know if you have time for a movie    
    
    
    @tonejonzz Keep hope alive; you will get past this!    
    
    
    I'm thinking of doing consulting work for companies. What's the average salary for a de-motivational speaker?    
    
    
    #UPGRADDE ~  Why two D's?  So we can get a double dose of dis pimpin'!    
    
    
    What are Canadian only curse words?    
    
    
    I never know how to compliment women that have nicer sideburns than me    
    
    
    Ever give someone the wrong directions on purpose?    
    
    
    Is there a way to make deli meat a dessert?    
    
    
    #Fact - Your penis grows 1/2 inch every time you peel out of a driveway    
    
    
    Is there a way to make multi level parking not make everyone sound like a formula 1 racer?    
    
    
    Do I have to have a playlist before I start going to a gym? Sidenote- Is that why everyone is a #DJ now?    
    
    
    Waking up early for no reason is not as awesome as Id hoped.    
    
    
    Photo: Side effects may include a happier, satisfying life. (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wp-q4rh     
    
    
    Photo: Seeing what an IPA in a can tastes like. Doing a self guided tour of #LA #craftbeer - so far, so good... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wq0qOPz     
    
    
    The first time I went to #Texas, I expected to bump into Hank Hill    
    
    
    Any burrito worth more than $7 better be like a carne asada money shot in my mouth    
    
    
    There's a layer of filth, that'll never wash off    
    
    
    How often do "jumping jacks" just turn into "hopping and flailing"?    
    
    
    Maybe it was a bad idea to drink beers while laying on the couch. For a Homer Simpson thing going on #Doh    
    
    
    Photo: #AmericanAsylum #AmericanHorrorStory for the sake of #meme (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wq12loN     
    
    
    @ikunsaurus Good to meet you man    
    
    
    Puns will always be funny to me    
    
    
    Need to start playing shows more often. Playing once next month. Any good traditional #ska or #reggae bands in #LA need a good #bass player?    
    
    
    @pdxcreep Ha! Thanks for the RT #grateful    
    
    
    @shesananteater The back of women's knees is like men's  5th favorite erotic zone. Right after armpits.    
    
    
    The next marketing campaign for @RollingStone is just going to be called #OurBad    
    
    
    Eyebrow shaping is a constant struggle with an inevitable loss. To them.    
    
    
    Apparently I already had a KIK account. Add me now ~ ErnieVelas    
    
    
    I'm to old to know people who claim to hate shit they were doing last week.    
    
    
    Older video & the sound isnt the best. Still awesome. #SkinheadReggae The Aggrolites "Funky Fire" http://youtu.be/hi4Ys9CgSfE     
    
    
    @Ernycakes It's always a beautiful city. #ComicCon just gums up commuting & bars for a few days    
    
    
    @Angeleyes_619 Great fucking band. My neighbors might hate by now. Haven't met them yet, have a few friends in common w/ those dudes    
    
    
    @Ernycakes I wanna go to this    
    
    
    That angry/vengeful/satisfying feeling when a mosquito goes up your nose. You're angry it happened, and he got what he deserved    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 [maybe] written in crayon    
    
    
    @Angeleyes_619 No prob. Are you from #SanDiego?    
    
    
    @Angeleyes_619 I asked cause you have 619 in your handle and I lived in San Diego a few years. I live in #NorthHollywood now    
    
    
    @Ernycakes Dope. I'm there    
    
    
    @CackleClub The DMV might take issue to a name that long    
    
    
    Add me on @Kik: ErnieVelas http://kik.com/u/ErnieVelas     
    
    
    Video: Din din http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wq5cbg5     
    
    
    Photo: "Be as a lion in the path. Be dangerous even in defeat." —Anton Szandor LaVey #COS #HS #LaVeyQuote... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wq6fIa6     
    
    
    Why do stupid people love to give advice?    
    
    
    Maybe I will start my own business after all. Everyone else in this city is doing it    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 I'm already selling this video to food fetish sites    
    
    
    The Old Firm Casuals live at Pieffe Factory 2012 (full show) HD http://youtu.be/nYsN2XQTdBE     
    
    
    @uladhexile He had a big closet cleaning sale on eBay w/ his punk rock gear & became a freshcut at 40. I still like his bands n all. Thanks!    
    
    
    How does one go stir crazy?    
    
    
    Checking my temperature for cabin fever    
    
    
    How good were you at #Monopoly? Did you feel bad when you took other people's money?    
    
    
    Photo: I quite possibly may now have the coolest twitter header ever. #Bootleg verification check mark and a... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqHR0ep     
    
    
    Don't let anyone tell you how dumb you are. You should already be aware, after a lifetime of stupid decisions.    
    
    
    They should make a #LemonySnicket remake & have it take place in the ghetto,where an entirely different series of unfortunate events happen    
    
    
    Ever feel that street signs come off as being pushy?    
    
    
    @ErnieVelas: Do they have a refrigerated pillow yet? If not @thesharperimage needs to step up their game    
    
    
    When is #hypercolor clothing gonna make a comeback?    
    
    
    I wonder if all of my old @McDonalds #HappyMeal toys are together somewhere & playing w/ my lost socks, talking about how they don't need me    
    
    
    #SanDiego #craftbeer --- I miss you. Do you think about me also?    
    
    
    Photo: I’ve actually been looking for a chart like this. Wanna start cooking and never know what’s in... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqHuUbw     
    
    
    Somebody needs to talk me out of buying these boots on eBay    
    
    
    @LisaMariaOrtiz You're to far to be throwing down challenges like that, lady :)    
    
    
    @HLove19 Thank you. Cooler heads prevailed and I chose to hold off. eBay is my cryptonite    
    
    
    @LisaMariaOrtiz Ha! I'm a musician, so I flail around on the beat    
    
    
    @LisaMariaOrtiz I guess that's what I was trying to say :p    
    
    
    This country fought for independence so we wouldn't have to care about the #RoyalBaby pic.twitter.com/8BL8RAvlgP    
    
    
    @radiomaru parallels for Mac    
    
    
    The Kids in the Hall are Reuniting Again – IFC http://www.ifc.com/fix/2013/07/the-kids-in-the-hall-reuniting …    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 pic.twitter.com/X2XwKdtzqu    
    
    
    Photo: This freakin guy :) (at Chateau De Beelzebub) http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqNKdAe     
    
    
    Boots with the furrrrrrr    
    
    
    Melatonin you're my only fr.......    
    
    
    How many super moons are we gonna have?    
    
    
    Boom, boom pow    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 bad grammar. Disgusting    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 Digusting    
    
    
    You wouldn't think it'd be this hard to find good musicians in LA    
    
    
    Why do white denim jeans exist?    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 I'd Does flinging these at you with a slingshot count? pic.twitter.com/A60diRWbxW    
    
    
    Netflix needs a late night section. Not softcore, something like infomercials    
    
    
    @SunsetSherry tweeting about it counts as soliciting    
    
    
    @SunsetSherry Let me know if you need "management" I have a snazzy outfit & a fucking fish bowl I've been wanting to drink out of in public    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 A true romantic :)    
    
    
    @shesananteater Yes. We should split a pizza    
    
    
    @DIDUSAYCHEESE It learned to tweet.    
    
    
    @jenlaw_11 Tell me more about the Taco Bell    
    
    
    #KanyeWestIsTheKindOfGuyThatWill RT one of his own tweets and star that one as well.  @kanyewest likes that about @kanyewest    
    
    
    Wtf is a #bumgun!?    
    
    
    Those fake friend requests are extremely obvious there guy. Wouldn't expect anything creative though.    
    
    
    Keep on truckin, nerd :)    
    
    
    Photo: Randomly found this. Ead designer. #TradSkin #Spiritof69 #HardMod #Skinhead #Suedehead #subculture http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqYCFAK     
    
    
    Photo: Has anyone played #BovverBoysoftheDead? You play as a skin, listen to ska, and kill zombies. It’s... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqYIFxc     
    
    
    "I'm a full-on-rapist. Y'know? Africans. Dyslexics. Children. That sorta thing."    
    
    
    Can I offer you a nice egg in these trying times?    
    
    
    I find it weird and complimentary that I have to block as many people as I do    
    
    
    I hate the word "epic" and I hate the word "fail". I loathe the term "epic fail"    
    
    
    What collective actions do you feel we should be taking as an American society to combat self entitlement?    
    
    
    Participation ribbons, should be destroyed.    
    
    
    Photo: Found this randomly at #Bevmo. Probably gonna be the last time I buy this. Bought some stuff as a... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqhFD0D     
    
    
    Photo: Got this #IslanderIPA from #CoronadoBrewing as a backup. Proving once again that #SanDiego #craftbeer... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqhOF42     
    
    
    Photo: The truth hurts http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqnGdCN     
    
    
    Photo: I definitely am gonna get a #Condorito #tattoo http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqneqtH     
    
    
    Photo: Children’s literature. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqxgnCl     
    
    
    Photo: Steven #Urkel opens up the pit! #DidIDoThat http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wqyTscI     
    
    
    Photo: Out of Step and on point! Yeahhh Booyyyyyyyyyyy! #MinorThreat #PublicEnemy #ChuckD and #FlavorFlav... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wr2X27b     
    
    
    My laptop froze for a bit. Weird! It's only happened 2-3 times since I've owned it. So rare I had to document it via twitter. #macbookpro    
    
    
    Photo: I wonder what card game they’d be playing? #SuicidalTendencies #IronMaiden #Megadeth #Motorhead... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wr5vfK_     
    
    
    Photo: I got your romantic quote right heeeah!! http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wr8FdN7     
    
    
    Photo: Got a few booboos today http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrCka3X     
    
    
    Photo: Checking to see if I really need to shave. Pretty sure I’m using the hidef capabilities on my phone... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrD6FSr     
    
    
    Getting shit handled! That's what's up!    
    
    
    Photo: Do all dogs sleep like this? He’s been doing it a couple years now http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrJVEJw     
    
    
    I feel like such an old person every time I write a check    
    
    
    How do I never get tired of watching #Frasier? Probably been through the whole series a few times    
    
    
    #FearAndLoathing is #LostWages AKA #LasVegas #RenAndStimpy like to party too http://fb.me/CJHX8JZp     
    
    
    No, no no Meester Griffin #Consuela http://fb.me/2RRcFGKy0     
    
    
    I'm on fiyaaaa today. Can't stop, won't stop #uhuh    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1YGrgSKyG     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2fFbivFpT     
    
    
    Photo: Yet another thing I need to get for my future office/man cave. #Seinfeld #Costanza #seduction http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrWORiZ     
    
    
    #bowls #blunts or #dabs http://fb.me/PM46QB8Y     
    
    
    Everyday http://fb.me/2X0jgqE8m     
    
    
    Photo: The answer to all your financial woes. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrZlNO_     
    
    
    Photo: The #Kramer http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrf6cBH     
    
    
    Photo: I feel this being sent to me was no accident. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wrsrgi8     
    
    
    Photo: #PeeWee dancing on a bar with bikers while wearing platform shows, never gets old for me. http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wr_ZPIg     
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 @there_she_goz I liked his segments. Made me feel grown up, because he was so serious & talked about stuff I was interested    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 looks awesome    
    
    
    @TinyNightmare1 #DickJoke    
    
    
    Photo: #KanyeWest is a dipshit. I know that’s old news, but his record company, PR and marketing people... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0ws2HLGF     
    
    
    Photo: WTF does that even mean!!!!!?? http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0ws7NAPQ     
    
    
    Photo: No one was allowed to touch the TV when this dude came on the screen. #ChavoDel8 #Chespirito #pipipi... http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0ws9OXps     
    
    
    Photo: Abandoned at the #Greyhound station in #DowntownLA http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsK-GO4     
    
    
    Photo: #MovieQuote #RomperStomper http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsl9lQl     
    
    
    Are more pictures taken in female restrooms, teenage girl bedrooms or gyms?    
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxRD-c     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxRLIJ     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxRSsM     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxRwAK     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxSOJl     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsxTPDa     
    
    
    Video: #KnickKnackPaddyWhack http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wsyG0wb     
    
    
    Photo: Real life #DaleGribble AKA #RustyShackleford #KingOfTheHill #ShiShaw http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wt0F7Xi     
    
    
    Photo: He stole my pillow again. #Jerk http://tmblr.co/ZSS_0wt2AJAi     
    
    
    