Colorado State volleyball moves up to No. 9 in this week's AVCA Coaches Poll. Rams are undefeated.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball moves up to No. 9 in this week's AVCA Coaches Poll. Rams are undefeated.    
    
    
    New Mexico's Alex Kirk is the Mountain West men's basketball Player of the Week. #MWBB    
    
    
    Colorado State is No. 20 in this week's NCAA volleyball RPI. Not looking good for the undefeated Rams to host the NCAA tournament.    
    
    
    @kyle_mccall totally ...    
    
    
    Per @KellyLyell, Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs not expected to play in must-win game against Air Force on Saturday http://www.coloradoan.com/article/20131125/SPORTS0201/311250074/Injury-sidelines-Colorado-State-s-record-breaking-back-Kapri-Bibbs …    
    
    
    Colorado State kicker Jared Roberts did not make the cut to be one of 3 finalists for the Groza Award. Roberts was a semifinalist.    
    
    
    @kyle_mccall totally ...    
    
    
    @kyle_mccall totally ...    
    
    
    Colorado State kicker Jared Roberts did not make the cut to be one of 3 finalists for the Groza Award. Roberts was a semifinalist.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball's chances of hosting NCAA tournament take a hit in latest RPI http://noconow.co/1biXAUW     
    
    
    New entrance to Colorado State's McGraw Center. Looks really nice. pic.twitter.com/WsLVrvSDwv    
    
    
    The Colorado State basketball team is breaking out new gold uniforms vs. Prairie View A&M tonight #mwbb pic.twitter.com/eBCpYajMMP    
    
    
    This is the first time Colorado State has worn gold uniforms in men's basketball since at least 2006-07.    
    
    
    Eight minutes until Colorado State and Prairie View A&M tip off at Moby Arena and it's clear fall break has started. pic.twitter.com/sLiBwXMcC7    
    
    
    COLUMN: Some of you wanted Colorado State's football coaches fired? http://noconow.co/19UZ4OR  #mwfb    
    
    
    Octeus, Cohn, Avila, Bejarano and Santo starting for Colorado State vs. PVAMU    
    
    
    Wonder if there's any history between PVAMU's John Brisco and Colorado State's JJ Avila. Brisco made it a point to deny pregame handshake    
    
    
    Both are from Texas    
    
    
    Prairie View A&M calls a time out. Colorado State leads 8-6 with 16:38 left in the first. #mwbb    
    
    
    Back-to-back 3-pointers by David Cohn. Colorado State leads Prairie View A&M 14-8.    
    
    
    Prairie View A&M's man-to-man defense is so bad, it looks like the Panthers are trying to run a zone.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Prairie View A&M 22-12 with 11:20 left in the first half. David Cohn has 8 points. #mwbb    
    
    
    Joe De Ciman with 5 straight points, prompting a Prairie View A&M TO. Colorado State leads 28-12 with 9:05 left in the first.    
    
    
    Prairie View A&M's Demondre Chapman hurt going for a loose ball. Has 9 points, 2 boards.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Prairie View A&M 35-24 with 3:53 remaining in the first half. #mwbb    
    
    
    Rams are shooting 63 percent from the field.    
    
    
    There's a female Colorado State fan at Moby Arena tonight wearing a Willis Gardner jersey. Repping 2007!    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Prairie View A&M 49-31 at halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    At halftime, Colorado State is shooting 65 percent from the field, 66 percent from the free-throw line. #mwbb    
    
    
    There's a female Colorado State fan at Moby Arena tonight wearing a Willis Gardner jersey. Repping 2007!    
    
    
    Gerson Santo just tied his career high with 12 points.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball's chances of hosting NCAA tournament take a hit in latest RPI http://noconow.co/1biXAUW     
    
    
    David Cohn rattles home his third 3-pointer of the game. 11 points from the true freshman    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Prairie View A&M 60-41 with 15:10 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    CSU gets the jump ball, but I'm pretty sure not a single Ram was touching it. Officials should next try to get the jump call correct    
    
    
    With 11:48 remaining, Colorado State leads Prairie View A&M 69-46. #mwbb    
    
    
    CSU gets the jump ball, but I'm pretty sure not a single Ram was touching it. Officials should next try to get the jump call correct    
    
    
    Colorado State is up 79-58 on Prairie View A&M with 7:12 to play. Marcus Holt will shoot two after the TO. #mwbb    
    
    
    At the final media TO, Colorado State leads Prairie View A&M 86-63. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State makes easy work of Prairie View A&M, winning 95-68. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State out-rebounded Prairie View A&M, 46-23. 19 of the Rams' boards were on offense. #mwbb    
    
    
    Unselfish Colorado State basketball team beats down Prairie View A&M http://noconow.co/19YqV0N  #mwbb    
    
    
    VIDEO: Tip off of Colorado State vs. PVAMU http://instagram.com/p/hKsgFvsMUU/     
    
    
    What does everyone think of Colorado State's new gold basketball uniforms? http://noconow.co/19YqV0N  (PHOTO GALLERY) @uniwatch    
    
    
    Colorado State has green, white, orange and gold basketball uniforms. What do players want next? Jon Octeus says gray. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State has green, white, orange and gold basketball uniforms. What do players want next? Jon Octeus says gray. #mwbb    
    
    
    Join @KellyLyell at noon for our weekly Colorado State football chat http://noconow.co/1a0SMNU  #mwfb    
    
    
    I asked Colorado State coach Larry Eustachy how the Rams have cut back on fouls the past two games. He said it's "home cooking."    
    
    
    I'm at MoJeaux's Bar & Grill (Fort Collins, CO) http://4sq.com/1bUeIv7     
    
    
    Reminder: The Colorado State men's basketball game vs. Bethune-Cookman is at 2 p.m. today at Moby Arena. #mwbb    
    
    
    Regional men's hoops RPI rankings: CU (16), Wyoming (87) Northern Colorado (116), Denver (186), Colorado State (242), Air Force (328).    
    
    
    Sorry, noticed I botched my slug    
    
    
    Less than 2,000 tickets remain for Tuesday's CU vs. Colorado State basketball game at Moby Arena. Student tix go up for grabs this weekend.    
    
    
    Octeus, Bejarano, Hurst, Santo and Avila starting for Colorado State today. First career start for Carlton Hurst.    
    
    
    Gian Luis Clavell and the NW Technical College basketball team are the the CSU game today. Clavell signed with CSU pic.twitter.com/Fskqa42QKq    
    
    
    Colorado State with an early 7-2 lead over Bethune-Cookman. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Bethune-Cookman 7-4 with 15:30 remaining in the first half. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Bethune-Cookman 15-10 at the second media TO. Daniel Bejarnao and JJ Avila both lead the Rams with 4 points. #mwbb    
    
    
    Bethune-Cookman's Maurice Taylor picks up a technical. JJ Avila sinks both FTs. #mwbb    
    
    
    Gerson Santo just picked up foul No. 3 with 8:58 to go in the first half. Had a career-high 16 points Monday.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Bethune-Cookman 24-11 with 7:52 left in the first. JJ Avila has 13 points fo the Rams and 2 rebounds. #mwbb    
    
    
    Less than 2,000 tickets remain for Tuesday's CU vs. Colorado State basketball game at Moby Arena. Student tix go up for grabs this weekend.    
    
    
    Bethune-Cookman trails Colorado State 30-17 with 3:49 until halftime. Lower scoring game than I was expecting, but Rams shooting 53 percent.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Bethune-Cookman 35-21 at the half. JJ Avila leads the Rams with 16 points. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Rams lead Bethune-Cookman 35-28 with 16:13 remaining. #mwbb    
    
    
    Bethune-Cookman has cut Colorado State's lead down to six with 13:30 to go    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Bethune-Cookman 42-35 with 11:49 remaining. #mwbb    
    
    
    Former Colorado State defensive coordinator Larry Kerr is at the Rams' basketball game vs. Bethune-Cookman.    
    
    
    Colorado State is leading Bethune-Cookman 62-44 with 3:34 to play. Rams are going to move to 5-2 on the season. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State beats Bethune-Cookman 66-52. Rams move to 5-2 on the season and will next play New Mexico State on Saturday. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State wins low-scoring basketball game against Bethune-Cookman http://noconow.co/1a6klp5  #mwbb    
    
    
    VIDEO: Colorado State basketball recruit Gian Clavell (@clavelito04) makes surprise visit to Rams' game  http://noconow.co/1a6klp5     
    
    
    I'm at Carmike 10 Cinemas for The Hunger Games: Catching Fire (Fort Collins, CO) http://4sq.com/1fKJ3Dl     
    
    
    The worst part of Texas A&M leaving the Big 12: Texas vs. TAMU used to be my favorite Thanksgiving tradition.    
    
    
    I'm thankful for my Twitter followers. #kissup    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving! http://instagram.com/p/hSEdmgsMZz/     
    
    
    Five Mountain West volleyball titles in five seasons for Colorado State's Michelle Smith http://noconow.co/17ZzCLz  #ncaavb    
    
    
    Michelle Smith is only the second player in @CSUVolleyball history to win five regular season MW titles http://noconow.co/17ZzCLz     
    
    
    New Mexico State leads the nation in free throw attempts. Colorado State ranks 5th. Saturday could be a long basketball game.    
    
    
    New Mexico State also leads the nation in free throws made. CSU ranks fourth, nationally, in that category.    
    
    
    Colorado State capitalizing on free throws taking over college basketball http://noconow.co/1aeFuNV  #mwbb    
    
    
    A very bad day for Mountain West football outside of the Bay Area. So much for that payday.    
    
    
    San Jose State might have just knocked UNLV out of a bowl game. That is, of course, if CSU beats Air Force tomorrow.    
    
    
    I think a bowl easily takes a 7-6 Colorado State team over a 6-6 UNLV squad. If UNLV beats SDSU, things get complicated.    
    
    
    What Colorado State has going for it is Kapri Bibbs (if healthy) and bordering New Mexico. That will help travel to NM Bowl.    
    
    
    Watching the Union-Broken Arrow semifinal game online. #ilovetechnology    
    
    
    Watching the Union-Broken Arrow semifinal game online. #ilovetechnology    
    
    
    Here at Moby Arena to cover No. 9 Colorado State against UNLV for the Rams' volleyball senior night.    
    
    
    Al Bundy is one of the officials for this Colorado State vs. UNLV volleyball match    
    
    
    Denny, Foss, Culbert, Peters, Snider, Reynolds and Colaizzi (libero) starting for Colorado State tonight vs. UNLV    
    
    
    UNLV calls a TO. Colorado State leads 7-2 in the first set. #vbscores    
    
    
    Another TO by UNLV. Colorado State leads 16-8 in Set 1. #vbscores    
    
    
    No. 9 Colorado State takes Set 1 from UNLV, 25-15. #vbscores    
    
    
    Colorado State is out to an early 5-0 lead in Set 2 vs. UNLV    
    
    
    Colorado State takes Set 2 from UNLV, 25-9. Rams lead the match 2-0. First time CSU has held a team to single digits #vbscores    
    
    
    UNLV jumps out to an early 4-1 lead over Colorado State in Set 3. Rams call a TO (2-0, CSU). #vbscores    
    
    
    Colorado State leads UNLV 10-6 in the third set. Rams going for a sweep on Senior Night. #vbscores    
    
    
    No. 9 Colorado State sweeps UNLV on Senior Night. Rams finish the regular season 28-1 and win their fifth straight Mountain West title.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball makes final push to host NCAA tournament with sweep of UNLV http://noconow.co/183e8xk  #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State women's basketball team get past Hawaii in overtime http://noconow.co/183oA80  via @KellyLyell    
    
    
    For your Colorado State vs. NMSU preview, learn about how free throws are taking over basketball http://noconow.co/1aeFuNV  #mwbb #wac    
    
    
    VIDEO: @CSUVolleyball celebrates Mountain West championship on senior night http://noconow.co/183pxx6  #ncaavb    
    
    
    @GoRamsGo sorry, noticed a typo and tweeted it again    
    
    
    Come join @KellyLyell and me for our Colorado State vs. Air Force pregame chat http://noconow.co/1ai5tE2  #mwfb    
    
    
    Colorado State will be wearing green tops with gold pants today vs. Air Force.    
    
    
    Air Force is wearing gray helmets, jerseys and pants today against Colorado State. #mwfb    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs doing more than just taking quick reps. He's running with the first offense in pregame drills.    
    
    
    The Tanner Hedstrom clan tailgating pregame. pic.twitter.com/dPPVoICgTb    
    
    
    Chris Nwoke officially announced as the starter at RB for Colorado State today over Kapri Bibbs.    
    
    
    Here's a shot of Colorado State celebrating its 5th straight MW volleyball title on senior night pic.twitter.com/fXmpzf10us    
    
    
    Colorado State and Air Force have kicked off. Come join our @coloradoan live game chat http://noconow.co/1ai5tE2  #mwfb    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs is in the game    
    
    
    Colorado State QB Garrett Grayson needs 34 yards to reach 3,000 passing this season. #mwfb    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs with a 3-yard TD run, his 26th of the year. Colorado State leads Air Force 7-0 in the first quarter.    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs with his second TD of the first quarter for Colorado State. 27th of the season. Rams lead Air Force 13-0 (PAT pending).    
    
    
    Shaq Bell with a beautiful INT, but called for interference. Tough break for him, should have been offensive PI. Pretty clear    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Air Force 13-0 at the end of the first quarter.    
    
    
    Colorado State QB Garrett Grayson was 10 of 14 passing in the first quarter for 140 yards.    
    
    
    Air Force goes for the fake punt from its own 43 and comes up about a yard short. Colorado State with good field position.    
    
    
    Two perfect deep TD passes by Garrett Grayson have been dropped by receivers.    
    
    
    Garrett Grayson with a 23-yard TD pass to Rashard Higgins on the trick play. Rams lead Air Force 20-0 in the second quarter.    
    
    
    With the bowl situation, Colorado State shouldn't worry about UNLV. Rams win, they get a bowl. It'll come down to UNLV and SJSU.    
    
    
    For those who were asking    
    
    
    Air Force doing a good job of showing why its defense ranks 111th nationally. CSU already has 228 yards of offense. 12:52 to go until half    
    
    
    Air Force goes for it on 4th and 4 from the 27 and comes up short. Rams take over.    
    
    
    Great punt by Jared Roberts, downed inside the 1 yard line.    
    
    
    19-yard TD pass from Garrett Grayson to Rashard Higgins, their second scoring connection of the game. Colorado State leads AFA 27-0.    
    
    
    Colorado State safety Trent Matthews injured on the play. Being helped off the field.    
    
    
    Colorado State will attempt a 54-yard FG to end the half    
    
    
    Colorado State ends the half with a 54-yard FG by Jared Roberts. Rams lead Air Force 30-0 at the break. #mwfb    
    
    
    Colorado State QB Garrett Grayson needs 99 yards to set the school's single season passing record, set by Terry Nugent in 1983.    
    
    
    22 yard touchdown scramble for Garrett Grayson. Red Sea parted there and he took off. Rams up 37-0 on Air Force.    
    
    
    CSU recovers Air Force fumble on the 4. Rams trying to score again    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs with a 4-yard TD run. That's his third TD run of the game and 28th of season. Colorado State leads Air Force 44-0. #mwfb    
    
    
    Garrett Grayson breaks the Colorado State single-season passing record with a 49-yard TD strike to Jordon Vaden. Rams lead AFA 51-0.    
    
    
    Here are the first half video highlights of Colorado State vs. Air Force http://noconow.co/1aiYFWF  #mwfb    
    
    
    Colorado State is leading Air Force 51-0 at the end of the third quarter. #mwfb    
    
    
    Chris Nwoke with an 8-yard TD run. Colorado State leads Air Force 58-0 in the fourth quarter. #mwfb    
    
    
    Air Force scoring garbage time points. Colorado State leads 58-13 with 2:40 remaining.    
    
    
    Colorado State becomes bowl eligible with 58-13 victory over Air Force. #mwfb    
    
    
    Fixed my spelling error    
    
    
    Colorado State routs Air Force to become bowl eligible for first time since 2008 http://noconow.co/1ajaQTo  #mwfb    
    
    
    Still at the Field of Dreams, so I'm missing tip of NMSU at Colorado State. A good follow is Rams reporter @MattStephens    
    
    
    Colorado State leads New Mexico State 77-71 with 1:24 remaining. #mwbb #wac    
    
    
    JJ Avila's buzzer-beat lets Colorado State upset New Mexico State, 85-83. #mwbb #wac    
    
    
    Eustachy: I'm used to those games going into overtime and us losing. It's nice to be able to zip it up the court.    
    
    
    Eustachy: Are we ready for CU yet? I don't know. I didn't think we were ready for NMSU, but I was surprised.    
    
    
    Here's the video of the last-second shot by JJ Avila (@NotLilJay) to lift Colorado State over NMSU #mwbb http://www.gannett-tv.com/tools/brightcove/playvideo.ashx?sid=ftc&bctid=2881055053001 …    
    
    
    How about the ole' alma mater Missouri?? #MIZ    
    
    
    Colorado State football notes: Rams are bowl-eligible but not assured of a bowl bid http://noconow.co/1ajWfHo  via @KellyLyell    
    
    
    Hey CSU Ram fans/reporters, anyone have any clue which, if any, bowl game CSU will end up in? @MattStephens @seanvstar @dillonwithlife    
    
    
    Hey CSU Ram fans/reporters, anyone have any clue which, if any, bowl game CSU will end up in? @MattStephens @seanvstar @dillonwithlife    
    
    
    ICYMI: Colorado State beats New Mexico State on last-second shot http://noconow.co/1ajYevr  via @Kevin_Lytle    
    
    
    Haven't had Checkers since my last trip to Tampa in 2008. At least I can bring the fries home. pic.twitter.com/64JwD1yEMy    
    
    
    It's selection Sunday for the NCAA volleyball tournament. @CSUvolleyball will have a watch party at Fuzzy's around 6:30    
    
    
    Two Mountain West basketball games today: Northern Arizona vs. Fresno State and Marquette vs. San Diego State. #mwbb    
    
    
    Dave Hunziker is on the radio in Fort Collins. I feel like I'm in HS again, driving around listening to OSU hoops.    
    
    
    NCAA volleyball tournament selection show watch party for Colorado State #ncaavb pic.twitter.com/t4volVpcZC    
    
    
    Fresno State moved to 6-3 today with an overtime win against Northern Arizona. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball coach Tom Hilbert says hopes of hosting are slim, but is trying to keep crowd hopeful.    
    
    
    NCAA tournament selection show for volleyball begins in five minutes. I'll let you know where the Rams are heading.    
    
    
    Colorado State not announced yet, but will not be playing at Texas, Penn State, Missouri, Washington, Nebraska or San Diego    
    
    
    Half the bracket announced and no Colorado State yet, but Rams are guaranteed a spot. CSU won't be heading to Wisconsin or Florida.    
    
    
    The University of Colorado made the NCAA volleyball tournament.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball will play Cal State Northridge in the first round of the NCAA tournament in Los Angeles. USC is the host.    
    
    
    Colorado State's NCAA tournament match against Northridge is at 6 p.m. on Thursday.    
    
    
    Colorado State not selected to host NCAA volleyball tournament, will travel to Los Angeles http://noconow.co/189mNyl  #ncaavb    
    
    
    Just hung Mario on the Christmas tree. #nintendo pic.twitter.com/zowhVziYOl    
    
    
    ICYMI: Colorado State not selected to host NCAA volleyball tournament, will play CS-Northridge http://noconow.co/189mNyl  #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State prepping for CU this morning. pic.twitter.com/cAtFGU8H07    
    
    
    Colorado State's victory over New Mexico State jumped the Rams' RPI from 193 to 113. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State's victory over New Mexico State jumped the Rams' RPI from 193 to 113. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State's victory over New Mexico State jumped the Rams' RPI from 193 to 113. #mwbb    
    
    
    @JimmyWoodCU sorry for the double. Had to fix a typo    
    
    
    Front Range RPI as of Monday: CU (20), CSU (113), Northern Colorado (143), Denver (236), Air Force (322).    
    
    
    Larry Eustachy said today that freshman Carlton Hurst will start against Colorado. 3rd straight start for the Aurora Central grad.    
    
    
    @MattStephens actually about midpoint in season there is enough results, that results become valuable.  Thats why they wait to release.    
    
    
    San Diego State moves into the AP Top 25 this week at No. 25. New Mexico and Boise State receiving votes. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado received 17 votes in this week's poll.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball is ranked No. 12 in the final regular season AVCA Coaches Poll.    
    
    
    Xavier Thames is the Mountain West Player of the Week. Strong showing by the Aztecs last week.    
    
    
    Colorado State's volleyball team back on the practice floor, prepping for the NCAA tournament. pic.twitter.com/d1HYyQi4Bo    
    
    
    Flight is booked. Heading to Los Angeles on Wednesday to cover @CSUvolleyball in the NCAA tournament.    
    
    
    Loving these epic 3-cent discounts on XBox One and PS4 games for Cyber Monday. Why even advertise that?    
    
    
    I didn't want to finish reading the book, so I asked Siri instead pic.twitter.com/s1nsmfjjd9    
    
    
    Colorado is a 1.5-point favorite at Colorado State tonight. Tip is at 7 p.m., but a limited broadcast on http://ESPN3.com .    
    
    
    There we go. Accidentally hit the "/" instead of "." What, you've never heard of Vegas going off a fifth of a point?    
    
    
    Trash talk from Buffs not distracting Colorado State basketball from rivalry http://noconow.co/18cVi6W  #mwbb #pac12    
    
    
    Colorado State's Sam Peters is the Mountain West volleyball player of the Year. Tom Hilbert is Coach of the Year.    
    
    
    CSU volleyball's Peters, Hilbert earn Mountain West player and coach of the year honors http://noconow.co/1av6Tv5  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Colorado State freshman guard Carlton Hurst is a game-time decision for CU tonight. If Hurst's foot isn't bothering him, he'll play.    
    
    
    Come join our weekly CSU chat to talk about the Rams vs. CU in basketball and possible bowls for football http://noconow.co/1avaOYQ  #mwfb    
    
    
    I wonder if any Colorado State students will print off a giant picture of the actual moon, rather than a big head, tonight?    
    
    
    I just confirmed with Colorado State Associate AD Steve Cottingham that the Rams will play in the Great Alaska Shootout in 2014. #mwbb    
    
    
    Real talk though @RyanKrous @MattStephens... do we have sellout finally in FoCo for this game tonight?    
    
    
    Nice new behind-the-scenes addition to Moby Arena along Colorado State's tunnel from the locker to the court pic.twitter.com/53vuqLEpoS    
    
    
    It's really a nice, pretty, steady snow coming down at Moby Arena right now. pic.twitter.com/eIucmcORz3    
    
    
    Colorado State freshman guard Carlton Hurst is warming up. He's probable tonight with a foot injury.    
    
    
    Students are really filling up Moby Arena right now. As for the rest of the the arena, looks like snow taking its toll.    
    
    
    Colorado State and CU tip off at Moby Arena in 20 minutes. Students vs. everyone else. Weather is bad. pic.twitter.com/yj17pOuyYm    
    
    
    You've never seen so many Larry Eustachy heads in you life. Colorado State students living Larry vs. CU pic.twitter.com/aIrQba97kb    
    
    
    Avila, Octeus, Santo, Hurst and Bejarano starting for Colorado State vs. CU.    
    
    
    Booker, Scott, Dinwiddie, Johnson and Gordon starting for CU.    
    
    
    I love Spencer Dinwiddie's shoes. Beautiful yellow.    
    
    
    CSU wins the tip and here we go    
    
    
    Very sloppy start for Colorado State. Rams are 0-3. Buffs lead 1-0 with 18:50 left in the first.    
    
    
    Gerson Santo gets fouled on the dunk as CSU leads 4-1. Xavier Johnson with two early fouls.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads CU 4-3 at the first media TO. Rams are 1 of 8 from the field. #mwbb    
    
    
    Jon Octeus just picked up his second foul. A charge on a breakaway    
    
    
    Crowd chanting "Larry." Eustachy called a TO to yell at the refs after what looked to be a pretty clear blown call for Octeus' second.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads CU 8-7 with 11:51 remaining in the first half. #mwbb    
    
    
    Gerson Santo has both of Colorado State's field goals, getting fouled on both attempts. Rams are 2-12 from the field.    
    
    
    Colorado's Askia Booker just picked up his second foul, also on a charge and a ball call.    
    
    
    Gerson Santo picks up his second foul trying to draw a charge. Media TO with 7:38 to play. CSU and CU tied at 12-12. #mwbb    
    
    
    Play in the first half, that is.    
    
    
    Foul trouble for CSU in the first half: Santo, Octeus De Ciman all with 2.    
    
    
    Foul trouble for CU in the first half: Johnson, Booker, Thomas and Hopkins with 2.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads CU 8-7 with 11:51 remaining in the first half. #mwbb    
    
    
    Quick 7-0 run by CU has Colorado State calling a TO. Buffs lead 19-12 with 6:59 to play in the first half.    
    
    
    Octeus back in for the Rams with two fouls. Their best off-ball defender.    
    
    
    Media TO with 3:19 remaining in the first half. Colorado State and CU tied at 23-23. David Cohn will shoot 2. #mwbb    
    
    
    Daniel Bejarano with a nice 3-pointer in Dinwiddie's face    
    
    
    Buffs call a TO with 0:43.5 until halftime. Colorado State leads CU 34-28. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads CU 34-30 at halftime. #mwbb #pac12    
    
    
    CSU vs. CU halftime stat sheet pic.twitter.com/LZlthkXOZm    
    
    
    Larry Eustachy calls TO. Colorado State and CU tied at 40-40 with 16:49 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Media TO with 15:51 remaining in regulation. Colorado State and CU tied at 40-40. #mwbb    
    
    
    Askia Booker is really hurting the Rams. 10 points and is doing most of it by pulling up for jumpers.    
    
    
    Jon Octeus just picked up his fourth foul, this one also on a charge. 12:24 remaining.    
    
    
    Under-12 media TO. Colorado State leads CU 46-44. JJ Avila will shoot two.    
    
    
    Gerson Santo just picked up his fourth foul because Spencer Dinwiddie ran through him on a beautiful screen    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Rams lead CU 53-52 with 6:45 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State and CU tied at 55-55 with 3:51 remaining. Jon Octeus will shoot two when we come back.    
    
    
    Colorado State center Gerson Santo has fouled out. CU leads 61-58 with 2:54 to play.    
    
    
    CU calls a TO with 0:24.8 remaining. Buffs lead Colorado State 63-61. JJ Avila is shooting two.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO with 0:11.6 remaining. CU leads 65-62. Rams have the ball near their basket. #mwbb    
    
    
    JJ Avila air balls a 3-pointer. Buffs will shoot 2 with 3 seconds left to win it.    
    
    
    Booker hits the front end and that'll do it.    
    
    
    Colorado State loses a close one at home to CU, 67-62. #mwbb    
    
    
    Took me more than two hours to drive from Fort Collins to DIA in this weather, but made it safely. God is good.    
    
    
    Just a little snow at the airport here in Denver. pic.twitter.com/NqxrYkeQud    
    
    
    Just a little snow at the airport here in Denver. pic.twitter.com/NqxrYkeQud    
    
    
    I'm at Los Angeles International Airport (LAX) - @lax_official (Los Angeles, CA) w/ 131 others http://4sq.com/18D6i0a     
    
    
    I'm at Los Angeles International Airport (LAX) - @lax_official (Los Angeles, CA) w/ 131 others http://4sq.com/18D6i0a     
    
    
    Looking east from my hotel in downtown LA. Rams and CS-Northridge battling it out tomorrow at USC. pic.twitter.com/TKowmL1Ece    
    
    
    Colorado State will play in Great Alaska Shootout in 2014 http://noconow.co/18j9kUS  #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State AD Jack Graham on volleyball coach Tom Hilbert: I don't know if I can trust him. He told me this was a rebuilding year.    
    
    
    @MattStephens Uh, what?    
    
    
    @youreyeondenver keep me in check. 16 hours of sleep in the last five days. Lack of shut eye is taking its toll.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball team balancing academic, athletic stress at NCAA tournament http://noconow.co/18jK6pm  #ncaavb    
    
    
    Just wrapped up a nice chat with Colorado State volleyball coach Tom Hilbert about the longer-term success of the program.    
    
    
    He also discussed why CSU and CU don't play each other in volleyball anymore.    
    
    
    Colorado State coach Jim McElwain not a candidate for competing football job openings http://noconow.co/1aDEl2z  #mwfb    
    
    
    Checking out what Little Tokyo has to offer ... With American food (@ Flying Pig Cafe - @flyingpigtruck) http://4sq.com/1kgpsZf     
    
    
    I had a few people in downtown LA complain to me today about it "freezing." It's 55 degrees. pic.twitter.com/3ytlXKThYF    
    
    
    Finally got to the USC campus pic.twitter.com/HKrymRp7hI    
    
    
    I'm here at the USC Galen Center to cover Colorado State vs. CS-Northridge in the NCAA volleyball tournament. pic.twitter.com/W8BCQSkdT4    
    
    
    Colorado State warming up for its NCAA tournament match vs. Cal State-Northridge. #ncaavb pic.twitter.com/xUt75hYnDj    
    
    
    Denny, Foss, Reynolds, Culbert, Peters, Snider and Colaizzi (libero) starting for CSU.    
    
    
    CS-Northridge with an early 5-3 lead over Colorado State.    
    
    
    Colorado State and CS-Northridge tied at 7-7. Three early kills for Michelle Lawrence.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Colorado State calls another TO. CS-Northridge has scored 9 straight points and leads Set 1, 17-9. #ncaavb    
    
    
    Rams haven't scored since before their last time out.    
    
    
    After three straight Colorado State points, CS-Northridge calls TO. Matadors lead Rams 20-14 in Set 1. #ncaavb    
    
    
    CS-Northridge takes Set 1 from Colorado State, 25-15. Matadors completely controlled the floor. #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads 4-2 in the second set over CS-Northridge. Rams trail the match, 1-0.    
    
    
    CS-Northridge leads Colorado State 15-14 in Set 2. Rams starting to have trouble handling serves. #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State MB Kelsey Snider has 4 kills and 4 blocks. Really playing a complete match.    
    
    
    Another TO called by Colorado State. CS-Northridge leads Set 2, 18-14 (1-0, Matadors). #ncaavb    
    
    
    Rams are in big trouble. CS-Northridge leads Colorado State 21-15 in the second set. #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State on a mini-run to force CS-Northridge to call a TO. Matadors lead Set 2, 21-18. #ncaavb    
    
    
    CS-Northridge takes Set 2 from Colorado State, 25-21. Matadors trying to sweep off the Rams' season here in the NCAA tournament.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads CS-Northridge in the third set, 6-2. Rams needing to win three straight sets.    
    
    
    CS-Northridge calls a TO. Colorado State leads Set 3, 9-3. Rams blocking very well (2-0, Matadors). #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State freshman OH Michelle Lawrence is leading the Rams with 7 kills.    
    
    
    CS-Northridge takes Set 2 from Colorado State, 25-21. Matadors trying to sweep off the Rams' season here in the NCAA tournament.    
    
    
    Colorado State in control in Set 3. Rams lead CS-Northridge 16-7. #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State takes Set 3 from CS-Northridge, 25-13. Matadors lead the match, 2-1. #ncaavb    
    
    
    CS-Northridge leads Colorado State 8-5 in the fourth set.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. CS-Northridge has a groove going and leads the Rams 9-5 in Set 4. #ncaavb    
    
    
    CS-Northridge calls a time out. Colorado State making a run, trailing 11-10 in the fourth set. #ncaavb    
    
    
    And the Rams have tied it up    
    
    
    CS-Northridge calls its second TO. Colorado State leads Set 4, 20-16. #vbscores    
    
    
    Anthony Drmic not warming up here against Carroll. Also not on the floor in street clothes, either. Will find out ASAP what's up.    
    
    
    Colorado State takes Set 4 from CS-Northridge, 25-18. We're heading to a deciding fifth set. #ncaavb    
    
    
    CS-Northridge calls a TO. Colorado State leads 7-4 in Set 4. #vbscores #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Rams and CS-Northridge tied at 7-7 in Set 5. #ncaavb #vbscores    
    
    
    CS-Northridge calls a TO. Colorado State leads 7-4 in Set 4. #vbscores #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State and CS-Northridge tied at 10-10 in Set 5.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls its second TO. CS-Northridge leads 12-10 in Set 5. Rams need a rally to extend their season. #NCAAVB    
    
    
    CS-Northridge calls a TO. Matadors are one point away from the win, leading Colorado State 14-12 in Set 5.    
    
    
    CS-Northridge upsets Colorado State in the NCAA tournament, wins 3-2. #vbscores #NCAAVB    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball upset in NCAA tournament by CS-Northridge http://noconow.co/1aEEraa  #ncaavb    
    
    
    USC band member leaving the Galen Center is walking around outside playing the Imperial March from Star Wars on his sousaphone.    
    
    
    @VegasRebelFan burger was good. Covered in teriyaki    
    
    
    Instead of heading back to my hotel after leaving USC, I jumped on I-10 until I hit the ocean. Late night walk around Santa Monica time.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball team falls in first round of NCAA tournament  http://noconow.co/1aEEraa  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball notes: Freshman Michelle Lawrence (@mashellee17) has big match in NCAA tournament loss http://noconow.co/1aEIGCo     
    
    
    I'm at Pitfire Pizza (Los Angeles, CA) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/19mPTHG     
    
    
    Colorado State adds game at Boston College, home date with UC-Davis to 2014 football schedule http://noconow.co/18pl6wU     
    
    
    Is that The Brain Surgeon from Dexter in a K-Mart commercial??    
    
    
    Big thanks to Diane at @JohnnyRockets for the great ketchup portrait with my cheesesteak last night in Santa Monica pic.twitter.com/gAa6UABRk8    
    
    
    Northern Illinois is trailing BGSU 31-20 after three quarters. That stings a little if you're a Mountain West fan    
    
    
    Northern Illinois is trailing BGSU 31-20 after three quarters. That stings a little if you're a Mountain West fan    
    
    
    Forgot Cowboys Stadium was renamed AT&T Stadium. I was trying to figure out why Baylor and Kentucky were playing in Lubbock.    
    
    
    Cal State-Northridge lost tonight to USC in the second round of the NCAA tournament. Had the Rams won yesterday, I'd have liked the matchup.    
    
    
    It's raining in Los Angeles? I was hoping to get another afternoon of good weather before heading back to Colorado today.    
    
    
    I've watched that 1988 Bedlam game countless times. Eventually, Brent Parker is going to catch Gundy's pass. History can change.    
    
    
    "Virgin is now boarding group A as in awesome at Gate 33 B. That's B as in boo-ya!"    
    
    
    Girl sitting behind me waiting for her flight at LAX is cracking me up, listening to her phone call. #laxgirl    
    
    
    "Why didn't you tell me to bring my jewelry. I could have made it and sold it to all the <bleeps> here. They'd love it." #laxgirl    
    
    
    "My boyfriend wants to take me to Hawaii, so why don't you take me to Cancun instead?" #laxgirl    
    
    
    "What if the [adult film actresses] wore my jewelry in my videos? I'd be so famous."    
    
    
    "I am the <bleeping> best. I am so in love with myself. I spend money to make money." #laxgirl    
    
    
    As much as I hate giant airports like LAX, the people make them so interesting.    
    
    
    "I am the <bleeping> best. I am so in love with myself. I spend money to make money." #laxgirl    
    
    
    "Hold on, someone is calling. Hello? I'm in LA. I'm making money, don't you like that?" #laxgirl    
    
    
    "No, I didn't pay for my ticket. Do you think I pay for my own flights? I get paid, you know that." #laxgirl    
    
    
    "Babe, I miss you. I'm so bored. My flight is in like 40 minutes." Yeah, mine is in three hours. #laxgirl    
    
    
    "Are you kidding me? I don't need money. Money needs me. OK? Money needs me." #laxgirl    
    
    
    "Oh <bleep>! You're on my Instagram? You can't afford to look at that." #laxgirl    
    
    
    "TSA acts so weird around me. It's like they want to check me out but are scared to. They know I don't want them. I make money." #laxgirl    
    
    
    "What was your favorite part of my Instagram? You know I do it for you." And anyone else who will stroke your ego. #laxgirl    
    
    
    "Babe, this guy keep looking at me and smiling. I don't know why. He's not gonna help me make money." No, I'm laughing #laxgirl    
    
    
    "Since you don't want to come pick me up from the airport, I guess I'm going to Vegas! That's where the money is at." laxgirl    
    
    
    "Spirit Air tries to make you pay for carry on bags. I'm not a sucker. I won't pay, babe. You watch." #laxgirl    
    
    
    As #laxgirl walks away, a little part of me dies.    
    
    
    It became pretty clear #laxgirl worked in an adult industry or sold drugs. I don't have much knowledge of either field, but recommend ...    
    
    
    ... She test out the waters of standup comedy. Maybe start with an open mic improv. I guarantee she'd be discovered so she could make money    
    
    
    "Oh <bleep>! You're on my Instagram? You can't afford to look at that." #laxgirl    
    
    
    Dear @FlyFrontier, if a flight is delayed, then it's delayed. That's life. Don't tell me it's on time if it's not. pic.twitter.com/IkNlFsQKOp    
    
    
    Dear @FlyFrontier, if a flight is delayed, then it's delayed. That's life. Don't tell me it's on time if it's not. pic.twitter.com/IkNlFsQKOp    
    
    
    With Cranky Kong trending, here's a fun fact: Cranky is the original Donkey Kong from the 1980s arcade game. Current DK was DK Jr.    
    
    
    Bets on my car battery being dead? (@ Denver International Airport (DEN) - @denairport w/ @oldtownbob) http://4sq.com/18LPSmm     
    
    
    Volleyball sets an unmatched standard for Colorado State athletics http://noconow.co/18sFld6  #ncaavb    
    
    
    Until an official announcement, all bowl picks are speculation--like a mock NCAA tournament bracket. @KellyLyell will have you covered    
    
    
    I'll never forget bowl selection in 2007, driving back from the SEC title game in Atlanta. Spent the day hitting "refresh" on the AP wire.    
    
    
    It was a long drive from Atlanta to Northwest Arkansas, but it provided plenty of time to speculate where the Hogs were heading.    
    
    
    I'll never forget bowl selection in 2007, driving back from the SEC title game in Atlanta. Spent the day hitting "refresh" on the AP wire.    
    
    
    Got back from covering volleyball in LA late last night. @Kevin_Lytle is a trooper covering CSU basketball today. He has updates.    
    
    
    Armed Force Bowl announcing its match up at 12:30 p.m. MT.    
    
    
    MTSU will play Navy in the Armed Forces Bowl, instead of a Mountain West team. MW could end up in Heart of Dallas vs. North Texas.    
    
    
    Second Heart of Dallas Bowl won't be officially announced until after Big Ten sets all of its bowl games.    
    
    
    Is New Mexico where you want to see Colorado State play its bowl game?    
    
    
    Is New Mexico where you want to see Colorado State play its bowl game?    
    
    
    Here's what we know: Fresno State is heading to the Las Vegas Bowl, no MW in Armed Forces, UNLV likely in Heart of Dallas.    
    
    
    Live updates: Mountain West bowl selection ticker http://noconow.co/18u4J1Z  #mwfb    
    
    
    Looks like Colorado State QB commitment Coleman Key made his official to Fort Collins this weekend.    
    
    
        
    
    
    If Colorado State does go to the New Mexico Bowl, Frontier has $59 flights from Denver to Albuquerque.    
    
    
    If Colorado State does go to the New Mexico Bowl, Frontier has $59 flights from Denver to Albuquerque.    
    
    
    Here's what we know: Fresno State is heading to the Las Vegas Bowl, no MW in Armed Forces, UNLV likely in Heart of Dallas.    
    
    
    Colorado State AD Jack Graham told me this week the Rams will either play in a bowl or die trying. We'll see.    
    
    
    Volleyball (@CSUVolleyball) sets an unmatched standard for Colorado State athletics http://noconow.co/18sFld6  @avcavolleyball    
    
    
    Looks like Frontier flights from Denver to Albuquerque have gone up in price, but just booked mine to NM Bowl on Southwest for $59.    
    
    
    Southwest has one flight from Denver to ABQ left for $79 on Friday. If you fly to NM Bowl day of, it'll cost at least $99.    
    
    
    Looks like Frontier flights from Denver to Albuquerque have gone up in price, but just booked mine to NM Bowl on Southwest for $59.    
    
    
    Looks like Frontier flights from Denver to Albuquerque have gone up in price, but just booked mine to NM Bowl on Southwest for $59.    
    
    
    Were you there the last time Colorado State went to the New Mexico Bowl in 2008? Rams knocked off Fresno State, then a member of the WAC.    
    
    
    Were you there the last time Colorado State went to the New Mexico Bowl in 2008? Rams knocked off Fresno State, then a member of the WAC.    
    
    
    Southwest has one flight from Denver to ABQ left for $79 on Friday. If you fly to NM Bowl day of, it'll cost at least $99.    
    
    
    VIDEO: Colorado State football team reacts to learning it will play in New Mexico Bowl (@GildanNMBowl) http://noconow.co/1aMEros  #mwfb    
    
    
    Stephens: Weak Mountain West plagued Colorado State in NCAA volleyball tournament http://noconow.co/1aNek0C  #ncaavb    
    
    
    Tickets for the New Mexico Bowl between Colorado State and Washington State are on sale. Cost is $50 after service charge.    
    
    
    Tickets for the New Mexico Bowl between Colorado State and Washington State are on sale. Cost is $50 after service charge.    
    
    
    New Mexico Bowl provides hefty gift package for Colorado State players, coaches http://noconow.co/18wQw4n  #mwfb    
    
    
    UPDATED: New Mexico Bowl provides hefty gift package for Colorado State players, coaches http://noconow.co/18wQw4n     
    
    
    Broken Arrow (Okla.) 2014 QB Coleman Key told me he picked up an offer from South Florida, but is still firm on his Colorado State verbal.    
    
    
    Just spoke  with Wichita Northwest RB Deron Thompson. Said if he comes to Colorado State, he hopes to be at least as good as Kapri Bibbs.    
    
    
    Wichita Northwest 2014 RB Deron Thompson has Colorado State and Minnesota as his top two schools. No decision timetable yet.    
    
    
    BOYS BASKETBALL: Falcon 67, Poudre 65. #copreps    
    
    
    BOYS BASKETBALL: Greeley West 53, Rocky Mountain 50. #copreps    
    
    
    Aaron Donald from Pitt has won the Nagurski Trophy.    
    
    
    @MattStephens  Collins and Poudre Tourney starts  Tuesday not Wednesday.  check out your story  about Rocky playing in that Tourney.    
    
    
    Colorado State reportedly picks up commitment from 2014 defensive tackle Colton Foster http://noconow.co/1aS3Kpd  #mwfb    
    
    
    I just confirmed with Bakersfield (Calif.) Frontier DT Colton Foster that he has committed to Colorado State for the 2014 class.    
    
    
    California 2014 defensive tackle Colton Foster commits to Colorado State http://noconow.co/1aS3Kpd  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    According to @RyanKrous and http://Rivals.com , 2-star JUCO tight end Christian Montes committed to Colorado State after his visit.    
    
    
    Colorado State volleyball coach Tom Hilbert is the Pacific North Region Coach of the Year.    
    
    
    Our weekly @Coloradoan CSU sports chat is live. Come join @KellyLyell and me for the next hour http://noconow.co/18A2Wb     
    
    
    Come join @KellyLyell and me for our weekly CSU sports chat http://www.coloradoan.com/interactive/article/20131210/SPORTS0201/312100046/csu-chat …    
    
    
    Colorado State C Weston Richburg: Washington State throws a lot of different fronts at you. We're excited about playing a Pac-12 team.    
    
    
    Colorado State C Weston Richburg: Wazzu coach Mike Leach is one of the best offensive minds in college football.    
    
    
    Colorado State TE Crockett Gillmore: In high school (Bushland, Texas), we ran the same kind of offense as Mike Leach does.    
    
    
    VIDEO: Colorado State linemen Weston Richburg and Ty Sambrailo named all-conference http://noconow.co/1aSFinQ  #mwfb    
    
    
    Colorado State TE Crockett Gillmore: Kapri Bibbs works the way John Mosure and Leonard Mason did. He doesn't take practice reps off.    
    
    
    Dwight Smith expected to return in time for Mountain West play for Colorado State http://noconow.co/18AVAoo  #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State football adds three commitments to 2014 recruiting class http://noconow.co/1aS3Kpd  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    @erinfhull welcome aboard!    
    
    
    Colorado State vs. Denver tomorrow night. First time the Rams have faced a Princeton offense this year.    
    
    
    Gonzaga uses a lot of back cuts, but Denver's offense gets teams tired. Should be a fun game to watch.    
    
    
    Denver is 2-5 this season, but last four losses for the Pioneers have been by nine points or fewer.    
    
    
    Junior year of high school, Brett Anderson broke our team's 19-game winning streak. 2-0, two-hit shutout. Still hurts nearly 9 years later.    
    
    
    Junior year of high school, Brett Anderson broke our team's 19-game winning streak. 2-0, two-hit shutout. Still hurts nearly 9 years later.    
    
    
    ICYMI: Colorado State football adds three commitments to 2014 recruiting class http://noconow.co/1aS3Kpd  #mwfb    
    
    
    Denver game a must-win for Colorado State basketball before 12-day break http://noconow.co/18Bvkug  #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State recruits Deron Thompson, Coleman Key built a friendship before meeting http://noconow.co/1aWH4UO  #mwfb    
    
    
    Colorado State vs. Denver is the only Mountain West guy tonight. #mwbb    
    
    
    Denver and Colorado State warming up at Moby Arena. #mwbb pic.twitter.com/3q5KZ3eKl9    
    
    
    Dave Hall is one of the refs tonight for the Colorado State vs. Denver game. So at least part of the crew is good.    
    
    
    @MattStephens you had to wear the fedora tonight. I believe the rule is 1 fedora per arena. You better hope no one else shows up with one    
    
    
    David Hall, Randy McCall and Randy Heimerman are the officials for Colorado State vs. Denver. #mwbb    
    
    
    Udofia, Samac, Griffin, Love and Olson starting tonight for Denver.    
    
    
    Octeus, Avila, De Ciman, Santo and Bejarano starting for Colorado State vs. Denver.    
    
    
    Colorado State's football team is sitting in the student section tonight, cheering on the Rams vs. Denver. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State on the board first with a jumper from Bejarano. Rams lead DU 2-0.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Rams lead Denver 7-6 with 15:44 left in the first. #mwbb    
    
    
    Denver leads Colorado State 8-7 at the first media TO. Chris Udofia with 4 points and a block for the Pios. #mwbb    
    
    
    @MattStephens quick question?? When and how did u get a checkmark by your name??    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Denver 13-10 at the second media TO. Avila and Bejarano both with 4 points, 2 boards. #mwbb    
    
    
    Carlton Hurst checks into the game for CSU. He replaces Avila. First man to sub in for the Rams.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Denver 19-17 with 7:58 remaining in the first half. Bejarano with 7 points, 4 rebounds to lead the Rams. #mwbb    
    
    
    Denver's offense is so fun to watch. Princeton style; someone is always cutting to the basket.    
    
    
    Colorado State freshman David Cohn just hit a fade away jumper over a guy 7 inches taller than him. Good art to perfect.    
    
    
    Giving up offensive rebounds is killing Colorado State. Rams lead DU 25-24, but Pioneers have grabbed 5 offensive boards to CSU's 2.    
    
    
    Octeus called for a carry. Colorado State leads Denver 28-26 with 2:30 until halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Denver leads Colorado State 31-29 at halftime. Moby Arena has been silent all night. #mwbb    
    
    
    New Mexico Bowl bound Colorado State football team being honored at halftime of the basketball game pic.twitter.com/vF5SHRh2c2    
    
    
    Denver ball to start the second half.    
    
    
    Original starting five back on the floor for CSU: Octeus, Santo, Avila, De Ciman and Bejarano.    
    
    
    Off the back! Brett Olson just bounced the ball off the back of JJ Avila on the inbound to himself and finished with a layup    
    
    
    JJ Avila has all of Colorado State's second-half points. Denver leads the Rams 40-35.    
    
    
    Colorado State has scored six unanswered points. Rams and Denver tied at 43-43 with 14:03 remaining.    
    
    
    Denver leads Colorado State 48-45 with 11:50 remaining. Pioneers will shoot two after the TO. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Denver leads the Rams 58-49 with 8:42 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State is down by 9 with almost 9 minutes left and quite a few fans are already heading to the exits. Not much support tonight.    
    
    
    Media TO with 6:51 remaining. Denver leads Colorado State 61-53 at Moby Arena. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State is getting its fanny kicked by a sub-par Denver team. Pioneers had 3 offensive rebounds on that possession and lead 63-54.    
    
    
    Denver has 18 second-chance points tonight    
    
    
    Media TO with 3:33 remaining. Denver leads Colorado State 67-56. Pios are working the clock then nailing deep jumpers.    
    
    
    Colorado State is getting its fanny kicked by a sub-par Denver team. Pioneers had 3 offensive rebounds on that possession and lead 63-54.    
    
    
    Denver pulls the upset against Colorado State at Moby, 80-70. Rams go into a 12-day break with an ugly loss. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State is getting its fanny kicked by a sub-par Denver team. Pioneers had 3 offensive rebounds on that possession and lead 63-54.    
    
    
    Colorado State shot 54.3 percent from the field, but lost by 10. Rebounds just a bit of an issue tonight.    
    
    
    Colorado State guard Daniel Bejarano is taking ownership of this loss. "We got our asses kicked," he said.    
    
    
    Colorado State had won 13 consecutive games against Denver at home until tonight, dating back to 1973.    
    
    
    Poor effort by Colorado State leads to Denver's rare basketball upset at Moby http://noconow.co/1aXovjx  #mwbb    
    
    
    The new Twitter layout is absolutely awful. Looks more like my browser failed to load a style sheet than a redesign.    
    
    
    Colorado State recruits Deron Thompson, Coleman Key built a friendship before meeting http://noconow.co/1aWH4UO  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Poor effort by Colorado State leads to rare upset by Denver at Moby Arena http://noconow.co/1aXovjx  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    I missed the new on Boise State hiring Bryan Harsin yesterday. Poor Arkansas State. Red Wolves can't keep a coach. Gotta feel bad for them.    
    
    
    Heads up: With CSU basketball on a break, I'm on vacation until flying down to ABQ on Wednesday for New Mexico Bowl coverage.    
    
    
    I'll still be around the Twitter, though.    
    
    
    Elite running back recruit Deron Thompson (@deronTHETRUTH20) has Colorado State as one of two finalists http://noconow.co/1aWH4UO     
    
    
    Colorado State football fans: Be sure check out @Coloradoan.com tomorrow morning. I'm revealing a fun, ongoing project I think you'll like.    
    
    
    Don't be jealous of my NBA 2K14 skills (or outfit). I'm dropping @OKCThunder buzzer-beaters from Kevin Durant all day http://youtu.be/iN2mQHfpHLs     
    
    
    Don't be jealous of my NBA 2K14 skills (or outfit). I'm dropping @OKCThunder buzzer-beaters from Kevin Durant all day http://youtu.be/iN2mQHfpHLs     
    
    
    Just picked this shirt up from Shirt Woot....I know @MattStephens will appreciate it ;-) pic.twitter.com/rr8AuHGz0w    
    
    
    As Erin said, I'm so married. (@ Candlelight Dinner Playhouse for Scrooge: The Musical) http://4sq.com/JkRmZj     
    
    
    Colorado State football uniform retrospective: 1998-2012 http://noconow.co/1b2xHD8  #mwfb    
    
    
    Here is a look back at @CSUFootball uniforms from 1998-2012 http://noconow.co/1b2xHD8  @uniwatch    
    
    
    Colorado State football uniform retrospective: 1998-2012 http://noconow.co/1b2xHD8  #mwfb    
    
    
    Parents are in town from Oklahoma and we're spending the day in Boulder. Can't wait to see Tig NOtaro tonight @blastoffpodcast    
    
    
    Take a look and compare all of Colorado State's football uniforms since 1998 http://noconow.co/1b2xHD8  #mwfb #csurams    
    
    
    Washington State doubling up CSU in New Mexico Bowl ticket sales http://noconow.co/1b2Aigh  via @KellyLyell #mwfb    
    
    
    No current Colorado State football players are graduates of Arapahoe H.S.    
    
    
    What's a trip to Boulder without eating here? (@ The Sink) http://4sq.com/18qUeyJ     
    
    
    Although, the lack of @SportsStatement hurt the experience.    
    
    
    Tig Notaro show was so good! (at @BoulderTheater w/ 12 others) http://4sq.com/JpgsGl     
    
    
    Went up to Horsetooth at 1 a.m. with the family to watch the meteor shower. Perfect way to end a great day. It was beautiful up there.    
    
    
    Trying to write my farewell column for the @Coloradoan. Fact: Trackpads don't work with tears on 'em. #worstcountrysongever #seriouslytough    
    
    
    Took a beautiful drive today, 50 miles up the frozen Poudre River. I definitely recommend it. Relaxing. pic.twitter.com/MFsxb4S680    
    
    
    Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs needs to rush for at least 2 TDs in the New Mexico Bowl to have the national lead. Now behind Navy's Reynolds.    
    
    
    Denver is a 2.5 point favorite over Wyoming at home today. Pioneers upset Colorado State on Wednesday at Moby. #mwbb    
    
    
    Wyoming's Larry Nance Jr. is the Mountain West Men's Basketball Player of the Week. #mwbb    
    
    
    San Diego State (24) is the only Mountain West team in this week's AP Top 25. Colorado is ranked No. 20.    
    
    
    Gus Malzahn wins the Eddie Robinson Coach of the Year Award. No surprise there.    
    
    
    Home Alone only has a 54 percent on Rotten Tomatoes. Parents just don't understand.    
    
    
    Vacation has been nice, but ready to be back at work tomorrow. Flying down to Albuquerque for New Mexico Bowl coverage.    
    
    
    The last time Colorado State beat a Pac-12 opponent other than CU, Rams' QB Garrett Grayson was in 6th grade. Does that change Saturday?    
    
    
    And no, Utah doesn't count. Utah was a Mountain West team at the time.    
    
    
    The last time Colorado State beat a Pac-12 opponent other than CU, Rams' QB Garrett Grayson was in 6th grade. Does that change Saturday?    
    
    
    Do you know what would take @NBA2KGames to a new level? Spotify integration. That would be amazing.    
    
    
    #ThunderUp (@ MoJeaux's Bar & Grill) http://4sq.com/1kfoMX3     
    
    
    Beautiful sunrise over DIA this morning. pic.twitter.com/iim577DkPK    
    
    
    VIDEO: The Coloradoan is live in Albuquerque for the New Mexico Bowl #mwfb http://www.coloradoan.com/videonetwork/2947069542001 …    
    
    
    Mariachi band walking out to greet the Colorado State football team as it arrives in Albuquerque. @GildanNMbowl pic.twitter.com/nrGR2Ai3bV    
    
    
    The Colorado State football team has arrived in Albuquerque for the @GildanNMbowl #mwfb #csurams pic.twitter.com/BRICAmfNo5    
    
    
    University Stadium in Albuquerque looks ready to host @CSUFootball and #Wazzu in the New Mexico Bowl pic.twitter.com/OGvstrYgNi    
    
    
    Live coverage: Colorado State arrives in Albuquerque for New Mexico Bowl http://noconow.co/18RVgib  #mwfb    
    
    
    Hotel employees at the Marriott are wearing Colorado State shirts today.    
    
    
    Didn't look like any significant injuries to report from Colorado State's football practice today in Albuquerque.    
    
    
    Colorado State football coach Jim McElwain leading the Rams off their charter flight to New Mexico. pic.twitter.com/RFdfbNUJZn    
    
    
    Colorado State holding a press event now at the team hotel. Getting new video up now then will be down there.    
    
    
    Rams football coach Jim McElwain was focused at @CSUFootball practice in Albuquerque on Wednesday. pic.twitter.com/Z2GllazupO    
    
    
    VIDEO: Colorado State hits the practice field less than an hour after arriving for New Mexico Bowl http://noconow.co/18XIp0Z  #mwfb    
    
    
    No Mountain West players on the FWAA 2013 All-American team. I voted for Davante Adams and Kapri Bibbs.    
    
    
    JUCO All-American Steven Walker headlines four signings for Colorado State football http://noconow.co/18SwLBp  #mwfb    
    
    
    Colorado State RBs coach Jeff Hammerschmidt and @KapriBibbs sharing a laugh at practice today. pic.twitter.com/sXFp3GW5yE    
    
    
    PHOTOS: Bowl mode setting in for Colorado State football in New Mexico http://noconow.co/18Y69Cl  #mwfb #csurams    
    
    
    She's right, thanks Jess! RT @jessicaireneee: 12 more people need to follow @Kevin_Lytle”    
    
    
    Be sure to join @kellylyell and me at noon for a special New Mexico Bowl preview chat at @coloradoan.com. #csurams #wazzu    
    
    
    Come join @KellyLyell and me for our live chat, previewing #CSURams and #Wazzu in the New Mexico Bowl http://noconow.co/18UbzuM     
    
    
    Colorado State ranks third, nationally, in yards per punt return, but doesn't have a player ranked in the top 65 in the same category.    
    
    
    Top 5 most memorable bowl moments in Colorado State football history http://noconow.co/18USMQe  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Colorado State passes Washington State in New Mexico Bowl ticket sales http://noconow.co/190EL6s  #mwfb    
    
    
    Top 5 most memorable bowl moments in Colorado State football history http://noconow.co/18USMQe  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Colorado State and Washington State uniforms. Both schools sharing a New Mexico Bowl team dinner. pic.twitter.com/z3VklmfyBW    
    
    
    .@CSUFootball beat Washington State today in a game show at the team dinner. Winner always wins the New Mexico Bowl pic.twitter.com/MrnokIBWK7    
    
    
    The #CSURams have passed #Wazzu in ticket sales for the @GildanNMBowl http://noconow.co/190EL6s     
    
    
    Wisconsin just knocked off No. 1 seed Texas in the volleyball Final Four. Badgers moving on.    
    
    
    I'm at Kelly's Brewery (Albuquerque, NM) http://4sq.com/J09dV1     
    
    
    The #CSURams have passed #Wazzu in ticket sales for the @GildanNMBowl http://noconow.co/190EL6s     
    
    
    The #CSURams have passed #Wazzu in ticket sales for the @GildanNMBowl http://noconow.co/190EL6s     
    
    
    The #CSURams have passed #Wazzu in ticket sales for the @GildanNMBowl http://noconow.co/190EL6s     
    
    
    The #CSURams have passed #Wazzu in ticket sales for the @GildanNMBowl http://noconow.co/190EL6s     
    
    
    Colorado State football team beats Washington State in pre-New Mexico Bowl game show http://noconow.co/192pORs  (photos & video)    
    
    
    ICYMI: Top 5 most memorable bowl games in #CSURams history http://noconow.co/18USMQe  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Check out photos and video of #CSURams beating #Wazzu last night in a pre-bowl game show http://noconow.co/192pORs  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Defensive coordinators at Colorado State, Washington State worked together for 19 years http://noconow.co/192tEKh  via @KellyLyell    
    
    
    Rams fans shopping at a mini CSU Bookstore that is setup in the team hotel @GildanNMbowl pic.twitter.com/RbLQHX5JBm    
    
    
    New Mexico coach Bob Davie just walked into the lobby at the Colorado State team hotel. pic.twitter.com/h9oy5LWpuo    
    
    
    New Mexico Bowl a chance for #CSURams RB Donnell Alexander to showcase skills on national TV http://noconow.co/18XRkwq     
    
    
    Colorado State fans picking up their New Mexico Bowl tickets at the team hotel. pic.twitter.com/hD6KvD4yx4    
    
    
    CAM the Ram is now on Snapchat. This is awesome. Probably the best news of bowl season so far.    
    
    
    Clouds over Albuquerque. pic.twitter.com/m0F15p7HOT    
    
    
    Colorado State backup QB Nick Stevens: Washington State may have a W in its name, but we have a W in our game. #csurams #wazzu    
    
    
    Brightcove, you've picked a bad time for your video cloud studio to be down.    
    
    
    Next step for Brightcove is to allow for videos to be uploaded.    
    
    
    @MattStephens thnks for the article on Donnell much appreciated spoken from true heart    
    
    
    New Mexico Bowl a chance for #CSURams RB Donnell Alexander to showcase skills on national TV http://noconow.co/18XRkwq     
    
    
    Deciding between a nice, sit down dinner and Whataburger tonight in ABQ is actually a tough decision. @D_Riddick28 knows what I'm saying    
    
    
    Colorado State fans packing the lobby and bar at the team hotel before the New Mexico Bowl. pic.twitter.com/H4MF8v3GLU    
    
    
    Battle of the marching bands: #CSURams, #Wazzu sound off at New Mexico Bowl pep rally http://noconow.co/193PpcT     
    
    
    @MattStephens told you we were gonna go bowling. pic.twitter.com/tMs722yEIE    
    
    
    To hold you over until the New Mexico Bowl, check out the #CSURams and #Wazzu bands battling it out http://noconow.co/193PpcT     
    
    
    Is Bibbs the next CJ2K? @MattStephens #gorams    
    
    
    Be sure to join @KellyLyell and me for our New Mexico Bowl live chat, beginning at 11 a.m. http://noconow.co/194YMJ8  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    @MattStephens who would you say the X-factor is for the #CSURams on both offense and defense?    
    
    
    Colorado State's special teams are on the field warming up. Rams with green tops, gold pants.    
    
    
    Fans starting to file into the New Mexico Bowl. pic.twitter.com/zj3HtVAk4S    
    
    
    Only 38 minutes until kickoff here in Albuquerque #WSUvsCSU    
    
    
    Is Bibbs the next CJ2K? @MattStephens #gorams    
    
    
    Line on New Mexico Bowl has changed. Most have Washington State now as a 5.5-point favorite over Colorado State. #WSUvsCSU    
    
    
    Colorado State has distributed 5,105 tickets for the New Mexico Bowl. Of those, 3,909 were sold.    
    
    
    Washington State is coming out of the tunnel onto the field now. Cougars are wearing white tops and pants and red helmets    
    
    
    Shaq Bell, Shaquil Barrett, Max Morgan and Weston Richburg are the captains for Colorado State today.    
    
    
    Washington State wins the toss and will receive    
    
    
    Max Morgan picks off Connor Halliday on the second play of the game. CSU takes over at the 31    
    
    
    Next play, Garrett Grayson throws a pick. Wazzu gets the ball back with a big return. Geeze    
    
    
    Ruling is changed from an interception to a fumble by Rashard Higgins    
    
    
    Our live New Mexico Bowl chat is online. Come join @KellyLyell and me as we break down the action http://noconow.co/194YMJ8  #WSUvsCSU    
    
    
    Washington State gets on the board with a 25-yard pass from Halliday to River Cracaft. Cougars lead CSU 7-0.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Rams are facing 3rd and 2 from their own 28. No run plays for CSU so far.    
    
    
    Colorado State's offensive line looks incredibly weak right now. Grayson has no time, sacked at the 2.    
    
    
    Officially a grounding call. 4th down    
    
    
    We're not even four minutes into the game and Colorado State has been flagged four times    
    
    
    Halliday connects with Marks for 1-yard TD pass. Washington State leads CSU 14-0, less than 4 minutes into the game.    
    
    
    Did the #CSURams ast coach really just tell the @WSUCougars QB, "Fuck you you Fucking Faggot?" #NewMexicoBowl #ReadingLips    
    
    
    Colorado State converts the fourth down with a run by Schlager. Rams have the ball at their own 37    
    
    
    Garrett Grayson hits Charles Lovett for a 63-yard TD pass. CSU cuts Washington State's lead to 14-7 in the first. #mwfb    
    
    
    With the blocking Washington State is getting on these screens, Cougars can run them all game    
    
    
    Washington State now up 21-7 on Colorado State in the first quarter.    
    
    
    Washington leads Colorado State 21-10 with 2:52 remaining in the first quarter of the New Mexico Bowl.    
    
    
    Washington State leads Colorado State 21-10 at the end of the first quarter of the New Mexico Bowl.    
    
    
    Wondering when Colorado State's offensive line is going to get to the New Mexico Bowl?    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs now holds Colorado State's single-season rushing record. 1,602 yards.    
    
    
    Colorado State FG cuts Washington State's lead to 21-13 with 9:55 until halftime.    
    
    
    Colorado State's defense is starting to make some plays and force punts    
    
    
    Colorado State offensive lineman Brandon Haynes has left the game with an ankle injury. Return is questionable.    
    
    
    Garrett Grayson just threw his second INT of the first half. Lovett was completely covered and he tried to force it    
    
    
    Washington State scores again. Cougars lead CSU 28-13 in the second quarter.    
    
    
    Washington State is just toying with CSU, making the Rams look silly. Cougars lead 35-13. 2:48 until halftime.    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs with a 1-yard TD run. Washington State leads Colorado State 35-20 with 0:59 until halftime.    
    
    
    Washington State leads Colorado State 35-23 at halftime of the New Mexico Bowl. Rams get the ball in the third quarter.    
    
    
    If Colorado State scores a TD, do they go for two to tie it?    
    
    
    Colorado State WR Jordon Vaden just fumbled, trying to make a nice cut. Caught from behind. WSU recovers    
    
    
    Washington State leads Colorado State 38-30 at the end of the third quarter. #csurams #wazzu    
    
    
    Connor Halliday with his 6th passing TD of the game. Washington State leads CSU 45-30 with 9:35 to play.    
    
    
    It's not over yet. Garrett Grayson connects with Jordon Vaden for a TD pass. WSU leads Colorado State 45-37 with 2:52 to play.    
    
    
    Connor Halliday just fumbled and CSU recovers. The Rams are down by 8 at the WSU 38    
    
    
    The fumble is being reviewed    
    
    
    Halliday was down. Call will be overturned    
    
    
    After review, Halliday is ruled down. WSU ball, 2nd down, 2:01 remaining.    
    
    
    Holy! WSU fumbles again on the next play. No overturning this one. Colorado State is going to have a chance to tie.    
    
    
    Halliday was down. Call will be overturned    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs with a 1-yard TD run. Colorado State trails Wazzu 45-43 with 0:33 to play. 2-pt try coming    
    
    
    Colorado State runs the Statue of Liberty, but Donnell Alexander was called OOB short of the end zone    
    
    
    Play will be reviewed. Looks like we have a tie game between CSU and WSU    
    
    
    Colorado State and Washington State are tied at 45-45 with 0:33 remaining.    
    
    
    Jared Roberts hits a 42 yard FG as time expires. Colorado State beats Washington State in the New Mexico Bowl, 48-45.    
    
    
    Colorado State fans rushed the field after winning the New Mexico Bowl today, just like in 2008. Party in ABQ. pic.twitter.com/bt5z92fcGK    
    
    
    Colorado State LB Shaquil Barrett: A lot of fans are going to be sad they left early.    
    
    
    Washington State QB Connor Halliday said CSU assistant coach said "some really profane things" to him.    
    
    
    Game-winning field goal completes improbable comeback for Colorado State in New Mexico Bowl http://noconow.co/191MCxH  #csurams    
    
    
    Colorado State running back Donnell Alexander @Dnell_7 grinning after the Rams' New Mexico Bowl win pic.twitter.com/5NeUoFCzBl    
    
    
    Who's at the Marriott bar tonight?    
    
    
    Heading home. (@ Albuquerque International Sunport (ABQ) - @cabq w/ 8 others) http://4sq.com/JhT0tA     
    
    
    Mitch Hedberg is a liar. pic.twitter.com/n3ED3HuVGi    
    
    
    Just ran into CU assistant hoops coach @rodneybillups at DIA. He was also on my flight from Denver to LA two weeks ago. I just be stalking.    
    
    
    Just ran into CU assistant hoops coach @rodneybillups at DIA. He was also on my flight from Denver to LA two weeks ago. I just be stalking.    
    
    
    Stephens: Colorado State must do the right thing and fire assistant coach Greg Lupfer for gay slur http://noconow.co/194XN8L     
    
    
    Stephens: Colorado State must do the right thing and fire assistant coach Greg Lupfer for gay slur http://noconow.co/194XN8L     
    
    
    Stephens: Colorado State must do the right thing and fire assistant coach Greg Lupfer for gay slur http://noconow.co/194XN8L     
    
    
    Fort Collins forward Toby Van Ry, who has signed with Colorado State, is averaging 18.9 points and 8.7 rebounds per game.    
    
    
    Starting Jan. 6, I am off to a new adventure with @CSUFootball as the Director of Football Administration... exciting times ahead!    
    
    
    Burgers that are 60 percent beef, 40 percent bacon are 100 percent amazing. (@ Big Al's Burgers & Dogs) http://4sq.com/1gSnAcm     
    
    
    Fun sign posted on one of the hotel doors on our floor during the New Mexico Bowl. pic.twitter.com/0rtNpKIBIq    
    
    
    According to the university, Colorado State's 22-point comeback against WSU in the New Mexico Bowl was the second largest in school history.    
    
    
    Colorado State ranked No. 21 in final Top 25 volleyball poll http://noconow.co/198JArs  #ncaavb    
    
    
    Colorado State defensive line coach Greg Lupfer has been suspended without pay and will complete mandatory anger management.    
    
    
    After 12 days off, Colorado State basketball returns to the court tonight vs. UIC. What do you think the key for CSU is tonight?    
    
    
    The Flames beat CSU last season in Chicago.    
    
    
    Just talked to Colorado State guard Dwight Smith during shoot around. Said he'll play tonight vs. UIC. Been hurt since season-opener. #mwbb    
    
    
    Tune into the pregame broadcast at 6:33 p.m. as I talk about tonight's game between CSU and UIC with @thegarymiller.    
    
    
    Colorado State will be wearing gold uniforms tonight against Illinois-Chicago. Flames are wearing blue.    
    
    
    Mike Scyphers, Randy Heimerman and Brad Ferrie are the officials for tonight's CSU vs. UIC game.    
    
    
    JJ Avila, Jon Octeus, Gerson Santo, Joe De Ciman and Daniel Bejarano starting for Colorado State tonight    
    
    
    UIC associate head coach Al Biancalana was Colorado State PG David Cohn's high school coach his freshman year.    
    
    
    Illinois-Chicago guard Kelsey Barlow has 2 fouls in the first 3 minutes. Leads the Flames in scoring and rebounding.    
    
    
    Colorado State and UIC tied at 5-5 with 15:43 remaining in the first. 5 team fouls for the Flames. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State junior guard Dwight Smith gets a standing ovation from the crowd at Moby Arena as he checks in for the first time.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls TO after a rebound. UIC leads the Rams 8-7 with 13:55 left in the first.    
    
    
    UIC leads Colorado State 8-7 at the second media TO. Dwight Smith with two fouls.    
    
    
    Colorado State is shooting 20 percent from the field here in the first half vs. UIC. Rams average 45.5 percent. #mwbb    
    
    
    UIC sophomore guard Gabe Snider injured on the last play. Collided with teammate Marc Brown under the basket    
    
    
    Colorado State leads UIC 17-14 with 7:34 until halftime. David Cohn will shoot the 1-and-1. #mwbb    
    
    
    UIC has three offensive fouls in the first half. I didn't think that was allowed under the new rule emphasis.    
    
    
    Colorado State and UIC are a combined 0-7 from the free-throw line tonight.    
    
    
    UIC calls a TO with 3:52 remaining until halftime. Colorado State leads the Flames 25-16. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State just grabbed three offensive rebounds on a single possession. That's more like the Rams we're used to.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads UIC 30-23 at halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Rams allowed UIC to run the court and make a pass under the basket for an easy layup as time expired.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Rams lead UIC 45-34 with 13:33 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    JJ Avila, Jon Octeus, Gerson Santo, Joe De Ciman and Daniel Bejarano starting for Colorado State tonight    
    
    
    Colorado State is starting to pull away from UIC. Rams lead the Flames 57-45 with 7:10 to play. #Mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Rams lead UIC 45-34 with 13:33 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads UIC 64-49 with 3:58 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State beats Illinois-Chicago, 74-61. Rams move to 8-4 on the season. #mwbb    
    
    
    Just asked CSU guard Jon Octeus what he was doing for Christmas. Said he was watching Home Alone and invited everyone over. Love it.    
    
    
    Big games from Bejarano, Octeus lead rejuvenated Colorado State basketball team past UIC http://noconow.co/19a1IkL  #mwbb    
    
    
    UNLV really frustrates me because I can't tell how good the Rebels are (or aren't). Beating Mississippi State would give me some faith.    
    
    
    On the prowl! No one can stop the power of night guy! pic.twitter.com/ZbBYr3gGwF    
    
    
    Give some credit to Colorado State center Marcus Holt. He got scored on a few times vs. UIC, but played great defense. He's come a long way    
    
    
    Holt's positioning has gotten a lot better and is now going straight up on shot block attempts rather than clobbering a guy with his body.    
    
    
    Colorado State senior long snapper Tanner Hedstrom has been invited to the Medal of Honor Bowl on Jan. 11.    
    
    
    Living in #NewMexico is difficult. Can't decide whether to look east or west. Both are splendidly lit at sunset. #SantaFe    
    
    
    Merry Christmas to everyone!    
    
    
    The Mrs. is out of town; family is in Oklahoma. This is a weird Christmas day being home alone. Thankfully, good friends make it easier.    
    
    
    Sports trivia you forgot: JR Smith played for Oklahoma City for a season.    
    
    
    That was pretty.    
    
    
    Sports trivia you forgot: JR Smith played for Oklahoma City for a season.    
    
    
    Has anyone ever witnessed offensive goaltending called on someone finishing an alley-oop? Surely it's happened before.    
    
    
    Sports trivia you forgot: JR Smith played for Oklahoma City for a season.    
    
    
    Gotta love going to a Chinese buffet and not knowing they charge for refills until the bill comes. #Doh    
    
    
    Sports trivia you forgot: JR Smith played for Oklahoma City for a season.    
    
    
    Most of us spend plenty of money on gifts for loved ones during Christmas, but how much do we give that's actually meaningful?    
    
    
    Whenever you need a late, cheap, blindside push, count on Matt Barnes to be there.    
    
    
    Whenever you need a late, cheap, blindside push, count on Matt Barnes to be there.    
    
    
    @KyleSalomonMN amen to that    
    
    
    Colorado Eagles forward Trent Daavettila named ECHL Player of the Week http://noconow.co/19kOAfM  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Former Colorado State basketball stars Iverson, Eikmeier and Smith having success as pros http://noconow.co/19lwbQ3  #mwbb    
    
    
    No debate: CSU players with the biggest upside for 2014 are Steven Michel (@SteveOtattedup4), Jasen Oden (@jay_owe716) and @Schlager_Jake.    
    
    
    No debate: CSU players with the biggest upside for 2014 are Steven Michel (@SteveOtattedup4), Jasen Oden (@jay_owe716) and @Schlager_Jake.    
    
    
    I'm really looking forward to tonight. Watching the Poinsettia Bowl while learning how to play Dota 2. Proudly nerding it up.    
    
    
    Really not going to call a PI on that? I mean, great catch, so it wouldn't matter, but come on. Yanked him pretty hard.    
    
    
    Downside to playing in the Hawaii Bowl? Boise State official told me today the school only distributed about 700 tickets to the game. #mwfb    
    
    
    Downside to playing in the Hawaii Bowl? Boise State official told me today the school only distributed about 700 tickets to the game. #mwfb    
    
    
    Pretty good bowl game going on in Detroit. Pitt and Bowling Green tied at 27-27 with 4:42 to play.    
    
    
    Pittsburgh freshman RB James Conner had 570 yards during the regular season. He had 229 for #Pitt tonight in the bowl game.    
    
    
    This is great. Las Vegas and Denton, Texas, mayors place $100 wager on UNLV and UNT in Heart of Dallas Bowl http://www.fox5vegas.com/story/24310290/mayor-goodman-bets-heart-of-dallas-bowl-with-tx-mayor …    
    
    
    My grandma, Ene, brought plenty of good to the world, including her queso recipe. We call it "Ene Dip." pic.twitter.com/KZpVC5l6gX    
    
    
    Ed Hochuli's son, Shawn, is the head referee for the Poinsettia Bowl. Looks exactly like his dad, minus the biceps. #mwfb    
    
    
    Downside to playing in the Hawaii Bowl? Boise State official told me today the school only distributed about 700 tickets to the game. #mwfb    
    
    
    If the Poinsettia Bowl wants to help me on deadline issues and announce official attendance early, I won't complain.    
    
    
    @PoinsettiaBowl what's the official attendance tonight?    
    
    
    @PoinsettiaBowl what's the official attendance tonight?    
    
    
    Tonight's attendance for the Poinsettia Bowl is 23,408.    
    
    
    Tonight's attendance for the Poinsettia Bowl is 23,408.    
    
    
    Colorado State ranks second in Mountain West in bowl attendance http://noconow.co/19lqxtX  #mwfb    
    
    
    The Google Maps car is in Fort Collins, driving around Campus West.    
    
    
    Colorado State basketball practicing at Moby Arena right now, getting ready for Lamar. #mwbb pic.twitter.com/M1M9Jh07vi    
    
    
    ICYMI: Former Colorado State stars Iverson, Eikmeier and Smith having success as pros http://noconow.co/19lwbQ3  #mwbb    
    
    
    END 1: North Little Rock 20, Texas 11 #ARpreps Tigers not embarrassing themselves at all.    
    
    
    END 1: North Little Rock 20, Texas 11 #ARpreps Tigers not embarrassing themselves at all.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Syracuse got one block on that punt return. All it needed.    
    
    
    Tonight's culinary masterpiece. pic.twitter.com/V3UXni3lxv    
    
    
    Head referee of this BYU vs. Washington game was my HS history teacher sophomore year and a dang good one. Clay Martin, Jenks HS hoops coach    
    
    
    Guess who's celebrating a birthday today? @KellyHinesTW. Go give her a big follow for the occasion.    
    
    
    The two Mountain West players leaving early for the NFL Draft, Davante Adams (Fresno State) and Brett Smith (Wyoming), were 2-star recruits.    
    
    
    The two Mountain West players leaving early for the NFL Draft, Davante Adams (Fresno State) and Brett Smith (Wyoming), were 2-star recruits.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Lamar (1-10) warming up for its basketball game today against Colorado State #mwbb pic.twitter.com/5OZRVuD78A    
    
    
    Colorado State will be wearing white home uniforms today vs. Lamar. Rams wore their gold alternates vs. UIC.    
    
    
    Here is a quick-hitting college basketball preview for you: Lamar at Colorado State http://noconow.co/19qnPn7  #mwbb    
    
    
    Tim Marion, Brent Meaux and Bob Staffen are the officials for Colorado State vs. Lamar.    
    
    
    Holliday, Wilson, Mitchell, Ross, Hilliard are starting for Lamar vs. Colorado State. #mwbb    
    
    
    Avila, Octeus, Santo, De Ciman and Bejarano starting for Colorado State vs. Lamar. #Mwbb    
    
    
    Joe De Ciman with the first 5 points for Colorado State. Rams lead Lamar 5-0.    
    
    
    Holliday, Wilson, Mitchell, Ross, Hilliard are starting for Lamar vs. Colorado State. #mwbb    
    
    
    Four fouls called in the first 1:30. Jon Octeus has two of them.    
    
    
    Larry Eustachy calls a TO to yell at the ref, saying the inbound play happened when he was trying to ask a question. Rams lead 7-4.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Lamar 19-6 with 14:28 remaining in the first. Daniel Bejarano with 8 points, Avila 6, De Ciman 5. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leading Lamar 23-12 with 11:06 remaining in the first half. #mwbb    
    
    
    Lamar (1-10) has an RPI ranking of 343 with the 296th weakest schedule in Division I.    
    
    
    Jon Octeus just picked up his third foul, this on the offensive end. Seemed pretty obvious. Really extended his arm to push off.    
    
    
    Colorado State 27, Lamar 19. 7:47 until halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Lamar 38-27 with 3:09 until halftime. JJ Avila has 14 points. Daniel Bejarano has 10 points, 8 rebounds.    
    
    
    Lamar calls a time out trailing Colorado State 40-30 with 1:19 until halftime. Rams looking horrible at the line, shooting 5-12.    
    
    
    Colorado State junior guard Daniel Bejarano has a double-double vs. Lamar in the first half. 10 points, 10 rebounds. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Lamar 43-33 at halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Former Colorado State AD Mark Driscoll is sitting third row for today's basketball game.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO. Rams lead Lamar 49-38 with 18:26 to play. JJ Avila with 18 points. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Lamar 58-46 with 14:57 to play. Daniel Bejarano with 17 points, 12 boards. JJ Avila with 23 points. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State's JJ Avila ties his career-high scoring mark with 31 points. Still 11:23 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO with 9:39 to play. Rams lead Lamar 72-59. #mwbb    
    
    
    Daniel Bejarano is three assists shy of a triple-double. 4:40 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Lamar 81-65 with 3:47 remaining. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State makes a subsitution time out to bring in its bench. Rams lead Lamar 81-65 with 1:32 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State takes care of Lamar, 86-71 at Moby Arena. Rams finish nonconference play 9-4. #mwbb    
    
    
    Daniel Bejarano has near triple-double as Colorado State basketball bounces Lamar http://noconow.co/19sJ1sw  #mwbb    
    
    
    @MattStephens So is it Bueno or Leite or what's the deal with that? Haha it confuses us    
    
    
    Watching "Grizzly Man." This is an incredible documentary. Werner Herzog is a great filmmaker.    
    
    
    @MattStephens Joey O'Connor is still on track to be a Ram next year, right? Sat out this year because of transfer?    
    
    
    @MattStephens Joey O'Connor is still on track to be a Ram next year, right? Sat out this year because of transfer?    
    
    
    Colorado State running back Kapri Bibbs to enter NFL Draft http://noconow.co/19vC3Dh  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    I just confirmed with Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs that it was him who Tweeted the NFL Draft announcement, not a hacker.    
    
    
    (Updated w/ reaction from Shaquil Barrett) Colorado State running back Kapri Bibbs to enter 2014 NFL Draft http://noconow.co/19vC3Dh     
    
    
    For the two of you unfamiliar with @KapriBibbs, here's a .gif of his 75-yard TD run vs. Wazzu http://fansided.com/2013/12/21/csu-rb-kapri-bibbs-75-yard-td-run-gif/ …    
    
    
    Statement from CSU coach Jim McElwain on Bibbs leaving: Whatever decision Kapri chooses to make we will support him and be here to help him.    
    
    
    I just spoke with Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs. He hasn't hired an agent, but says he's definitely heading to the NFL draft.    
    
    
    Colorado State RB @KapriBibbs says decision to enter NFL draft a matter of chasing dreams http://noconow.co/19vC3Dh     
    
    
    I just spoke with Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs. He hasn't hired an agent, but says he's definitely heading to the NFL draft.    
    
    
    What made this an even bigger day for Kapri Bibbs? He's a Packers fan and was at the game in Chicago today. Green Bay is playoff bound.    
    
    
    For a guy who wasn't allowed by coaches to talk to the media this year, Kapri Bibbs was a very smart, well-spoken young man on the phone.    
    
    
    For a guy who wasn't allowed by coaches to talk to the media this year, Kapri Bibbs was a very smart, well-spoken young man on the phone.    
    
    
    Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs gives his take on why he decided to enter the NFL draft http://noconow.co/19vC3Dh  #mwfb    
    
    
    Gave my mom my Netflix log in. Better be careful about sticking to PG-13 viewing so nothing questionable shows up on the "recently watched."    
    
    
    @MStepAngelique: Finally hit that three-zero! Now my mom can get off my rump! 🙏    
    
    
    @MStepAngelique: Finally hit that three-zero! Now my mom can get off my rump! 🙏    
    
    
    @MStepAngelique: Finally hit that three-zero! Now my mom can get off my rump! 🙏    
    
    
    Gave my mom my Netflix log in. Better be careful about sticking to PG-13 viewing so nothing questionable shows up on the "recently watched."    
    
    
    Gave my mom my Netflix log in. Better be careful about sticking to PG-13 viewing so nothing questionable shows up on the "recently watched."    
    
    
    Stephens: Wyoming QB Brett Smith taking a surprising risk in early departure for NFL draft http://noconow.co/19xJ1rk  #mwfb    
    
    
    I talked with an NFL draft scout last night who told me the only time he'd seen Kapri Bibbs was when studying film on Weston Richburg.    
    
    
    Colorado State coach Jim McElwain said today Kapri Bibbs wasn't a guy who was really on NFL scouts radars.    
    
    
    Colorado State guard Daniel Bejarano wins his first Mountain West Player of the Week award.    
    
    
    He's the first Ram to win it this season.    
    
    
    Coach, analyst say Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs not yet on the radar of NFL scouts http://www.coloradoan.com/article/20131230/SPORTS0201/312300055/Coach-analyst-say-Colorado-State-RB-Kapri-Bibbs-not-yet-radar-NFL-scouts?nclick_check=1 …    
    
    
    Coach, analyst say Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs not yet on the radar of NFL scouts http://www.coloradoan.com/article/20131230/SPORTS0201/312300055/Coach-analyst-say-Colorado-State-RB-Kapri-Bibbs-not-yet-radar-NFL-scouts?nclick_check=1 …    
    
    
    Colorado State's Crockett Gillmore and Weston Richburg invited to NFL combine http://noconow.co/19Bgy3P  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    I'm at Denver International Airport (DEN) - @denairport (Denver, CO) w/ 114 others http://4sq.com/1cDMfhj     
    
    
    I'm the Grinch of NYE. I don't understand the celebration of the calendar changing a day. Yesterday was a year from a year ago yesterday.    
    
    
    Colorado State forward JJ Avila didn't participate in drills at practice today and is questionable tomorrow vs. No. 21 SDSU #mwbb    
    
    
    Revenge of the Nerds is on Comedy Central right now. You're welcome.    
    
    
    You have to give @EA credit. Its dedication to turn gamers away with no working matchmaking and no team balance in BF4 is gutsy.    
    
    
    You have to give @EA credit. Its dedication to turn gamers away with no working matchmaking and no team balance in BF4 is gutsy.    
    
    
    Flights booked to cover Colorado State basketball on the road this season. Hitting up Albuquerque, San Jose and Logan in the next two weeks.    
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State is only a 4.5-point favorite at Colorado State tomorrow night. #mwbb    
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State is only a 4.5-point favorite at Colorado State tomorrow night. #mwbb    
    
    
    I forgot Jake Spavital was the QBs coach at Texas A&M. Remember watching him plenty at Union HS in some great games vs. Jenks.    
    
    
    I forgot Jake Spavital was the QBs coach at Texas A&M. Remember watching him plenty at Union HS in some great games vs. Jenks.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just a bit of an embarrassing choke job by Oklahoma City. Yikes. That one has to sting.    
    
    
    NYE (@ Old Chicago) http://4sq.com/1lz0Rja     
    
    
    Vegas says: SDSU over CSU by 3.5, UNLV over Fresno State by 4, Nevada over SJSU by 2, Utah State by 8 at Air Force. #mwbb    
    
    
    Five things to know about Mountain West basketball heading into 2014 http://noconow.co/19GD23z  #mwbb    
    
    
    Khem Birch with 9 points, 11 rebounds and 3 blocks so far against Fresno State. UNLV leads 56-48 with less than 8:00 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    Without any big pregame news about JJ Avila, I'm guessing line on No. 21 SDSU at Colorado State remains 3.5. Was 4.5 yesterday. #mwbb    
    
    
    UNLV earns the first Mountain West win of the year, beating Fresno State 75-62 on the road. Rebels lost both to Fresno last season. #mwbb    
    
    
    As of 2:40 p.m., Colorado State had distributed 4,000 tickets to tonight's men's basketball game against No. 21 San Diego State #mwbb    
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State at Colorado State is the only Top 25 college basketball game today. Game will be televised on @CBSSportsNet #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State forward JJ Avila is dressed and participated in shootaround. He'll try to play tonight vs. SDSU. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State will be wearing gold uniforms tonight vs. San Diego State.    
    
    
    San Diego State stretching before the game vs. CSU. pic.twitter.com/yETpi24Hge    
    
    
    No big injuries for San Diego State. Josh Davis missed last game because he had his wisdom teeth out. O'Brien with a pad on his hand. #mwbb    
    
    
    NBA scouts from the Utah Jazz and Washington Wizards are here at the San Diego State vs. Colorado State. #mwbb    
    
    
    CSU only No. 21 San Diego State's second true road game of the year. Aztecs beat San Diego 65-64 in the other. #mwbb    
    
    
    Pretty decent officiating crew tonight for Colorado State vs. San Diego State: Dave Hall, Dick Cartmell and Chris Rastetter. #mwbb    
    
    
    Jon Octeus, Daniel Bejarano, Joe De Ciman, JJ Avila and Gerson Santo starting for Colorado State vs. No. 21 SDSU. #mwbb    
    
    
        
    
    
    Small addition to the floor at Moby Arena. Added the text "Colorado State University" at midcourt. #mwbb pic.twitter.com/jSLcal3PDi    
    
    
    Tipoff between Colorado State and No. 21 San Diego State at Moby Arena. #mwbb pic.twitter.com/sN0HcJihC9    
    
    
    San Diego State opens to an early 4-0 lead. Two missed jumpers by Daniel Bejarano.    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO with 16:40 remaining in the half. SDSU leads 6-0. JJ O'Brien hasn't been challenged, driving to the hoop twice.    
    
    
    Media TO with 15:55 left in the half. No. 21 San Diego State leads CSU, 6-2. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State and SDSU tied at 8-8 with 13:44 until halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State leads Colorado State 15-12 with 10:59 until halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    No. 21 SDSU leads Colorado State 20-16 with 7:43 until halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Not sure where Colorado State would be without JJ Avila tonight. He has 9 points and is 4-4 from the field. #mwbb    
    
    
    JJ Avila is walking slow, looks to be feeling that back injury, but his play doesn't show it.    
    
    
    @MattStephens it's 69-66 Utah state    
    
    
    Scratch my Air Force vs. Utah State Tweet. That's what I get for trusting http://ESPN.com  to autorefresh.    
    
    
    Colorado State and San Diego State tied at 23-23 with 3:58 until halftime. Rams battling back after each blow from the Aztecs. #mwbb    
    
    
    Giving up offensive rebounds killing CSU right now. San Diego State with a 4-point possession to take a 29-25 lead. #mwbb    
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State calls a TO with 0:40.6 until halftime. Aztecs lead Colorado State 34-27. #mwbb    
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State leads Colorado State 36-27 at halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State averages 8.7 turnovers per game. At halftime, the Rams have given the ball away 9 times. #mwbb    
    
    
    Air Force with an upset at home over Utah State in the Mountain West-opener. Falcons win, 73-72. #mwbb    
    
    
    The 9-point halftime deficit is Colorado State's second largest of the season. The biggest was 21 points at Gonzaga. #mwbb    
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State leads Colorado State 40-34 with 15:30 remaining. #mwbb    
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State leads Colorado State 52-43 with 11:39 remaining. SDSU ball. #mwbb    
    
    
    Simultaneous calls by two refs. One was a foul on Colorado State, the other a travel. Foul stood, resulting in a made 3-pointer by SDSU.    
    
    
    CSU coach Larry Eustachy is going off on the officials. Called a TO to do so. SDSU leads CSU 55-46 with 9:23 to play. #mwbb    
    
    
    San Diego State's JJ O'Brien just fouled out with 5:16 to play. Had 9 points and a rebound. #mwbb    
    
    
    Dick Cartmell just turned and snapped at Larry Eustachy. Telling him he's had enough.    
    
    
    JJ Avila just fouled out going for a rebound. 50-50 ball, but refs say he didn't have positioning. Finished with 15 points, 6 boards. #mwbb    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    No. 21 San Diego State beats Colorado State 71-61 at Moby Arena. Rams drop their Mountain West-opener. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State basketball hangs tough in loss to No. 21 San Diego State http://www.coloradoan.com/article/20140101/SPORTS0202/301010050/csu-sdsu-mbb … #mwbb    
    
    
    Top 3 quarterback targets Colorado State went after in 2010: Blake Bortles, Clint Trickett, Pete Thomas.    
    
    
    I said in my Mountain West preview today Utah State opened with an easy conference schedule and wouldn't be tested until CSU. Whoops. #mwbb    
    
    
    Top 3 quarterback targets Colorado State went after in 2010: Blake Bortles, Clint Trickett, Pete Thomas.    
    
    
    Colorado State basketball team hangs tough in loss to No. 21 San Diego State http://noconow.co/19JUbt7  #mwbb    
    
    
    Good column by @stemeyer about @KapriBibbs making the right decision to enter the NFL draft http://noconow.co/19J2pBI     
    
    
        
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs currently ranked as No. 15 running back in 2014 NFL draft class http://noconow.co/19NaWqt  #mwfb    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs currently ranked as No. 15 running back in 2014 NFL draft class http://noconow.co/19NaWqt  #mwfb    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs currently ranked as No. 15 running back in 2014 NFL draft class http://noconow.co/19NaWqt  #mwfb    
    
    
    Kapri Bibbs currently ranked as No. 15 running back in 2014 NFL draft class http://noconow.co/19NaWqt  #mwfb    
    
    
    Denver Broncos TE Joel Dreessen is the only former Colorado State player in the NFL Playoffs this year.    
    
    
    CSU guard Jon Octeus (@ImJusAHooper) had 166 points & 45 assists last season. He's stepped up as a starter this year, already at 175 and 39.    
    
    
    Assist-to-turnover ratio for Octeus is also much better. It was 1.22 in 2012-13. After last night's game vs. SDSU, it's now 2.44 on the year    
    
    
    CSU's Daniel Bejarano (@bejarano02) scored 219 points last season with 191 rebounds. 14 games into this year, he has 202 points, 133 boards.    
    
    
    Obviously, playing increased minutes has helped those numbers this year, but being near equal to last season at this point shows progression    
    
    
    Dear @EA and @EA_DICE, why is Battlefield 4 so broken? Why can I put an entire clip in a guy point blank, but no damage in melee animation?    
    
    
    Good pass interference call. Saban can gripe all he wants. It was the right call.    
    
    
    Alabama = Oklahoma State. I mean, in terms of OU shoving it down their throats at the end.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Q&A: NFL draft analyst gives full scouting report of Colorado State RB Kapri Bibbs http://noconow.co/19QpdQ2  #mwfb    
    
    
    Colorado State's basketball team arrived in New Mexico at 2:35 p.m. today. Here is the flight course. pic.twitter.com/gLL3PpPmG2    
    
    
    Colorado State's basketball team arrived in New Mexico at 2:35 p.m. today. Here is the flight course. pic.twitter.com/gLL3PpPmG2    
    
    
    I'm at MoJeaux's Bar & Grill (Fort Collins, CO) http://4sq.com/1f1GDB4     
    
    
    Heading back to Albuquerque. (@ Denver International Airport (DEN) - @denairport w/ 63 others) http://4sq.com/1cPGxJv     
    
    
    Joe De Ciman sets example of development for young Colorado State basketball team http://noconow.co/1lbR84O  #mwbb    
    
    
    I'm at Albuquerque International Sunport (ABQ) - @cabq (Albuquerque, NM) w/ 13 others http://4sq.com/KqMW3x     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm told Colorado State guard Dwight Smith might not play against New Mexico today, but MRI showed no serious injury.    
    
    
    New Mexico junior guard Hugh Greenwood has missed the Lobos' last three games. Looks like he'll return today vs. Colorado State. #mwbb    
    
    
    NFL Draft analyst gives his full scouting report on Colorado State RB @KapriBibbs http://www.coloradoan.com/article/20140103/SPORTS0201/301020113/bibbs-draft-qa …    
    
    
    As a pregame read, here is a story on the development of Colorado State sophomore guard Joe De Ciman http://noconow.co/1lbR84O  #mwbb    
    
    
    @passthepumpkin yes    
    
    
    Colorado State starters vs. New Mexico: Octeus, Bejarano, Avila, De Ciman, Santo. #mwbb    
    
    
        
    
    
    Officials for Colorado State at New Mexico: Mark Whitehead, Tony Padilla, Winston Stith. #mwbb    
    
    
    New Mexico students are chanting "Larry" and holding up the infamous party photo of Eustachy at Iowa State. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State wins the tip, and here we go    
    
    
    Daniel Bejarano jumper gives Colorado State its first lead of Mountain West play, 2-0.    
    
    
    Colorado State leads Cameron Bairstow 8-7 with 16:40 left in the first. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State calls a TO after an Alex Kirk dunk. Got in the face of Jon Octeus after. Lobos lead CSU, 9-8. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State leads New Mexico 10-9 at the first media TO. Daniel Bejarano with 7 points. #mwbb    
    
    
    Cameron Bairstow giving Colorado State problems early. 3 fouls drawn and has 7 points. #mwbb    
    
    
    Gerson Santo with a nice block on Alex Kirk's dunk attempt.    
    
    
    New Mexico students are chanting "Larry" and holding up the infamous party photo of Eustachy at Iowa State. #mwbb    
    
    
    Dwight Smith is in the game. Seems like his knee if fine.    
    
    
    New Mexico leads Colorado State 17-15 with 11:28 until halftime. Rams without a layup. #mwbb    
    
    
    Daniel Bejarano heads to the bench with 2 fouls. 10 minutes until half    
    
    
    Colorado State uses a second TO in the first half. New Mexico leads 24-18 with 8:44 until halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State really has no answer for New Mexico's Cameron Bairstow. Already with 10 points, 3 rebounds. No size to shut him down    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hard to believe Colorado State's first points in the paint came more than 12 minutes into the game and from Hurst vs. Kirk.    
    
    
    New Mexico leads Colorado State 32-23 with 3:52 until halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Hard to believe Colorado State's first points in the paint came more than 12 minutes into the game and from Hurst vs. Kirk.    
    
    
    New Mexico TO with 1:55 until halftime. Lobos lead Colorado State, 34-27. Rams trying to make jumpers in transition, but not working. #mwbb    
    
    
    New Mexico leads Colorado State, 39-31, at halftime. #mwbb    
    
    
    Daniel Bejarano just picked up his fourth foul on a charge. 17 minutes to go. New Mexico leads CSU, 45-35. #mwbb    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Media TO with 7:44 to play. New Mexico leads Colorado State 61-48. #mwbb    
    
    
    New Mexico leads Colorado State 69-58 with 3:45 to play. Cameron Bairstow with 26 points and 12 rebounds to pace the Lobos. #mwbb    
    
    
    Colorado State sophomore Joe De Ciman has fouled out with 13 points, 7 rebounds. #mwbb    
    
    
    Watching my fist CSU basketball game! Looking for you @MattStephens    
    
    
    Colorado State only trails New Mexico by 6 with 1:18 remaining. Rams doing a good job of staying within reach. #mwbb    
    
    
    Cullen Neal has come noticeable hair and tights that make him stand out, but I like this kid. Has a bright future in the Mountain West.    
    
    
    TO with 0:19.5 to play. New Mexico leads Colorado State 78-73. Lobos ball. #mwbb    
    
    
    Daniel Bejarano has a career-high 25 points. He's played most of the second half with four fouls. #mwbb    
    
    
    New Mexico holds off Colorado State 80-73 to beat the Rams at The Pit. CSU drops ot 0-2 in Mountain West play. #mwbb    
    
    
        
    
    
    So far, unlike last time I was here a few weeks ago, no strange couple has asked if they can eat with me http://4sq.com/JT9rNq     
    
    
    Daniel Bejarano overcomes foul trouble to score career-high for Colorado State in loss to Lobos http://noconow.co/1ljhIcq  via @coloradoan    
    
    
    Classy. @United cancels our family's flights, doesn't reschedule, and tells us to call phone support. Phone support robo-hangs up.    
    
    
        
    
    
    