@Hostgator broke my site in the process of transferring me to dedicated hosting from shared. It's still down. Bad service. Poorly trained.    
    
    
    @wizardprang Yep - @Hostgator has totally screwed up my upgrade to a more expensive hosting plan. Sorry for the problems they have created.    
    
    
    @hostgator - Still having problems. Front end appears to be back, but can't log in to admin. Getting error messages.    
    
    
    @w3edge Is Total Cache compatible with DB Cache Reloaded? Should I use that plugin to add speed?    
    
    
    I think the site is live. Lost comments over the last 3-4 days, unfortunately. Let me know if you run into problems. Tweets inspire results.    
    
    
    @w3edge Does it do everything and more? They claim to be the fastest, but everyone claims that. Or are all types of DB caching the same.    
    
    
    The U.S. credit rating was cut by S&P on Friday. Don't panic! Learn how to save yourself from the coming... http://fb.me/13joGmvcb    
    
    
    At long last, my site is back to normal. Now if I can only get @hostgator to give me a credit for all of the trouble, I'd feel good.    
    
    
    @steelcase_store If I wanted to buy a replacement arm for a leap,  how would I do that?    
    
    
    @amandaabella thanks Amanda!    
    
    
    @AshleyACray thanks Ashley!    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post::  http://20somethingfinance.com/2787/    
    
    
    I admit my addiction to being a consumer and get counseled by Mother Earth. It's not too late for your own recovery. http://fb.me/1drtqSf7h    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: American Paternity & Maternity Leave vs. The Rest of the World http://bit.ly/cImWfX    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 6 Reasons why your Next Car Should be a Ford Fiesta http://20somethingfinance.com/ford-fiesta/    
    
    
    Is buying a home for the tax deduction smart? I run the numbers. http://fb.me/1fPFbm4tg     
    
    
    3 things that would fix our dysfunctional political system. http://fb.me/17idSaPsy     
    
    
    The new era of emergency savings: 1 year +. http://fb.me/11aVOePGi     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Credit Card Act Gift Card Protections to Make Gift Cards LESS of a Rip Off http://bit.ly/bSK90a    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: TrueEarnings Costco American Express Credit Card Review http://bit.ly/93ybqc    
    
    
    This is a VERY tough bracket this year!    
    
    
    Buy one pair of eyeglasses and get one free! http://bit.ly/cSPqqo    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Buying or Rent a Home: The 1 Number you Need to Look at http://bit.ly/ck5oFc    
    
    
    12 tips on how to increase traffic and sales at your next garage sale. http://fb.me/DJQwXaug     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: H&R Block at Home Premium Contest Giveaway! http://20somethingfinance.com/hr-block-contest-giveaway-2010/    
    
    
    What is an ETF and should you invest in one? I give you a rundown. http://fb.me/J9HblMT2     
    
    
    I felt the earthquake in Michigan. Only a few in my office did. Where did you feel the earthquake?    
    
    
    @mogasanet Thanks - I'll have an article about 'getting rid of crap' in the next week.    
    
    
    http://20somethingfinance.com/chinese-housing-crisis/ … http://fb.me/tm1g7tXC     
    
    
    You thought the U.S. housing crisis was scary. Just wait until you see China's. http://fb.me/XRyPQUOb     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Free H&R Block Tax Software Contest Deadline Tomorrow! http://bit.ly/9seM5n    
    
    
    Only 3 days left to get the $100 bonus for a new TradeKing account. Check out how:... http://fb.me/x3zxsAiR     
    
    
    I just negotiated 30% off my Comcast bill. Here's how I did it. http://fb.me/1dv1jfSlb     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How to Use a Trailing Stop-Loss Order to Preserve your Market Gains http://bit.ly/aGHsx7    
    
    
    How to calculate your personal savings rate. Includes a reader poll on what 20SF readers are saving. http://fb.me/16fBMEPBQ     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Healthcare Reform: How it Impacts You http://20somethingfinance.com/healthcare-reform-how-it-impacts-you/    
    
    
    Odds are you have a ton of crap in your house/apt. There is no better time to purge than now. Here's 5 BIG... http://fb.me/1bjCufZvD     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 2010 IRS Federal Home Energy Tax Credit Guide http://bit.ly/ahIORu    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: REI Review: Why the Lifetime REI Membership was Worth the Money http://bit.ly/c5dtyJ    
    
    
    Find out how the U.S. personal savings rate stacks up against the rest of the world. http://fb.me/1gWIKqJYK     
    
    
    The U.S. blocking AT&T's acquisition of T-Mobile is significant. Find out what it means for you (if it sticks). http://fb.me/EIiHOuXl     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of November 29, 2010. http://fb.me/AAlzGYwP    
    
    
    Want to become vegetarian but don't know how or are afraid of the costs. Here are some tips for you. http://fb.me/ynvxkxht     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: FTC Cracks Down on Free Credit Report Scams with Catchy Parody Spoofs http://bit.ly/ceUbFl    
    
    
    Love for the Spartans. 6 final fours in 12 years. Simply amazing. Tom Izzo may be the best coach of all time.    
    
    
    @machead1 20 {((at))} 20somethingfinance.com    
    
    
    Do you love your job so much that you'd do it if you didn't get paid? Let us know why or why not! http://fb.me/FEuAj5il     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 5 Personal Finance Goals for your Thirties http://20somethingfinance.com/personal-finance-thirties/    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Death of the Staycation & the Return of the Vacation? http://20somethingfinance.com/vacation-staycation/    
    
    
    Facebook seems kind of jacked up right now.    
    
    
    I select the five retailers that I think offer up the best return policies. http://fb.me/KOi2rKKO    
    
    
    I discuss the basics on what a REIT is, how to invest in one, and where to start. http://fb.me/x8vUfbGV     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Buyer Remorse Storytime: 3 Times I Felt it & How you can Avoid it http://bit.ly/bIJI75    
    
    
    Spartans were robbed by the officials. NCAA wanted a Cinderella story. They got it.    
    
    
    Netflix, Qwikster, & the Official Guide to Killing your Customer Base. Are you done as a Netflix customer? http://fb.me/xn299PxQ     
    
    
    @AtikaEnciso Thanks for the compliment and sharing 20somethingfinance!    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: iPad Review: Is it Worth Adding to your Apple Collection? http://bit.ly/bDplqs    
    
    
    The Discover More credit card makes my top 5 credit card list. It offers no annual fee,  up to 5 and even 20%... http://fb.me/NFpKvk7H    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How to Check your Federal Income Tax Refund Status http://bit.ly/99KsEq    
    
    
    Here are seven places you can get free wifi access across the country. http://fb.me/15Fro4r6y     
    
    
    Straw poll. How long can this market keep going up?    
    
    
    Chase is kicking out some new timely Q4 5% bonus categories starting this Saturday - dining, charitable donations,... http://fb.me/Zwvj9QjG     
    
    
    Would you support your financially negligent parents in their later years? http://fb.me/1bGcs2z5N     
    
    
    Crazy deal. Restaurant.com is offering 90% off their gift certificates ($25 for just $1)!! http://fb.me/15n8mMap3     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Tax Filing Deadline is April 15 - What if I Need a Tax Extension? http://bit.ly/cuJrPk    
    
    
    Beautiful weather. Waiting for the winter to return. Have a feeling we'll see more snow.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 8 Personal Finance Spring Cleaning Ninja Moves http://bit.ly/ccbNJ1    
    
    
    How the Internet has destroyed the American economy & what you can do about it. http://fb.me/16XwaZowc     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How Much is your Time Worth? When Outsourcing your Life Makes Sense Financially http://bit.ly/ajajN2    
    
    
    Beyond cool electronic devices, Steve Job's legacy is very murky. http://fb.me/GaN1vmYw     
    
    
    The Tigers are giving me a heart attack.    
    
    
    @EverydayFinance Too soon?    
    
    
    http://20somethingfinance.com/where-to-get-cheap-or-free-flu-shots/ … http://fb.me/PmrCM8vc     
    
    
    More than 200K Americans are hospitalized for the flu each year. Don't be one of them. Here is a list of the... http://fb.me/1mg3z3bhF     
    
    
    This Fiat J-Lo commercial is driving me crazy.    
    
    
    Forget Wall St. Occupy first needs to head to DC if they want real change. http://fb.me/1o4BB9Jyi     
    
    
    @OccupyWallSt You've made the 1st step, but you need to focus on DC, not Wall St. Kill the disease, not the symptoms: http://20somethingfinance.com/occupy-wall-st-washington-dc/ …    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Save on Groceries? Not if it Means Sacrificing these 6 Food Qualities http://bit.ly/djAg6g    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How to Get the Most Out of Auto Insurance Quotes http://20somethingfinance.com/auto-insurance-quote-rates/    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Comcast Class Action Lawsuit: is it Worth $16? http://20somethingfinance.com/comcast-class-action-lawsuit/    
    
    
    Found a good outlet for selling gift cards you won't use and buying ones you will (at a discount). http://fb.me/P6IZwQYi    
    
    
    I love disc golf.    
    
    
    @erinlorraine happy you like the site!    
    
    
    Sick of the new checking account and debit card fees? Here are 5 banks where they are both still FREE. http://fb.me/WHT7ZFBZ     
    
    
    Michigan State put an absolute beatdown on UM this past weekend. Wisconsin better take note.    
    
    
    Has an entire generation lose all confidence in the stock market? http://fb.me/P16sEXr2     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: EverBank MarketSafe Diversified Metals CD - 50% Upside, Zero Downside http://bit.ly/9K5fhg    
    
    
    10 interview tips from a real interviewer - ME! http://fb.me/xkN3sAMB     
    
    
    The IRS announced an increase to the 2012 401K maximum contribution limit! http://fb.me/GincCjhj     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: The 4 Keys to Saving Money on Food & Groceries without Sacrifice http://bit.ly/bkiPsU    
    
    
    The Roth and Traditional IRA maximum contribution and income limits for 2012 have been announced. http://fb.me/15ecU0gM4     
    
    
    Citi Dividend World Mastercard has no annual fee, cashback on everything, and a $200 cash back promotion that is... http://fb.me/SHdnBTOW     
    
    
    Speed interning? Brilliant! http://fb.me/1n0G8bzcN     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Craigslist & Other Classified Ad Phrases Alternative Meaning Humor http://bit.ly/95WK7D    
    
    
    Redwings played like champs last night.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: The 4 Grocers that Stock my Pantry - Where do you Shop? http://20somethingfinance.com/best-grocery-stores/    
    
    
    A look at Obama's new student loan relief plan and whether it will impact you and help fix U.S. student debt problems. http://fb.me/XIO8mCgt     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Best Personal Finance Blog Posts & Other Oddities - Week of 4-25-10 http://bit.ly/adK5g4    
    
    
    Everbank's Yield Pledge checking offers a $60 cash bonus through November in addition to no checking, debit, or... http://fb.me/16znK1qQJ     
    
    
    2011 IRA contribution limits are announced by the IRS. Here are the details. http://fb.me/veMcLlze    
    
    
    Do you really need wedding insurance? I take a look at it to see what it covers and if it is worth it or not. http://fb.me/11nwRRsI1     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Lala Shut Down by Apple: A Sad Day for Music Lovers http://20somethingfinance.com/lala-shut-down-by-apple/    
    
    
    Bank of America joins the other big banks who caved in on debit card fees due to consumer pressure. http://fb.me/RS1veeAs     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Ooma Review: 1 Year After Making the Switch http://bit.ly/d3dYns    
    
    
    The gulf coast oil spill will go down as the greatest environmental disaster in history. Corporate profit is never worth this.    
    
    
    Wow, did the Sharks make a deal with the refs: "you flop, we'll call it"?    
    
    
    Want a matching tax credit from the government for your retirement contributions? See if you qualify for the... http://fb.me/KmfPKDKC     
    
    
    10 NINJA tips to cut the cost of dining out at restaurants. http://fb.me/EYF6u8eu     
    
    
    @republicwrless Excited about you guys. Virgin Mobile raising prices to $35 was a big let down for the cheap data plan niche.    
    
    
    It's open enrollment season! Here are six things you'll want to make sure you do this year. http://fb.me/17o5eZh42     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of December 6, 2010. http://fb.me/Lw72sugO    
    
    
    The Age wealth gap is growing and the net worth of younger generations is ridiculously low. Here are 4 things we... http://fb.me/1k35t0SjH     
    
    
    @amyers Hi Aaron - Check out this article for some tips: http://20somethingfinance.com/free-checking-accounts-debit-cards/ …    
    
    
    RIP Ernie.    
    
    
    Here are my best customer service tips to get results. What are yours? http://fb.me/13FAIt6DQ     
    
    
    Could your social media profiles be preventing you from getting hired? Here's how to protect yourself. http://fb.me/zjUAdFGq     
    
    
    Help! My template is broken in IE. Anyone good with CSS/HTML? Send me a note.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Box of Tricks: 1 Apartment, 24 Rooms, 344 Square Feet http://bit.ly/9jhYsz    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: What are you Worried About Financially? http://20somethingfinance.com/what-are-you-worried-about-financially/    
    
    
    What is a high deductible health plan (HDHP)? I give a rundown & where you can find one for the lowest cost. http://fb.me/1ks3FQhZu     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Mark Cuban's Solutions to Fix the Stock Market http://20somethingfinance.com/mark-cuban-stock-market/    
    
    
    What should the government do when it impacts your bottom line? Take the American values poll! http://fb.me/R6o3w9bI     
    
    
    What are the top 10 cheapest college towns? Find out & I highlight why you should consider moving to one. http://fb.me/1leYRgJW8     
    
    
    What are the top 10 cheapest college towns? Find out & I highlight why you should consider moving to one. http://fb.me/1n3Kl8L5W     
    
    
    What are the top 10 cheapest college towns? Find out & I highlight why you should consider moving to one. http://fb.me/1gVOENGh8     
    
    
    What are the top 10 cheapest college towns? Find out & I highlight why you should consider moving to one. http://fb.me/113MfhXgE     
    
    
    What are the top 10 cheapest college towns? Find out & I highlight why you should consider moving to one. http://fb.me/11HksXOD9     
    
    
    Do you have a balance remaining in your FSA account? If so, you will lose that money (which you contributed) if... http://fb.me/AzyQE6wt    
    
    
    Free online checking cash back bonus incentive promos end tomorrow for Ing Direct & Wed. for EverBank! http://fb.me/H6Wud3mv     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How to Donate your Car to Charity in 7 Steps http://20somethingfinance.com/how-to-donate-your-car-to-charity/    
    
    
    Here are 25 awful tasks that still beat shopping on Black Friday? What awful things can you add to this list? http://fb.me/sWEmUTDQ     
    
    
    Looks like a Facebook stock IPO is expected early 2012. Should you buy it? I discuss. http://fb.me/XwAZwb7i     
    
    
    Google Maps + A-Team Van = Hella Fun. http://www.youtube.com/drivetheateamvan    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: What are your Costly Pleasures? http://20somethingfinance.com/what-are-your-costly-pleasures/    
    
    
    I discuss the basics on Health Savings Accounts (HSA's) & how they pair with HDHP's. http://fb.me/Y58kUpsH     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Roth 401K Contibution Maximums & Comparisons to Traditional 401K http://bit.ly/cG8kbk    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 7 Money Saving Gift Ideas that Truly Keep on Giving http://20somethingfinance.com/money-saving-gift-ideas/    
    
    
    It's not too late for thoughtful holiday gift purchases. Here are 7 gifts that will save your loved ones a TON of... http://fb.me/vnx80U1B    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Small Non-Profit Tax Exempt Status Could be at Jeopardy http://bit.ly/dAmWml    
    
    
    89% of Canadians report being overworked. Are they overworked as Americans? I take a look. http://fb.me/1tHa5FwLn     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: WTDirect High Yield Savings Account: $500 Cash Bonus! http://bit.ly/bpw143    
    
    
    I review the best grocery cash back rewards card - the American Express Blue Cash Preferred card - 6% cash back!? http://fb.me/1vavlbrEj     
    
    
    Health care expense Nirvana can be reached! Here's how to do it. http://fb.me/TSL1Lwsr     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: The Top 5 Best Android Personal Finance Apps to Save you Money http://bit.ly/9OnTex    
    
    
    Perhaps the key to personal finance is effectively separating wants from needs. I give a 4-step process on how to... http://fb.me/De0Kfiay     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: What are you Worried About Financially: Reader Poll Results http://bit.ly/b6TZ2r    
    
    
    Finally! The 2012 Chase Freedom 5% bonus category calendar has been released. http://fb.me/1uVSULZm5     
    
    
    A look at six last-minute gift ideas that will save your gift recipient (or you) some serious cash. http://fb.me/14yChtwai     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How to Check Tire Pressure & Inflate your Tires http://bit.ly/a4Lv7W    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: What Debts are you Struggling to Pay Off? Reader Poll http://bit.ly/daE7V9    
    
    
    Good cliche or bad: "A penny saved is a penny earned." I give my verdict. You give yours. http://fb.me/Vkr5FfYE     
    
    
    Want a method to control your wants & impulsive buying? I've got it! http://fb.me/1ciLK3xf5     
    
    
    What is the REAL lifetime cost of cable TV? I run the numbers. Warning: It will shock you... http://fb.me/D0e8D9gW     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: The 5 Worst Retailer Return Policies http://20somethingfinance.com/worst-return-policies/    
    
    
    Last week I wrote about the 5 best retailer return policies. This week, I call out the 5 worst. See who made the... http://fb.me/DwixJVMo    
    
    
    Christmas Eve - time to watch some Chevy Chase Christmas Vacation!    
    
    
    Is the "your home is an investment" cliche still legit? I take a look. http://fb.me/1epBccoYd     
    
    
    I just launched my Google+ profile. Circle me to hear about hangouts, unique content, and much more. http://fb.me/17g5FJPEX     
    
    
    20SomethingFinance turns 4 this week. To celebrate, I highlight the top posts of 2011. Thanks for another great year! http://fb.me/JFVb6RJk     
    
    
    20SomethingFinance turns 4 this week. To celebrate, I highlight the top posts of 2011. Thanks for another great year! http://fb.me/17ed2O9Z9     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: I Got Burgled! 10 Tips to Avoid Theft when Traveling Abroad http://bit.ly/9v7ILF    
    
    
    Armando - that was a perfect game. You were robbed. Instant replay in baseball, please.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 3 Ooma Referral Coupon Codes Available http://20somethingfinance.com/ooma-referral-code/    
    
    
    @smoovekc Awesome. Good stuff!    
    
    
    What were your biggest financial accomplishments in 2011 & what are you most excited about in 2012? I share mine,... http://fb.me/12yGiw5id     
    
    
    Here is a rundown of the top 15 cheapest new cars of the 2012 model year. http://fb.me/K6XskWJN     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Highlights, Favorites, Deals, & Other Oddities – Week of 5-30-10 http://bit.ly/aSRB4X    
    
    
    There are tax bracket & standard deduction changes across the board for 2012. Find out what changes for you! http://fb.me/1Bt4I3kDZ     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Zecco ZapTrade Makes Researching & Buying Stocks Much Easier http://20somethingfinance.com/zecco-zaptrade/    
    
    
    Credit Karma now offers free credit monitoring (usually $15+/mo.) in addition to free credit scores! http://fb.me/1puPxKhG4     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Does Nitrogen Tire Inflation Improve Mileage & Save Money? http://bit.ly/aYLFsY    
    
    
    Have a big home project you were hoping for a home energy tax credit on? Your options are a whole lot more limited... http://fb.me/LfjWFuJH     
    
    
    Here are the top 15 most fuel efficient cars of 2012. There are some pretty cool new entrants! http://fb.me/1lvA5SDWb     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Unemployed? Many Hiring Employers Won't Even Give you a Look http://bit.ly/9mDE1j    
    
    
    The 2012 tax deadline (for 2011 taxes) is extended to April 17 this year in observance of Emancipation Day. http://fb.me/IoTkrTiv     
    
    
    Here is how to get three free credit reports per year (without getting ripped off). http://fb.me/xS4IAP7r     
    
    
    I have 5 coupon codes to get $10 off an Ooma, free shipping, & a bluetooth adapter! http://fb.me/1FkAJmL4P     
    
    
    I have 5 premium H&R Block online tax prep codes (federal and state) to give away! $84.90 value. Contest ends Sunday. http://fb.me/KWzFJDcN     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Turning Lemons into Lemon... Preserves http://20somethingfinance.com/turning-lemons-into-lemon-preserves/    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Using 0% APR Balance Transfer Credit Cards to Pay off Debt  http://bit.ly/c8som2    
    
    
    It's so muggy out, that I'm sweating just thinking about it.    
    
    
    Here is the tale of 'Grandy', my dying car, a 2000 Pontiac Grand Am. Share your old car stories in memorandum. http://fb.me/1FwD7PALR     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of December 13, 2010. http://fb.me/PI6OhQfi    
    
    
    Why the advice to "spend less than you earn" is severely flawed. http://fb.me/1B3oUfIe7     
    
    
    Have you quit cable TV? Share your story on how you did it and how it impacted you! http://fb.me/1Alqgrfct     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Tom Izzo Turns Down the Cavs: Life Lessons Learned http://bit.ly/bN5BR7    
    
    
    Thanks Tom. Glad to have you in town for life.    
    
    
    Why are there no good apps to integrate facebook, twitter, and wordpress?    
    
    
    Vowing to spend more time on the 20somethingfinance Facebook page. One problem I'm having though is my Twitter... http://fb.me/zKGnxomh    
    
    
    Update: my customer referral coupon codes to get $10 off an Ooma, free shipping, & a free bluetooth adapter ends... http://fb.me/E39q732I     
    
    
    I tested how much electricity costs to power common household devices & share the results. There are some surprises! http://fb.me/17FeJgtQs     
    
    
    Find out how I was able to find 25% off MSRP on a new car BEFORE negotiation. http://fb.me/13OwcB1XN     
    
    
    Here is a little jumpstarter guide to get you going on your 2011 tax return. http://fb.me/FTdPGWcW     
    
    
    3 Airlines are offering up free wifi on flights through Jan. 2. http://fb.me/NTRGM8LG    
    
    
    A post on the dangers and benefits of using credit cards to pay off credit card debt. http://fb.me/Bop8aNyZ    
    
    
    One of my top 5 favorite posts I've ever written. Accurately covers exactly where I'm at with my personal... http://fb.me/tfqGaOq5    
    
    
    Tom Izzo staying with the Spartans literally made my summer. But there are ultimately some great personal... http://fb.me/vbFbEG6U    
    
    
    Highlights for the week - some of my favorite blog posts. http://fb.me/z1npCgvr    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: American Express Purchase Protection Plan - a Rare Credit Card Benefit http://bit.ly/bNvtGp    
    
    
    A rare (and actually helpful) benefit from a rare consumer-focused credit card company. Imagine that! http://fb.me/ABMG3ZBL    
    
    
    World Cup is starting to get old... bring on Le Tour! http://fb.me/BphYEGZf    
    
    
    Puppy bowl!!!!!!!!! Why did they change the ref. who made the weird, but endearing facial expressions?    
    
    
    I FINALLY get a chance to read and review the personal finance classic: Your Money or Your Life. http://fb.me/1jGWWPk6R     
    
    
    I detail my research and negotiation strategy for buying a new car. http://fb.me/15KoKrrv2     
    
    
    Tax planning shouldn't begin in December. Be cognizant of where your income will end up in 2010! http://fb.me/yacShBAJ    
    
    
    Finally just got power back after 3 days. And it wasn't half bad going without! Less stress, more free time, and... http://fb.me/AE4lVxx8    
    
    
    @hostgator broke my site again. Been down for a few hours, it looks like. Rep I'm chatting with took 15 minutes to ask me what my domain is.    
    
    
    @hostgator restarted the server, site is back up again. Too much downtime in the last few months to be happy. Any host recommendations?    
    
    
    When does it make sense to file "married filing separately"? We have a tax preparer take a look. http://fb.me/1FbibfA0X     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How Much do you Tip for Food Delivery? http://20somethingfinance.com/how-much-to-tip-for-food-delivery/    
    
    
    How much do you tip food delivery drivers? http://fb.me/CcbXbF6G    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Real Estate Capital Gains Taxes on the Sale of a Home http://bit.ly/aQecSc    
    
    
    I rank the 4 major U.S. wireless carriers from most friendly early termination fee policy to least - and highlight... http://fb.me/GBf25zuD    
    
    
    Don't sell your home without knowing capital gains tax rules! http://fb.me/uxRQrEb1    
    
    
    YouTube win vs. Viacom a big win for free speech and continued internet content growth. http://fb.me/xDKqWVh8    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 20SomethingFinance Facebook Page Worth Liking? http://20somethingfinance.com/20somethingfinance-facebook/    
    
    
    How can I improve the 20somethingfinance Facebook page??? http://fb.me/BMVwCJHd    
    
    
    How much should you spend on an engagement ring? How about nothing? I make the case for engagement frugality. http://fb.me/HWyWgVv2     
    
    
    Has anyone elses bank notified them about changes they are making to their overdraft policy in August? Not sure if... http://fb.me/tDWCErWk    
    
    
    Want an opportunity to save on credit card debt interest? Discover now offering a rare no transfer fee, 0% APR card. http://fb.me/uNhROYKB     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Get Microsoft Office 2010 for Free - for 60 Days http://bit.ly/a1P4YU    
    
    
    Hate reliance on paid software (particularly Microsoft)? Me too. At least you can download it now for free for 60... http://fb.me/D1aq3IrE    
    
    
    A historic look at the rise of the modern economy, it's eventual fall, & what you need to do to prepare. http://fb.me/1z5jjutvh     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Highlights, Favorites, Deals, & Oddities – Week of 6-21-10 http://bit.ly/b7Pbyn    
    
    
    Highlights and Deals for the week of June 20th! http://fb.me/vBIDZl6c    
    
    
    Nice to be home after a week on the road. http://fb.me/Dj1fXUaX    
    
    
    How would you define "financial independence"? http://fb.me/114OVYWct     
    
    
    New cash rewards from Perkstreet are very generous! http://fb.me/uRWzPB0T    
    
    
    Like ETF's? Like ETF's you can trade for free? Here are 7 online brokers with commission-free ETF trades. http://fb.me/1uE668QkE     
    
    
    10 very simple to follow food tips to help you save money and live a healthier life... http://fb.me/tZWh5stL    
    
    
    5 stupid post-grad financial mistakes to avoid. http://fb.me/1zy7HCJvz     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Would you Lend Money to Family or a Friend? (Reader Poll) http://bit.ly/af9UzL    
    
    
    Anyone advertised their blog through Facebook? Effective?    
    
    
    Take the poll... would you lend money to a friend or family member? http://fb.me/AGEX3Zrz    
    
    
    The Social Security payroll tax cuts were extended throughout the rest of 2012. You'll continue paying 32% less. http://fb.me/168yaLJ89     
    
    
    Betterment significantly lowers their management fees and adds IRA's! http://fb.me/1apfJGsEs     
    
    
    Is the US vs. international stock 80/20 - rule a conspiracy? I look at the surprising data. http://fb.me/1cGER59uw     
    
    
    Did you know that 75% of electrical use for appliances comes from when the appliance is turned off?? That's a damn... http://fb.me/CucaEzRy    
    
    
    Contemplating going without cable...    
    
    
    The homebuyer tax credit was extended this week.... sort of. It may not be what you were hoping for...    
    
    
    The homebuyer tax credit was extended this week. Sort of.... It might not be what you hoped for.... http://fb.me/AMzbpAg0    
    
    
    The Internet has effectively killed the "dumb card". Do you welcome the change? http://fb.me/1POIDyror     
    
    
    An overview of private mortgage insurance (PMI) & how to avoid or get rid of it. http://fb.me/1t62WLZxj     
    
    
    Happy 4th! Here are the highlights, oddities, and deals of the last week... http://fb.me/vl0IiEUP    
    
    
    What are your favorite personal finance topics to read about and discuss? http://fb.me/1MJLz6ZeE     
    
    
    Through Dec. 25, get 92% off face value on gift certificates from Restaurant.com. http://fb.me/DqgkUjdd    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: A Guide to the New Bank Overdraft Protection Fees Rules http://bit.ly/b8LLzM    
    
    
    Have you been asked by your bank lately, "would you like to opt-in to overdraft protection?". Sounds great, right?... http://fb.me/uF6iOdPL    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Are Losses on the Sale of a Home Tax Deductible? http://20somethingfinance.com/home-sale-loss-tax-deduction/    
    
    
    Are losses on the sale of a home tax deductible in the same way losses on equity investments are? Find out... http://fb.me/COxtOe5D    
    
    
    Your utility company has money to give you. You just need to find it. Here are 12 rebates/freebies to look for. http://fb.me/1Nq49ozXe     
    
    
    Here are the Roth IRA Basics in a Q & A format for 2012. http://fb.me/146Vq43NZ     
    
    
    Did Best Buy eliminate restocking fees due to my bashing their return policy just 2 days earlier? Hmmm..... me... http://fb.me/GBkMhYF1    
    
    
    What is the "Crossover Point"? I think it's the quantitative definition of financial independence. http://fb.me/1ShqTm5NN     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Do you Give Money to Panhandlers? (Reader Poll) http://bit.ly/bOWBBb    
    
    
    Do you give money to panhandlers? Take the poll! http://fb.me/B4tJpP7U    
    
    
    The Goldman Sachs resignation letter from Greg Smith lacks credibility for these 4 reasons... http://fb.me/T7nkaiaq     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Highlights, Favorites, Deals, & Oddities – Week of 7-5-10 http://bit.ly/9zCnKo    
    
    
    Chase Freedom Q2 5% cash back bonus categories include groceries! It could net you an extra $75 cash back. http://fb.me/1gffgZlym     
    
    
    What does Devo have to do with this weeks highlights & oddities? http://fb.me/zC54JIzg    
    
    
    You can get free entrance to all 397 national parks for a week in April with National Park Week. http://fb.me/1GD1qZoRr     
    
    
    Chase Sapphire credit card review: If you're looking for a no annual fee credit card that has a good cash back... http://fb.me/D5iyb6Yy    
    
    
    Tour de France is heating up! If you've never watched, check out one of the mountain stages this week.    
    
    
    Finally! Learn what 'use by', 'sell by', and 'best before' REALLY mean... http://fb.me/BrZmvE0s    
    
    
    Miller Chill and Bud Light Lime... yay or nay??    
    
    
    @lancearmstrong your form has been great. Your luck has been shit. Come back for one more & go out on top. You deserve better than this.    
    
    
    Gen Y: On a boomerang to nowhere? http://fb.me/1VzUwm1GA     
    
    
    Here is how to do a quick tax refund status check. http://fb.me/1hBW3RqMO     
    
    
    Think you might not need home insurance? Don't roll the dice. http://fb.me/1J3pmtrqu     
    
    
    How much is 'just right' to spend on the first date? http://fb.me/BEEGKaZ8    
    
    
    I won the Mega Millions! http://20somethingfinance.com/mega-millions/  http://fb.me/1UUVe6SC0     
    
    
    20somethingfinance is rated as a top 10 personal finance blog by Kiplinger! Much love for Kip:... http://fb.me/Rf0ZnQcl     
    
    
    How I cut my electric bill with one $30 device. Now it's your turn to take the electricity use challenge!... http://fb.me/1OzTbEKWq     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Highlights, Favorites, Deals, & Oddities – Week of 7-5-10 http://bit.ly/bVCWp8    
    
    
    Highlights, Oddities, & Deals of the week of July 12. http://fb.me/CEmCPdzs    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 3 Guerrilla Tactics to Get Rid of Clutter http://20somethingfinance.com/get-rid-of-clutter-tactics/    
    
    
    Have problems with clutter? Just can't seem to get rid of those M.C. Hammer pants or that Ace of Base cd? It's... http://fb.me/vEu0Rjc6    
    
    
    $4 per gallon gas: from Apocalypse to necessary evil in 4 short years? We Americans are a funny bunch:... http://fb.me/1OFpaVuZs     
    
    
    Love apartment hunting on Craigslist, but find locating specific searching unbearable because you have to look up... http://fb.me/F1FvHdxY    
    
    
    Anyone here fought property taxes?    
    
    
    How much does your home insurance cost? Readers share their costs & tips on how to lower your premium:... http://fb.me/KTiVRFyw     
    
    
    I have 5 Ooma refer-a-friend coupons for $50 off! (best price I've seen on a new Ooma):... http://fb.me/1yyIKqmnt     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week - Holiday, 2010 Edition. http://fb.me/AlMck8vT    
    
    
    Time to stop complaining and start acting on high gas prices (you will feel better):... http://fb.me/1d096Khe6     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: An Intro to Urban Homesteading with the Dervaes Family http://bit.ly/9gj5Wh    
    
    
    An introduction to urban homesteading. Contains a very inspiring video - you'll NEED to check this out! http://fb.me/CJDKlNQw    
    
    
    There is a marriage between impact reduction & personal wealth. It's time for you to take action:... http://fb.me/18jLonhOK     
    
    
    Is Craigslist the #1 planet and money saving invention ever?... http://fb.me/1F4PtVGfT     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Napping at Work - Why don't Employers Encourage it? http://20somethingfinance.com/nap-at-work/    
    
    
    Think employees should be allowed to nap on the job? Yeah, me too. Why aren't more employers encouraging it? http://fb.me/Ry2VKQWn    
    
    
    Protect Yourself! Here are 3 credit car theft scenarios you might not be protecting yourself against...... http://fb.me/1mbZDgehy     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Highlights, Favorites, Deals, & Oddities – Week of 7-19-10 http://bit.ly/bxPbjx    
    
    
    I am declaring death to the "cheapskate" phrase! http://20somethingfinance.com/cheapskate-definition/ … http://fb.me/1GbWDqOXb     
    
    
    Highlights, Oddities, & Deals of the week of July 19. http://fb.me/EbtPXMzM    
    
    
    Don't want to have to wait another 11 months for the Tour de France. Guess it's better than 4 years for the World Cup.    
    
    
    @lancearmstrong - a couple bad breaks but the form was there. Best Tour de France cyclist in history. Congrats on a great career.    
    
    
    A review of the top 10 cities for young professionals to live in. http://fb.me/DtkPGenk    
    
    
    Looking for the absolute cheapest prepaid wireless? Tracfone might be a good bet. Check out my review. http://fb.me/DkxeQL1Z    
    
    
    Here is an intro to socially responsible investing, or SRI, for those with a guilty investing conscience:... http://fb.me/1JNaFW8PM     
    
    
    @creditkarma Are you guys asking for credit card on sign-ups now? Reader was concerned you've been hijacked.    
    
    
    @shannonmcnay thanks Shannon!    
    
    
    @misslysskiss making Earth Day every day... I like it!    
    
    
    @misslysskiss You need to start commenting on the blog more! We need a positive voice amongst the vocal haters! LOL.    
    
    
    @drew8788 Thought you might like Bear's reply today: http://www.bearmccreary.com/blog/?p=2001&cpage=3#comment-8583    
    
    
    Chase Slate is offering a no-balance transfer fee, zero APR card option, for a limited time! If you have credit... http://fb.me/1QSZUGBEn     
    
    
    Money & happiness studies like to look at a magical income $ amount, but I think they all have 1 fatal flaw:... http://fb.me/10OCylK8N     
    
    
    Find out how much in saved taxes the new Obama/Republican tax cut deal will result in for you... http://fb.me/GXtjPA45    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Unemployment Benefits Extended: Do you Agree with this Move? (Reader Poll) http://bit.ly/bweOLU    
    
    
    What do you think about the political debate to extend unemployment benefits, which was passed last week? http://fb.me/CuxjZ9TW    
    
    
    Hate your job? 55% of Americans agree. Here are 5 steps you can take to fix it! http://fb.me/LUJ9YQL0    
    
    
    Highlights, Oddities, & Deals for the week of July 26. http://fb.me/wqEFIByC    
    
    
    8 tips to protect yourself against mail fraud and identity theft:... http://fb.me/DjHgOuY3     
    
    
    The full story about why I created http://20somethingfinance.com : http://20somethingfinance.com/my-story/  http://fb.me/1cSuvjZ51     
    
    
    There is a real funny thing about "convenience"... (hint: it's not so funny at all):... http://fb.me/1DexT3k0R     
    
    
    Can't get Wordpress Automatic Upgrade to work. Scared of doing it manually!    
    
    
    Tough question: what is more fulfilling to you: saving money, or making money? (take the poll!)... http://fb.me/MTbyPJGE     
    
    
    Picked 3 quarts of blackberries and 3 quarts of raspberries today. Now I'm picking at the 7 mosquito bites on my face.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Adjusted Gross Income (AGI) Vs. Modified Adjusted Gross Income (MAGI) http://bit.ly/dt8tm0    
    
    
    What the difference between gross income, adjusted gross income, and modified adjusted gross income are - and why... http://fb.me/DYgHAlgG    
    
    
    I grew up in the 80's. Am I just nostalgic about how enjoyable the music was, or was it really that good?    
    
    
    10 FREE financial services to help you DOMINATE your personal finances in the new year. This is Epic! http://fb.me/HLUwCFn1    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: GM's Chevy Volt Vs. Nissan Leaf: The Mass-Market Electric Vehicle Wars Begin http://bit.ly/ceWDX1    
    
    
    Chevy Volt Vs. Nissan Leaf - which would you pick? http://fb.me/Ace8xbP0    
    
    
    Is Gen Y becoming "The Frugal Generation"? http://20somethingfinance.com/gen-y-frugal-purchasing-habits/ … http://fb.me/159xrim92     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: New Amazon Kindle WiFi Retails for $139 - But are you Buying? http://20somethingfinance.com/kindle-wifi-3g/    
    
    
    A look at the new Kindle wi-fi. Despite the price being one-third of the previous generation..... I still like my... http://fb.me/DCrVcw9j    
    
    
    Here's a way to get cheap dental care without having dental insurance:... http://fb.me/1qrJRxZoa     
    
    
    TradeKing and Zecco, two of the lowest cost online brokers, are merging into one company:... http://fb.me/1G9w6gGiI     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: TradeKing Promotion: $50 Signup Bonus http://20somethingfinance.com/tradeking-promotion/    
    
    
    $50 annual TradeKing promotion live now through August. Great discount broker. http://fb.me/Et2oYFmx    
    
    
    There is a dark side to budgeting: http://20somethingfinance.com/the-dark-side-of-budgeting/ … http://fb.me/1lXtqBvb4     
    
    
    Should you buy mortgage life insurance or kick it to the curb?... http://fb.me/1SaCwTvya     
    
    
    Money is great, but... here are 50 things that are better:... http://fb.me/1s5YXbURl     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Traditional & Roth IRA Income Limits http://20somethingfinance.com/traditional-roth-ira-income-limits/    
    
    
    Did you know that your income could be so high that you are not able to contribute to a Roth IRA or deduct taxes... http://fb.me/AW5kLEXp    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: CouchSurfing: The New Way to Travel? http://20somethingfinance.com/couchsurfing/    
    
    
    CouchSurfing 101: I did it for the first time this past weekend. This post highlights all the basics of this... http://fb.me/xbHWEGhO    
    
    
    You can save money (& time) on prescription drugs through home mail order delivery by your health insurer:... http://fb.me/1txlxwPml     
    
    
    You NEED to start investing (even if just small amounts). Here's 4 reasons why:... http://fb.me/PwFCTAeW     
    
    
    I found 3 ways to get rid of your Comcast modem rental fee (may also apply to other ISP's):... http://fb.me/17Buc4w8c     
    
    
    Here is a recap of the 57 best posts of 2010 published on 20somethingfinance. Thanks for making 2010 a great one!... http://fb.me/PX4J0uyw    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 7 HUGE Benefits to Downsizing into a Tiny Home http://20somethingfinance.com/tiny-home-benefits/    
    
    
    Tiny homes have HUGE benefits. Here's a list of 7 reasons why you should consider downsizing your dwelling. http://fb.me/EbP3A65h    
    
    
    Want to know how to invest in small amounts as a beginner? Here you go:... http://fb.me/KBNDSwLs     
    
    
    Ruh Roh! The wife was in a car accident and shares her story: http://20somethingfinance.com/car-accident-story/ … http://fb.me/1ufnq7b6f     
    
    
    Your employer may offer HDHP & HSA bonus incentives. Take advantage while you can!... http://fb.me/Bm7S2aka     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Highlights, Favorites, Deals, & Oddities – Week of 8-9-10 http://bit.ly/byUkp2    
    
    
    Highlights & Deals of the week of August 9th http://fb.me/GS7Tr1zv    
    
    
    We just took a 6-day, $346 vacation. Here's how we did it... http://20somethingfinance.com/cheap-vacation-tips/ … http://fb.me/1Kcg2IDoy     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 2010 Roth IRA Conversion Rules: What's the Big Deal About 2010? http://bit.ly/bjowSt    
    
    
    What's the big deal about Roth IRA conversions in 2010? Find out in this simple overview.. http://fb.me/A4MNB1XV    
    
    
    Comcast offers $10 internet to low income families. Goodwill? Not exactly, but take advantage if you can:... http://fb.me/1XZPgDKP0     
    
    
    Could you live below the United States poverty line?... http://fb.me/11taJwNaI     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 70% of Americans want to be Self-Employed. What is Stopping you? (Reader Poll) http://bit.ly/9231DX    
    
    
    70% of Americans want to be self employed. So why haven't you?? Take the poll! http://fb.me/E5OcFpKS    
    
    
    I wrote a new post on Wisebread that gives my story of how I got involved in personal finance blogging and what... http://fb.me/GV7Bz2Zv    
    
    
    You can reduce points & get an auto insurance discount by taking an online defensive driver class:... http://fb.me/1suUcCsXg     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: TradeKing Review http://20somethingfinance.com/tradeking-review/    
    
    
    I review the discount broker, TradeKing, in full... http://fb.me/G06NvRYp    
    
    
    When personal finance overlooks ideology...you lose: http://20somethingfinance.com/personal-finance/ … http://fb.me/KKmKSsIw     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: $50 Sign-Up Bonus TradeKing Promo is Back http://20somethingfinance.com/tradeking-promo/    
    
    
    TradeKing's annual $50 bonus signup promo is back. Runs through the end of January. This is a special offer not... http://fb.me/HE7ETpia    
    
    
    Just how much should you put towards a down payment on a home? http://20somethingfinance.com/down-payment/  http://fb.me/1Mfy7BZsL     
    
    
    @philipbrewer No problem. Enjoy your stuff and have come to a very similar philosophy. Still have to grab a beer sometime.    
    
    
    @kiasuchick great question.... wife is about to go back to school, and owning a home on no legit income could spell disaster.    
    
    
    The origins of frugality: why are we frugal? http://20somethingfinance.com/frugal/  http://fb.me/1CdLFtsv1     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Highlights, Favorites, Deals, & Oddities – Week of 8-16-10 http://bit.ly/adgwxi    
    
    
    Highlights, Deals, Favorites, & Oddities for the week of 8/16/10 http://fb.me/ya8wHZ1q    
    
    
    The Breaking Bad guide to personal finance: http://20somethingfinance.com/breaking-bad-guide-to-personal-finance/ … http://fb.me/1T7Rq9LjI     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Lawnmower Class Action Lawsuit Could Bring you $75 (Sign up by August 31) http://bit.ly/dw8CBO    
    
    
    http://20somethingfinance.com/lawnmower-class-action-lawsuit/Bought a lawnmower in the last 16 years? You might be... http://fb.me/Eti3dVMw    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Get it On. Child Tax Credit Extended through 2012 http://20somethingfinance.com/child-tax-credit/    
    
    
    It might just be time to start pro-creating again. You have roughly through March to seal the deal. Why? The Child... http://fb.me/NhGGk5Oe    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 10 Fun Summer Activities for Under $10 that you May Have Forgot About http://bit.ly/bV6sLw    
    
    
    10 cheap summer fun things to do before summer is over! http://fb.me/GCG6cIZ6    
    
    
    The BIG home: is it an American dream, or a nightmare? http://20somethingfinance.com/big-home-american-dream-disease/ … http://fb.me/28c4y9VZc     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Zappos Offers Free Overnight Shipping Membership (Ends Today) http://bit.ly/a2u6PC    
    
    
    Zappos offers free overnight shipping membership. No purchase necessary. Ends today! http://fb.me/uUwCe9Dy    
    
    
    @hostgator admins can't seem to keep my site up for more than a minute at a time. Was much better before I asked them to fix, now it's worse    
    
    
    @ooma When are you going to start doing the refer-a-friend for Amazon cards again? That was a sweet promo! iPad raffle - not so much.    
    
    
    @smartasafox I hope you are addicted! Haha. Thanks for the mention.    
    
    
    Last week the Supreme Court upheld Obamacare as constitutional. Here is what it means for you:... http://fb.me/1LIQfzlwU     
    
    
    @EXEDoN Thanks, Rudo!    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Mark Cuban, Tony Robbins, & My Personal Rants on the Economy http://bit.ly/dh4Plq    
    
    
    Mark Cuban, Tony Robbins, and I rant about the economy. http://fb.me/t930nTWP    
    
    
    Does opening or closing a credit card impact your credit score? And how much? I found out:... http://fb.me/1ziaHLO3B     
    
    
    I have an Ooma refer-a-friend code for $50 discount and free shipping. Only 5 uses before it can't be used any... http://fb.me/1STYoPJS5     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: The Hidden 401K Fees that Can Crack your Nest Egg http://20somethingfinance.com/hidden-401k-fees/    
    
    
    Hidden 401k fees could wipe out your account balance by 28% or more by retirement. Find out how you can avoid that... http://fb.me/HVTBPYbt    
    
    
    Dave Ramsey's 7 baby steps are good. But here's a much better version:... http://fb.me/269UbgxCv     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, & Deals for the week of August 23rd. http://fb.me/GDjNNtIU    
    
    
    Consolidate those 401K's into an IRA!! Here's why you should:... http://fb.me/1te24Jj9U     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 5 Ways to Recession-Proof Yourself http://20somethingfinance.com/recession-proof-yourself/    
    
    
    Got economy concerns on your mind? Here's 5 ways to recession-proof yourself. http://fb.me/GFw6fel9    
    
    
    Which type of insurance covers you if you are at fault in an accident?... http://fb.me/11pwbcfzP     
    
    
    How to roll over your 401K to an IRA: http://20somethingfinance.com/how-to-roll-over-your-401k-to-an-ira/ … http://fb.me/1vNTYTzhx     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: CouchSurfing 101: 10 Tips for First-Time Surfers http://20somethingfinance.com/couchsurfing-tips/    
    
    
    Interested in CouchSurfing, but don't know where to start? Here's 10 tips for first-time couch surfers. http://fb.me/EHvfc96o    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 2011 Tax Rate Bracket Changes Announced by IRS http://20somethingfinance.com/2011-tax-rate-brackets/    
    
    
    I have all the details on the 2011 tax rate bracket changes... http://fb.me/x3wXK9gA    
    
    
    Since when did all runners start running against traffic on the side of the road?    
    
    
    How to replace a Comcast-owned modem with your own:... http://fb.me/21PNuXeTS     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: What are Closed End Funds? http://20somethingfinance.com/what-are-closed-end-funds/    
    
    
    Ever run into a closed-end fund and wondered what it was? Here's your chance to find out. http://fb.me/yPN6dWZN    
    
    
    Accident forgiveness: how does it work, and which insurers offer it?... http://fb.me/19EXRsoNe     
    
    
    How to get your Social Security Statement online (& why you should check it annually):... http://fb.me/1YYxzwxQl     
    
    
    Lifestyle inflation... justified: http://20somethingfinance.com/lifestyle-inflation-justified/ … http://fb.me/2jMjYqpc8     
    
    
    College football is back edition of the highlights, favorites, oddities, and deals of the week. Happy Labor Day! http://fb.me/HM71hBjy    
    
    
    New Obamacare women's preventative care benefits kicked in yesterday (including free birth control):... http://fb.me/Yg1vx8Zc     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Chase Freedom Card Review http://20somethingfinance.com/chase-freedom-review/    
    
    
    I review the Chase Freedom credit card and compare it to the Chase Sapphire. No annual fee, unlimited 1% cash back... http://fb.me/HM3pX8F8    
    
    
    Do you or a friend or family member have an upcoming birthday? Take the Birthday Glutton Marathon Challenge! 10... http://fb.me/JftaY4wq    
    
    
    Dividend investing: an introductory guide: http://20somethingfinance.com/dividend-investing/ … http://fb.me/1MASVazC0     
    
    
    I share what's in my wallet: http://20somethingfinance.com/my-wallet/  http://fb.me/1fqWhzutV     
    
    
    Olympic athlete finances: from poverty to the penthouse: http://20somethingfinance.com/olympic-athlete-finances/ … http://fb.me/1tbAyELLA     
    
    
    Interested in dividend investing? Get familiar with the "Dividend Aristocrats":... http://fb.me/sI1n5MrA     
    
    
    Have a financially irresponsible significant other? Here are 5 conversation starters to inspire them:... http://fb.me/180geZHO7     
    
    
    What is prime rate? Find out how it impacts you: http://20somethingfinance.com/prime-rate/  http://fb.me/1YXbJzEKg     
    
    
    Sometimes personal finance is dark. Share your somewhat shady ideas on how to save & make money:... http://fb.me/1c2caZEhz     
    
    
    Dividend ETF's: the passive way to invest in dividends. Here are some dividend ETF lists for you:... http://fb.me/2aZhKGYcd     
    
    
    At what income level does money no longer add to daily happiness levels? See the study results and take the poll. http://fb.me/ASKBqCSp    
    
    
    Still a student? Here's a list of tax credits & deductions for the 2012 year:... http://fb.me/1A4hicrUH     
    
    
    Here is an easy way to pick up a free $25 from Amex by getting a prepaid gift card:... http://fb.me/NqjR5acQ     
    
    
    @lucagrandicelli It produces a fatal error. I have the latest version of wordpress. Line 80.    
    
    
    How much money would YOU need to just walk away? http://20somethingfinance.com/how-much-money-do-i-need-to-retire/ … http://fb.me/1Blhh8tfK     
    
    
    @lucagrandicelli FREE. I went back to the previous version, but it occurs when updating in the WP backend. It tries to update, then fails    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals for the week of September 6. http://fb.me/IYcJn7b4    
    
    
    54.5 MPG by 2025? The Obama administration came to an agreement with automakers last week:... http://fb.me/28zmBmNfi     
    
    
    My wife and I put together a resource on student loan deferment, forbearance, & forgiveness options:... http://fb.me/J2wlFME4     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 10 Library Freebies you Might Not have Known (or Forgot) About http://20somethingfinance.com/library-free/    
    
    
    10 freebies from your local library that you might not have known (or forgot) about. http://fb.me/HeNVgN18    
    
    
    Woah, just passed Tweet #1,000!!    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Energy Tax Credits Extended but Reduced in 2011 http://20somethingfinance.com/2011-energy-tax-credits/    
    
    
    The generous Home Energy Tax Credits were extended into 2011, however, the benefits were reduced. There are still... http://fb.me/xoAPEkvH    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Hipmunk Makes Airfare Comparison Shopping Fun for a Change http://20somethingfinance.com/hipmunk/    
    
    
    Hipmunk.com is an airfare comparison site that takes a visual approach to finding the cheapest flights. And it's... http://fb.me/JnU9Mzxf    
    
    
    Only 2 personal finance magazines remain - my response to Smart Money ceasing publication:... http://fb.me/H57Drl4h     
    
    
    Home Equity Loans vs. Home Equity Line of Credit (HELOC): which wins? I take a look:... http://fb.me/wh7RLqTq     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Do you Tip for Takeout (Carryout) Food? http://20somethingfinance.com/do-you-tip-for-takeout/    
    
    
    Do you tip for takeout food? How much? http://fb.me/uZ4tsRRG    
    
    
    We all yearn for employer commitment, but would you sign a job contract?... http://fb.me/1Splh9bN8     
    
    
    A bit perplexed on charitable donation receipts for tax deductions? I try to clear up the confusion:... http://fb.me/2jlKWGppM     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: The Top 15 Cheapest New Cars of 2011 http://20somethingfinance.com/cheapest-new-cars-of-2011/    
    
    
    Check out the top 15 cheapest new cars of 2011 - includes dealer cost & annual fuel costs! http://fb.me/QYOadSJu    
    
    
    @AllyBank @Time Don't mention it - you guys have a great online bank! Interview was great, thank you!    
    
    
    @FordFiesta Is my pick for the best inexpensive vehicle of 2011: http://20somethingfinance.com/cheapest-new-cars-of-2011/    
    
    
    I sit down with @AllyBank for a brief interview: http://tlk.tc/JJx #personalfinance #money    
    
    
    What happens when utility company's and Super PAC's unite? I have the answer (and it will save you money):... http://fb.me/1ScmYVYIp     
    
    
    What happens when utility companies and Super PAC's unite? I have the answer (and it will save you money):... http://fb.me/22yZitqhO     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of September 13, 2010. http://fb.me/G2jejcg3    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Cheapest Data Plans for Mobile Phones http://20somethingfinance.com/cheapest-data-plan-smartphones/    
    
    
    I review the cost and features of all national mobile phone data plans. http://fb.me/HAsitMyZ    
    
    
    The U.S. retirement crisis that could lead to a zombie apocalypse is coming...... http://fb.me/23QR9EXxO     
    
    
    The 2013 Child Tax Credit drops to $500 Jan. 1. Better get that c-section or inducement scheduled for late Dec.!... http://fb.me/2bh33W0k3     
    
    
    Is the manager special ever a good idea? Take the poll! http://fb.me/J24Ilexm    
    
    
    2011 tax filing deadline extended, but filing start for those who itemize delayed. http://fb.me/SwUZESQF    
    
    
    Romney Vs. Obama on Capital Gains & Dividend Tax Rates & the Bush tax cuts expiration:... http://fb.me/1jZ7mC7gl     
    
    
    How much life insurance should you buy? Here's my take:... http://fb.me/2cwKVH7ex     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of September 20, 2010. http://fb.me/vMeQWdf6    
    
    
    Still need a flu shot? Here's how to get one for free, or at least cheaply:... http://fb.me/1UVm0EmnX     
    
    
    APR vs APY: what's the difference, and why it matters: http://20somethingfinance.com/apr-vs-apy/  http://fb.me/2mSsGv7qA     
    
    
    I have 5 ooma referral codes for $40 off ($139 after) w/ free shipping. Expires end of October. These will go... http://fb.me/1lu5mPq4L     
    
    
    We live in an age of disloyalty and career change. Are we obligated to tell our employers when we are changing... http://fb.me/xlbKJyfS    
    
    
    Here are 7 tips to protect yourself and against mail theft and fraud. http://fb.me/GNxcH2Tf    
    
    
    I review "No Impact Man": http://20somethingfinance.com/no-impact-man-review/ … http://fb.me/1mqE5ka2i     
    
    
    The 2013 maximum 401K contribution has been increased! http://20somethingfinance.com/2013-maximum-401k-contribution/ … http://fb.me/1ZeOzEtUi     
    
    
    ALWAYS check your bill. I discovered an error on a statement that saved me $702. Here's the story. http://fb.me/HNcR6FPX    
    
    
    There are 2 quick & easy things EVERYONE should do to lower heating costs before anything else:... http://fb.me/2vOp6v9pQ     
    
    
    The IRA maximum contribution limit increase for first time since 2008:... http://fb.me/xz1VcJgo     
    
    
    The IRA maximum contribution limit increase for first time since 2008:... http://fb.me/1FgF0h2se     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of September 27, 2010. http://fb.me/I2bsUHwu    
    
    
    CEO's threatening job & pay cuts based on election results? Yep, it's happening. Thanks again, Citizens United...... http://fb.me/yYyvg79Y     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of January 10, 2011. http://fb.me/IYbjaAN9    
    
    
    Open enrollment season is here. Here are 6 things to make sure you review:... http://fb.me/1oPrxMhl0     
    
    
    Bartering is back! Here's how to do it, the best websites, and why national bartering networks usually fail. http://fb.me/GRgz1wWW    
    
    
    CPT codes: why you NEED to know what they are & why it could save you thousands of $:... http://fb.me/1EyQfBnN3     
    
    
    Hard credit inquiries vs. soft credit inquiries and how each impacts your credit score. http://fb.me/uIGLmcZs    
    
    
    An EPA audit found Kia/Hyundai overstated fuel economy mpg for last 3 years. If you own one, you may be entitled... http://fb.me/1oqWWxBiJ     
    
    
    Online discount broker, TradeKing, is offering a $50 bonus promo for new customers through the end of Nov. I have... http://fb.me/1KXWMAvg2     
    
    
    Last year I voluntarily switched from a PPO to a HDHP. I just published the costs & savings for those interested:... http://fb.me/AEQJ6ev5     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Bartering Taxes: How to Report Barter Income to the IRS http://20somethingfinance.com/bartering-tax-irs/    
    
    
    What?! You have to pay taxes when you barter? Yep. Here's the details. http://fb.me/BwXmO8eo    
    
    
    What is this "fiscal cliff" & the politics behind it? & can we avoid it? Here is an overview:... http://fb.me/N91rTAGW     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of October 4, 2010. http://fb.me/Hrh9qRsk    
    
    
    Max out your HSA! Why I'm doing it in 2013 & beyond... while I still can:... http://fb.me/1YDFniw7v     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: The Most Fuel Efficient Cars of 2011 http://20somethingfinance.com/most-fuel-efficient-cars-of-2011/    
    
    
    Here are the 15 most fuel efficient cars of 2011 under $30k! http://fb.me/xV2YI7fx    
    
    
    Huge Spartan victory!    
    
    
    Perkstreet Financial (a debit card company), is offering an amazing 5% cashback rewards for new accounts from... http://fb.me/KVZjdUr3    
    
    
    Perkstreet Financial (a debit card company), is offering an amazing 5% cashback rewards for new accounts from... http://fb.me/IAlRLa6h    
    
    
    Black Thanksgiving? Who is to blame for this? http://20somethingfinance.com/black-thanksgiving-hours/ … http://fb.me/zT2QRk6L     
    
    
    @hostgator must have blown up. My hosted site is down and so is theirs! Crap!    
    
    
    Americans work too damn much! Don't believe me? Check out this post: http://fb.me/I4mdujcy    
    
    
    Site is down @hostgator can't seem to get it back up. Frustrating to pay for a dedicated server for a blog and they can't keep it up.    
    
    
    @hostgator It's down again. It's been down for 14 hours now. 20somethingfinance.com    
    
    
    Hey guys, anyone have a recommendation for a good web host that can consistently keep your site up and running fast?    
    
    
    @hostgator IIM-14060912 and FAN-14061113    
    
    
    @hostgator still not working.    
    
    
    Hi everyone. Sorry for all of the website problems. You write one post that goes viral and all of a sudden, no website. Bad news.    
    
    
    @hostgator Just responded. It's every single page taking minutes to load. Friends have verified. Site worked fine until yesterday. Level 4?    
    
    
    The Saver's Tax Credit: free money just for saving for retirement? Yep!... http://fb.me/2jrZwXwuQ     
    
    
    Billy Walter, the most feared sports better in history, is afraid of Wall Street. Find out why & what it means for... http://fb.me/T5QLRgwf    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How to Use a Secured Credit Card to Build your Credit http://20somethingfinance.com/secured-credit-card/    
    
    
    One of the most common questions I get is "how do I build credit when I don't have any?". Secured credit cards may... http://fb.me/LAPSXNS7    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Live Sporting Events Vs. HDTV: Which do you Prefer? http://20somethingfinance.com/live-sporting-event-vs-hdtv/    
    
    
    Live sporting events vs. HDTV - which do you prefer? Vote in the poll! http://fb.me/vyMvnWYO    
    
    
    A lifetime of chiropractor, massage therapy, & physical therapy work for just $60?!... http://fb.me/1IQ0umoPT     
    
    
    My wife's nursing career change story: http://20somethingfinance.com/nursing-career-change/ … http://fb.me/1YxHjRiX7     
    
    
    5 huge takeaways from the Great Recession that might just better prepare you for the next one:... http://fb.me/298McV9Va     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: iPad Contest? Take your iPad and Shove it! http://20somethingfinance.com/ipad-contest/    
    
    
    @Steelcase_Store Wait, 15th has already passed.    
    
    
    Want to de-commercialize the holidays in your family? Here's how I did it and you can too:... http://fb.me/MN9NirSf     
    
    
    Best gas rewards card? Penfed offers this card that gives 5% cash back with no caps & no annual fee!... http://fb.me/1nUbkAZXe     
    
    
    2013 energy tax credits? Go big or go home: http://20somethingfinance.com/2013-energy-tax-credits/ … http://fb.me/200XF3GFZ     
    
    
    What are the 4 keys to keeping your job and boosting your income? Find out - this is must read material... http://fb.me/Dqons3kS    
    
    
    Are investments protected just like bank account deposits? Find out more about the SIPC, what, & how much it... http://fb.me/2AQbgf47g     
    
    
    "Help, where's all my money going!?" - I tackle my first ever reader case study:... http://fb.me/22w753gBJ     
    
    
    2013 Roth IRA Basics unleashed: http://20somethingfinance.com/roth-ira-basics-in-a-question-and-answer-format/ … http://fb.me/2z3pgwRew     
    
    
    20somethingfinance turns 5 years old! Here is my 5 biggest learnings from running a personal finance blog for 5... http://fb.me/1jLQDm9Cn     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of October 18, 2010. http://fb.me/xyzaCo4X    
    
    
    In to philosophy? Here are the top 25 ideological posts of the first 5 years of http://20somethingfinance.com .... http://fb.me/2uwAe4p3z     
    
    
        
    
    
    Here are the best 20somethingfinance posts of 2012. Happy New Year everyone!... http://fb.me/1sjRztza5     
    
    
    I share my biggest financial accomplishments in 2012 and goals for 2013. It'd be fun to have you stop by to do... http://fb.me/1i95cTOb3     
    
    
    I discuss why job performance is mostly unrelated to job security (believe it or not!). http://fb.me/sEJ4Teie    
    
    
    Fiscal cliff deal details are final (Obama has signed). Find out how it impacts you:... http://fb.me/1rKpEFXfD     
    
    
    The top 15 cheapest new cars of 2013: http://20somethingfinance.com/cheapest-new-cars-2013/ … http://fb.me/1tjjDMiVX     
    
    
    Ooma referrals are back: $40 off plus free shipping (use of my code limited to 5 of you):... http://fb.me/2b97nBWca     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How to Get Rid of Cable: Share your Story! http://20somethingfinance.com/how-to-get-rid-of-cable/    
    
    
    20somethingfinance readers want your tips on how you got rid of cable. Let's brainstorm! http://fb.me/CDYrAaCb    
    
    
    I'm giving away five $85 codes for H&R Block tax prep. Find out how to win!... http://fb.me/ve80IRIm     
    
    
    Sorry, comments are on now for the H&R Block giveaway:... http://fb.me/1aAvn4KyJ     
    
    
    Roth 401K conversions are now here: should you make the switch? http://20somethingfinance.com/roth-401k-conversion/ … http://fb.me/2wadZcD1M     
    
    
    Should employers be required to give employees paid sick days? Share your take:... http://fb.me/1Y0p77foI     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals - Special Halloween weekend edition! http://fb.me/uI2bCIIZ    
    
    
    20somethingfinance named the best money blog for twenty-somethings by Kiplinger. Thanks, Kip! http://fb.me/LY78LGLY    
    
    
    The 2011 401K maximum contribution limit has just been announced by the IRS. You may find the news disappointing.... http://fb.me/ybkjmIhI    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of January 17, 2011. http://fb.me/QR9KKNPy    
    
    
    Here are the top 15 most fuel efficient cars of 2013: http://20somethingfinance.com/most-fuel-efficient-cars-of-2013/ … http://fb.me/Um0GFv5v     
    
    
    Have crippling student loans? The new federal "Pay As You Earn" repayment plan might help:... http://fb.me/1urZlqBJN     
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Get Out and Vote! http://20somethingfinance.com/get-out-and-vote/    
    
    
    Only 25% of voters aged 18-29 vote in the mid-terms. This year is too important to let that trend continue. Get... http://fb.me/MYgLkENh    
    
    
    The delayed start date for itemized tax deductions has been officially announced. February 14 is the date. http://fb.me/Tr47bQJZ    
    
    
    Is it a good idea or not to move back in with your parents? We take a look. http://fb.me/MR00aJ07    
    
    
    Free birth control to all women under Obamacare... almost, there's still a few catches:... http://fb.me/2H5t2U23I     
    
    
    Love and marriage... and money. I tackle the classic debate of whether you should combine or keep finances... http://fb.me/2aRPxCfLv     
    
    
    More excited for Puppy Bowl than Super Bowl.    
    
    
    Here's a guide to a (less) painful 2012 income tax return: http://20somethingfinance.com/2012-tax-return-guide/ … http://fb.me/2cmdLDYVE     
    
    
    Big question: what would you do with your life if money were not an issue? Would it be the same thing you're doing... http://fb.me/Mjtlp0l5    
    
    
    E-file tax identity theft fraud has exploded! Here's how to protect yourself:... http://fb.me/28h8lAMCW     
    
    
    Anyone see 60 Minutes last night? There's going to be some fall out with the credit bureaus.    
    
    
    Secured vs. unsecured debt: which should you pay off first?... http://fb.me/1xU9fmBPf     
    
    
    There are some unique opportunities to optimize your finances and cash flow when you move in with a significant... http://fb.me/1xW5XQSE9     
    
    
    Michigan State and Izzo re-affirmed last night that there is only room for one elite basketball program in the state of Michigan.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Should we raise & index the national minimum wage? I examine the debate & facts:... http://fb.me/1pYZ4Yncn     
    
    
    Ever thought about getting your child in to investing early on? Check out a custodial IRA:... http://fb.me/LzyvmGGi     
    
    
    Influence what I write! Here is a survey for my wonderful readers and commenters:... http://fb.me/21CfwEibG     
    
    
    The average cost of college in 2030 at a public university? $205,000! Are 529 plans the answer? I give an... http://fb.me/2KGCVMUfK     
    
    
    I just gave the weekend my sweet embrace. Weekend, I love you. I'll never let you go, baby. <Monday> Please come back.    
    
    
    I got $435 (6%) cash back last year just for buying by regular groceries! Here's how:... http://fb.me/uG6lJBH5     
    
    
    Marissa Mayer ending telecommuting at Yahoo? No big deal. Your personal work-life balance? Now that's a big deal:... http://fb.me/Da2z6L5g     
    
    
    New blog post: Battle of the Sub Sandwich Franchises: Quiznos - Blimpie - Subway & Jimmy Johns http://bit.ly/14cZhp    
    
    
    @MonroeOnABudget How's the Monroe News holding up?    
    
    
    There's been a lot of confusion on the new 2013 tax brackets. Here's the real deal:... http://fb.me/2eGNc4SJ4     
    
    
    EVERY American should read Steven Brill's "Bitter Pill" article on why health care costs are so high:... http://fb.me/FZVJK3D4     
    
    
    20somethingfinance reader survey results are in. Here's what we learned & how it will influence my writing focus:... http://fb.me/1N8RNOxPx     
    
    
    I share my average monthly budget (spending) over the last year, highlight the U.S. average, & ask readers to... http://fb.me/GA4jLjf5     
    
    
    What if you want to be a custodian on a non-retirement account for a minor? I discuss what UGMA/UTMA accounts... http://fb.me/1CkpaN6cb     
    
    
    @EmpoweredDollar Hi Stephanie. Thanks for the interest. I've had a # of people reach out so I'll be in touch in the coming weeks. Hang tight    
    
    
    Should payday loans be entirely banned? New research helps make that case:... http://fb.me/1i5ar8fvp     
    
    
    Want to switch your HSA? Here's the list of best HSA's (& yes, you CAN switch):... http://fb.me/LbOT7t6Y     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of January 24, 2011. http://fb.me/RUarsodw    
    
    
    Having a tough time getting a job interview? Try this simple old-school strategy:... http://fb.me/uBfA80Aj     
    
    
    WTF? I actually MADE money on health insurance & health care last year?... http://fb.me/2uBoX7Q3i     
    
    
    New blog post: What is your Favorite Employee Benefit? Take the Poll! http://bit.ly/2NWi9    
    
    
    Going to watch Gran Torino tonight.    
    
    
    I didn't know who Kevin Ware was before today, but man, you've got a new fan. I wish you a full recovery.    
    
    
    How do Coverdell Education Savings Accounts compare to 529 Plans? I do a deep dive:... http://fb.me/1uyhUIOT3     
    
    
    Worried about landing the perfect job? Sometimes you just need to take the best job you can get and worry about... http://fb.me/30qznth9n     
    
    
    New blog post: A Look Into the Tiny House Movement with Tiny Home Pioneer Jay Shafer http://bit.ly/46MIJS    
    
    
    I review the $249 Samsung Chromebook: http://20somethingfinance.com/samsung-chromebook-review/ … http://fb.me/JGirJFFK     
    
    
    What should you do with money gifted to your child? Here's the answer:... http://fb.me/1BrmlXpbF     
    
    
    I have 5 uses of an Ooma referral discount code, available through 4/30/13: get the Ooma for $139 and free... http://fb.me/uvB4xkSt     
    
    
    A whole bunch of new things going on at 20somethingfinance. Check it out... http://fb.me/QJwK8yI2    
    
    
    Gran Torino was a great movie. Eastwood is one of the greatest actors/directors of all time.    
    
    
    Don't forget: tax filing deadline is tomorrow!... http://fb.me/1sFFoL8pr     
    
    
    Only YOU can prevent Tax Refund Windfall Syndrome: http://20somethingfinance.com/tax-refund-check-windfall/ … http://fb.me/FmAZpCC8     
    
    
    I put together a handy little 2010 taxes guide with the basics to help you get motivated this year. So pick up a... http://fb.me/Tiq3oz6r    
    
    
    Here is how to make a duct tape wallet: http://20somethingfinance.com/duct-tape-wallet/ … Total cost? Under $0.50. http://fb.me/1v4FcCS22     
    
    
    @Adreian_Payne Nothing would make hundreds of thousands in Spartan nation happier than to see you come back, finish degree, & win title.    
    
    
    New blog post: 4 Investment Learnings from the Stock Market Collapse & Rally http://bit.ly/1PZX2X    
    
    
    Seeing the light with low cost ETF's.    
    
    
    Free admission to national parks starts tomorrow with 2013 National Park Week:... http://fb.me/240Vktgka     
    
    
    10 easy (but extremely effective ways) to reduce your impact & save money (Earth Day Special!):... http://fb.me/2XlzTGRSQ     
    
    
    Seems like there are 4 common reactions to frugality (and I have a response to the haters):... http://fb.me/1EVATfSl7     
    
    
    @Adreian_Payne - when it doubt, you must come back. You can get paid a year from now - you can only finish out your college career once.    
    
    
    A letter to the management of Comcast, AT&T, Dish, Chase, BofA, & every other company with hated customer... http://fb.me/1yrvlW6sl     
    
    
    Why the name of my blog (http://20somethingfinance.com ) was an epic fail:... http://fb.me/I3oxF7VW     
    
    
    The perfect stock: http://20somethingfinance.com/the-perfect-stock-pick/ … http://fb.me/2olQ8ITLj     
    
    
    The top 20 occupations with the lowest unemployment rate are highlighted (and 10 with the highest). http://fb.me/uD4r7mXj    
    
    
    New post on Wisebread: 5 Tips for my career-clueless college self. If you could go back in time to give your... http://fb.me/QI8Gm06Y    
    
    
    How much does watering your lawn cost? The results may be shocking:... http://fb.me/2VyuZBLGR     
    
    
    The Retirement Gamble: an interview with Jack Bogle & why low-cost investing reduces your risk in retirement:... http://fb.me/2vhOMybld     
    
    
    10 of the cheapest cities for new college grads (& everyone else) to live in:... http://fb.me/AwXbSf2j     
    
    
    Does the "college experience" justify the price? It's time for some healthy debate:... http://fb.me/2KePlWBUa     
    
    
    Sometimes personal finance bloggers F up. And when we do, the response can be.... interesting....... http://fb.me/27kQDW87R     
    
    
    FDIC Insurance: I cover the interesting history behind the FDIC, coverage amounts, & how to protect your bank... http://fb.me/1IELMIQxQ     
    
    
    New blog post: The Beginners Guide to Playing Disc Golf http://bit.ly/RHD7e    
    
    
    A look at the average tax refund this year & how it stands up to recent averages historically:... http://fb.me/1pVhzGX59     
    
    
    Want to get a sneak peek at what your health insurance premiums might be under Obamacare?... http://fb.me/ABJDW6VN     
    
    
    Roth vs. Traditional Retirement Accounts: Why Roths are Not Always the Clear Winner:... http://fb.me/OagOq6Cr     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of January 31, 2011. http://fb.me/Aw7giRn9    
    
    
    HUGE ANNOUNCEMENT: Summer of Saving: 4 Months, 60+ Posts, All Geared to Saving you Money -... http://fb.me/x9KuPCcU     
    
    
    How to save money on food & groceries: your secret weapon:... http://fb.me/1cts1qOXA     
    
    
    Want to lower your food costs? Become a vegetarian. Here's why it's cheaper (& better):... http://fb.me/2aY1JGtyZ     
    
    
    Lets create a list of the best warehouse deals out there! I've got it started. What are your picks?... http://fb.me/Pk3dmg35     
    
    
    What are your favorite cheap "go-to" foods and why? Lets create an awesome resource for everyone:... http://fb.me/27K5KQ3dq     
    
    
    Here are my favorite cheap breakfast recipes. What are yours? http://20somethingfinance.com/cheap-breakfast/ … http://fb.me/WHuUv1Dg     
    
    
    Here are my favorite cheap lunch recipes. What are yours? http://20somethingfinance.com/cheap-lunch/  #summerofsaving http://fb.me/1c0k8nQyv     
    
    
    Here are my favorite cheap dinner recipes. What are your favorites? http://20somethingfinance.com/cheap-dinner/ ... http://fb.me/KtgwJike     
    
    
    Start planning for the 2011 National Park Week!    
    
    
    Start planning for the 2011 free National Park week! Free entrance to national parks. http://fb.me/TQq2a81x    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of November 8, 2010. http://fb.me/JYnliuUG    
    
    
    #summerofsaving moves on to utilities & entertainment expenses. What's your biggest problem utility expense?... http://fb.me/2j6wvO0Pl     
    
    
    Cutting the cord: the best alternatives to cable TV:... http://fb.me/1d8kGSPbI     
    
    
    How to get the cheapest high-speed internet service: http://20somethingfinance.com/cheapest-internet/ … Let's... http://fb.me/1O2LGOOrW     
    
    
    Woah! For all you business owners out there, the cheapest VOIP provider, Ooma, is now offering really cheap... http://fb.me/1cEpoPwxQ     
    
    
    64% of Americans still have landlines? Get rid of them now!... http://fb.me/2ou0A1v84     
    
    
    Brilliant. The perfect crime: http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/06/the-perfect-crime.html …    
    
    
    Want to know the REAL lifetime cost of a smartphone? Shocking:... http://fb.me/WJcLHbTD     
    
    
    Here is a list of the best & cheapest MVNO prepaid wireless plans:... http://fb.me/6lUV3hs6n     
    
    
    A no-contract "smartphone" for under $30? I review the Net10 LG900G. http://fb.me/DM2Q4M8i    
    
    
    Want to save on electricity? EVERYONE should do these 4 things: http://20somethingfinance.com/saving-electricity/ …... http://fb.me/2a5pxeKed     
    
    
    New blog post: Don't Move Without First Using these 4 Real Estate Search Tools http://bit.ly/s62ny    
    
    
    @hostgator broke site for 12 hours, but it's back up now: http://20somethingfinance.com     
    
    
    Want to cut your water bill: Pareto's Principle says to make these 5 changes:... http://fb.me/6nH9ubJkV     
    
    
    Here are 6 cheap & easy ways to lower your heating & cooling bills:... http://fb.me/6je6NgyBC     
    
    
    An URGENT message to the 5,000 20somethingfinance readers using Google Reader:... http://fb.me/2chRMgNcd     
    
    
    1 month of the #summerofsaving series is in the books. Here's a recap:... http://fb.me/1rCNS5bAb     
    
    
    Are health care costs the most challenging of any expense category? I think so. Here's why:... http://fb.me/H74yN4JD     
    
    
    How to find affordable health insurance, post Obamacare:... http://fb.me/38ljh8iMz     
    
    
    Preventative health care is as easy as doing these two things:... http://fb.me/MgyLAh8k     
    
    
    New post on WiseBread: 5 things other grocery stores should steal from Trader Joe's. http://fb.me/DKObcSpJ    
    
    
    Win a free copy of H&R Block at Home Premium Tax Software! I have 5 to give away (a $49.95 value). Check out my... http://fb.me/Opm48FfP    
    
    
    You truly are what you eat. Here are 8 food rules to improve your health & save you money:... http://fb.me/1kEuNCEXM     
    
    
    New blog post: Zecco Coupon Code for Free Trades - Limited Time Only http://bit.ly/14dF3t    
    
    
    Here are 4 ways to cut your medical bills, that you may not have thought of:... http://fb.me/uz1V5oQ4     
    
    
    The 7-Minute workout is a free, high intensity workout you can do from the comfort of your own home. Here's how:... http://fb.me/2K0mJ2pgW     
    
    
    I have 5 Ooma referral codes to get $50 off a refurbished Ooma ($99 total). Lowest price I've seen. Code uses are... http://fb.me/GcZObHxW     
    
    
    Get rid of your gym membership! Here are 7 items to piece together an affordable home gym. What would you add to... http://fb.me/3b1T6HojM     
    
    
    Why the cost of housing can completely ruin your finances if you're not careful:... http://fb.me/6pA0lbxYK     
    
    
    Can't figure out whether to rent or buy? You MUST calculate the price-to-rent ratio first:... http://fb.me/2Qf3VcYD8     
    
    
    Downsizing: the most impactful financial move you can make: http://20somethingfinance.com/downsizing/  http://fb.me/2nFL1kFpZ     
    
    
    Before renting or buying, calculate the "total cost of homeownership". Here is how:... http://fb.me/2UssYog4k     
    
    
    Your home is NOT an investment. Here is why: http://20somethingfinance.com/a-home-is-not-an-investment/ … http://fb.me/2xsNWWAjS     
    
    
    15 or 30 year mortgage? Here is an infographic to help you decide:... http://fb.me/12y9c8NmZ     
    
    
    15 or 30 year mortgage? This infographic breaks it down for you: http://20somethingfinance.com/15-vs-30-year-mortgage/ … http://fb.me/SMSPprkr     
    
    
    Not sure when to refinance a mortgage? Here are some tips:... http://fb.me/1zMl12T2F     
    
    
    Should you buy a house for a mortgage tax deduction? Not so fast!... http://fb.me/1mZypY7Mh     
    
    
    7 reasons to NOT buy a home: http://20somethingfinance.com/reasons-to-not-buy-a-home/ … http://fb.me/6qXeL9e9B     
    
    
    Save 6% of your equity when selling for sale by owner (FSBO). It's now easier than ever to do:... http://fb.me/1nZqwkZh8     
    
    
    Summer of Saving, month 2 recap! http://20somethingfinance.com/summer-of-saving-month-2-recap/ … #summerofsaving http://fb.me/1Tzkk06G0     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of February 7, 2011. http://fb.me/PrqLG7Ld    
    
    
    Transportation costs are the #2 expense for U.S. households, on average. More than the food we eat!... http://fb.me/1iHmUgUmQ     
    
    
    Serious about saving money? Get serious about getting rid of a car: http://20somethingfinance.com/get-rid-of-a-car/ … http://fb.me/2D1am7JN2     
    
    
        
    
    
    @nem_is_rad not me.    
    
    
    @ClintGossmeyer Not bad at all! Stay posted. Much more on bike commuting this week.    
    
    
    @ClintGossmeyer and next    
    
    
    How to choose a residence that strategically cuts your commuting costs:... http://fb.me/2oVuYzZW6     
    
    
    Taking the dog to the dog park.    
    
    
    Looking for a good commuter bike? Here is what you should consider:... http://fb.me/2Hj8XFmrI     
    
    
    New blog post: Can you Cash in on Cash for Refrigerators? http://bit.ly/t90g1    
    
    
    Tomorrow at noon is the deadline to sign up for the free tax program from H&R Block contest. Your odds are pretty good, at this stage!    
    
    
    Here are some bike commuter gear & tips to enhance your safety and enjoyment on the road:... http://fb.me/2rFWOf6I5     
    
    
    Bike maintenance 101: get the right tools & learn these 4 skills & you'll be a happy biker:... http://fb.me/6ohJOKLhq     
    
    
    Just got a new disc golf bag and some discs. I'm pumped and can't wait to use them. Ah, the simple pleasures in life.    
    
    
    The most powerful tool to cut miles driven, gasoline, & vehicle costs is free to use!... http://fb.me/1SIwIxf2P     
    
    
    Save on auto insurance with these 11 discounts: http://20somethingfinance.com/how-to-save-on-auto-insurance/ … http://fb.me/36RgW0lgZ     
    
    
    "Insource" your way to financial and life success: http://20somethingfinance.com/insource/  http://fb.me/1GOiEhRn3     
    
    
    Learn how to cut your own hair - and save MILLIONS! http://20somethingfinance.com/how-to-cut-your-own-hair/ … http://fb.me/XRpT8ZPz     
    
    
    New blog post: Why you Need to Put a Monetary & Qualitative Value on your Employee Benefits http://bit.ly/17b1Zq    
    
    
    Like beer, but not the cost? Homebrew your own and save 50%! Here's how to get started:... http://fb.me/1LgRDiMM9     
    
    
    How to port your number to Google Voice - and some things to consider before you do. http://fb.me/T57YTD9E    
    
    
    Zen and the art of DIY home maintenance and repair: http://20somethingfinance.com/diy-home-maintenance-and-repair/ … http://fb.me/2krTHePXr     
    
    
    Your toilet is probably leaking. Here's how to detect & fix a leaky toilet:... http://fb.me/2J7kMlyga     
    
    
    How to make your own non-toxic cleaning products! http://20somethingfinance.com/make-non-toxic-cleaner/ … http://fb.me/2OkiNLHDb     
    
    
    Itemizers can start filing today!    
    
    
    The Summer of Saving series is over. Here's a recap & next steps:... http://fb.me/27xc0PJaf     
    
    
    I still subscribe to a print newspaper, and here's 6 reasons why. Do you? (Take the poll) http://fb.me/zWTHdkpu    
    
    
    IRS will start recognizing same-sex marriage status for federal tax purposes starting later this month:... http://fb.me/334uOajev     
    
    
    Would you quit your job if you won $10M? Find out what % of Americans would. It might surprise you.... http://fb.me/1UwaJ4kwq     
    
    
    @joerexrode best hope for the MSU program to improve: Don Treadwell re-hire on a Miami firing, after a 3rd straight subpar year? #plantseeds    
    
    
    @MikeValenti971 cheers to hoping Treadwell gets fired, rehired & makes off./receivers respectable again in '14. Amateur hour since he left.    
    
    
    @MikeVichich @joerexrode at times he was brilliant. At worst, you always felt like the O had a pulse. Even year of inheriting JLS disaster.    
    
    
    @MikeVichich @joerexrode Treadwell also WR coach. Molded D Thomas, Cunningham, Martin, Nichol, B White, Dell. None highly recruited. #missed    
    
    
    Save for retirement or a first home? & what if a 401K match is involved? Here's my take:... http://fb.me/KaZ3Lhkf     
    
    
    You're killing your clothes! Here are 10 things you can do to extend the life of your clothing:... http://fb.me/6xQBuD9BZ     
    
    
    @MikeValenti971 Agree. Dantonio will always roll w/his boys though. That's why I say he re-hires Treadwell after season. Or his era is done.    
    
    
    Do you NEED renter's insurance? Only 31% have it. Here's my take:... http://fb.me/2pq4LR4fB     
    
    
    @MikeValenti971 Maxwell, 6-6. Terry, 5-7    
    
    
    Should you drop a financial deadbeat? Financial compatibility is the #1 determinate of long-term financial... http://fb.me/2U2ch9rGE     
    
    
    Defined benefit vs defined contribution retirement plans - what are they & what are the pros/cons of each? Lets... http://fb.me/2mqrrOpgh     
    
    
    Getting a job when you have no experience or are unemployed seems impossible. Here are a few things you can do to... http://fb.me/2JCq1mq43     
    
    
    5 tips on how to cool off that heating bill. Mine was $150 freaking dollars this past month! What was yours? http://fb.me/EFGr8dTb    
    
    
        
    
    
    Flexible spending account (FSA) basics are detailed in a Q&A format (open enrollment is here soon!):... http://fb.me/30cszD15S     
    
    
    Flu season has come early. Here is where to get the cheapest or free flu shots in 2013:... http://fb.me/2kDd2h1QD     
    
    
    New blog post: I Could Buy my Old House for One-Third of the Price? http://bit.ly/4lfHnz    
    
    
    @brian_calloway I believe it would be his 3rd chance, actually. 2nd chance resulted in Rather Hall.    
    
    
    Does it make sense to pay the Obamacare individual mandate penalty? Here are my thoughts:... http://fb.me/3fAOvFTKL     
    
    
    5 core values demonstrated by happy, wealthy, and wise individuals:... http://fb.me/13rCUJpel     
    
    
    The Obamacare insurance exchanges are open. Now what? Here's a clear & simple guide:... http://fb.me/2r0xpS6A2     
    
    
    The unpopular "automatic gratuity" could soon be a thing of the past. Here's why:... http://fb.me/6jJiw36NZ     
    
    
    Surprise! Moving expenses can be tax deductible. But there are some strings attached:... http://fb.me/RsqOnTQL     
    
    
    New Ooma for $99 ($50 off) + free shipping. Best deal I've seen. I have 5 referral codes. 1st come, 1st serve: http://20somethingfinance.com/ooma-referral-code/ …    
    
    
    How much should you save? 10%, 20%, more? Here's my take: http://20somethingfinance.com/how-much-should-i-save/ … http://fb.me/MBP67GgC     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of February 14, 2011. http://fb.me/Rn3Gphs7    
    
    
    New blog post: Harvard's Huge Hoard of Endowment Greed http://bit.ly/iDlMX    
    
    
    At the core of every purchasing decision is deciphering between cheap, quality, & luxury. Here's how:... http://fb.me/Mp3IXT2H     
    
    
    Why Personal Finance is so Taboo (& how we can Change that): http://20somethingfinance.com/personal-finance-taboo/ … http://fb.me/1KwkxTFyJ     
    
    
    One week left to use my Ooma referral code ($50 off, or $99 total) + free shipping! Best price ever on a new... http://fb.me/37d7K2xYy     
    
    
    Is organic food a "luxury"? What's your take? http://20somethingfinance.com/organic-food-luxury/ …    
    
    
    @MikeGriffith32 You sir, are an idiot.    
    
    
    @Graham_Couch @chrissolari You sir, can't pick a game.    
    
    
    Dude, where's my open enrollment? Here's why 2014 open enrollment is late, & what to expect:... http://fb.me/6tPFSUYIE     
    
    
    @ChrisVannini @Pietrang5 This one still the best: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q3PKMzD5ogo …    
    
    
    The 2014 maximum 401K contribution limit was announced by the IRS today:... http://fb.me/124fJyI8u     
    
    
    The 2014 maximum IRA contribution limits & income phaseouts were announced by the IRS today as well:... http://fb.me/2tg1lYPU5     
    
    
    New blog post: Why Getting Rid of Clutter is so Dang Hard http://bit.ly/qIpYC    
    
    
        
    
    
    The maximum HSA contribution increases in 2014. Here's why I will be maxing out again (and you should too):... http://fb.me/2S69xdo3S     
    
    
    The 2014 tax brackets & standard deductions have been increased for inflation. Here are the details:... http://fb.me/18bfWZN6x     
    
    
    How do HDHP costs & savings stack up against a PPO? Here are my personal results in year 2, after switching:... http://fb.me/12HfuI5yG     
    
    
    You might now be able to carry over $500 in FSA funds for the first time. Check out the details here:... http://fb.me/23amtZ1aN     
    
    
    I have some ideas on how to use Google's new "Google Helpouts" to save & make money:... http://fb.me/2w4wpFM1E     
    
    
    @Josh_Friedman here's a rundown of 'use by' dates and what they really mean: http://bit.ly/cL4LfV
You're probably ok.    
    
    
    Buying cars on Craigslist: 7 steps to get to them before the vultures arrive. http://fb.me/wbQTHXGE    
    
    
    How to qualify for the little-known Saver's Tax Credit in 2013 & 2014:... http://fb.me/1ZSAXZiBz     
    
    
    Have a pension? You better get to know the PBGC & how it impacts you:... http://fb.me/6o5gQPQGY     
    
    
    How much are your 2014 health insurance premiums increasing/decreasing? It's time for a roll call...... http://fb.me/10P9jwSTf     
    
    
    The current "state of retirement" for Gen X & Y is not looking good. Here's why:... http://fb.me/2FvyPnQzL     
    
    
    Bikes outselling cars? Yep. The return of the mighty bicycle has arrived:... http://fb.me/S2yihjH3     
    
    
    Planning on deducting job search expenses? Better know the rules, first:... http://fb.me/33dwFY9za     
    
    
    Frugality through Vegetarianism: How to save $2-3K per year & the planet by moving away from a meat-based diet. http://fb.me/GbUYQiuo    
    
    
    @ChrisVannini @BarryJonathan Yes, but with SC loss, SC stays behind MSU, even with MSU loss next week. Clemson would pass MSU.    
    
    
    Beware of this threatening letter from your auto insurance company & what to do with it:... http://fb.me/OFDjQihM     
    
    
    How does your credit and credit score compare to the averages for your generation? Find out here:... http://fb.me/17P3zUAgz     
    
    
    Fixed vs. Adjustable Rate Mortgages (ARM's): which is better?... http://fb.me/ODQ7W914     
    
    
    @mrmoneymustache @BudgetsAreSexy MMM - time for a fat tire bike article w/ a still of you doing a wheelie off your newly engineered roof?    
    
    
    Damn the spam (filter)! An update to 20somethingfinance readers: http://20somethingfinance.com/damn-spam/  http://fb.me/1dMwGFhy2     
    
    
    CHOOSING part-time vs. full-time? http://20somethingfinance.com/choosing-part-time-vs-full-time-work/ … http://fb.me/25zzBuKcv     
    
    
    Make online purchases without THIS rewards card? You're losing money:... http://fb.me/2V4KNASRI     
    
    
    @chrissolari No - he's just drinking the Green Kool-Aid.    
    
    
    How I got burned & learned lessons from the greatest undocumented investment bubble & crash in modern history:... http://fb.me/2aXfH38m1     
    
    
    New blog post: 3 Simplistic Strategies for Conquering Physical Clutter http://bit.ly/jfcLT    
    
    
    Holiday break is a great time to reflect, set goals, & move forward. Here's my holiday 'to-do list'. What does... http://fb.me/2BBR04GCt     
    
    
    Merry Christmas, ya filthy animals.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Quantitative Easing Definition & How it Impacts you http://20somethingfinance.com/quantitative-easing/    
    
    
    Not sure what quantitative easing is or how it might impact you? Here's my take... http://fb.me/xIh06yvC    
    
    
    Should you contribute to a 401K or IRA when in debt? Here is a rule to apply:... http://fb.me/26Lk6pZDm     
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of February 21, 2011. http://fb.me/I9HL6lZH    
    
    
    Going to watch Food Inc. tonight. Ever get that feeling before you watch a documentary that you're a glutton for punishment?    
    
    
    Enjoy the best 20somethingfinance posts of 2013: http://20somethingfinance.com/best-20somethingfinance-posts-2013/ … http://fb.me/14jStAhbB     
    
    
    I share my biggest successes/failures for 2013, & set some goals for 2014. Your turn to do the same:... http://fb.me/6mEt4s9V7     
    
    
    @BudgetsAreSexy The 4-Minute workout is the new 7-Min. workout. Get with the times, bro. Pretty soon it will be the 0-Min. workout ;-)    
    
    
    Congrats to the MSU Spartans - 2014 Rose Bowl champs. With ugly Auburn win - could they be national champs? #Arrived    
    
    
    @BudgetsAreSexy Bam: http://well.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/06/19/the-4-minute-workout/ …    
    
    
    I explore whether you actually need to buy the insurance rental car companies offer or not. http://fb.me/LKCPaTXz    
    
    
    If you have a TradeKing non-retirement account, you can start referring friends for $100 a shot! (and they get... http://fb.me/GuE0aR11    
    
    
    The U.S. is broke & broken & I highlight the main reasons why. It's time to start demanding a fix! http://fb.me/SOv5S2yc    
    
    
    New blog post: Ways to Minimize the Material Impact of E-Clutter http://bit.ly/2VRCyt    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of February 28, 2011. http://fb.me/sWO24qzt    
    
    
    Anyone else getting excited for March Madness already? 12 days to go!    
    
    
    New blog post: Are you Taking Advantage of the First-Time Home Buyer Tax Credit? http://bit.ly/kNoLQ    
    
    
    All 401K plans were not created equally. How does yours match up? Lets look at the averages. http://fb.me/QGNPjrjI    
    
    
        
    
    
    A FREE credit score service that TRULY doesn't charge you? I review Credit Karma in depth. http://fb.me/J2CbhAbc    
    
    
    Every wonder what bottled water REALLY costs compared to tap? I crunched the numbers. http://fb.me/xxgRWbZW    
    
    
    Passed 1,000 followers. WooHoo!!    
    
    
    @landonloveall Entitlements are a big problem as well. But you can't just cut them like you can defense. They need tweaking, not slashing.    
    
    
    @wizardprang I've started buying grass fed cheese.    
    
    
    I recently found out that ZERO of my peers are investing outside of their 401K. Now I'm curious as to why. Share... http://fb.me/TzQurXIb    
    
    
    Back from backpacking trip up north. Freezing, but great.    
    
    
    New blog post: The Next Sin Tax - Twinkies & Ice Cream? http://bit.ly/NXlGf    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of March 7, 2011. http://fb.me/tGdeS6gy    
    
    
    Took my dog for the first bike ride of the year last year (yes, you heard that right).    
    
    
    New blog post: Best Employee Benefits Ever: Nustar Energy? http://bit.ly/c07Ez    
    
    
    What does the average wedding cost? The answer might shock you. How much did your wedding cost? http://fb.me/TnjmGERl    
    
    
    Test your IRA knowledge with this IRA basics quiz! http://fb.me/EjKpnBou    
    
    
    Putting the finishing touches on a new website.    
    
    
    @RFham No trailer..... he runs next to me. He's very high energy, but focused on moving straight ahead.    
    
    
    Round 1 of the tournament? Please, it's still a 'play-in' in my book. Round 1 starts Thursday. I can't wait!    
    
    
    New frugal tip: Welcome to MicroFrugality.com! http://bit.ly/iVrvI    
    
    
    New frugal tip: Your Comments & Vote on the Direction of MicroFrugality.com http://bit.ly/fWe54    
    
    
    New frugal tip: Use RSS to Beat Others on Craigslist to the Used Car of your Dreams http://bit.ly/3B0Q5U    
    
    
    New blog post: The Launch of my New Blog: MicroFrugality.com http://bit.ly/3ocTNR    
    
    
    Wondering where a wicked draft is coming from! Fall is in full season for sure.    
    
    
    Is the stick still worth it? I look at manual vs. automatic transmission to see if the cost savings are still there. http://fb.me/vtEP1WBk    
    
    
    RIP Nate Dogg. Your G-funk stylings will be forever missed.    
    
    
    Pretty excited about the new site, microfrugality.com!    
    
    
    Anyone watching 'The Cleveland Show'? Not great, but better than 1st season of Family Guy.    
    
    
    New frugal tip: The Best Inexpensive Halloween Costumes  http://bit.ly/rps8G    
    
    
    @uv_searching Thanks. Hope to see you on the site!    
    
    
    Blog Action Day - this year's topic Climate Change.    
    
    
    New blog post: Win a $10K Scholarship for a Tweet? http://bit.ly/KjW6V    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of March 14, 2011 http://fb.me/EwSPCLWH    
    
    
    My cheap wedding: 7 steps that kept my wedding to $2,500 & how you can do it to! http://fb.me/D7ekV802    
    
    
    Make a lot of international calls? Find out where to get the cheapest international call rates. http://fb.me/K9itXGOe    
    
    
    Having shared financial values is one of the major keys to a successful relationship. But how do you fix things... http://fb.me/ECbGwQEJ    
    
    
    Hoping the winner of MSU vs. Iowa wins the Big Ten - & that winner is MSU. I'll be there.    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of March 21, 2011. http://fb.me/GStdP3Ji    
    
    
    Should you pay off your debt or invest? It depends. http://fb.me/UypgwwbS    
    
    
    Do you use an FSA, MSA, or HSA? There is a big change in over-the-counter expenses coming in 2011, and I also... http://fb.me/Mn6r308s    
    
    
    Personal finance is not a sprint, it's a marathon. Here are some tips on how to stay on track for the long haul. http://fb.me/VYB6uNju    
    
    
    Thinking of building your dream home? Here are 5 reasons why you should re-consider. http://fb.me/yhbpI8D2    
    
    
    Thinking of building a dream home? Here are 5 reasons why you should reconsider. http://fb.me/vekY1Miz    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals - April Fool's Edition! http://fb.me/SVI7NZHy    
    
    
    Rooting for Butler and VCU today. Wait... they play each other? Damn! Well... rooting for whomever wins to beat... http://fb.me/XcNcGhLs    
    
    
    @melissaghoffman thanks, Melissa!    
    
    
    7 IRS red flags to be aware of - tips from a tax preparer! http://fb.me/H4lJn3I0    
    
    
    I go through the basics of how to open a discount online broker account and compare 6 of the best brokers against... http://fb.me/SfbLedu4    
    
    
    If Thanksgiving is your favorite holiday, give a shout! Turkey, sweet potato, green bean casserole, 2 days off of work.... mmmmmmm    
    
    
    Are even the cheapest diesel cars worth their price? I take a deep look. http://fb.me/RL7OXqJY    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals - Elections week edition. http://fb.me/tD64XZHC    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of April 4, 2011. http://fb.me/NUQimuTg    
    
    
    Did anyone watch the pilot for "the Killing"? Intense!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Have you diversified your income by choice? Share your story with other readers! http://fb.me/xQpA8gfY    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Personal Finance DeathMatch: You Vs. Your Parents - who Wins? http://bit.ly/46Mvmv/    
    
    
    Like the coldest winter chill... heaven beside you.    
    
    
    If you use credit of any kind and don't know what a VantageScore is or where to get it, this is a must read. http://fb.me/TqPo1iA8    
    
    
    Wow! British Airways Visa is offering up 2 trans-Atlantic flights (100K miles) with a new card. That could be... http://fb.me/YEfstY93    
    
    
    Looking forward to reading Al Gore's new book.    
    
    
    Prediction: MSU Spartans beat Kansas in March Madness for the title.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Why I Switched my IRA to TradeKing http://bit.ly/3HRVrq/    
    
    
    @AVazquez87 At the moment, Costco True Earnings is great (if you have a Costco membership). Very high rewards in common categories.    
    
    
    @melissaghoffman Thanks for the idea, it's a good one!    
    
    
    @melissaghoffman Glad to hear. That's why I did it. Now and then I like to go back to basics for those just starting out.    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of April 11, 2011. http://fb.me/xmWkrAGD    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: The 5 Worst Twenty Something Personal Finance Blunders http://bit.ly/6PK5qc/    
    
    
    After this weekend, I never want to rake another leaf again.    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of November 15, 2010. http://fb.me/OaGTRqlt    
    
    
    One more day at work. Then it's Thanksgiving break. I love how non-commercial Thanksgiving is. Black Friday? Different story.    
    
    
    New frugal tip: How Low can your Toilet Flow? A Poop Story http://bit.ly/4LHbJs/    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Exciting 20SomethingFinance TGIA-Thanksgiving Updates http://bit.ly/5GdbZi/    
    
    
    This is a great way to bring awareness to Earth Day and do something good that everyone will enjoy! http://fb.me/xXICvCl0    
    
    
    Nutmeg. My sweet nutmeg.    
    
    
    Dark @ 5 PM. Can someone remind me why we have daylight savings time? Murdock (my dog) wants to go to the dog park!    
    
    
    Is Colbert doing a Christmas special again?    
    
    
    I discuss how to get over that initial fear of investing and the prospect of losing money. http://fb.me/LKg4Aqag    
    
    
    Sitting in front of the fireplace with the family, drinking a beer, watching the Spartans, with a fully belly. Doesn't get much better.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Pet Owner? The HAPPY Act Might Bring you Tax Deductions http://bit.ly/8rrbQI/    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Final Day for TradeKing $50 Bonus http://bit.ly/5E2Een/    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of April 18, 2011. http://fb.me/10jMxDdzE    
    
    
    5 day weekend somehow seemed like it was only 2 or 3.    
    
    
    A tragic reminder of what life is really all about. http://fb.me/A5DBiI0l    
    
    
    An intro. to passive index investing and why it beats the pros 8 times out of 10. http://fb.me/103MhqoFs    
    
    
    The new airline bump fees rules mean more leverage for you if you voluntarily switch flights. Also, check out the... http://fb.me/WhWaMq0I    
    
    
    New frugal tip: Use RoomAtlas to Find a Cheap Hotel in a Good Location http://bit.ly/8ZYZQc    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: My Personal Quest to De-Commercialize the Holidays http://bit.ly/7bIvTr    
    
    
    Winter has finally arrived in Michigan this weekend. Only 6 months to warm weather. Good god.    
    
    
    Worst franchise in all of sports: Detroit Lions    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of April 25, 2011. http://fb.me/TwRzX0zh    
    
    
    Straw poll. Do you want BP to start drilling in the Gulf again as they plan to? Put down a 'hell no' for me. Maybe... http://fb.me/PtvcDtjP    
    
    
    The Student Debt Cocktail: When Student Debt, Poor Credit, & Unemployment Wipe Out the Increased Earning Power of... http://fb.me/F74mmYXj    
    
    
    Wondering what I'll be re-gifting this year.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: The Story of Stuff & its Impact on your Personal Finances http://bit.ly/51uQH3    
    
    
    I review the NEW American Express Blue Cash Everyday Card. 3% cashback at supermarkets, and 2% at gas stations &... http://fb.me/Et1MDcC2    
    
    
    UPDATE: I just received word that the Chase British Airways Visa offer will end this Thursday, 5/5/11. It gave you... http://fb.me/Qm8ew3eV    
    
    
    I have three Ooma referral coupons for you to get $50 back on a new Ooma! http://fb.me/WVWA4lsy    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: I Have 3 Ooma Referral Coupon Codes http://bit.ly/4HG1Zt    
    
    
    New Ninja Warriors. Finally! 6 months wait is just too long.    
    
    
    About to do some mad research to completely rework my investment strategy - going all ETF.    
    
    
    Y'All Suckers Write Me Checks And Then They Bounce. So I Reach Into My Pocket For The Fresh Amount.    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of May 2, 2011. http://fb.me/Qk9RBXUw    
    
    
    Rat race making you tired? Me too. I look at why we do it and give 3 steps we need to take to pull away from it. http://fb.me/JwaEeAUZ    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Around the PF Blogosphere & Welcome GetRichSlowly and Mint.com Visitors http://bit.ly/6jmqQC    
    
    
    Wow. E-Trade just gave me a $60 'Don't let the door hit you on the way out' transfer fee. Apparently they don't care if you come back.    
    
    
    Can't wait to begin getting that sweet co. match on my 401k again. Been maxed out since August.    
    
    
    New frugal tip: Frugality Requires Budgeting: Free MicroFrugality Budgeting Spreadsheet http://bit.ly/5Ozmly    
    
    
    The price of silver dropped over 30% at one point last week. I discuss why this selloff presents some great... http://fb.me/uJKl5Rh1    
    
    
    Extreme couponing is now mainstream. But is it worth it? Share your take. http://fb.me/XOUzy7qE    
    
    
    Reel mower vs. gas powered? Here are five reasons to opt for the reel mower. http://fb.me/MSyHNu5H    
    
    
    Watching American Ninja Warrior. Go Levi!    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: The 3 Questions you MUST Ask Yourself Before Reading Another Personal Finance Post http://bit.ly/85yspq    
    
    
    Time to break out the nutmeg.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: The Average American's Holiday Spending will Drop. What About Yours? http://bit.ly/7VkXEy    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of May 9, 2011. http://fb.me/XL4zYBx4    
    
    
    Big game tonight - Spartans v. Texas in a possible final 4 matchup. Calling the final 4 right now: Texas, MSU, Kansas, Purdue    
    
    
    Holiday break begins. Over/under on boredom? It doesn't matter - still beats working.    
    
    
    Best holiday song... Torn between "So this is Christmas" (Lennon) and "Drummer Boy" (Crosby/Bowie).    
    
    
    @JeremyVoh Lucas pooped his pants. Too many turnovers.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: The 12 Best Songs About Money. EVER. http://bit.ly/8r4bbz    
    
    
    AT&T & Comcast bandwidth usage caps threaten the future of the internet. Why you should be concerned AND pissed! http://fb.me/XPvXdGw4    
    
    
    Should you invest in a Roth IRA or 401K? Here's my take on this very popular question. http://fb.me/ZZyO99Hc    
    
    
    How would you balance the U.S. budget deficit? http://fb.me/wbUiR7S0    
    
    
    I share 5 specific multiple income stream strategies shared by 20somethingfinance readers. It should get your... http://fb.me/11aOUiFqY    
    
    
    Monday.... back to w..... nah, got another week off. =)    
    
    
    I keep wondering when this market rebound is going to take pullback a bit.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: 2010 Financial Resolution Guide: 10 Choices - A La Carte Style http://bit.ly/4Zn3sM    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of May 16, 2011. http://fb.me/Y21tJ26k    
    
    
        
    
    
    I highlight all of the basics on the Roth 401K and compare it to the traditional 401K. http://fb.me/vI3aEhdM    
    
    
    New frugal tip: Dried Versus Canned Beans: One is 50 Percent Cheaper http://bit.ly/5Q2l67    
    
    
    A list of 7 things that will destroy a young professionals financial situation. http://fb.me/LTiV4Dbt    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Reader Question: Bank of America Closing my Account After I Opted out of a Rate Increase http://bit.ly/7Dbcsa    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: How to Waste Money in 9 Easy Steps http://bit.ly/7eu6Vi    
    
    
    A personal note to Comcast on why their customer service is so poor, featuring a chat transcript with one of their... http://fb.me/yIn6iSrs    
    
    
    New frugal tip: 10 Uses for Witch Hazel - A Frugal Necessity http://bit.ly/6Yk3oV    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of May 23, 2011. http://fb.me/xtsCccc3    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Finally! TransUnion Delivers on their Class Action Settlement Benefits http://bit.ly/5mmRA1    
    
    
    An excellent reminder of what Memorial Day is all about. http://fb.me/ulDM4REl    
    
    
    7 personal finance spring cleaning fixes! Start fixing your finances today with these tactics. http://fb.me/BZTCqWRK    
    
    
    Anyone ever hooked their dog up to a harness and had them pull your around in a sled?? Thinking it might work.    
    
    
    Traditional retirement is dead! Now what? This is a very important read for younger generations. http://fb.me/GmxRY40l    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: The Free Alternatives to Microsoft Office: Stop Wasting Money! http://bit.ly/4J0QNs    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Better at Finance Because of your Parents - Or In Spite of them? http://bit.ly/6x2R0D    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of May 30, 2011. http://fb.me/ML6M5yik    
    
    
    Great post on how to live for free, in London: http://www.guardian.co.uk/environment/2010/jan/02/katherine-hibbert-living-without-money    
    
    
    Scrapers are stealing my copyrighted work. I need all of my readers to help! http://fb.me/13FWN5Vlv    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Reader Question: I Cant Get Approved for a Credit Card! How do I Build Credit? http://bit.ly/4nTSMv    
    
    
    I devised a simple, but effective strategy to declutter and make money. http://fb.me/T9UTnScZ    
    
    
    Finally, a secured credit card that doesn't rip off its users. Check out the Applied Bank Secured Visa Gold. http://fb.me/ZcVfUsOY    
    
    
    Money means nothing when you are on your deathbed. A palliative nurse shares her wisdom. http://fb.me/TeFdHHSR    
    
    
        
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Deals, & Oddities – Week of 6-6-11 http://fb.me/AUGhQX0s    
    
    
    5 Craigslist tips from a power user that will help you sell anything super fast on Craigslist! http://fb.me/vvBwomAr    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Why Graduate Degrees Are a Rip Off: Crunching the Numbers http://bit.ly/7EjhOq    
    
    
    At what age do you expect to be able to partially and full retire? Reader poll. http://fb.me/ZuzwDTp0    
    
    
    A look at whether or not closing a savings or checking account can hurt your credit score. Do you know the answer? http://fb.me/yNLzXPBi    
    
    
    @georgiemiller5 Sorry, they just expired! I usually post them on the site when I get them (every 6 months or so).    
    
    
    @RebeccaCondon Thanks, Rebecca.    
    
    
    I could eat Mexican food every day of the week and be a very happy man.    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: 20SomethingFinance Now Offered Up on Kindle! http://bit.ly/7GQrg7    
    
    
    Finance highlights of the week: Vancouver riots edition http://fb.me/LUVkNggn    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: EyeBuyDirect.com Buy One Get One EyeGlasses Sale Ends at Midnight http://bit.ly/8Xm8GU    
    
    
    Chase Freedom bumps its new account bonus to $200. You may be able to get a bump if you signed up for previous... http://fb.me/P6OBBSBz    
    
    
    Anyone watch the The Killing finale? On one hand I thought it was incredible. On the other... just tell us who did it!!!    
    
    
    @srapacon I'm going to have to start charging you guys ;-)  Let me know what you're thinking.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Here are 5 employers that offering health insurance & other great benefits to PART-TIMERS! http://fb.me/IlEmr1fW    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Haiti Donations Tax Deductible for 2009 or 2010 http://bit.ly/d58SvD    
    
    
    http://20somethingfinance.com/pay-off-student-loan-debt-or-save-for-retirement/    
    
    
    Should you pay off your students loans or save for retirement? Help a reader and share your take. http://fb.me/XaemhoTR    
    
    
    I hope Madonna is getting royalty kickbacks for "Born this Way". Express Yourself? Not fooling me, Gaga.    
    
    
    Money highlights of the week: student finances edition. http://fb.me/Vr3Q3n2Q    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Avoid Putting your Bridesmaid & Groomsmen in Debt http://bit.ly/dAA9DN    
    
    
    http://20somethingfinance.com/how-to-save-money-fast/ http://fb.me/AXb7T1Tt    
    
    
    Maybe we should start re-thinking our addiction to AC? I look at the costs of a fan vs. an AC unit. http://fb.me/VpMYfMn0    
    
    
    Highlights, Favorites, Oddities, and Deals of the Week of Thanksgiving. http://fb.me/FSiK1dbq    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: My 5 Favorite NON-Personal Finance Blogs http://bit.ly/9uGHk8    
    
    
    What makes your top 10 list of things money CAN buy? http://fb.me/PMkUmWrB    
    
    
    @impulsesave Everyone's list is a bit different, indeed!    
    
    
    @YPMoney thanks, man!    
    
    
    Money Highlights of the week: Damn it's Hot! Edition http://fb.me/OD2vC2om    
    
    
    It's Independence Day, and 20somethingfinance has an appropriate new slogan I think you will enjoy! http://fb.me/xrN9F2KT    
    
    
    @OrnellaGrosz I swear that was not planned out ahead of time (until this morning, then it made a lot of sense)    
    
    
    Is it wrong to hope someone's hair catches on fire while playing with fireworks (without suffering burns, of course).    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post: Gender & Personal Finance: Do Men Still Dominate Personal Finance in the Home? http://bit.ly/9ri8A1    
    
    
    This weeks highlights cover the gamut of 'freedom' topics and asks readers whether we should cut or tax our way to... http://fb.me/B6Q5PXUR    
    
    
    Putting off the taxes.    
    
    
    What is net worth? I discuss what it is, how to calculate it, and why it's an over-rated metric that is a bit... http://fb.me/15pMSDMdN    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Never Hire a Contractor without Following These 5 Steps First http://bit.ly/cMQmCV    
    
    
    Chinese Ghost Towns? Get Ready to Feel Good About Being American Again http://fb.me/VQ1JfYkv    
    
    
    The site should be up and running functionally again now. Was having some theme problems with comments. If it's... http://fb.me/1aHvbFRDl    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: The First Steps to Stop Dreaming & Start Retiring - NOW! http://bit.ly/94jXYI    
    
    
    Just learned what a 'Burpee' is - and now I'm tired. Clean thoughts, folks.    
    
    
    Andy Schleck as a decoy! Brilliant.    
    
    
    As a lover of infographics, visual.ly is pretty damn cool. http://fb.me/KpVWpfm9    
    
    
    Corporate profits for Q3 were at an ALL-TIME high. Yet unemployment is still at 9%. What does this mean for our... http://fb.me/MFNAqzLh    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Perkstreet Financial Review: A Free Debit Card with Rewards http://bit.ly/aiqtO8    
    
    
    I dissect the Netflix price increase. Perhaps it's time to cancel? http://fb.me/14395EsZD    
    
    
    An exhaustive list of electric & hybrid tax credits by state. http://fb.me/SCU90a0f    
    
    
    This Tour de France is pretty fun to watch. Voeckler has guts.    
    
    
    @leahgfulford I guess it's always good to put the bad guys in comparative perspective. =)    
    
    
    There are 2 paths to financial independence. Which will you take? http://fb.me/DWWMitTb    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: Getting Paid to Do What you Love: A Close Look at Marketable Hobbies http://bit.ly/co7us3    
    
    
    Want to give curling a try.    
    
    
    Vote for my 'Checklist' post to win in a personal finance March Madness battle: http://bit.ly/cBQKF3    
    
    
    I give 5 reasons to ride a bike to work based on personal experience. http://fb.me/15bKsb4tN    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: What you Need to Know About the Credit Card Act http://20somethingfinance.com/credit-card-ac/    
    
    
    New rules dictate that you will now get a free credit score if you are denied credit or given less than the best... http://fb.me/19XrdbpeL    
    
    
    The internet sales tax debate rages on. I look at both sides of the argument. Where do you stand? http://fb.me/14JXrwFBp    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: 55 Marketable Hobbies that you Love & Can Get Paid For http://bit.ly/aYHanR    
    
    
    I just did Warrior Dash. Here's what I learned about myself and others. http://fb.me/12FGqim0P    
    
    
    TradeKing, an online broker, is offering up it's biggest new account promotion yet - $100 - through the end of... http://fb.me/w9d3zOIA    
    
    
    Virgin Mobile raised their unlimited plan by 40%. Not a good day for cheap data plan seekers. http://fb.me/ApL8Ccg3    
    
    
    I've had a few questions on the TradeKing promotion highlighted the other day. Note that this does not include... http://fb.me/NGmJHQOq    
    
    
    New 20somethingfinance post:: How to Avoid Getting Burned by the Magazine Industry http://bit.ly/9v7BmR    
    
    
        
    
    
    Netflix launches streaming-only option. Are you switching plans? http://fb.me/NvmvFFQU    
    
    
    