@RakkAttackk Be happy that they aren't working you from day 1!    
    
    
    @katiedel LOL, cool, I'm looking forward to it working.    
    
    
    @drewwilson @gmph @dialoggs is that all? =)  looking forward to it!    
    
    
    @tchaten Well you are seeing ramifications now. If I tell you I am gonna sock u in the face last week, it hurts a lot more when I do it 2day    
    
    
    @atjamie @erikamkay but how did that person send you a text with a dead phone? I am calling iPhone with either mac or iPad iMessage. No?    
    
    
    @juviwhale ANOTHER BARAKA! Oh no!!!!    
    
    
    @BrianNorgard you are not alone my friend.  Check it out: http://www.insidemobileapps.com/2012/05/31/how-to-double-user-retention-with-push-notifications-urban-airship-shares-best-practices/ …    
    
    
    @atjamie lol. It's not that bad is it???    
    
    
    @bryanmwolfe easiest money of your life    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ FINALLY! I was shocked by your previous decision. Welcome back!    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @andynico_  lol. Yes you will be welcomed to the club too!    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk NOOOOO!  Are you kidding me. Freaking Tamme    
    
    
    @BrentDirks WOW. That is crazy!    
    
    
    @reneritchie Can you preorder for a different carrier and port your number without ever walking into a store and getting new iPhone shipped    
    
    
    @asronline @atjamie @christyxcore COOL! Now you can airplay movies on TV, make awesome keynotes for class, & run it for next 10 yrs! Oh wait    
    
    
    @julipuli @atjamie and the new iPhone is getting even bigger.  Apple is not doing your pockets any favors ;)    
    
    
    @BrianNorgard latest rumors are pre-orders start Friday morning.    
    
    
    is panorama only available on iPhone 5 and the new iPod touch?  If it works on iPod Touch's A5 chip, why won't it run on 4s?    
    
    
    Confirmed: iPhone 4S WILL feature panorama mode, but not iPhone 4    
    
    
    If I am switching from AT&T to Verizon and want to port my number do I preorder from Apple or Verizon?    
    
    
    @reneritchie I read your posts about it (marketing, mass appeal, yada, yada, yada)…but I am still shocked!    
    
    
    @reneritchie Give me iPhone 6, iPhone LTE, anything…but not the iPhone 5!!! ;)    
    
    
    Why can't I put in my phone number for Messages on mac like I can on my iPad.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps I read your post about switching…but what about porting 2 number's onto 1 verizon share everything plan. Need to use VZN site?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Does this worry you: http://www.theverge.com/2012/9/13/3328492/iphone-5-simultaneous-voice-data-verizon-sprint …    
    
    
    @atjamie check email    
    
    
    @llofte I finally found one reason the move to Verizon is not perfect: http://www.theverge.com/2012/9/13/3328492/iphone-5-simultaneous-voice-data-verizon-sprint …    
    
    
    @llofte ah, i see you guys already discussed this. Alright I'll see you on the verizon side =)    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Ah…I thought I was gonna see a great Jeff response and then see a troll go nuts.  RESPOND!!! It's fun..for us at least =)    
    
    
    @christyxcore LOL. Sounds expensive.    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Thanks for the reply. I am bringing my wife with me, and I want to join my family on a share everything plan. How should I do it    
    
    
    @vzwsupport also was sad to learn no talk & text for iPhone 5 on LTE. Any chance this will be changed or permanent hardware issue    
    
    
    @christyxcore That's why I hate kickstarter.  I love the ideas, but products never ship on time and for iPhone always too late    
    
    
    @reneritchie umm nice picture on iPhone 5 preorder forum post…can I come to your next slumber party. LOL    
    
    
    Riddle me this Batman: On Verizon, if I am on a phone call (voice) then hit FaceTime (data) does that work? Or do I have to hang up?    
    
    
    @christyxcore Did tests. We discovered if you initiate it,  it's seamless, but it hangs up on other person and calls them back as FaceTime    
    
    
    @christyxcore I tested it with Dom. He had Verizon. It still works okay. It's better on AT&T but this is fine.    
    
    
    @reneritchie @drbarnard @att @verizon @llofte it's got me thinking twice. But I am ready to "rule the air"    
    
    
    @christyxcore umm maybe, @robinrhys would know better than me. We'll check tomorrow    
    
    
    @atjamie Y U NO AIM?  If you're up I am gonna make you work!    
    
    
    @atjamie where are the excitement posts! apple store down, att has countdown taking over site, verizon is ready to rock…lets get excited!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ CALL.IN.SICK    
    
    
    @AppAdvice duh. We are waiting to order new lightning connectors!    
    
    
    @christyxcore get me some too!!!!    
    
    
    @robinrhys att?    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Very happy! I ported 2 number.Only issue was it asked me for my account info from att, but didn't ask on 2nd line for wife.    
    
    
    @vzwsupport is that going to be an issue? we have diff account numbers. Confirm #: 9210925800132005    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @christyxcore LOL, i said respectfully!  I bought the 4s off contract so I could jump ship for iPhone 5 =) Nice job C!    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Oh really?  I was able to put in her number? Can we fix it now, or do I have to wait tip I get it?  I am happy to be here!    
    
    
    @atjamie we have never been affected this long.  I am really worried.  Do what you can!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ view on computer…they look awesome    
    
    
    @VZWSupport I know the no simult. voice/data is b/c of how apple built phone,but it's really a huge issue w/ imessage & navi any fix?LTEvoip    
    
    
    @llofte how did they tell you? they called you?    
    
    
    @llofte why would they move his and not yours? And how did you get that date? No more Verizon?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps yes sir!  We are now part of  @vzwsupport Though I did I lot of tests and iMessages not being delivered during call is BIG neg.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps first @llofte now you!  You guys are all leaving me to go to Verizon by myself =(    
    
    
    @atjamie DAWSON'S CREEK is my favorite show of all time. No joke. And I am in love with Joey Potter.    
    
    
    @erondu happy birthday buddy!    
    
    
    @gruber It was very easy to do using verizon's site.  I was skeptical, but it was a pleasant experience. Also ported from AT&T    
    
    
    @llofte call back. Be angry. Ask for manager.    
    
    
    @llofte My experience is reps in store will just call customer support anyway. I would keep trying.  This is ridiculous!    
    
    
    @drbarnard It's even worse.  Even if the results were right and there were no bugs, that is an awful interface to try to find anything    
    
    
    @erondu on what?    
    
    
    @erondu oh LOL, I got married 4 yrs ago…but somehow I lost the connection on FB so I reeded it today.    
    
    
    @atjamie Okay, I just checked what I can afford for you from there.  I'll get the "free ground shipping" please mark it off the registry    
    
    
    @Book_Dork @atjamie lol    
    
    
    .@mittromney I've unsubscribed from your mailing list 3x & I still get emails. WTF, man? cc @FECupdates http://cl.ly/image/260r3J3W0Q2i …    
    
    
    Everyone please try the new appbump feature in AppsGoneFree 2.0. Huge update http://getapp.cc/app/470693788     
    
    
    Wow, AppsGoneFree is ranked #19 in the entire iPad App Store. Thanks for everyone who is supporting AppBump! http://getapp.cc/app/470693788     
    
    
    @reneritchie What about the HTML 5 App Store update?  I am pretty worried about it. you okay with it?    
    
    
    Finally! Your phone # receives iMessages on your phone, iPad, & Mac. Unless you are on Verizon and on a phone call. Then iPad & Mac only    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Yeah when you hang up, they come in.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps If it was already received on iPad or mac (and read), because the message window was open, it won't come in new, just slide in    
    
    
    @jeff148apps I picked Verizon, but I am really worried about it!    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Jeff, if you know anyone to share with Verizon can be pretty cheap. I am sharing with 3 other low data users, should save $$    
    
    
    @Mark_T_Willard ask Michael what about the "Jordan Rules" his era. He says it didn't happen.    
    
    
    @macmixing CULT OF MAC? where we at    
    
    
    Remember when we used to text in tweets and @ replies? Me neither, I started Twitter with Twitterific    
    
    
    @atjamie You know how much I hate that stupid iPhone 5 name.  #callitiPhone6    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie NO NO NO!  3G makes sense. 1st phone with 3G support! You can call this iPhone LTE, just not 5!    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie iPhone(1st one), iPhone 3G (first w/ 3g), 3gs (like 3g but fast, 4 (4th one), 4s (like 4 but better), 5 (explanation?)    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie iPhone high-five!!! I like it! Let's call it that =)    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie wow Bad reason! I'll drop it now.But you never answered about App Store app.Everyone talking maps, App Store is issue!    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie oh just your experience.You think it's an issue, or you think I'll get used to it. Feels like so many steps back.    
    
    
    @atjamie @reneritchie Jamie, that's where you go everyday from 8-3 right?    
    
    
    @christyxcore @reneritchie @atjamie haha, I like that    
    
    
    @reneritchie Very true, I don't know why they did those cards in search. But whole thing is slow and buggy    
    
    
    @atjamie @reneritchie LOL, nicely played.  Okay too much tweeting…back to work!    
    
    
    Siri doesn't like apps, that start with "app." So if you want Siri to launch AppAdvice you have to say "launch app appadvice" #protip    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon It's true! Your app works because it starts with apps,not app.Our AppsGoneFree app works fine, it's just the singular word app    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon  Siri uses natural language. So appadvice becomes app advice. "App" throws Siri off. AppsFire becomes apps fire. "Apps" is ok    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon LOL. I think that would just confuse Siri. #notworthit    
    
    
    @RippsUp i can't get that to work. It's really working? It says "open appadvice" in text but response is "cannot find an app named advice"    
    
    
    @lsliang2001 What's bothering you?    
    
    
    @lsliang2001 iOS 6    
    
    
    @lsliang2001 I hate the new app store, aside from all the bugs, the search is killing me larry!    
    
    
    @lsliang2001 you getting iPhone 5?    
    
    
    @KanePoehlman What do you mean?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps yay! I have a verizon friend…@llofte ditched us ;)    
    
    
    @KanePoehlman I sent you the code via DM    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @christyxcore In the US we can leave a note and have it dropped off, not over there?    
    
    
    @christyxcore SHHH, don't give away our secrets ;)    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ angel? halo over head?    
    
    
    @christyxcore midnight? It's 1AM!!!! Midnight was so an hour ago    
    
    
    @reneritchie you're crazy! I can't believe you were up for your slumber party last week and didn't preorder!    
    
    
    @reneritchie Hanging with apple folk is cool but up all night in the freezing cold waiting in a line?!    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett @christyxcore GOOD LUCK!!! Let us know how it goes. You going black or white?    
    
    
    Sorry to everyone I direct message'd nonsense too. Does these people really have nothing better to do. Anyway, sorry!    
    
    
    @jeff148apps NOOO!!! What changed your mind?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps LOL, by unknown you mean fear of no data while on phone calls, I have fear of "unknown" too    
    
    
    I was so sure the black iPhone 5 was the way to go... I was wrong!    
    
    
    @christyxcore for what? you can't change color with applecare can you?    
    
    
    @chasesclouds Nothing wrong with black, white is just so HOT!!!    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie LOL, well I couldn't be part of an Apple site without complaining about meaningless Apple stuff right?    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman I love it, but in photos the black looked so much better (i thought) but in real life I love white    
    
    
    @chasesclouds I too had the white 4S.  I never use it case. Iove the beauty of the device…but we'll see how scratches go.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps is that really doable. With upgrade eligibility and such?    
    
    
    @chasesclouds How.wouldn't it be a return rebuy…and if so how fast does my eligibility come back?    
    
    
    Does anyone want to trade a new Verizon iPad for an AT&T iPad one? 32GB model. My AT&T new iPad is literally mint condition.    
    
    
    Thanks for everyone who helped. White iPhone 5 obtained. pic.twitter.com/TML899ws    
    
    
    @christyxcore lol. Sorry, still in the iPhone 5 fam with you! Non iPhone 5 optimized apps look a lot better on black though.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps It would have been super easy to swap if bought it from apple.But since I didn't I had to go to Vzn. Return then buy at apple    
    
    
    @tchaten I thought so too. But in person I loved the white.    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk make sure you change your password. They have there password.    
    
    
    @tchaten how far along are you. Any scheduled release? preview teaser?    
    
    
    @atjamie eh, I don't think passbook warrants it…At least not now. But isn't the idea it pops up for you? No need to launch?    
    
    
    @tchaten cool good luck! you publishing in iBookstore?    
    
    
    @tchaten cool, good luck. We'll check it out at macworld!    
    
    
    @atjamie At least you have @AppAdvice app on your homescreen, unlike someone else I know…named @christyxcore and yes iPhone 5 support coming    
    
    
    @christyxcore LOL..okay okay…just busting your chops.    
    
    
    @llofte There's an app for that: http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/grubhub-food-delivery-takeout/id302920553?mt=8 …    
    
    
    @christyxcore I miss myspace. I don't care how much people make fun of the awful page designs. Cool you got your "space" to personalize.    
    
    
    @christyxcore and no "news feed" meant endless navigation to all your friend's pages to see what was new. Less efficient, more fun.    
    
    
    @christyxcore Not to sound like a creeper, but it was more acceptable to hit up friends of friends…okay now i sound like a creeper #stopping    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Oh yeah, well I am playing with something cool too, but I'm not telling either. J/k it's an iPhone 5 =)    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Has Verizon released a statement on their plans & estimate timelines for VoLTE? Bringing simultaneous voice/date & hd calls    
    
    
    @tchaten any idea how much data you used? I know you are unlimited, but that would be great to know    
    
    
    @tchaten I remember video, forgot findings…do you remember old findings?    
    
    
    @christyxcore link    
    
    
    "Some part of me wishes I had gotten white instead" - @christyxcore discussing her choice oh iPhone color.    
    
    
    @christyxcore lol. I know. Busting your chops for the 2nd time today!    
    
    
    Email I got Apple is giving me an iPad 3. 1 problem…there is no such thing as an iPad 3 & I think Apple knows that http://cl.ly/image/1J0x0t312p1h …    
    
    
    @erondu those appetizers look pretty bomb though    
    
    
    @asronline you can get a ton of free space pretty easy… i have 24GB…hit me up if you want tips    
    
    
    @christyxcore lol…at least he's realistic..wait he said they'd beat out windows 8, nevermind    
    
    
    @christyxcore maybe it's stuck in apple approval process like AppsGoneFree... Oh wait, just kidding.    
    
    
    @christyxcore I know! Thus the "just kidding." I guess I shouldn't quit my day job. LOL.    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk lets make a trade happen for your sorry RBs..    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk how about sjack, c. johnson and nelson…for fitz, witten, and moreno? You aint playing sjack or CJ anyway?    
    
    
    @rakkattackk I am just scared sjack will get hurt…and ur loaded with RBs    
    
    
    @rakkattackk witten is big upgrade at TE too…had an awful game last week but lots of targets and he is healthy now    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk Sent a trade, added heath miller. Let me know what you think. If you don't like why not    
    
    
    @christyxcore standby eh?    
    
    
    @christyxcore seriously. Bring me something cool on Friday!    
    
    
    @christyxcore oh booo! I thought it was for the 5    
    
    
    @christyxcore I was talking about the box that showed up today. I didn't see the bags    
    
    
    @bryanmwolfe AppsGoneFree has been sitting there a week already =(    
    
    
    @christyxcore I do love my phone with no case. My dream is to find a nice case one day but I have never seen one that convinced me to use    
    
    
    @christyxcore you're right.My iPhone 5 is lasting forever with 1%.But that's not good that it is not calculating the percentages correctly.    
    
    
    @chpwn Siri repeats the last thing she said to you when you say "what" ... So you must have asked to send a tweet previously.    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett @kimkimcachoo @bryanmwolfe all i am saying is despite how fast it seems, these devs probably all submitted over a week ago    
    
    
    @JulieVaughn @cluckstv @viddy @sol @aolmobile Nice, I will have the @AppAdvice team cover this for you!    
    
    
    @julievaughn @cluckstv @viddy @sol @aolmobile Ah, not out yet! I will cover it once it goes live. Keep us posted =)    
    
    
    @Book_Dork Send us a link!  I wanna see    
    
    
    @reneritchie  InstaPockaBility’d nice!    
    
    
    @Book_Dork nice!!! Congrats.    
    
    
    @bryanmwolfe you still posting your thoughts on it today?    
    
    
    @JulieVaughn @cluckstv @viddy @sol @aolmobile Here's the writeup we did: http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/09/aol-releases-clucks-a-cross-between-viddy-and-draw-something … Good luck!    
    
    
    AppsGoneFree featured on ABC San Diego local news http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pe6bUjecAzU …    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Thanks…We are not from San Diego & They got appbump wrong, but it's still cool. LOL    
    
    
    @christyxcore no one does buy full price and extend your contract. Do they? Hello iPhone 6    
    
    
    Nice placement advertising by Apple “@pdparticle: Samsung wants you to purchase an iPhone 5 too. http://i.imgur.com/vLlrC.jpg ”    
    
    
    @alyssabernal you're on!  Going now    
    
    
    @alyssabernal Small 11" macbook air, but you can see it here: http://cl.ly/image/0P1G1c2t1W0W …    
    
    
    @drewwilson @screenyapp  Check it out:  http://reviewtimes.shinydevelopment.com     
    
    
    @alyssabernal Thanks! Good luck, I will keep voting =)    
    
    
    Non-apple tweet for my girl @jenienb    
    
    
    @JailbreakCon wrote an article @AppAdvice http://apadv.co/QmYYai     
    
    
    @chasesclouds when it comes to tea, I always vote Pepsi    
    
    
    @chasesclouds @heatherblansett Hmm tough call, both are great. Coke did have MJ (http://youtu.be/UfwzizFhUIU ) but Pepsi had http://youtu.be/aYywiQ3-6To     
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @heatherblansett @chasesclouds an epic battle that is guaranteed to end in thirst quenching pic.twitter.com/ripiJ9Wr    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @heatherblansett @chasesclouds The whole "next generation" campaign was brilliant and gave coke a run for their money in 80s    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @heatherblansett @chasesclouds I love the current Pepsi font. And last Xmas coke did white cans? Ruining their iconic branding    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @heatherblansett @chasesclouds yeah as far as marketing - Pepsi wins.Coke won in mass distribution, especially internationally    
    
    
    I love "carmageddon" it's the only time I ever get to average more than 80mph for an entire hour long drive    
    
    
    I hate college football. So many huge plays. You are never safe    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo they closed a freeway for the weekend and everyone is freaking out. We drive a lot in LA http://m.travelerstoday.com/articles/3208/20120929/carmageddon-2012-busy-los-angeles-freeway-closed-drivers-warned-to-stay-off-roads-carmageddon-ii-2-california-traffic-interstate-405-sepulveda-pass.htm …    
    
    
    All the AppAdvice apps, including the retired ones.  http://instagr.am/p/QLtKOnMUFh/     
    
    
    @RakkAttackk what's up with tech?    
    
    
    @tchaten http://mobile.theverge.com/2012/9/27/3417870/apple-ipod-click-wheel-games-history …    
    
    
    @jeff148apps It's Monday!!! Waiting on the exciting news you teased last week    
    
    
    @jeff148apps You mean like what 4KB is today?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps LOL. In that case congrats on composing a tweet at all!    
    
    
    @chasesclouds LOl, not til lunch!    
    
    
    I figured it out. The black iPhone 5 always looks like it's in a case due to the smoked out side covering. I've always loved iPhones naked.    
    
    
    @christyxcore it does. Put it on the table so the screen is facing up. Look at it. See the black casing around the side.    
    
    
    @christyxcore lol where is @Noobocity for the "no dude" love    
    
    
    @christyxcore @kimkimcachoo http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FVIOBtGVbvs …    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett @juviwhale congrats!! We are lucky to have you =)    
    
    
    @jeff148apps WOW. Huge news.  Congrats. I hope you're still going to be a big part of the team over there!    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Nice! I am excited then.  Our bets were a new app, or maybe an exclusive about what you erased under NDA a couple weeks ago    
    
    
    @LifeInTents Yeah but the problem on iOS is you don't notice any practical difference. Test att "4g" vs let in real life setting. no diff.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps No dodgers, no angles? Come on…Next year is the year of Los Angeles Baseball =)    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Everyone here is crazy and they wanna give the AL MVP to  Trout over Cabrera…is this a national thing or just crazy LA?    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett you reminded me! I need I cancel my gym subscription.    
    
    
    @christyxcore wow..I just looked, didn't realize how far it dropped… ranks: 213 paid iPhone 170 free iPhone, 235 paid iPad,198 free iPad    
    
    
    .@christyxcore But then again, Draw Something is still making more than 1/2 a million every month by my estimates    
    
    
    Rachel gives one of the most moving love speeches of all time, then says she's done? Doesn't make sense. And yes that was a #glee tweet!    
    
    
    @msleamichele that was actually pretty amazing performance. I didn't know you had it in you. Not just for #glee that was all-time level.    
    
    
    anyone?  Trade a Verizon LTE iPad for an AT&T one?  These share everything plans messed everything up...    
    
    
    @jenienb @buzzfeed lol. That is crazy. He must have been pretty pissed that Joey chose Pacey and he wants everyone to forget about it    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo try clicking on any file and pushing space bar. It's the best    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo get an Apple TV too. So you can AirPlay stuff to your TV!    
    
    
    @christyxcore @kimkimcachoo it's not out yet right? Only alpha stuff and they submitted yesterday right? So like 2 more weeks to wait    
    
    
    @mnengle "that is dress is becoming on you...but then again if I was on you..."(rest is NSFW!)    
    
    
    The things I miss about jailbreak is becoming less & less, but not being able to forward voicemail is a big thing I really miss. #additapple    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis LOL, yes you are!    
    
    
    @superpixels that is not native in iOS. Only thing I can think of is someone using the new iOS 6 framework in their app on a ss within app    
    
    
    @jenienb better than being at work!    
    
    
    @superpixels looks like an iPhone app in landscape, so can't be App Store, can you ask what app that's in?    
    
    
    @superpixels Pretty cool. I wonder if they hard coded it or used the new framework. I have not seen that in action yet. I'll check    
    
    
    @148Apps to answer that, we need to define the need for http://app.net  in the first place. As for Tapbots they made a lot of money!    
    
    
    @jenienb r u going to xx concert in 2 weeks?    
    
    
    @jenienb LOL, yeah i am still kinda young. I need 2 tickets. any extras?    
    
    
    OMG! My cracked iPhone 5 screen was actually covered under warranty.It's called single hairline crack and is covered.no tricks or apple care    
    
    
    this now means I have had 3 iPhone 5's in under 3 weeks. Black exchanged for white, then cracked screen replaced…some can't even get 1?    
    
    
    @rsmoz I dropped it from about 1 foot off the ground and a small crack appeared. looked like under glass: http://forums.macrumors.com/showthread.php?t=1060998 …    
    
    
    @rsmoz from black to white? Within 30 days from apple not hard at all. Just bring it in and they swap it. Assuming they have stock.    
    
    
    @rsmoz for crack screen, genius bar appt    
    
    
    @jeff148apps LOL…of course I am, I'm a friend of Jeff Scott's! That's all I tell them every time    
    
    
    @jenienb LOL…I thought your mom said you could jack the upgrade.    
    
    
    @jenienb I still can't believe you don't Glee….you should catch up and watch...    
    
    
    So it is confirmed by me. All 3 iPhone 5's I had all came with a crazy robotic Siri voice. After restore she sounded like herself.    
    
    
    @atjamie Wasn't it jay betting money it wasn't happening. LOL    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo Nice.  Yeah none in Los Angeles. Even Sprint is sold out ;)    
    
    
    @christyxcore At least you have wifi at home, LOL.  If you can only pick LTE while out or at hime, while out is better    
    
    
    @atjamie @macmixing LOL…Dam if it's your life we're talking about, I would at least get Apple Care PLUS!    
    
    
    @atjamie can u find me asap please    
    
    
    “@Behance: All QR codes look alike…until now. ILLUSTRATED QR CODES: http://on.be.net/QTlgRr ” yup that's me retweeting a prompted tweet    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ wow. Really coming all the way back to iOS huh? Welcome back!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ can you send me your wallpaper. I like it.    
    
    
    @tchaten don't forget: http://youtu.be/p6FKKpMH5eA     
    
    
    Epic Hearts, the new FREE fantasy RPG for iOS, is partnering with us to give away an iPod Touch to our loyal readers! http://splur.gy/OFGp4C     
    
    
    Can I win an iPod touch in my own event LOL http://splur.gy/OFGp4C     
    
    
    @w1kedZ LOL, I won't tell if you won't    
    
    
    @w1kedZ alright. Driving to lunch now. I will after    
    
    
    The best part of the presidential debates is watching the candidates fight the mediators.    
    
    
    @superpixels Hey you're in our neck of the woods!  If you wanna grab a drink or some lunch with some dudes from @AppAdvice let me know!    
    
    
    @tchaten you are finally believing in the product that I heard was "fake fake fakety fake" lol /@ndyfaust    
    
    
    @superpixels too bad! We're going to hold you to it next time.    
    
    
    @robinrhys lol! Boredom! Come work. We have appisodes to do woman! Until then, say hi to Joey for me. I miss her    
    
    
    @llofte my cousin is having issues. Need any info? I can ask him    
    
    
    @llofte ah nice! I should have checked the link!    
    
    
    Anyone going to be in San Jose for apple event on Tuesday and want to meet up?    
    
    
    @w1kedZ looks sweet!!! Congrats. Awesome turn of events.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @heatherblansett @christyxcore hey Andy. I live in CA and love Vegas. Feel free to email me    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @heatherblansett @christyxcore oh and congrats!    
    
    
    Doesn't feel very apple, but we're here! pic.twitter.com/gvnsVhYK    
    
    
    #GoDodgers    
    
    
    @jeff148apps congrats on the win. You coming to the show tomorrow?    
    
    
    @jenienb go #HEAT    
    
    
    @jeff148apps yes!!! @juviwhale @dubbalubagis and in are in San Jose. Tyler will be live blogging. We'll look for you.    
    
    
    I think Apple just killed the iPad. I don't see the the value proposition of the 4th gen iPad mini, I know @reneritchie will disagree    
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagr.am/p/RIsIEosUF6/     
    
    
    @jeff148apps @juviwhale @dubbalubagis lunch?    
    
    
    @reneritchie have you heard any more info on how much apple will charge to replace broken iPhone 5 screen?Saw your post last month.Any info?    
    
    
    @reneritchie yes. No apple care+    
    
    
    @chasesclouds my phone is okay. I didn't crack it. Just trying to get info so I can give people buying advice on apple care    
    
    
    @macmixing I been working on mine all day: pic.twitter.com/2ltIvERL    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Sadly I think it's more of a bad supply issue than a cagy demand issue    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @jeff148apps naw it was nov. 2nd here    
    
    
    @christyxcore still time for black on first day…i ordered let so i gotta wait =(    
    
    
    It's a tweet costume!!! pic.twitter.com/C05liFjY    
    
    
    @jenienb did you do it?!!!    
    
    
    @jenienb do you use Rdio?  Spotify?    
    
    
    @jenienb rdio has a much nicer UI. I like it more. Get on it!    
    
    
    @w1kedZ @atjamie I don’t wanna lose my text messages though, so i always restore from backup    
    
    
    @reneritchie But boy is it a brutal attack in the US.  To the layman it’s a very compelling argument    
    
    
    @jenienb is it good music?    
    
    
    @christyxcore ohh a negative tweetbot tweet from Christine, I didn’t think I’d see the day.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ power for the future’s sake!  If you have more powerful hardware developers will push those limits. They are aware of constraint    
    
    
    @jenienb fail to see how that's a bad thing? Would you really prefer the weather in NY right now.    
    
    
    @jenienb I missed it. What he say    
    
    
    @jenienb a better tweet?    
    
    
    LAKERS!!!!    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett you will surely be able to. It is just an iPad 2 with diff form    
    
    
    😄😄8⃣    
    
    
    @WCHamilton lol! My first ever pocket tweet!    
    
    
    @macmixing WOW!  You take a picture of the iOS family and don’t include the grand daddy of it all, the iPHONE!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    @jenienb says my tweets are too boring. So here is something really interesting. It actually is the best thing you will see twitter ever.    
    
    
    @jenienb damn I ran outta characters. Oh well.    
    
    
    @jenienb sure I will if u really make it!!! Don't be jealous of @robinrhys    
    
    
    @drewwilson lol to you just seeing this now! Weird they decided to change that single screen right? No functional change, weird design redo    
    
    
    @susbelief I didn't know you were on Twitter!  That's so cool. I look forward to tweeting with you =)    
    
    
    @susbelief BTW, everyone likes the Tweetbot app for their iPhone.  I still prefer the official twitter app. But Tweetbot is nice on the mac    
    
    
    Long election line and the janitor who is supposed to unlock this place isn't here yet. #whencanwevoteonline    
    
    
    @llofte you sure are tweeting a lot about the elections for someone who promise no election tweets ;)    
    
    
    @atjamie because….YOLO!    
    
    
    @erondu 4S users will work just fine too ;)    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ how much did you get for it. I’d love to move my 32GB LTE (AT&T) model    
    
    
    @jenienb it's raining in LA. You happy now? I hate it    
    
    
    Just saw someone get pulled over on the 10 for being in new "fastrrack" lane #lahotlane    
    
    
    It's so ridiculous how much more I love the iPad mini than the full size retina display iPad.    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Star Scales Pro For Guitar http://appsgonefree.getapp.cc/app/US/303486854 …    
    
    
    @macmixing DO IT!!!    
    
    
    @juviwhale and loved it!    
    
    
    @juviwhale The way you were looking at that waitress I think you need a COLD shower 😮    
    
    
    @juviwhale @wchamilton Don't worry, we'll be going again soon!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Just saw this, sorry for not replying.  I don't know any in that area, I would just check hotwire. #nohelp    
    
    
    @jenienb cuz you are!    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Commando Jack is free http://appsgonefree.getapp.cc/app/US/506645742 …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: FreeSkate Xtreme testing app http://appsgonefree.getapp.cc/app/US/536482799 …    
    
    
    Wow. All of a sudden the Gmail app fr iOS is really good.    
    
    
    From @appadvice: iOver Golf - The First Step to a Great Putt http://appsgonefree.getapp.cc/app/US/555076579 …    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk shit goes in the toilet....not the trash can.    
    
    
    @reneritchie apple fanboy syndrome LOL!    
    
    
    @superpixels why'd you ditch the DVR    
    
    
    My boys knew it was the Fantasy Football finals and they didn't disappoint! #200Points pic.twitter.com/MKnqztw1    
    
    
    “@julipuli: Christmas sandman http://instagr.am/p/Tq0feglTDz/ ” only in California.    
    
    
    @chasesclouds @atjamie @karensfreeman @juviwhale @appadvice thanks Jen. Merry Xmas guys    
    
    
    @robinrhys @chasesclouds @atjamie @karensfreeman @juviwhale @appadvice lol! Merry Xmas ms. Rhys    
    
    
    @christyxcore @robinrhys @chasesclouds @atjamie @karensfreeman @juviwhale @appadvice I didn't start the thread. Just replied!  Merry Xmas!    
    
    
    @atjamie ohhh I want to see. (My money is on google maps)    
    
    
    @ReggieMillerTNT I'll send you a Buffalo Braves jersey if you follow me on Twitter!    
    
    
    @llofte are you able to get the alerts to pop up on HIS phone at a certain time? The notifications only pop up on the device that created    
    
    
    @llofte it is sooo annoying. would be a killer feature if it worked. Weird thing is it show the due date on other phone. Just no alerts    
    
    
    @JonesOnTheNBA Fantasy Basketball (daily changes): do I pick up granger, rose, or Bynum yet? These guys worth the wasted games this early?    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ you have the coolest wallpapers. Can you send me this one!    
    
    
    @macmixing y u no post on appadvice?    
    
    
    @WCHamilton  SCOREBOARD HOMIE! pic.twitter.com/6zti9Oaf    
    
    
    @WCHamilton patience requires time. And at an avg age of 50 the lakers don't have time for patience    
    
    
    @WCHamilton better game than I thought.    
    
    
    @WCHamilton not my clips. I am just a laker hater! Lol #mambatweets    
    
    
    @jsnell @reneritchie @atjamie @gibranhyder I guess we should be flattered he used us to "validate" his idea but no good karma for lying!    
    
    
    @jsnell @reneritchie @atjamie @gibranhyder funny if he woulda just emailed us i would have probably looked into it. Guess it doesn't work?    
    
    
    @JonesOnTheNBA works on $99 Apple TV. You get all the http://NBA.com  post game press conferences and highlights.    
    
    
    @Book_Dork we have wayyyy more readers than that.    
    
    
    They gotta pull RG3.    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo he's not helping at all. You see his face when he limped those 9 yards? And the throws are awful. He's  great but hurt    
    
    
    Idiots. I don't know anything and I knew he should not be in the game.    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis too soon. Give the poor guy a day before bashing him.    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis plus he's gotta better head than Vick. I see him more like mcnabb if anything    
    
    
    @juviwhale no way    
    
    
    @atjamie @juviwhale lol. That comes outta your paycheck. Or should I say paychecks. Multiple paychecks.    
    
    
    Nice way to dispel the rumor. I still think its true though “@kobebryant: The mamba vs d12 !! It's on lol pic.twitter.com/n63PDX5Y”    
    
    
    @juviwhale CES gets lamer and lamer every year!  You guys enjoying it    
    
    
    @jenienb hey who won the game tonight?    
    
    
    .@jenienb who would have thought after signing Howard and Nash Laker fans would be thrilled and tweeting about winning 2 games is a row    
    
    
    @BrianNorgard I don't know.Too much money for it to die.I see the cracks but if they start guaranteeing contracts & paying NBA money...    
    
    
    How fast is the internet in AOL's Palo Alto office?  Well, let's just say we're not in Kansas anymore... pic.twitter.com/jMkqF10o    
    
    
    @jeff148apps already thought that! But didn't wanna publish that in a public forum. #redacttweet    
    
    
    @jeff148apps @juviwhale thanks! When we going out for drinks.    
    
    
    @mtrctyjoe let's just say they've come a long way since dial up    
    
    
    @reneritchie I don’t doubt that! But for reason I always associate AOL with dial up, safe to say they’ve come a long way since then    
    
    
    @robinrhys Your videos would upload in about 2 mins =)    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @christyxcore email away. Mahmoud@appadvice    
    
    
    @llofte good luck! You'll get to meet the little one soon!    
    
    
    @darkrxn this late???    
    
    
    Tip @Techmeme http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/01/how-to-put-apps-inside-of-newsstand-without-a-jailbroken-device …    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo lol no worries    
    
    
    Email I received…And this is why we do what we do…”The First Mobile App That Let Singles Enjoy a Virtual One-night Stand Launches Globally”    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett @kimkimcachoo which app?    
    
    
    @Appaholik Remote app on iPhone/iPad didn't cut it for you?    
    
    
    I don't know Apple, which one did I mean? pic.twitter.com/NgoXo0NK    
    
    
    People name drop in Silicon Valley more than they do in Hollywood! Only difference is in Hollywood the names they drop are actually famous !    
    
    
    @macmixing LOL.  Macworld….You’re home!    
    
    
    @atjamie @macmixing Do you think Big “Macs” were Apple inspired?    
    
    
    @atjamie since you don't respond to texts I'll try twitter...what's your plan woman.    
    
    
    "She's bashful!" Really you think you think she is shy? "No I mean she bashes around a lot." That's @juviwhale talking about @atjamie    
    
    
    @macmixing @atjamie lol. She texted me. I see the plan is already in full effect.    
    
    
    @LaurenGoode @wsj when will Nintendo embrace iOS and Android and make billions: http://appadvice.com/appnn/2011/07/nintendos-barely-treading-water-but-apples-got-extra-life-jackets …    
    
    
    @julipuli it was nice meeting you too Sunnyvale neighbor!    
    
    
    @SCbchbum @WCHamilton HEY how else are we gonna know if we have another 6 weeks of winter or not. Huh? Huh? #earlyspring    
    
    
    Refacetweet! Check out the pic. You'll get it. pic.twitter.com/Dl9Y7qrd    
    
    
    What if Rajon Rando didn't play and the lakers lost to Boston by 30. Oh wait...    
    
    
    Anyone else trying @aol take on chatroulette? It's actually really fun, and so far no flashing! http://getapp.cc/app/559328825     
    
    
    @llofte what are your favorite pregnancy apps?    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon which app we talking about this time?    
    
    
    Anyone know any good iOS devs looking for work?  Need someone who is experienced who can join our current iOS team    
    
    
    @mleatherb thanks for the intro! Hey @tyler_nettleton, I'd love to setup a time to chat. Can you email me at mahmoud@appadvice.com    
    
    
    @taylorswift13 what happened to this?! #source=fired! pic.twitter.com/EYoR2jTs    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Here is that story on YouSendIt I was talking about: http://www.inc.com/magazine/201203/burt-helm/a-silicon-valley-tale-of-humiliation-and-revenge.html …    
    
    
    @docrock I wanna introduce you to someone, what’s the  best email to use! (Don’t worry it’s not like what we talked about at Macworld) ;)    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ the built in boomerang feature is nice    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ I have it setup but still using the stock mail app. Until iOS let's you choose default apps its too much work to replace them    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Wow, Awesome to see AppsGoneFree won a best app ever award.  You were so tight lipped!  http://bestappever.com/awards/2012/winner/barg … 
Thanks!!    
    
    
    http://bestappever.com/awards/2012/winner/barg … #betterthananoscar @jeff148apps    
    
    
    Peek at you! pic.twitter.com/LJOjshh0lF    
    
    
    @jenienb how do you get to go to so many games?! By the way you can't call a glorified role player part of a power couple #ShaqWonAllMVPs    
    
    
    @jenienb Waaa.  Why does a team that was supposed to win the title cry about playing a team that isn't even that good. #waitforheat!    
    
    
    @SHAQ "gotta different girl every day of the week?" Was that the reference you were going for? Nice!    
    
    
    @tonyparker fantasy basketball playoffs start Monday. If at all possible please come back next week. Please I need you! #parkerforMVP    
    
    
    How do the Lakers always get so lucky. pic.twitter.com/xwA2BOCQZH    
    
    
    @kobebryant awesome excuse to wear my LM jersey! Hit me back! pic.twitter.com/J9rNl41Kci    
    
    
    @asronline happy birthday    
    
    
    @xonder congrats! We will cover. Let me know if you ever wanna go free. I can really help then.    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman thanks! We are having fun with her =)    
    
    
    Is this a joke?Was anyone ever even questioning this?Shaq top 10 all-time “@kwarner8: @SHAQ got him beat hands down. pic.twitter.com/pJ7rPHFXjG”    
    
    
    @DuaneKinsey sorry Duane. The banner went up last night and I will respond to other emails tonight. Still thinking on other deal    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis @ourielohayon TYLER! Y U NO LINK APPADVICE: http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/04/apple-adds-prominent-age-rating-box-in-ios-app-store …    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon @dubbalubagis what did you find?!    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon twitter won't let me reply. Says you no longer follow me?    
    
    
    @juviwhale yeah for sure. I don't buy apple being scared. Some of the tactics they were using may have not been so kosher.    
    
    
    @romaindillet Shot you an email that should be of interest to you. Let me know if you want to chat.    
    
    
    @romaindillet thanks. Couldn't reply because you don't follow me. Be in touch if I can be of any help.    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon @dubbalubagis LOL. Glad to see Apple bugs don't discriminate on size of company.    
    
    
    @stevekovach hey Steve. Just saw this. Sure. I am at mahmoud@appadvice.com    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ wow. I didn't know. Have fun. I liked your demo. Wanna try a couple ideas. Let's do it when u get back    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ oh wow. What part of California.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ it will be AWESOME    
    
    
    “@lsliang2001: Not a Lakers fan, but my condolences. I have huge respect for #kobe.” My feelings exactly.    
    
    
    When watching kobe talk in the locker room I saw the lakers had this posted on the wall: http://www.poundingtherock.com/pages/the-stonecutters-creedo …    
    
    
    @juviwhale what cha got    
    
    
    @macmixing let's see a pic    
    
    
    @macmixing lol I like! Less rock bandy but I like the look.    
    
    
    @jenienb what a sad sad day in laker land. We are celebrating the 7th seed.    
    
    
    @erondu wait you live in SF now? We are in palo alto. Come hang out    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk lol. They are a game away from missing playoffs and you want the MVP. It's not like he was playing with the best center    
    
    
    @jenienb lol. I am thinking they need all the help they can get against the spurs. And that's what u notice? No beautiful Layann comment!    
    
    
    @jenienb Janan says "good save" pretty smooth ms. bottle. Laker shirt is a PJ. FYI twitter is 140    
    
    
    @jenienb look what I am sitting on right now though :/ pic.twitter.com/ozcPUKMG0X    
    
    
    @jenienb hahaha. Better yet you come be the photographer. You should visit us up here. U know u got time!    
    
    
    @jenienb oh no?! Not for a few years then?    
    
    
    @jenienb oh wait you mean the actual finals?! I thought you meant a single playoff series. You are never coming! Why is Nadia moving here    
    
    
    @jenienb lol. That's a real hash tag. I just checked. What a diss to Howard. No way he's signing again    
    
    
    Growing apart is okay...as long as you do it together. #originalquotes    
    
    
    @atjamie okay then. My baby is 0. But don't ask me again until next year because the answer won't change!    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk why? For real. Not trying to fight but they play the right way and lebron is a joy to watch play. Regardless if u like him    
    
    
    @arnoldkim congrats! About time you are back in the store. We had so many people emailing us asking about it.    
    
    
    @reneritchie You better get a ticket!!!    
    
    
    MightyText now has 3 million users; Launches photo/video syncing http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/24/mightytext-the-imessage-for-android-targets-icloud-with-new-cross-device-photo-and-video-sync/ … via @mightytext    
    
    
    @dantoml press don't get tickets to WWDC. They just invite some press to the keynote. Not the actual sessions, which are for devs    
    
    
    @macmixing not really. Because it seems no matter what they do to revenue, the stock wants to keep going south.    
    
    
    @dantoml those are devs with developer accounts. Apple invites press for free to keynote. Those who also have Dev accounts can buy for 1,600    
    
    
    @dantoml maybe the answer is only let devs who have app in store go? To weed out press buying? But is that fair to upcoming devs?    
    
    
    @chasesclouds sorry to hear. Saying a prayer for her now.    
    
    
    @atjamie @macmixing that was the best come back I have ever read on twitter. EVER    
    
    
    T-Mac made it out the first round ya'll! /cc @JonesOnTheNBA pic.twitter.com/CQHpRuiXnj    
    
    
    @erondu welcome! If you want a place to work in Palo Alto we got one for you    
    
    
    @atjamie i always knew you as a woman of many faces so it seems appropriate to have a face wash for each of them.    
    
    
    @atjamie , “If I had another face, do you think I’d wear this one?” Abraham Lincoln    
    
    
    LA fans- remember at the beginning of the year there was so much chatter about if the @Lakers or @LAClippers would go further? You both won    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis I love Marc Gasol. I think spurs will come out the west though. No matter anyway...HEAT!!!!    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis although if fisher keeps playing like this...    
    
    
    @tyler_nettleton wait!!! They are updating it next month    
    
    
    @tyler_nettleton well the air for sure (but still no retina) but I expect a spec update on pros too.    
    
    
    @tyler_nettleton @macmixing return policy rebuy may be in your future    
    
    
    @chasesclouds what's 25 alt method of entry limit?    
    
    
    #MVP pic.twitter.com/9vPlAgj7cL    
    
    
    I just got approved for the adoption of Creamsicle, and it's excited to meet you! @Hatch http://hatchpet.com/share/creamsicle …    
    
    
    @tyler_nettleton y?    
    
    
    @stevekovach this would be a great business insider post idea for people wearing Google Glass! #DoIt    
    
    
    Wow Siri didn't mince any words on that one, #whysoharsh pic.twitter.com/dBUwK7UBkM    
    
    
    @llofte how old is Lucy now.    
    
    
    @llofte she looks so big! We have a 2 month old at home, so I am trying to gauge time    
    
    
    @WCHamilton is that you?! Look at the awe on the face of the guy behind you    
    
    
    @erondu aapl!    
    
    
    @jenienb I don't know. When I was in college ...ahem... 10 years ago, his tracks made people get up! #hollaholla    
    
    
    @christyxcore @copyapp where is this share for 2 extra gigs link in the app    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk yeah....it's because of the refs that the Heat win. Riggggght    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk ah okay. I got ya now. I missed tonight's game.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ where in California are you?    
    
    
    @christyxcore i call "yeah right!" You tweet more than you talk! 😉    
    
    
    @agilestack Looking at your github and I wanted to see if you wanted to do something together. email me - mahmoud@appadvice.com    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk the great ones make it look easy. Kobe woulda settled for a 20 foot fade away. Was the 30-10-10 the easiest triple double too?    
    
    
    @tyler_nettleton we're puttin you through iOS boot camp son! Lol. You finish the feature???    
    
    
    Go bears! pic.twitter.com/wJaIFf0lS6    
    
    
    @reneritchie ours got lost in the email too I guess. You registered for the conference though or no? Alex and I will be there    
    
    
    @reneritchie alright well I'll see you there!    
    
    
    @chasesclouds “he” is a she =)    
    
    
    http://www.huffingtonpost.com/mobileweb/2013/05/23/teen-iphone_n_3322095.html …    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis HATER!    
    
    
    @christyxcore happy birthday!    
    
    
    I have never really given the Spurs the proper respect and never truly appreciated what they have done, but this is incredible. #hatsoff    
    
    
    You know what's scary? @spurs will have at least a week off...all that time for pop to prepare, and he's already swept lebron before #scared    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis you really rather watch spurs pacers?    
    
    
    "Life is a zero sum game" - @juviwhale    
    
    
    @juviwhale working with you has made me realize that.    
    
    
    @jenienb what happened    
    
    
    @jenienb I been tellin you that fool that was sorry since day 1.I truly believe if he didn't play against Dallas Heat be 3 pete-ing  now    
    
    
    We are rolling deep @appadvice this year - 4 people in keynote! pic.twitter.com/PKKJA1sUqD    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Azkend 2 HD - The World Beneath http://appsgonefree.getapp.cc/app/US/479473391 …    
    
    
    @jeff148apps I am going to try this, lol!    
    
    
    @jdalrymple No one from AppAdvice, got invited beard party this year.There will be 5 of us at WWDC, can we get on list?We'll do the karaoke!    
    
    
    @alyssabernal @lovelexi21 I love you Alyssa, but #letsgoheat    
    
    
    Why would sprint promote this retweet? pic.twitter.com/CpUMEMSHIr    
    
    
    @alyssabernal lol. Congrats. I have a pic for you pic.twitter.com/hQI3rNK1Fw    
    
    
    @alyssabernal haha. Because lebron has only won 1 championship, thus one ring, but Duncan has 5!    
    
    
    @UMAD @superpixels are you kidding? You are an animation extraordinaire. You will have a lot to say about iOS 7 redesign.    
    
    
    @CoreyTamas @christyxcore maybe they were using Siri? That personal assistant has butchered some texts for me. #needtospeakslower    
    
    
    @rsmoz @jeffmueller yeah...but can you get people to use it 150 million times a day?    
    
    
    @alyssabernal lol at the sign behind you. Someone is a rule breaker!    
    
    
    on the eve of WWDC @tyler_nettleton got bored and is developing a jailbreak tweak    
    
    
    @tchaten I am with you!    
    
    
    @juviwhale @atjamie aka - we are eating pizza and pounding Whiskey!    
    
    
    @markgurman nice job today.    
    
    
    @juviwhale I would not go that far. But then again, I have not installed it yet.    
    
    
    @bryanmwolfe why? Because they showed color iPod touches? Remember iPod touch is the game / music device. Makes sense to show it on iPod.    
    
    
    What's everyone's reaction to apple shoving the iTunes radio into iTunes instead of a separate radio app?    
    
    
    iTunes is already too clunky and stuffing the radio in it makes it just a lost feature of iTunes, rather than a serious product/service.    
    
    
    @comex ah, you haven't seen the icons yet. Lol    
    
    
    @erondu can you go more in depth. In a 140 chars, lol    
    
    
    Siri in a man's voice is tripping me out. Despite what SHE says, Siri is a girl. pic.twitter.com/ufPnDdhCql    
    
    
    @WCHamilton @erondu +1 for will?    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Bye bye mac address tracking; iOS 7 To Keep Advertisers From Accessing Personal Data http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/06/improved-privacy-changes-in-ios-7-to-keep-advertisers-from-accessing-personal-data …    
    
    
    Tip @techmeme: Improved Privacy Changes In iOS 7 To Keep Advertisers From Accessing Personal Data http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/06/improved-privacy-changes-in-ios-7-to-keep-advertisers-from-accessing-personal-data …    
    
    
    Tell me this doesn't feel straight out of a child's book! pic.twitter.com/GNVL1ZK9xp    
    
    
    @w1kedZ what was that regarding? The red fish blue fish?    
    
    
    @UMAD  what really?! Is this good news or bad news for you?    
    
    
    @w1kedZ ah makes sense.    
    
    
    I already miss the passbook shedder =( #ios7    
    
    
    @UMAD LOL, yes I didn't use passbook, but I appreciated that animation (though I know many hated it)/ BTW, there is a lot i like about ios7    
    
    
    Twitter's official app has A LOT of problems in #iOS7 sadly going to try tweetbot    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ issue 1 is this picture. The conversation never loads so I have to guess what they are replying to pic.twitter.com/FfMyommhX9    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ issue 2 is that many times i click retweet and nothing happens. But it just worked now.    
    
    
    @cagenagel omg! Congrats. I wanna meet him    
    
    
    Using #ios7 #yolo    
    
    
    That was for @tyler_nettleton  sorry for that last tweet!    
    
    
    @chasesclouds it's not apples native app. Its twitters's    
    
    
    Take off the headband!!!!    
    
    
    All these Samsung commercials are annoying me. #apple    
    
    
    Champions!!! pic.twitter.com/olQVEjyy6X    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk amazing that he lived up to the hype though. All that pressure. Most guys woulda messed it up    
    
    
    “@ImTheNorthWest: when i found out my name i was like "how could you be so heartless"”    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk http://www.businessinsider.com/lebron-james-life-story-2013-6 …    
    
    
    @atomicbird sent you an email via the webform on your site. You get it?    
    
    
    @chasesclouds try deleting and reinputting the account. That usually fixes it for me    
    
    
    LOL, @jenienb is easily impressed #howaboutwinning?    
    
    
    @jenienb LOL, that is a good kabean    
    
    
    @jenienb I really hope the Lakers don't do the impossible and sign Lebron next season.    
    
    
    @jenienb LOL, you are delusional if you think the Lakers wouldn't drop @kobebryant  in a second for @KingJames    
    
    
    @jenienb How'd they treat @SHAQ again? After he won 3 finals MVPs?    
    
    
    @AppStore AIM    
    
    
    @AppStore First app ever downloaded was AIM. Here is the video I made about it 5 years ago tomorrow! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y6kngBQwMmk …    
    
    
    @JCrossover @JonesOnTheNBA there's a bank in every city right?    
    
    
    @BrianNorgard Know any great co-working or incubator spaces in Los Angeles worth checking out for app related startup    
    
    
    Great Free Apps: gem 'em while they're hot. And by "hot," I mean FREE!  http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/07/all-of-the-paid-apps-that-went-free-for-the-app-stores-fifth-anniversary …    
    
    
    Much love to @Oday_Aboushi75 for handling the unjust attack on his character with so much class.    
    
    
    @Reeve took me a sec. Lol    
    
    
    @stevekovach doesn't happen to me much=)    
    
    
    Hollywood Style CGI in an easy to use iOS app http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/07/efexio-now-includes-awesome-animations-from-famed-tippett-studio …    
    
    
    @JonesOnTheNBA HYPERLOOP!!!!    
    
    
    @WCHamilton how is he following you?    
    
    
    @Ncdaley no need to commit it to memory, it's forever engraved on Twitter    
    
    
    @christyxcore they had it in Santa Monica today at @theColoft    
    
    
    @christyxcore haha good point    
    
    
    @alyssabernal plain old vanilla "youtubers" don't get @verified by Twitter & they don't get a deal with @Pharrell    
    
    
    @kanyewest as long as 2pac is in the discussion I won't even consider someone else having the best rap verse of all time.    
    
    
    @superpixels don't forget to listen to the apple earnings recap with iOS in the car while driving to pickup your retina iPad mini!    
    
    
    @DuaneKinsey you coming to casual connect?    
    
    
    Nice now you can draft via the app“@AppAdvice: The Yahoo! Fantasy Sports - Football App Launches For 2013 NFL Season http://apadv.co/17GFs2c ”    
    
    
    @alariccole I work with AppAdvice and wanted to chat about an iOS project with you. Can you pass along your email so we can chat? DM is fine    
    
    
    @alariccole That's a tough one =)  Look for an email in just a few mins!    
    
    
    @UMAD LOL!  Okay we'll send it right after we finally get AppPosters done.  Where you at!!!!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ I use this. Don't know if it's the best. https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/white-noise/id289894882?mt=8 …    
    
    
    @markgurman @stevekovach I may be confused but wouldn't this easily solve your problem: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/cvs-pharmacy/id395545555?mt=8 …    
    
    
    New beta of iOS 7 auto shortening my contact names to first name + last initial is driving me nuts. pic.twitter.com/ihcvuM9iec    
    
    
    @asronline I wonder if that even makes sense in other languages. Seems very cultural. I don't think that works in arabic.    
    
    
    @w1kedZ you are right!!! Nice pic.twitter.com/TW2I9x9mIh    
    
    
    @asronline look! pic.twitter.com/7pM1EjEuJB    
    
    
    iOS 7 beta 4 reverts the App Store display to only show the number of reviews for current version. Previously showed all ratings. #damn    
    
    
    Lol. Wow. Too funny. pic.twitter.com/52neejpDuN    
    
    
    @SHAQ check out an app made by a huge fan who left the Laker bandwagon for how they treated you. http://getapp.cc/app/470693788  tweet if you like it    
    
    
    @atjamie you are up? Isn't it 6am    
    
    
    @liftapp @superpixels and be really really good at basketball and you'll figure it out =)    
    
    
    Everyone who got burned on Facebook IPO: Your shares are now safe as #fb has just passed $38. Now get out while you can! Fool me once...    
    
    
    @drewwilson lol to your reply.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps thought you were talking Tony Romo there for a second.    
    
    
    @superpixels just had same issue. Restart comp fixed for me.    
    
    
    @UMAD @BrianNorgard what's app worked for paid. Yes free now but was paid for years at #1 in App Store    
    
    
    Need a cheap gsm iPhone. Any model is fine. Any suggestions? (Yes I will check craigslist and eBay need other suggestions)    
    
    
    @WCHamilton yeah I will pay for it! Thanks    
    
    
    That moment when you yell YOLO, but then realize you're a Hindu...    
    
    
    @UMAD wow. But I thought iOS was supposed to be intuitive. #missforstall    
    
    
    @SteveStreza I am sure you have one in you. Come on...    
    
    
    @nabeel @rsmoz that's the point though. They had long history of social impact and still only a fraction of cost of other companies. Nuts    
    
    
    Lol I just got an email: a spam/scraper site wants to sell my data back to me    
    
    
    @jenienb are you going to that thing in moorpark today?    
    
    
    @jenienb you FAIL! I was showing my mom how fast you are at this stuff. But no response!!!    
    
    
    @jenienb lol. Okay that's acceptable I guess. We're in cerritos so we will pass. Have fun. My mom says hi    
    
    
    @jenienb did you look this up yet http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/news/10235261/Inside-the-Hyperloop-the-pneumatic-travel-system-faster-than-the-speed-of-sound.html …    
    
    
    @jenienb yeah.    
    
    
    @macmixing you tweeting from theatre?    
    
    
    @DanaRebecca how come the GLEE20 promo code is not working? Is there a new code? I have to buy a 5 year anniversary gift for my wife! #help    
    
    
    @chasesclouds why did he call you?    
    
    
    @chasesclouds oh I see! What did you ask him    
    
    
    @markgurman I want those 4 mins of my life back. Lol    
    
    
    @SteveStreza there are worse things that you can be spammed about. #You'veGotMoney!    
    
    
    @reneritchie nice job on your quick and dirty mockup of gold iPhone 5 last week. Looks like you nailed it    
    
    
    @erondu Which app?    
    
    
    Remember when everyone was obsessed about Adobe Flash coming to the iPhone and how it wouldn't work without it...    
    
    
    @thesamlytle what you doing?!    
    
    
    @markgurman hope they are on an unlimited plan.    
    
    
    Amazing how fast the human mind adapts. I am having trouble using iOS 6. Keep searching in the URL field and pulling down for spotlight.    
    
    
    @UMAD lol. I am commenting on how amazing the human mind is, not iOS 7. We can adapt to anything, even if it's lesser.    
    
    
    @UMAD all in all iOS 7 is fine. I do think iOS 6 is more beautiful and easier to use.    
    
    
    @UMAD like how many users are gonna figure out how to forward a text message now?You have to guess hold the bubble, then hit more then check    
    
    
    @UMAD it's true.If there a grand reason.Like design works on watches, cars, and tvs better okay. I Just hope it's not change for change sake    
    
    
    @UMAD lol! You caught me. The fact that my entire business is centered around only iOS apps is a front!    
    
    
    @superpixels yeah but they didn't go backwards. Yes iOS 7 icons may improve but point is Mac 1.0 icons were best we saw at time #missiOS6    
    
    
    .@superpixels BTW I am not convinced that this looks better than even Mac 1.0, looks very similar to me #missiOS6 pic.twitter.com/SnJ50yrGOq    
    
    
    @reneritchie I need the help of a Canadian. please DL http://appsto.re/us/CEJdC.i  & use it to follow any app to the app store. Does it work?    
    
    
    Silicon Valley quote of the day #1:  "Why does our company have to have revenue?"    
    
    
    Silicon Valley quote of the day #2: "I would never work there. You have to work every hour you're there"    
    
    
    @reneritchie okay thanks. Got a couple for emails both from CA saying it loads App Store but not proper app. Trying to diagnose if all CA    
    
    
    @reneritchie @gruber @sdw @gte I have always loved the ideas in this article from 2 years ago by a former writer: http://appadvice.com/appnn/2011/07/nintendos-barely-treading-water-but-apples-got-extra-life-jackets …    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon hiring is harder than both!    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon well I guess if you wanna overpay for rookies with inflated egos it's not too bad.    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon so you officially here now?    
    
    
    @superpixels this is how I feel about android =)    
    
    
    @alanwarms new app coming?    
    
    
    @drewwilson did you see these bad boys: pic.twitter.com/wnJmKU29GI    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon Would be great if it was all fake, but looks like too much evidence against the gold iPhone. #China    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon Did you think the new app icons were Apple taste? And these pic.twitter.com/1rnXVEHdt5    
    
    
    If Apple's iWatch is anything like this I am selling all my stock…This thing is UNUSABLE http://www.engadget.com/2013/09/04/galaxy-gear-hands-on/ …    
    
    
    @MirellaBelle @alyssabernal I am such an Appoholic that when I read this all I saw was "Pad" - all I could think of was iPad. #addicted    
    
    
    @elonmusk Let's focus on HYPERLOOP!    
    
    
    @ENLATL @DwyaneWade don't that matters to him. Lol. #99problems$$$aintone    
    
    
    @gruber you do realize football started today right?    
    
    
    the excitement over this event is sky high…very weird..even my non-apple crowd are tweeting about it and highly anticipating it.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Yeah that's why I am surprised. I guess people who follow this stuff know what we're getting and it's all kinda meh…    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Thing that kinda sucks is if they had something really new to show it could turn perception over night, #NextYear    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Let's throw the full TV in there too! I think 2014 it will finally happen!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ But retina mini this year no?    
    
    
    @Objective_Neo Download IPA.  Same way for iOS 6.    
    
    
    @chasesclouds why not order on 13th    
    
    
    @chasesclouds Nope. I didn't really see the benefit.  Fingerprint is cool but not useful enough, same with camera upgrades    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon I guess it's not too similar but I just got an email from tracking company named AppFireworks. I immediately thought of you    
    
    
    @markgurman @stroughtonsmith I am getting crashes on iPhone 5 still as well. #RadarTime    
    
    
    “@windowsphone: 8 megapixels is still just 8 megapixels. See what you can do with 41: http://newwp.it/1b1Yc0M  #timetoswitch to #WindowsPhone”    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk still wanna do the deal?    
    
    
    August and Everything After... That is all #countingcrows    
    
    
    You know that feeling when cool people start following you and then you feel the need to tweet something cool? #idontthinkthiscounts    
    
    
    @UMAD you my friend are fast!    
    
    
    @DuaneKinsey caught me red handed. Lol    
    
    
        
    
    
    From my sister this morning. pic.twitter.com/82D1N6V4zm    
    
    
    @reneritchie so how do you get slow mo clip off the device?    
    
    
    @timburks how so?    
    
    
    My iPhone is now in the same state as I am. Should have by tomorrow!    
    
    
    @christyxcore even though white is still the prettiest I wanted a change so 32gb space gray    
    
    
    @markgurman thanks!    
    
    
    So apparently I am the weird one for not knowing the channel H2. As @juviwhale explained it's "history channel 2... you know like MTV2"    
    
    
    @arnoldkim where does it say there is a change to the IAP policy? Do you just mean because users don't spend iap money within 24 hours?    
    
    
    @arnoldkim @markgurman if we send user on day 1 to a freemium app. Then again on day 3. And on day 3 the user buys iap from day 1 - counts?    
    
    
    @davidingle @MackFlavelle if you are on a @Verizon iPhone you still tell yourself that daily. #notalkandsurf #sucks    
    
    
    Can't believe Apple would approve this app. Clearly infringing....OnePassword by mattia scevola https://appsto.re/us/cwRBP.i     
    
    
    @everpix my wife and I share a photo library. Any chance we can add 2 Facebook and 2 gmail accounts? Would pay twice. #nolongeroneperson    
    
    
    @everpix awesome! Again I would be happy to pay twice. Not trying to save money it just doesn't make sense for us to have 2 unique accounts    
    
    
    @IURabah no critical govt services stay open    
    
    
    @christyxcore I sold an 8gb iPhone 4 today for $150. That's my suggestion.    
    
    
    I just disabled touch ID. I know...it is so amazing for everyone else and I must be programming it wrong. I never used a pass code before so    
    
    
    @christyxcore ah weird. That phone is so old. I had Verizon too    
    
    
    @reneritchie how are you doing this. When I keep the button pressed down I get Siri. When I just rest my finger on button I get touchid    
    
    
    @reneritchie oh I see If you disable Siri. Interesting. Not sure which I like better. I am getting more "try again" this way    
    
    
    @superpixels That's what I love about the App Store on iOS7, especially on the iPad. Good thing my business doesn't rely on that. Oh wait.    
    
    
    @markgurman Cool new app is out if that helps your boredom: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/tick/id683780016?mt=8 …    
    
    
    @phillryu I thought I was the only one! I gave up on the damn thing and went pass code-less    
    
    
    @Objective_Neo I don't follow? What are the facts    
    
    
    I guess I won't be seeing @OfficialSisQo  here: pic.twitter.com/2nHO7o3t7C    
    
    
    @UMAD lol. You called it. Only in #SanFrancisco    
    
    
    @UMAD well pier 39. Close enough.    
    
    
    WTF is apple doing keeping the iPad 2 around? 2+ year old hardware same price as new retina mini, only 100 less than 3 model newer iPad air    
    
    
    @superpixels point is not the iPad 2 sucks. Point is iPad 2 is old and it's not cheap at 400. Should have kept iPad 4 at that price    
    
    
    @arnoldkim New affiliate IAP policy has my total commission down over 60%.  Man, I never thought freemium would hurt this bad. You ok?    
    
    
    I still like official twitter app but tweetbot is the best use of #ios7 that I have seen    
    
    
    @arnoldkim Sent you a couple of emails over the weekend.  The last one I just sent you is most telling. Let me know if you want to chat!    
    
    
    @BrentDirks did not know that. Should do a post.    
    
    
    http://mashable.com/2013/10/18/facebook-ios-ads-more-profitable/?utm_cid=mash-com-Tw-main-link …    
    
    
    58.6% of my Gmail space is used by 1.9% of my mail. @FindBigMail works with #GoogleApps too! https://www.findbigmail.com     
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/piXFWqSD8o    
    
    
    @UMAD @markgurman why?    
    
    
    @everpix    
    
    
    @everpix any chance a buyer can still emerge with all the press the last couple of days? #keephopealive?    
    
    
    What happened to brydge ipad keyboard case. Is that still a thing? Work for iPad Air?    
    
    
    @w1kedz I know. But site not updated forever. I never hear about it. No mention of iPad air.    
    
    
    @markgurman needs to sit out both games?    
    
    
    Everpix Flashback = Ex-girlfriend reminder. I'll miss you! (Talking to @everpix not the ex-gfs) ;)    
    
    
    @alyssabernal you means guys who work at McDonalds aren't your type?!    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon affiliate revenue?    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon That’s great! we are down 60% since the IAP policy change.    
    
    
    @alariccole eh, it’s a move that matches their latest moves, but I don’t think it’s the right direction.    
    
    
    @JonesOnTheNBA looks like the fantasy gods ain't feeling him yet pic.twitter.com/qQ86xxvFvb    
    
    
    @Chris_Broussard seems smart. Take the power away from oppressor by embracing the term. "Yeah I am a xxx & proud" takes power out of word    
    
    
    So AOL is shutting down #winamp….Man, between AIM & Winamp I didn’t realize how much of my college life was controlled by AOL.    
    
    
    @appsfire @OurielOhayon congrats on the update guys!    
    
    
    @jeff148apps if you are still looking there is a new company I have used twice and give WAY higher prices than gazelle. @NewayaRecycling    
    
    
    @jenienb hey my older ipad mini is black. Cool? It's this one but for verizon and not refurb http://store.apple.com/us/product/FE215LL/A/refurbished-ipad-mini-with-wi-fi-cellular-for-sprint-16gb-black-slate …    
    
    
    @JenniferJolly @USATODAY great shopping article. Can I recommend an article about "best way to get hot apps FREE this holiday season"    
    
    
    @JenniferJolly @USATODAY we have more than 42k 5 star reviews. We hand curate great apps that have go free each day https://appsto.re/us/CEJdC.i     
    
    
    @AndyNico_ why loon over picture life. Picture life has the discovery stuff too    
    
    
    @JonesOnTheNBA a Bluetooth basketball, thoughts? http://allthingsd.com/20131125/no-cheap-shots-with-this-300-bluetooth-basketball/?refcat=reviews …    
    
    
    @Jason happy birthday!    
    
    
    @thecity2 @JonesOnTheNBA that's the best way to turn the ball over. #aggressive    
    
    
    @phillryu try "Many Thanks" it's a good one that has the same friendly vibe.    
    
    
    @phillryu Besides if you don't say exactly what the person wants to hear "cheers" sounds like  "F OFF" many thanks doesn't do it as much    
    
    
    @phillryu In all honestly if someone doesn't like what you have to say I don't think the salutation matters. Cheers it is! 

Many thanks =)    
    
    
    @reneritchie the most important question....what did you watch?!    
    
    
    Looking for an iPhone case that makes my black 5s look like a 5c. Anyone know any?    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ lol. It's a pretty phone. It looks like it has a case on it already. Should be easy to replicate    
    
    
    @superscientific @macmixing which networks? Sprint?    
    
    
    @macmixing hey dom. I want a case to make my black 5s look like a 5c. You see anything?    
    
    
    @macmixing I just think it looks HOT!!!    
    
    
    @jeff148apps I don't think they are getting app of the week. They just went to freemium they didn't go free    
    
    
    Yup http://youtu.be/MtN1YnoL46Q     
    
    
    What's the Lakers record with Kobe?    
    
    
    The @appsfire website is really nice. It's Pretty and well done. Good job team.    
    
    
    @iHaz3 @AppAdvice hey guys. I am not sure what I missed? What's up. I am here?    
    
    
    @AppAdvice @iHaz3 oh I thought I responded. We may use it when we update appadvice but we have not gotten far enough to decide.    
    
    
    @AppAdvice @iHaz3 feel free to share it if you like    
    
    
    @iHaz3 @AppAdvice oh okay. I will send you a code later today    
    
    
    @viticci last night at a party in SV, a man couldn't figure out how to switch to record video in camera app.kept tapping word not swiping    
    
    
    Maybe this will help me wake up in the morning. #5hours pic.twitter.com/u8054uvBpe    
    
    
    1--anTtra    
    
    
    @UMAD @stokefire flickering!    
    
    
    @stevekovach there's not a new one is there?    
    
    
    @reneritchie it's the little tweaks. Voicemail forwarder, contact pics in the contacts list, screen recording are few that come to mind    
    
    
    @reneritchie unlike most iPhone users I still use the phone app a lot, the voicemail forwarder is essential. But waiting on JB via @saurik    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ FESTIVUS FOR THE REST OF US! http://youtu.be/55fI9_D9lTs     
    
    
    @AndyNico_ see also the huge appadvice festival we did 2 years ago in its honor  http://appadvice.com/appnn/tag/days-of-festivus-giveaway …    
    
    
    @Objective_Neo they have rollback to previous version also.    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo CONGRATS!!!    
    
    
    @mattfriz Hey Matt, looked over your site...I'd love to discuss Angular with you with you. Email? I am mahmoud@appadvice.com    
    
    
    @launchticker @Jason @zynga that my friends is a publicity grab. It's a great idea too, people will talk about this.    
    
    
    @Objective_Neo sounds like Asem, lol    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk Be happy that they aren't working you from day 1!    
    
    
    @katiedel LOL, cool, I'm looking forward to it working.    
    
    
    @drewwilson @gmph @dialoggs is that all? =)  looking forward to it!    
    
    
    @tchaten Well you are seeing ramifications now. If I tell you I am gonna sock u in the face last week, it hurts a lot more when I do it 2day    
    
    
    @atjamie @erikamkay but how did that person send you a text with a dead phone? I am calling iPhone with either mac or iPad iMessage. No?    
    
    
    @juviwhale ANOTHER BARAKA! Oh no!!!!    
    
    
    @BrianNorgard you are not alone my friend.  Check it out: http://www.insidemobileapps.com/2012/05/31/how-to-double-user-retention-with-push-notifications-urban-airship-shares-best-practices/ …    
    
    
    @atjamie lol. It's not that bad is it???    
    
    
    @bryanmwolfe easiest money of your life    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ FINALLY! I was shocked by your previous decision. Welcome back!    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @andynico_  lol. Yes you will be welcomed to the club too!    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk NOOOOO!  Are you kidding me. Freaking Tamme    
    
    
    @BrentDirks WOW. That is crazy!    
    
    
    @reneritchie Can you preorder for a different carrier and port your number without ever walking into a store and getting new iPhone shipped    
    
    
    @asronline @atjamie @christyxcore COOL! Now you can airplay movies on TV, make awesome keynotes for class, & run it for next 10 yrs! Oh wait    
    
    
    @julipuli @atjamie and the new iPhone is getting even bigger.  Apple is not doing your pockets any favors ;)    
    
    
    @BrianNorgard latest rumors are pre-orders start Friday morning.    
    
    
    is panorama only available on iPhone 5 and the new iPod touch?  If it works on iPod Touch's A5 chip, why won't it run on 4s?    
    
    
    Confirmed: iPhone 4S WILL feature panorama mode, but not iPhone 4    
    
    
    If I am switching from AT&T to Verizon and want to port my number do I preorder from Apple or Verizon?    
    
    
    @reneritchie I read your posts about it (marketing, mass appeal, yada, yada, yada)…but I am still shocked!    
    
    
    @reneritchie Give me iPhone 6, iPhone LTE, anything…but not the iPhone 5!!! ;)    
    
    
    Why can't I put in my phone number for Messages on mac like I can on my iPad.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps I read your post about switching…but what about porting 2 number's onto 1 verizon share everything plan. Need to use VZN site?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Does this worry you: http://www.theverge.com/2012/9/13/3328492/iphone-5-simultaneous-voice-data-verizon-sprint …    
    
    
    @atjamie check email    
    
    
    @llofte I finally found one reason the move to Verizon is not perfect: http://www.theverge.com/2012/9/13/3328492/iphone-5-simultaneous-voice-data-verizon-sprint …    
    
    
    @llofte ah, i see you guys already discussed this. Alright I'll see you on the verizon side =)    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Ah…I thought I was gonna see a great Jeff response and then see a troll go nuts.  RESPOND!!! It's fun..for us at least =)    
    
    
    @christyxcore LOL. Sounds expensive.    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Thanks for the reply. I am bringing my wife with me, and I want to join my family on a share everything plan. How should I do it    
    
    
    @vzwsupport also was sad to learn no talk & text for iPhone 5 on LTE. Any chance this will be changed or permanent hardware issue    
    
    
    @christyxcore That's why I hate kickstarter.  I love the ideas, but products never ship on time and for iPhone always too late    
    
    
    @reneritchie umm nice picture on iPhone 5 preorder forum post…can I come to your next slumber party. LOL    
    
    
    Riddle me this Batman: On Verizon, if I am on a phone call (voice) then hit FaceTime (data) does that work? Or do I have to hang up?    
    
    
    @christyxcore Did tests. We discovered if you initiate it,  it's seamless, but it hangs up on other person and calls them back as FaceTime    
    
    
    @christyxcore I tested it with Dom. He had Verizon. It still works okay. It's better on AT&T but this is fine.    
    
    
    @reneritchie @drbarnard @att @verizon @llofte it's got me thinking twice. But I am ready to "rule the air"    
    
    
    @christyxcore umm maybe, @robinrhys would know better than me. We'll check tomorrow    
    
    
    @atjamie Y U NO AIM?  If you're up I am gonna make you work!    
    
    
    @atjamie where are the excitement posts! apple store down, att has countdown taking over site, verizon is ready to rock…lets get excited!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ CALL.IN.SICK    
    
    
    @AppAdvice duh. We are waiting to order new lightning connectors!    
    
    
    @christyxcore get me some too!!!!    
    
    
    @robinrhys att?    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Very happy! I ported 2 number.Only issue was it asked me for my account info from att, but didn't ask on 2nd line for wife.    
    
    
    @vzwsupport is that going to be an issue? we have diff account numbers. Confirm #: 9210925800132005    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @christyxcore LOL, i said respectfully!  I bought the 4s off contract so I could jump ship for iPhone 5 =) Nice job C!    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Oh really?  I was able to put in her number? Can we fix it now, or do I have to wait tip I get it?  I am happy to be here!    
    
    
    @atjamie we have never been affected this long.  I am really worried.  Do what you can!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ view on computer…they look awesome    
    
    
    @VZWSupport I know the no simult. voice/data is b/c of how apple built phone,but it's really a huge issue w/ imessage & navi any fix?LTEvoip    
    
    
    @llofte how did they tell you? they called you?    
    
    
    @llofte why would they move his and not yours? And how did you get that date? No more Verizon?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps yes sir!  We are now part of  @vzwsupport Though I did I lot of tests and iMessages not being delivered during call is BIG neg.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps first @llofte now you!  You guys are all leaving me to go to Verizon by myself =(    
    
    
    @atjamie DAWSON'S CREEK is my favorite show of all time. No joke. And I am in love with Joey Potter.    
    
    
    @erondu happy birthday buddy!    
    
    
    @gruber It was very easy to do using verizon's site.  I was skeptical, but it was a pleasant experience. Also ported from AT&T    
    
    
    @llofte call back. Be angry. Ask for manager.    
    
    
    @llofte My experience is reps in store will just call customer support anyway. I would keep trying.  This is ridiculous!    
    
    
    @drbarnard It's even worse.  Even if the results were right and there were no bugs, that is an awful interface to try to find anything    
    
    
    @erondu on what?    
    
    
    @erondu oh LOL, I got married 4 yrs ago…but somehow I lost the connection on FB so I reeded it today.    
    
    
    @atjamie Okay, I just checked what I can afford for you from there.  I'll get the "free ground shipping" please mark it off the registry    
    
    
    @Book_Dork @atjamie lol    
    
    
    .@mittromney I've unsubscribed from your mailing list 3x & I still get emails. WTF, man? cc @FECupdates http://cl.ly/image/260r3J3W0Q2i …    
    
    
    Everyone please try the new appbump feature in AppsGoneFree 2.0. Huge update http://getapp.cc/app/470693788     
    
    
    Wow, AppsGoneFree is ranked #19 in the entire iPad App Store. Thanks for everyone who is supporting AppBump! http://getapp.cc/app/470693788     
    
    
    @reneritchie What about the HTML 5 App Store update?  I am pretty worried about it. you okay with it?    
    
    
    Finally! Your phone # receives iMessages on your phone, iPad, & Mac. Unless you are on Verizon and on a phone call. Then iPad & Mac only    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Yeah when you hang up, they come in.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps If it was already received on iPad or mac (and read), because the message window was open, it won't come in new, just slide in    
    
    
    @jeff148apps I picked Verizon, but I am really worried about it!    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Jeff, if you know anyone to share with Verizon can be pretty cheap. I am sharing with 3 other low data users, should save $$    
    
    
    @Mark_T_Willard ask Michael what about the "Jordan Rules" his era. He says it didn't happen.    
    
    
    @macmixing CULT OF MAC? where we at    
    
    
    Remember when we used to text in tweets and @ replies? Me neither, I started Twitter with Twitterific    
    
    
    @atjamie You know how much I hate that stupid iPhone 5 name.  #callitiPhone6    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie NO NO NO!  3G makes sense. 1st phone with 3G support! You can call this iPhone LTE, just not 5!    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie iPhone(1st one), iPhone 3G (first w/ 3g), 3gs (like 3g but fast, 4 (4th one), 4s (like 4 but better), 5 (explanation?)    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie iPhone high-five!!! I like it! Let's call it that =)    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie wow Bad reason! I'll drop it now.But you never answered about App Store app.Everyone talking maps, App Store is issue!    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie oh just your experience.You think it's an issue, or you think I'll get used to it. Feels like so many steps back.    
    
    
    @atjamie @reneritchie Jamie, that's where you go everyday from 8-3 right?    
    
    
    @christyxcore @reneritchie @atjamie haha, I like that    
    
    
    @reneritchie Very true, I don't know why they did those cards in search. But whole thing is slow and buggy    
    
    
    @atjamie @reneritchie LOL, nicely played.  Okay too much tweeting…back to work!    
    
    
    Siri doesn't like apps, that start with "app." So if you want Siri to launch AppAdvice you have to say "launch app appadvice" #protip    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon It's true! Your app works because it starts with apps,not app.Our AppsGoneFree app works fine, it's just the singular word app    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon  Siri uses natural language. So appadvice becomes app advice. "App" throws Siri off. AppsFire becomes apps fire. "Apps" is ok    
    
    
    @OurielOhayon LOL. I think that would just confuse Siri. #notworthit    
    
    
    @RippsUp i can't get that to work. It's really working? It says "open appadvice" in text but response is "cannot find an app named advice"    
    
    
    @lsliang2001 What's bothering you?    
    
    
    @lsliang2001 iOS 6    
    
    
    @lsliang2001 I hate the new app store, aside from all the bugs, the search is killing me larry!    
    
    
    @lsliang2001 you getting iPhone 5?    
    
    
    @KanePoehlman What do you mean?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps yay! I have a verizon friend…@llofte ditched us ;)    
    
    
    @KanePoehlman I sent you the code via DM    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @christyxcore In the US we can leave a note and have it dropped off, not over there?    
    
    
    @christyxcore SHHH, don't give away our secrets ;)    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ angel? halo over head?    
    
    
    @christyxcore midnight? It's 1AM!!!! Midnight was so an hour ago    
    
    
    @reneritchie you're crazy! I can't believe you were up for your slumber party last week and didn't preorder!    
    
    
    @reneritchie Hanging with apple folk is cool but up all night in the freezing cold waiting in a line?!    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett @christyxcore GOOD LUCK!!! Let us know how it goes. You going black or white?    
    
    
    Sorry to everyone I direct message'd nonsense too. Does these people really have nothing better to do. Anyway, sorry!    
    
    
    @jeff148apps NOOO!!! What changed your mind?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps LOL, by unknown you mean fear of no data while on phone calls, I have fear of "unknown" too    
    
    
    I was so sure the black iPhone 5 was the way to go... I was wrong!    
    
    
    @christyxcore for what? you can't change color with applecare can you?    
    
    
    @chasesclouds Nothing wrong with black, white is just so HOT!!!    
    
    
    @reneritchie @atjamie LOL, well I couldn't be part of an Apple site without complaining about meaningless Apple stuff right?    
    
    
    @KarenSFreeman I love it, but in photos the black looked so much better (i thought) but in real life I love white    
    
    
    @chasesclouds I too had the white 4S.  I never use it case. Iove the beauty of the device…but we'll see how scratches go.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps is that really doable. With upgrade eligibility and such?    
    
    
    @chasesclouds How.wouldn't it be a return rebuy…and if so how fast does my eligibility come back?    
    
    
    Does anyone want to trade a new Verizon iPad for an AT&T iPad one? 32GB model. My AT&T new iPad is literally mint condition.    
    
    
    Thanks for everyone who helped. White iPhone 5 obtained. pic.twitter.com/TML899ws    
    
    
    @christyxcore lol. Sorry, still in the iPhone 5 fam with you! Non iPhone 5 optimized apps look a lot better on black though.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps It would have been super easy to swap if bought it from apple.But since I didn't I had to go to Vzn. Return then buy at apple    
    
    
    @tchaten I thought so too. But in person I loved the white.    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk make sure you change your password. They have there password.    
    
    
    @tchaten how far along are you. Any scheduled release? preview teaser?    
    
    
    @atjamie eh, I don't think passbook warrants it…At least not now. But isn't the idea it pops up for you? No need to launch?    
    
    
    @tchaten cool good luck! you publishing in iBookstore?    
    
    
    @tchaten cool, good luck. We'll check it out at macworld!    
    
    
    @atjamie At least you have @AppAdvice app on your homescreen, unlike someone else I know…named @christyxcore and yes iPhone 5 support coming    
    
    
    @christyxcore LOL..okay okay…just busting your chops.    
    
    
    @llofte There's an app for that: http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/grubhub-food-delivery-takeout/id302920553?mt=8 …    
    
    
    @christyxcore I miss myspace. I don't care how much people make fun of the awful page designs. Cool you got your "space" to personalize.    
    
    
    @christyxcore and no "news feed" meant endless navigation to all your friend's pages to see what was new. Less efficient, more fun.    
    
    
    @christyxcore Not to sound like a creeper, but it was more acceptable to hit up friends of friends…okay now i sound like a creeper #stopping    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Oh yeah, well I am playing with something cool too, but I'm not telling either. J/k it's an iPhone 5 =)    
    
    
    @VZWSupport Has Verizon released a statement on their plans & estimate timelines for VoLTE? Bringing simultaneous voice/date & hd calls    
    
    
    @tchaten any idea how much data you used? I know you are unlimited, but that would be great to know    
    
    
    @tchaten I remember video, forgot findings…do you remember old findings?    
    
    
    @christyxcore link    
    
    
    "Some part of me wishes I had gotten white instead" - @christyxcore discussing her choice oh iPhone color.    
    
    
    @christyxcore lol. I know. Busting your chops for the 2nd time today!    
    
    
    Email I got Apple is giving me an iPad 3. 1 problem…there is no such thing as an iPad 3 & I think Apple knows that http://cl.ly/image/1J0x0t312p1h …    
    
    
    @erondu those appetizers look pretty bomb though    
    
    
    @asronline you can get a ton of free space pretty easy… i have 24GB…hit me up if you want tips    
    
    
    @christyxcore lol…at least he's realistic..wait he said they'd beat out windows 8, nevermind    
    
    
    @christyxcore maybe it's stuck in apple approval process like AppsGoneFree... Oh wait, just kidding.    
    
    
    @christyxcore I know! Thus the "just kidding." I guess I shouldn't quit my day job. LOL.    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk lets make a trade happen for your sorry RBs..    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk how about sjack, c. johnson and nelson…for fitz, witten, and moreno? You aint playing sjack or CJ anyway?    
    
    
    @rakkattackk I am just scared sjack will get hurt…and ur loaded with RBs    
    
    
    @rakkattackk witten is big upgrade at TE too…had an awful game last week but lots of targets and he is healthy now    
    
    
    @RakkAttackk Sent a trade, added heath miller. Let me know what you think. If you don't like why not    
    
    
    @christyxcore standby eh?    
    
    
    @christyxcore seriously. Bring me something cool on Friday!    
    
    
    @christyxcore oh booo! I thought it was for the 5    
    
    
    @christyxcore I was talking about the box that showed up today. I didn't see the bags    
    
    
    @bryanmwolfe AppsGoneFree has been sitting there a week already =(    
    
    
    @christyxcore I do love my phone with no case. My dream is to find a nice case one day but I have never seen one that convinced me to use    
    
    
    @christyxcore you're right.My iPhone 5 is lasting forever with 1%.But that's not good that it is not calculating the percentages correctly.    
    
    
    @chpwn Siri repeats the last thing she said to you when you say "what" ... So you must have asked to send a tweet previously.    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett @kimkimcachoo @bryanmwolfe all i am saying is despite how fast it seems, these devs probably all submitted over a week ago    
    
    
    @JulieVaughn @cluckstv @viddy @sol @aolmobile Nice, I will have the @AppAdvice team cover this for you!    
    
    
    @julievaughn @cluckstv @viddy @sol @aolmobile Ah, not out yet! I will cover it once it goes live. Keep us posted =)    
    
    
    @Book_Dork Send us a link!  I wanna see    
    
    
    @reneritchie  InstaPockaBility’d nice!    
    
    
    @Book_Dork nice!!! Congrats.    
    
    
    @bryanmwolfe you still posting your thoughts on it today?    
    
    
    @JulieVaughn @cluckstv @viddy @sol @aolmobile Here's the writeup we did: http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/09/aol-releases-clucks-a-cross-between-viddy-and-draw-something … Good luck!    
    
    
    AppsGoneFree featured on ABC San Diego local news http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pe6bUjecAzU …    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Thanks…We are not from San Diego & They got appbump wrong, but it's still cool. LOL    
    
    
    @christyxcore no one does buy full price and extend your contract. Do they? Hello iPhone 6    
    
    
    Nice placement advertising by Apple “@pdparticle: Samsung wants you to purchase an iPhone 5 too. http://i.imgur.com/vLlrC.jpg ”    
    
    
    @alyssabernal you're on!  Going now    
    
    
    @alyssabernal Small 11" macbook air, but you can see it here: http://cl.ly/image/0P1G1c2t1W0W …    
    
    
    @drewwilson @screenyapp  Check it out:  http://reviewtimes.shinydevelopment.com     
    
    
    @alyssabernal Thanks! Good luck, I will keep voting =)    
    
    
    Non-apple tweet for my girl @jenienb    
    
    
    @JailbreakCon wrote an article @AppAdvice http://apadv.co/QmYYai     
    
    
    @chasesclouds when it comes to tea, I always vote Pepsi    
    
    
    @chasesclouds @heatherblansett Hmm tough call, both are great. Coke did have MJ (http://youtu.be/UfwzizFhUIU ) but Pepsi had http://youtu.be/aYywiQ3-6To     
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @heatherblansett @chasesclouds an epic battle that is guaranteed to end in thirst quenching pic.twitter.com/ripiJ9Wr    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @heatherblansett @chasesclouds The whole "next generation" campaign was brilliant and gave coke a run for their money in 80s    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @heatherblansett @chasesclouds I love the current Pepsi font. And last Xmas coke did white cans? Ruining their iconic branding    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo @heatherblansett @chasesclouds yeah as far as marketing - Pepsi wins.Coke won in mass distribution, especially internationally    
    
    
    I love "carmageddon" it's the only time I ever get to average more than 80mph for an entire hour long drive    
    
    
    I hate college football. So many huge plays. You are never safe    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo they closed a freeway for the weekend and everyone is freaking out. We drive a lot in LA http://m.travelerstoday.com/articles/3208/20120929/carmageddon-2012-busy-los-angeles-freeway-closed-drivers-warned-to-stay-off-roads-carmageddon-ii-2-california-traffic-interstate-405-sepulveda-pass.htm …    
    
    
    All the AppAdvice apps, including the retired ones.  http://instagr.am/p/QLtKOnMUFh/     
    
    
    @RakkAttackk what's up with tech?    
    
    
    @tchaten http://mobile.theverge.com/2012/9/27/3417870/apple-ipod-click-wheel-games-history …    
    
    
    @jeff148apps It's Monday!!! Waiting on the exciting news you teased last week    
    
    
    @jeff148apps You mean like what 4KB is today?    
    
    
    @jeff148apps LOL. In that case congrats on composing a tweet at all!    
    
    
    @chasesclouds LOl, not til lunch!    
    
    
    I figured it out. The black iPhone 5 always looks like it's in a case due to the smoked out side covering. I've always loved iPhones naked.    
    
    
    @christyxcore it does. Put it on the table so the screen is facing up. Look at it. See the black casing around the side.    
    
    
    @christyxcore lol where is @Noobocity for the "no dude" love    
    
    
    @christyxcore @kimkimcachoo http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FVIOBtGVbvs …    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett @juviwhale congrats!! We are lucky to have you =)    
    
    
    @jeff148apps WOW. Huge news.  Congrats. I hope you're still going to be a big part of the team over there!    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Nice! I am excited then.  Our bets were a new app, or maybe an exclusive about what you erased under NDA a couple weeks ago    
    
    
    @LifeInTents Yeah but the problem on iOS is you don't notice any practical difference. Test att "4g" vs let in real life setting. no diff.    
    
    
    @jeff148apps No dodgers, no angles? Come on…Next year is the year of Los Angeles Baseball =)    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Everyone here is crazy and they wanna give the AL MVP to  Trout over Cabrera…is this a national thing or just crazy LA?    
    
    
    @HeatherBlansett you reminded me! I need I cancel my gym subscription.    
    
    
    @christyxcore wow..I just looked, didn't realize how far it dropped… ranks: 213 paid iPhone 170 free iPhone, 235 paid iPad,198 free iPad    
    
    
    .@christyxcore But then again, Draw Something is still making more than 1/2 a million every month by my estimates    
    
    
    Rachel gives one of the most moving love speeches of all time, then says she's done? Doesn't make sense. And yes that was a #glee tweet!    
    
    
    @msleamichele that was actually pretty amazing performance. I didn't know you had it in you. Not just for #glee that was all-time level.    
    
    
    anyone?  Trade a Verizon LTE iPad for an AT&T one?  These share everything plans messed everything up...    
    
    
    @jenienb @buzzfeed lol. That is crazy. He must have been pretty pissed that Joey chose Pacey and he wants everyone to forget about it    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo try clicking on any file and pushing space bar. It's the best    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo get an Apple TV too. So you can AirPlay stuff to your TV!    
    
    
    @christyxcore @kimkimcachoo it's not out yet right? Only alpha stuff and they submitted yesterday right? So like 2 more weeks to wait    
    
    
    @mnengle "that is dress is becoming on you...but then again if I was on you..."(rest is NSFW!)    
    
    
    The things I miss about jailbreak is becoming less & less, but not being able to forward voicemail is a big thing I really miss. #additapple    
    
    
    @dubbalubagis LOL, yes you are!    
    
    
    @superpixels that is not native in iOS. Only thing I can think of is someone using the new iOS 6 framework in their app on a ss within app    
    
    
    @jenienb better than being at work!    
    
    
    @superpixels looks like an iPhone app in landscape, so can't be App Store, can you ask what app that's in?    
    
    
    @superpixels Pretty cool. I wonder if they hard coded it or used the new framework. I have not seen that in action yet. I'll check    
    
    
    @148Apps to answer that, we need to define the need for http://app.net  in the first place. As for Tapbots they made a lot of money!    
    
    
    @jenienb r u going to xx concert in 2 weeks?    
    
    
    @jenienb LOL, yeah i am still kinda young. I need 2 tickets. any extras?    
    
    
    OMG! My cracked iPhone 5 screen was actually covered under warranty.It's called single hairline crack and is covered.no tricks or apple care    
    
    
    this now means I have had 3 iPhone 5's in under 3 weeks. Black exchanged for white, then cracked screen replaced…some can't even get 1?    
    
    
    @rsmoz I dropped it from about 1 foot off the ground and a small crack appeared. looked like under glass: http://forums.macrumors.com/showthread.php?t=1060998 …    
    
    
    @rsmoz from black to white? Within 30 days from apple not hard at all. Just bring it in and they swap it. Assuming they have stock.    
    
    
    @rsmoz for crack screen, genius bar appt    
    
    
    @jeff148apps LOL…of course I am, I'm a friend of Jeff Scott's! That's all I tell them every time    
    
    
    @jenienb LOL…I thought your mom said you could jack the upgrade.    
    
    
    @jenienb I still can't believe you don't Glee….you should catch up and watch...    
    
    
    So it is confirmed by me. All 3 iPhone 5's I had all came with a crazy robotic Siri voice. After restore she sounded like herself.    
    
    
    @atjamie Wasn't it jay betting money it wasn't happening. LOL    
    
    
    @kimkimcachoo Nice.  Yeah none in Los Angeles. Even Sprint is sold out ;)    
    
    
    @christyxcore At least you have wifi at home, LOL.  If you can only pick LTE while out or at hime, while out is better    
    
    
    @atjamie @macmixing LOL…Dam if it's your life we're talking about, I would at least get Apple Care PLUS!    
    
    
    @atjamie can u find me asap please    
    
    
    “@Behance: All QR codes look alike…until now. ILLUSTRATED QR CODES: http://on.be.net/QTlgRr ” yup that's me retweeting a prompted tweet    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ wow. Really coming all the way back to iOS huh? Welcome back!    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ can you send me your wallpaper. I like it.    
    
    
    @tchaten don't forget: http://youtu.be/p6FKKpMH5eA     
    
    
    Epic Hearts, the new FREE fantasy RPG for iOS, is partnering with us to give away an iPod Touch to our loyal readers! http://splur.gy/OFGp4C     
    
    
    Can I win an iPod touch in my own event LOL http://splur.gy/OFGp4C     
    
    
    @w1kedZ LOL, I won't tell if you won't    
    
    
    @w1kedZ alright. Driving to lunch now. I will after    
    
    
    The best part of the presidential debates is watching the candidates fight the mediators.    
    
    
    @superpixels Hey you're in our neck of the woods!  If you wanna grab a drink or some lunch with some dudes from @AppAdvice let me know!    
    
    
    @tchaten you are finally believing in the product that I heard was "fake fake fakety fake" lol /@ndyfaust    
    
    
    @superpixels too bad! We're going to hold you to it next time.    
    
    
    @robinrhys lol! Boredom! Come work. We have appisodes to do woman! Until then, say hi to Joey for me. I miss her    
    
    
    @llofte my cousin is having issues. Need any info? I can ask him    
    
    
    @llofte ah nice! I should have checked the link!    
    
    
    Anyone going to be in San Jose for apple event on Tuesday and want to meet up?    
    
    
    @w1kedZ looks sweet!!! Congrats. Awesome turn of events.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @heatherblansett @christyxcore hey Andy. I live in CA and love Vegas. Feel free to email me    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @heatherblansett @christyxcore oh and congrats!    
    
    
    Doesn't feel very apple, but we're here! pic.twitter.com/gvnsVhYK    
    
    
    #GoDodgers    
    
    
    @jeff148apps congrats on the win. You coming to the show tomorrow?    
    
    
    @jenienb go #HEAT    
    
    
    @jeff148apps yes!!! @juviwhale @dubbalubagis and in are in San Jose. Tyler will be live blogging. We'll look for you.    
    
    
    I think Apple just killed the iPad. I don't see the the value proposition of the 4th gen iPad mini, I know @reneritchie will disagree    
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagr.am/p/RIsIEosUF6/     
    
    
    @jeff148apps @juviwhale @dubbalubagis lunch?    
    
    
    @reneritchie have you heard any more info on how much apple will charge to replace broken iPhone 5 screen?Saw your post last month.Any info?    
    
    
    @reneritchie yes. No apple care+    
    
    
    @chasesclouds my phone is okay. I didn't crack it. Just trying to get info so I can give people buying advice on apple care    
    
    
    @macmixing I been working on mine all day: pic.twitter.com/2ltIvERL    
    
    
    @jeff148apps Sadly I think it's more of a bad supply issue than a cagy demand issue    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @jeff148apps naw it was nov. 2nd here    
    
    
    @christyxcore still time for black on first day…i ordered let so i gotta wait =(    
    
    
    It's a tweet costume!!! pic.twitter.com/C05liFjY    
    
    
    @jenienb did you do it?!!!    
    
    
    @jenienb do you use Rdio?  Spotify?    
    
    
    