Yepee! My first tweet!    
    
    
    Web game engine without Flash, only standards: http://bit.ly/7wjguz    
    
    
    #youtube "This video is not available in your country due to copyright restrictions" ¬_¬    
    
    
    Writing an article on global illumination algorithms and techniques.    
    
    
    Starcraft 2: Even more similar to Warhammer 40k.    
    
    
    Teach Yourself C++ in 21 Days. http://bit.ly/9g9ghw    
    
    
    Back to work!    
    
    
    ¿Una Constitucional neoliberal sin referéndum? http://menea.me/sxn1  via @meneame_net    
    
    
    http://www.eljueves.es/2011/08/24/zapatero_propone_modificar_constitucion_para_limitar_deficit_publico_rajoy_apoya.html …    
    
    
    Dilbert Daily Strip: 2011-08-25: http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2011-08-25/ …    
    
    
    Now selling photos on Getty Images http://bit.ly/ciJGHO    
    
    
    Vaya tela http://robberymaps.com/map.html#lt=41.379803 …&ln=2.172611&z=1&k=2&a=1&tab=1    
    
    
    @guxlightyear @Catatoonics Siempre tomo Chufi, tendré que probar la Carrefour.    
    
    
    Don't dare to create a GL_TEXTURE_CUBE_MAP with non square of 4 faces. The driver of the Nexus S crashes on tex creation. Mem align issues.    
    
    
    Environment mapping working now. Cube map downloaded from http://www.xsibase.com/forum/index.php?board=29;action=d … http://twitpic.com/6en0s2     
    
    
    Some issues solved. Different cubemap downloaded from hazelwhorley. http://twitpic.com/6fdgw9     
    
    
    Just discovered and fixed an old bug in the math core that mirrored the whole scene along the X axis.    
    
    
    I have finished the input system at last. Flexible, robust and works like a charm. #android    
    
    
    Bye, Google Desktop http://googledesktop.blogspot.com/2011/09/google-desktop-update.html …    
    
    
    @idaho06 A mí el wifi no me alcanza a la terraza xD    
    
    
    New picture on sale. Get it now! http://www.gettyimages.es/detail/124368745 …    
    
    
    The lack of proper multithreading support in OpenGL is exasperating.    
    
    
    Dilbert Daily Strip: 2011-08-14: http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2011-08-14/ …    
    
    
    Models with multiple materials applied are working now    
    
    
    @JuanKRuiz Jaja, yaya, estaba bromeando :D    
    
    
    Bitcasa - Infinite Storage on Your Desktop - Sign up for Beta now! http://www.bitcasa.com/beta-signup?share=562370881 … via @Bitcasa    
    
    
    Google Dart to “ultimately ... replace JavaScript”... http://www.2ality.com/2011/09/google-dart.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    "All of your hard work, regardless of how well it is intended, is for naught if it results in a pile of rubbage." - Bryce's Law    
    
    
    Impressive: http://bit.ly/b56wK2    
    
    
    @guxlightyear Well, they used WebGL, very similar to OpenGL ES 2.0, also defined by the Khronos Group.    
    
    
    @ddavity http://twitpic.com/6r2su0  - there be dragons...    
    
    
    Mi instituto en la prensa: http://www.20minutos.es/noticia/1170284/0/profesora/frances-madrid/no-sabe-frances/ …    
    
    
    European Users Overwhelm Facebook With Data Requests: http://bit.ly/n2zJ4K     
    
    
    Just received the OTA update to Android 2.3.6.    
    
    
    @kikogolk http://twitpic.com/6sxle4  - Nunca conseguí pasar del pimer nivel del Abu Simbel Profanation    
    
    
    Automatic mipmap generation. System-wide trilinear filtering enabled for compliant textures. http://twitpic.com/6u5ami     
    
    
    Android 2.2 Java API doesn't support VBOs. Someone forgot to wrap two C calls. Will have to wait until 2.3+ share grow way larger than 2.2.    
    
    
    Now let's implement automatic tangent and binormal vector generation on the OBJ model loader...    
    
    
    Normal mapping fully working. Up to three lights per material. http://twitpic.com/6z6ssb     
    
    
    Now working on cel shading    
    
    
    Cel shading implemented. Single-pass viewing angle based outline. http://twitpic.com/6zp7fx     
    
    
    Shader frenzy http://twitpic.com/707n78     
    
    
    Grand Tour of Closet-Sized Crew Quarters in Space http://www.universetoday.com/81424/grand-tour-of-closet-sized-crew-quarters-in-space/ … via @diythemes    
    
    
    First Private Spacecraft In Orbit After Perfect Launch (Updated) http://gizmodo.com/5709153/  via @gizmodo    
    
    
    Just left my current job. Interesting time ahead.    
    
    
    Reader Merging With Google+: http://bit.ly/rdpwmR     
    
    
    The first version of the text engine is working now http://twitpic.com/744g1q     
    
    
    Testing a small quake-like scene modeled in Blender. Textures extracted from a Tenebrae map by Willi Hammes. http://twitpic.com/74vybl     
    
    
    Lowering the specular exponent produces better visuals. http://twitpic.com/74wfn0     
    
    
    @idaho06 ¡Felicidades!    
    
    
    @kikogolk Alone in the Dark 2, Doom    
    
    
    Cubemap-based reflection modulated by fresnel factor and a checkerboard pattern intensity map. http://twitpic.com/77n5tp     
    
    
    The Phong+Bump+FresnelReflection shader is finished. Fast test with a model downloaded from Blender Swap. http://twitpic.com/78e8xw     
    
    
    Atontaus in Town http://goo.gl/fb/rPx1L    
    
    
    Simple earth test. Layer 1: Diffuse+Specular+Normal. Layer 2: Diffuse cloud map, with alpha channel. http://twitpic.com/7bk2sx     
    
    
    Excellent tool for exploring OpenGL blending options: http://www.andersriggelsen.dk/glblendfunc.php     
    
    
    Solid color can b defined instead of textures. New feat thx 2 d major rewrite of d materials system in progress. http://twitpic.com/7ewxe4     
    
    
    @valleruben Si solo fuera una persona...    
    
    
    Emission maps for materials (look at the ceiling):  http://twitpic.com/7fatyf     
    
    
    @ordend ¡Suerte!    
    
    
    When using shaders don't forget to set all the uniforms on your GL code. All kind of weird unrelated things could happen if you don't.    
    
    
    Parallax mapping, first take. Working on tangent space. http://twitpic.com/7hff37     
    
    
    Some specular added to enhance the effect. Wet bricks all over the place. http://twitpic.com/7hipqv     
    
    
    City lights at night http://twitpic.com/7hywg4     
    
    
    New planet atmosphere shader. Cheap scattering simulation. Color and opacity configurable via 1D texture. http://twitpic.com/7i23u7     
    
    
    @kikogolk Descargando las tengo ya.    
    
    
    Java generics are so ill-conceived that are almost unusable, except for the most trivial cases.    
    
    
    When using alpha-blended camera-plane-oriented billboards sort by distance to the plane instead of distance to the camera.    
    
    
    The information on random point picking at MathWorld is very useful for particle emitters creation and random sampling http://mathworld.wolfram.com/topics/RandomPointPicking.html …    
    
    
    Fire, Snow, Explosions... the brand new particle system is working ^_^ http://twitpic.com/7m8v3q     
    
    
    @ID_AA_Carmack Drink more water!    
    
    
    Live_ISS_Stream - NASAtelevision http://www.ustream.tv/channel/live-iss-stream …    
    
    
    I, for one, #hate when after following a tutorial I get completely different results    
    
    
    Inside Search: Showing some love to math lovers http://insidesearch.blogspot.com/2011/12/showing-some-love-to-math-lovers.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Dilbert Daily Strip: 2011-11-04: http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2011-11-04/ …    
    
    
    #Android "Starting with 2.2, the #NDK enables debugging native code on production devices" Yepee!    
    
    
    The first time you copy code from one class to another one you know you have to refactor and extract this reusable piece of code.    
    
    
    I've just finished the stand alone scene graph renderer. Different types of scene graphs can be changed on demand.    
    
    
    #youtube #vevo "who has blocked it in your country on copyright grounds" FUUUUUUUUUUUU!    
    
    
    Here's What People Look at on Facebook Brand Pages http://mashable.com/2011/12/14/eyetracking-facebook-brand-pages/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Daily Wrap: Microsoft's Apology for IE and More by @duzins http://rww.to/rsaqDC  via @RWW    
    
    
    The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey – See the trailer http://trailers.apple.com/trailers/wb/thehobbit/ …    
    
    
    Static Code Analysis http://altdevblogaday.com/2011/12/24/static-code-analysis/ …    
    
    
    FindBugs has shown some not noticed hard to find bugs in our code base. And it's free.    
    
    
    Mi calle parece Vietnam    
    
    
    Integrar Google Chrome en KDE http://goo.gl/fb/muqNR    
    
    
    #ComparteCultura: http://wp.me/pfKuH-298     
    
    
    Fog is supported now (exp2). No impact in performance so far.    
    
    
    I underestimated the amount of work to be spent on content creation tools.    
    
    
    Tools: Material Creator. 12 hours coding sprint. http://twitpic.com/85qii5     
    
    
    @idaho06 It's a tool to define parameters for the generator wich resides in the Android engine. Shaders are generated & compiled on demand.    
    
    
    L.A. Noire: The Technology Behind Performance http://www.gametrailers.com/video/developer-diary-l-a-noire/708504 …    
    
    
    The #Android Matrix.invertM() method internally allocates 448 bytes. Several uses per frame in real time and the GC goes crazy.    
    
    
    @ruben3d My previous post is no longer true on Android 4.0.    
    
    
    Discarding fragments early on alpha test reduces the performance impact of the branch. Still too costly to use on the full scene. Use wisely    
    
    
    WebGL now in Beta: here comes the 3D web! http://bit.ly/dOX0tq    
    
    
    Tools: Model Viewer. http://twitpic.com/87yo7j     
    
    
    A autoemplearse: http://www.navegapolis.net/content/view/1050/53/ …    
    
    
    I support #wikipediablackout! Show your support here http://tinyurl.com/7vq4o8g     
    
    
    New Blender free and open short film. Help the project! http://www.blender3d.org/e-shop/product_info_n.php?products_id=143 …    
    
    
    #Chrome 9 #WebGL Aquarium 1000 fishes 50+ FPS http://www.chromeexperiments.com/detail/webgl-aquarium …    
    
    
    In-game graphic level modification is working. It freezes 200ms while compiling new shaders. Now the framerate vary between 18 and 55 fps.    
    
    
    The heavy fragmentation of #Android devices is driving me nuts. Can't find two GPUs with the same load of issues and bugs.    
    
    
    @kikogolk http://identi.ca/     
    
    
    The GalaxyS2 graphic driver does a pretty good job removing death code from shaders. Sadly it forgets to notify which uniforms were removed.    
    
    
    View frustum culling has dramatically improved performance in some situations.    
    
    
    With multitouch support the soft feature freeze finally arrived to the engine. Bugfixes and urgent small changes from now on.    
    
    
    Facebook Files for $5 Billion IPO http://mashable.com/2012/02/01/facebook-files-ipo/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Misteriously the Nexus S is limited to 300 GL drawing calls per frame. After that the ZBuffer fails. Could not reproduce on other devices.    
    
    
    Ended up building my own GL based widget toolkit.    
    
    
    Listening to the album Irish Jig by Gwendal #nowplaying #tunesday http://tny.gs/zOYVAf     
    
    
    Coder facts! http://coderfacts.com/post/15503997383/analista-sr-experiencia-en-uml-ms-project … via @coderfacts    
    
    
    The XML Schema editor in Eclipse is great. Editing XSD files never was so fast.    
    
    
    Working again...    
    
    
    @XaV1uzz Yo fui de http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/ZXSpectrum48k.jpg …    
    
    
    I tried to watch Game of Thrones and this is what happened - The Oatmeal http://theoatmeal.com/comics/game_of_thrones … via @Oatmeal    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/0YpcacekDSY?a  TRAILER DE JESUCRISTO 2009    
    
    
    @ddavity ¿Qué terminal es?    
    
    
    @ddavity Una app    
    
    
    @ddavity Pasame un mail por privado.    
    
    
    @alberticomf No tiene mala pinta    
    
    
    Just fixed a bug in the perspective matrix calculation that went unnoticed for 11 months :O    
    
    
    I wish you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!!    
    
    
    Emprender o emigrar http://www.equiposytalento.com/noticias/2012/03/30/espana-vive-una-fuga-de-ingenieros-informaticos-debido-a-sus-malas-condiciones …    
    
    
    The hardest decision of my childhood http://randomgag.com/funny-image/6183/lol.html …    
    
    
    My Nexus S got the official Android 4.0 ICS update. Lots of eye candy.    
    
    
    Menus almost ready for release http://twitpic.com/9621mf     
    
    
    He marcado como favorito un vídeo de @YouTube. http://youtu.be/qURei6svd90?a  Doom II OST - Map 01,15 - Running from Ev    
    
    
    C'mon, who else does this? http://randomgag.com/funny-image/32509/lol.html …    
    
    
    The in-game tutorial is working. Everything almost ready for release.    
    
    
    Hard code freeze! Urgent bugfixes only from now on until release.    
    
    
    The PowerVR SGX 530 fails painting alpha-blended non-square mipmaps.    
    
    
    @kikogolk @elpixelilustre Spectrum 48k forever <3    
    
    
    City Lights - http://bit.ly/hPS4hE (via @NASA)    
    
    
    According to @klout, my Klout score is 45. How influential are you? http://klout.com/user/ruben3d/score-analysis?n=tw&v=klout_score …    
    
    
    Fibonacci spiral http://bit.ly/JxLxSc     
    
    
    An update for Aerial Wild Adventure is in the oven... #android    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video from @bass_boss_ http://youtu.be/Hppky-V77B8?a  Patten Live @ LEV Festival 2012    
    
    
    Preparing a course on Windows Phone 7 #wp7    
    
    
    Carmageddon: Reincarnation by Stainless Games — Kickstarter http://kck.st/IFBdGm  via @kickstarter    
    
    
    Something is cooking in the oven. Smells like... Chapter 2 with 10 new levels! https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tapasinteractive.aerialwildadventurefree … #android #free #game    
    
    
    I'm greatly surprised. The nvidia Tegra 3 executing complex shaders on complex scenes at 720p is astonishing. @NVIDIATegra    
    
    
    The Tegra 3 GPU driver crashes when using gl_FrontFacing on a shader on the Asus Transformer Prime.    
    
    
    I just backed Carmageddon: Reincarnation on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/IFBdGm     
    
    
    #KDE SC 4.5.0 released!    
    
    
    Carmageddon Mobile http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jKjEfS0IRT8&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Awesome http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hgll-XTqcS4 …    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/XHmf_WWFLWg?a  Aerial Wild Adventure - Trailer #1    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/32fRW5AIcwk?a  Aerial Wild Adventure - Trailer #2    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/nIwrgAnx6Q8?a  O Fortuna Misheard Lyrics (Animated)    
    
    
    Defending Free Software against Oracle's attack http://bit.ly/crviSQ    
    
    
    631. Mea culpa http://shar.es/svM8J     
    
    
    About Microsoft Surface and Ipad. So true. http://yfrog.com/mgkcjxlj     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/tTXUuDiThzA?a  Hooverphonic - Vinegar & Salt (live @ Benicàssin Festival)    
    
    
    Arithmetic for Beginners http://abstrusegoose.com/474     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/P5_GlAOCHyE?a  Planet Earth seen from space (Full HD 1080p) ORIGINAL    
    
    
    Love making games pic.twitter.com/UhwEL7YM    
    
    
    Say god particle one more time http://shar.es/t1DXi     
    
    
    #Tron Legacy: Avoid watching it at all cost    
    
    
    Aerial Wild Adventure http://goo.gl/fb/Qguzh     
    
    
    Random terrain and cave generator, first take. http://twitpic.com/a68lgm     
    
    
    "This video contains content from UMG. It is not available in your country." FFFUUUU-    
    
    
    Just discovered my 6 year-old C++ build system doesn't work anymore with gcc 4.6.1. The order of parameters matters for the linker. Easy fix    
    
    
    It appears that the cellular automata wasn't necessary after all for pleasing results on the random terrain generator.    
    
    
    Physical assault by McDonald's for wearing Digital Eye Glass http://eyetap.blogspot.com/2012/07/physical-assault-by-mcdonalds-for.html … @McDonalds    
    
    
    Testing Windows phone 7    
    
    
    @ChickenTyping Moby Dick    
    
    
    Microsoft reports first public loss. Google reports stronger than expected earnings http://gu.com/p/396ef/tw     
    
    
    My Nexus S has been updated to Android 4.1 Jelly Bean. Better widget management, some performance improvement, Google Now.    
    
    
    Developer console crash reports: "java.lang.RuntimeException: eglSwapBuffers failed: EGL_SUCCESS" What the...?? Makes no sense.    
    
    
    Earth from space (#Blender 2.63 #Cycles) http://flic.kr/p/cDmFeJ     
    
    
    Amazing showcase of #HTML5 capabilities: http://bit.ly/aUFV3d (Google Chrome experiment)    
    
    
    Android beats iPhone in number of total users for first time http://androidcommunity.com/android-beats-iphone-in-number-of-total-users-for-first-time-20110107/ …    
    
    
    @iverona ¡Evitalo si puedes!    
    
    
    Android 2.3 Gingerbread Ported to iPhone 3G http://androidcommunity.com/android-2-3-gingerbread-ported-to-iphone-3g-video-20110108/ …    
    
    
    46-inch panel accepts unlimited touch inputs http://www.engadget.com/2011/01/08/multitouch-ltds-46-inch-panel-accepts-unlimited-touch-inputs-w/ …    
    
    
    Ya llegó mi Nexus 7 pic.twitter.com/3BMl54ij    
    
    
    Google Nexus7 tablet: Connect Nexus 7 to Linux via MTP using USB http://www.nexus7tablethelp.com/2012/07/connect-nexus-7-to-linux-via-mtp-using.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The World http://twitpic.com/3okgse     
    
    
    @ddavity Suerte, y que se dé bien :D    
    
    
    @notch I felt a great disturbance in the Force, as if millions of clean coders suddenly cried out in terror, and were suddenly silenced.    
    
    
    @Sosowski @notch If this is java he can't to that.    
    
    
    @Bitomule @gamevelop "Modern C++ Design: Generic Programming and Design Patterns Applied", Andrei Alexandrescu #LibrosDeveloper    
    
    
    @AnaMathius ¡Menudo robo!    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/-txDHDxklmc?a  Ben Prunty Music - FTL - 24 Rockmen (Battle) FTL Soundtrack    
    
    
    Developers Fork Mandriva Linux, Creating Mageia: http://bit.ly/dluWpb    
    
    
    Modern browsers in real-world benchmark: http://bit.ly/b5YEix    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/GZynD4bx-V8?a  Lluis Llach - L'estaca    
    
    
    That's no moon #iOS6 http://twitpic.com/axxa1j     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/SQngoCBvq3Q?a  Andromeda Software Development - Happiness is Around the Bend    
    
    
    He subido un vídeo de @YouTube (http://youtu.be/hGdx_82GFSM?a  - Earth from space - Blender 2.64 RC2 - 1080p).    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/JE2muDZksP4?a  8.Mozart's Requiem-Lacrimosa (lyrics+translation)    
    
    
    217 points http://html5test.com/ #Chrome 6.0.472.63 #HTML5    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/ExJShWGsAB0?a  Wizorb music - Slime Forest    
    
    
    @kikogolk Ya te daré envidia cuando me pueda descargar mi copia :D    
    
    
    He subido un vídeo de @YouTube (http://youtu.be/UKe2Wa9linU?a  - Earth from space HD 1080p - Realistic Version - Blender 2.64 Cycles).    
    
    
    He subido un vídeo de @YouTube (http://youtu.be/MlQKLZgCjLE?a  - Earth from space HD 1080p - Vintage Version - Blender 2.64 Cycles).    
    
    
    Depth of field implemented! http://flic.kr/p/dnyYKe 
http://flic.kr/p/dnyYQk  #raytracer    
    
    
    The Blender Foundation releases the open movie project Sintel: http://bit.ly/9RDaZH    
    
    
    Horn, published by @zynga, was so poorly localized into Spanish that I wanted to play the English version. Shame I can't choose the language    
    
    
    @kikogolk Yo lo dejé a mitad cansado de padecer.    
    
    
    @gamevelop Mejor    
    
    
    @eleizel ¿Pero qué te ha pasado?    
    
    
    #Windows Vista source #code leaked: http://bit.ly/cnUeWY    
    
    
    #IE marketshare falls below 50% http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/tech/news/internet/IE-marketshare-falls-below-50/articleshow/6692281.cms …    
    
    
    http://Amazon.com  recommends me books I've already purchased from them.    
    
    
    Space scenes created using #Blender #Cycles http://flic.kr/s/aHsjCKpXRd     
    
    
    "This video contains content from WMG and UMG. It is not available in your country." Okay. It's Grooveshark then.    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Zk-q4RD2fP4?a  Santana - Maggot Brain - Kaiser Gold Sounds 96 - São Paulo    
    
    
    CARL SAGAN: Make the most of this life  http://zenpencils.com/comic/carl-sagan-make-the-most-of-this-life/#.UJztEtNDVEQ.twitter …    
    
    
    Cross-Platform C/C++ Development with Eclipse CDT http://twb.io/MpnOZM     
    
    
    "Mathematics for 3D Game Programming and Computer Graphics" by Eric Lengyel is one of the most useful books I've ever had.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/h_gmX9  Both APIs can achieve the same results, but OpenGL. got my vote thanks to cross-platform compatibility. With...    
    
    
    Coded support for VBOs and the FPS are the same. So the bottleneck is still in the fragment shaders and we have space for tons of geometry.    
    
    
    Top+5+reasons+you+should+love+your+ternary+operator+http://wp.me/p10053-1P    
    
    
    Useful tip: you can enter unicode characters within the Inkscape Text Tool by pressing Ctrl+U, the code and then Enter.    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/OD0vMWg1ULE?a  Luciano Pavarotti "Recitar...vesti la giubba" Pagliacci    
    
    
    Sometimes when drawing diagrams you never know if they are easily understandable by other people or not. pic.twitter.com/HrsHqpnz    
    
    
    Cherry coke! pic.twitter.com/g7bvt8Fj    
    
    
    Averaging last frames time deltas for current solved lots of FPS issues but on demand shader compilation is still noticeable on some devices    
    
    
    @gamevelop Veo que todavía no podemos registrarnos :(    
    
    
    Testing my brand new Samsung #NexusS    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/aFjR5t #GoogleDocs launches new #chart maker    
    
    
    Most contradictory comment ever: 5 stars "Is f***ing great never download it piece of s**t unstall this!!!" #android #googleplay    
    
    
    @guxlightyear Yep    
    
    
    @buguibuguibuda Looks great! Make the menus show on mouse over, instead of showing them on mouse click.    
    
    
    @buguibuguibuda The menus at the navbar. I'll take a look into meteor.js when I have some spare time, it looks interesting.    
    
    
    Just upgraded to Fedora 14    
    
    
    @damianfm @elmundoes Menudo fail    
    
    
    @idaho06 Si te sirve, a mí me ha pasado eso a todas las edades.    
    
    
    Apple Promises To Fix Glitches In Map Software By Rearranging Earth's Geography   http://www.theonion.com/video/apple-promises-to-fix-glitches-in-map-software-by,30616/ …    
    
    
    Why Eric Schmidt Left As CEO of Google?: http://bit.ly/fvziqg    
    
    
    @TheJare It happened to me. It turned out that using the real deltatime every frame was a bad idea. Averaging past frames solved it.    
    
    
    @TheJare I keep the GC away from running. It appears that the time between calls to onDrawFrame varies greatly on sequential similar frames.    
    
    
    "Math for Game Developers" series teaching the basics http://www.youtube.com/user/BSVino/featured …    
    
    
    @ddavity Ha durado 10 minutos escasos.    
    
    
    @ArtX365 Great lighting!    
    
    
    Major Samantha Carter creates a virus for Goa'uld controlled Stargates, uses C# #microsoft #msdn cc/@JuanKRuiz pic.twitter.com/irKwplmR    
    
    
    #Android SDK Tools r9 and #ADT 9 just launched... now that's speed coding!    
    
    
    I scored 34 of 50 on the #MSDOS #screenshot challenge: http://tinyurl.com/dos-quiz  @StarfieldSoftUK    
    
    
    WolframAlpha - zoidberg curve http://wolfr.am/XeETK8     
    
    
    @Algunenano ¿Tras completar The Secret of Monkey Island?    
    
    
    Enjoying the new SimCity thanks to @LuisMorens    
    
    
    @aitorciki ¿Chrome zampar memoria? ¡Calumnias! pic.twitter.com/kt2H1M1v5x    
    
    
    #KPackageKit in #Fedora 14 tested on some computers... unstable in all of them.    
    
    
    Camera depth of field running in real-time on an Android device :D http://twitpic.com/cgi224     
    
    
    @MRLia ¿qué te ha pasado?    
    
    
    My raytracer is working now on Windows :D http://twitpic.com/cozn5p     
    
    
    @ID_AA_Carmack Compilation time, and keeping all these data on the application memory data segment at the same time, unless using DLLs.    
    
    
    FTL for $2.49 on gog! http://www.gog.com/gamecard/faster_than_light …    
    
    
    Android Fragmentation Report July 2013 http://opensignal.com/reports/fragmentation-2013/ …    
    
    
    This is geek on some many levels http://codepen.io/TimPietrusky/pen/eHGfj …    
    
    
    Intel CEO: Nokia Should Have Gone With Android http://tech.slashdot.org/story/11/02/18/1535257/?sms_ss=twitter&at_xt=4d5fc25d0365042d,0 …    
    
    
    Ya han llegado mis Sennheiser 439 ^_^ pic.twitter.com/yIEQSLAJDi    
    
    
    @Cibeles_ "This video contains content from NBC Universal, who has blocked it on copyright grounds." u_u    
    
    
    Nokia Sells Qt: http://bit.ly/gOH8Fl    
    
    
    Khronos Releases Final WebGL 1.0 Specification - Khronos Group Press Release http://shar.es/3iDl9     
    
    
    My #SVN is slowly rotting... again    
    
    
    Opinion: How the PC is making consoles look out of date http://www.pcauthority.com.au/?250462    
    
    
    #IE9 still lagging behind http://bit.ly/dYkqlK    
    
    
    What Happened to #Nokia?
http://mobilesoftware.tumblr.com/post/3565611897/what-happened-to-nokia    
    
    
    Game developers want DirectX to 'go away,' says AMD man http://www.engadget.com/2011/03/21/game-develops-want-directx-to-go-away-says-amd-man/ … via @engadget    
    
    
    Carmack: Direct3D is now better than OpenGL http://www.bit-tech.net/news/gaming/2011/03/11/carmack-directx-better-opengl/1 …    
    
    
    Rendimiento IE9-Chrome 10-Firefox 4-Opera 11.01-Safari 5 http://www.muycomputer.com/2011/03/23/comparativa-ie9-chrome-10-firefox-4-opera-11-01-safari-5 …    
    
    
    On Graphics APIs - http://www.gamedev.net/blog/42/entry-2249692-on-apis/    
    
    
    ISO C + Committee Approves C++0x Final Draft: http://bit.ly/fKRTWz    
    
    
    Nokia - No More Symbian Phones After 2012: http://bit.ly/gu2WDj    
    
    
    Coder facts! http://coderfacts.com/post/4216866300/a-todos-se-nos-ha-pasado-por-la-cabeza-alguna-vez … via @coderfacts    
    
    
    I'm very tired of #PHP    
    
    
    Facebook To Be 'Biggest Bank' By 2015: http://bit.ly/e8drud    
    
    
    Dating too Expensive? Get a 'Cloud Girlfriend'  http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2383485,00.asp … via @pcmag    
    
    
    Preview: #webOS 3.0 Beta 1 emulator leak http://www.precentral.net/preview-webos-3-0-beta-1-emulator-exclusive …    
    
    
    Stable #Blender 2.57 released! http://bit.ly/ezCvgL    
    
    
    How to fix any computer - The Oatmeal http://theoatmeal.com/blog/fix_computer … via @Oatmeal    
    
    
    My transformation pipeline for OpenGL ES 2 on #Android is working now :D    
    
    
    Preallocating large static buffers for many short-lived small objects reduces the GC overhead on #Android for real-time applications    
    
    
    After 50 hours of work, my multi-threaded 3D engine prototype for #Android 2.2+ is working :D    
    
    
    "The 30 people who dislike this can deep throat a cactus" Best comment I've read on #Youtube    
    
    
    CryTek For Free: CryEngine 3 SDK and Editor: http://bit.ly/hNP8GX    
    
    
    #PHP Passing and returning hashmaps as parameter lists should be outlawed. Maintenance is driving me crazy    
    
    
    I love debugging concurrent code on Saturday morning    
    
    
    Single-pass smooth transition between frames for animated textures is working now :D    
    
    
    It appears that using a frame of reference (pos,front,up) for cameras and actors is working better than using Euler angles. Easier dynamics.    
    
    
    Google Engineers Deny Hack Exploited Chrome: http://bit.ly/mTbkJu    
    
    
    Coder facts! http://coderfacts.com/post/4561743096  via @coderfacts    
    
    
    Rendering of multiple viewports, cameras and scene graphs is working now ^_^    
    
    
    Ubuntu Switches To OpenStack For Cloud: http://bit.ly/lrQegt    
    
    
    Just finished the OBJ loader. Optimizing the mesh was easier than expected but way slower on my NexusS. Will have to use a custom bin format    
    
    
    Models exported from Blender, downloaded from Blender Swap. http://twitpic.com/50q8sg    
    
    
    Simple phong lighting is working now! http://twitpic.com/522cyc    
    
    
    Specular maps are working.  http://twitpic.com/52nzdi    
    
    
    When working with multiple lights, it is way faster using a shader for each light count than using branching or looping on a single shader.    
    
    
    Microsoft Windows after 25 years: A visual history http://www.networkworld.com/slideshows/2010/110810-microsoft-windows-visual-history.html?ap1=rcb …    
    
    
    8 Free E-Books on C# http://rww.to/lIpieV  via @RWW    
    
    
    Per-pixel. Up to 3 lights + ambient. Performance is better than expected and there's room for some improvement. http://twitpic.com/54aauv    
    
    
    Microsoft has received five times more income from Android than from Windows Phone http://www.asymco.com/2011/05/27/microsoft-has-received-five-times-more-income-from-android-than-from-windows-phone/ …    
    
    
    Doom on the Web http://mzl.la/j2WAvM  via @mozhacks    
    
    
    Building "Windows 8" - Video #1 http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p92QfWOw88I&feature=share …    
    
    
    Debuging math code...    
    
    
    The set of lights contributing to each object is computed and the optimized shader for that set is used. http://twitpic.com/56famt    
    
    
    I felt in love with Thunderbird 5    
    
    
    @ddavity http://www.mozillamessaging.com/en-US/thunderbird/5.0b1/releasenotes/    
    
    
    13 Reasons Why One Developer Dropped Google App Engine http://rww.to/i7FhwA  via @RWW    
    
    
    Silverlight developers rally against Windows 8 plans http://www.itnews.com.au/News/259910,silverlight-developers-rally-against-windows-8-plans.aspx … via @itnews_au    
    
    
    If using quicksort, move to insertion sorting when your subarrays left after pivot selection are small (10-20 elems).    
    
    
    Very useful: http://www.touchtrigonometry.org/     
    
    
    “If I had six hours to cut down trees, I’d spend the first three hours sharpening my axe, and the last three cutting down the trees.”    
    
    
    Common sense http://imgur.com/eoi3d     
    
    
    Pedir http://www.linuxhispano.net/2011/06/21/pedir/ …    
    
    
    Ortographic camera working http://twitpic.com/5exjkm    
    
    
    Simple HUD test http://twitpic.com/5fnzdk    
    
    
    Rendering multiple scenes on multiple viewports http://twitpic.com/5hat08    
    
    
    @ddavity ¡Gracias!    
    
    
    When going mobile, manually unroll all your loops on #shaders. The branch penalties are really high. Got a 5x speed up on Nexus S.    
    
    
    Designing a flexible input system that integrates with 3D picking    
    
    
    @Blag oh my... tell me you have some spare invitations ^_^    
    
    
    Testing #Google+    
    
    
    Source Engine SDK To Be Free: http://bit.ly/j8bnIe     
    
    
    9 Reasons to Switch from Facebook to Google+ http://soc.li/id0fhAL     
    
    
    Just finished the implementation of the Unproject function. Given 2D screen coords produces 3D rays ready for scene intersection checks.    
    
    
    Full screen landscape layout http://twitpic.com/5n3k0o    
    
    
    Dilbert Daily Strip: 2011-07-07: http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2011-07-07/ …    
    
    
    Just substituted my 3 years old Fedora with a fresh Ubuntu install. I'm liking it so far.    
    
    
    Bruce Campbell Confirms New Evil Dead Movie: http://bit.ly/oLF8kT     
    
    
    Adobe Released 64-bit Flash For Linux: http://bit.ly/nWh5e0     
    
    
    Entrevista con Rafael Sanches creador de Recipe Search, Craiglist Notification y Asteroid Tower Defense http://and.roid.es/entrevista-con-rafael-sanches-creador-de-recipe-search-craiglist-notification-y-asteroid-tower-defense.html … via @androides    
    
    
    @ClaudiaTrasto ¡Qué te ha pasado?!?    
    
    
    Wikileaks Moves to Amazon Web Services by @klintron http://rww.to/ewpOhF  via @RWW    
    
    
    @unclebobmartin "Good idea but we don't have time for that" they usually say.    
    
    
    Cambiando de base http://goo.gl/fb/EU1g1    
    
    
    Google Open-Sources NoSQL Database Called LevelDB by @klintron http://rww.to/qrqOLN  via @RWW    
    
    
    The new input system is working for screen events (tap, hold, drag). Now debugging scene and entity events. Won't be ready before vacations.    
    
    
    Android takes almost 50% share of worldwide smart phone market | Canalys http://www.canalys.com/newsroom/android-takes-almost-50-share-worldwide-smart-phone-market …    
    
    
    @ClaudiaTrasto Angry Birds http://www.rovio.com/index.php?page=angry-birds    
    
    
    Yepee! My first tweet!    
    
    
    Web game engine without Flash, only standards: http://bit.ly/7wjguz    
    
    
    #youtube "This video is not available in your country due to copyright restrictions" ¬_¬    
    
    
    Writing an article on global illumination algorithms and techniques.    
    
    
    Starcraft 2: Even more similar to Warhammer 40k.    
    
    
    Teach Yourself C++ in 21 Days. http://bit.ly/9g9ghw    
    
    
    Back to work!    
    
    
    ¿Una Constitucional neoliberal sin referéndum? http://menea.me/sxn1  via @meneame_net    
    
    
    http://www.eljueves.es/2011/08/24/zapatero_propone_modificar_constitucion_para_limitar_deficit_publico_rajoy_apoya.html …    
    
    
    Dilbert Daily Strip: 2011-08-25: http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2011-08-25/ …    
    
    
    Now selling photos on Getty Images http://bit.ly/ciJGHO    
    
    
    Vaya tela http://robberymaps.com/map.html#lt=41.379803 …&ln=2.172611&z=1&k=2&a=1&tab=1    
    
    
    @guxlightyear @Catatoonics Siempre tomo Chufi, tendré que probar la Carrefour.    
    
    
    Don't dare to create a GL_TEXTURE_CUBE_MAP with non square of 4 faces. The driver of the Nexus S crashes on tex creation. Mem align issues.    
    
    
    Environment mapping working now. Cube map downloaded from http://www.xsibase.com/forum/index.php?board=29;action=d … http://twitpic.com/6en0s2     
    
    
    Some issues solved. Different cubemap downloaded from hazelwhorley. http://twitpic.com/6fdgw9     
    
    
    Just discovered and fixed an old bug in the math core that mirrored the whole scene along the X axis.    
    
    
    I have finished the input system at last. Flexible, robust and works like a charm. #android    
    
    
    Bye, Google Desktop http://googledesktop.blogspot.com/2011/09/google-desktop-update.html …    
    
    
    @idaho06 A mí el wifi no me alcanza a la terraza xD    
    
    
    New picture on sale. Get it now! http://www.gettyimages.es/detail/124368745 …    
    
    
    The lack of proper multithreading support in OpenGL is exasperating.    
    
    
    Dilbert Daily Strip: 2011-08-14: http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2011-08-14/ …    
    
    
    Models with multiple materials applied are working now    
    
    
    @JuanKRuiz Jaja, yaya, estaba bromeando :D    
    
    
    Bitcasa - Infinite Storage on Your Desktop - Sign up for Beta now! http://www.bitcasa.com/beta-signup?share=562370881 … via @Bitcasa    
    
    
    Google Dart to “ultimately ... replace JavaScript”... http://www.2ality.com/2011/09/google-dart.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    "All of your hard work, regardless of how well it is intended, is for naught if it results in a pile of rubbage." - Bryce's Law    
    
    
    Impressive: http://bit.ly/b56wK2    
    
    
    @guxlightyear Well, they used WebGL, very similar to OpenGL ES 2.0, also defined by the Khronos Group.    
    
    
    @ddavity http://twitpic.com/6r2su0  - there be dragons...    
    
    
    Mi instituto en la prensa: http://www.20minutos.es/noticia/1170284/0/profesora/frances-madrid/no-sabe-frances/ …    
    
    
    European Users Overwhelm Facebook With Data Requests: http://bit.ly/n2zJ4K     
    
    
    Just received the OTA update to Android 2.3.6.    
    
    
    @kikogolk http://twitpic.com/6sxle4  - Nunca conseguí pasar del pimer nivel del Abu Simbel Profanation    
    
    
    Automatic mipmap generation. System-wide trilinear filtering enabled for compliant textures. http://twitpic.com/6u5ami     
    
    
    Android 2.2 Java API doesn't support VBOs. Someone forgot to wrap two C calls. Will have to wait until 2.3+ share grow way larger than 2.2.    
    
    
    Now let's implement automatic tangent and binormal vector generation on the OBJ model loader...    
    
    
    Normal mapping fully working. Up to three lights per material. http://twitpic.com/6z6ssb     
    
    
    Now working on cel shading    
    
    
    Cel shading implemented. Single-pass viewing angle based outline. http://twitpic.com/6zp7fx     
    
    
    Shader frenzy http://twitpic.com/707n78     
    
    
    Grand Tour of Closet-Sized Crew Quarters in Space http://www.universetoday.com/81424/grand-tour-of-closet-sized-crew-quarters-in-space/ … via @diythemes    
    
    
    First Private Spacecraft In Orbit After Perfect Launch (Updated) http://gizmodo.com/5709153/  via @gizmodo    
    
    
    Just left my current job. Interesting time ahead.    
    
    
    Reader Merging With Google+: http://bit.ly/rdpwmR     
    
    
    The first version of the text engine is working now http://twitpic.com/744g1q     
    
    
    Testing a small quake-like scene modeled in Blender. Textures extracted from a Tenebrae map by Willi Hammes. http://twitpic.com/74vybl     
    
    
    Lowering the specular exponent produces better visuals. http://twitpic.com/74wfn0     
    
    
    @idaho06 ¡Felicidades!    
    
    
    @kikogolk Alone in the Dark 2, Doom    
    
    
    Cubemap-based reflection modulated by fresnel factor and a checkerboard pattern intensity map. http://twitpic.com/77n5tp     
    
    
    The Phong+Bump+FresnelReflection shader is finished. Fast test with a model downloaded from Blender Swap. http://twitpic.com/78e8xw     
    
    
    Atontaus in Town http://goo.gl/fb/rPx1L    
    
    
    Simple earth test. Layer 1: Diffuse+Specular+Normal. Layer 2: Diffuse cloud map, with alpha channel. http://twitpic.com/7bk2sx     
    
    
    Excellent tool for exploring OpenGL blending options: http://www.andersriggelsen.dk/glblendfunc.php     
    
    
    Solid color can b defined instead of textures. New feat thx 2 d major rewrite of d materials system in progress. http://twitpic.com/7ewxe4     
    
    
    @valleruben Si solo fuera una persona...    
    
    
    Emission maps for materials (look at the ceiling):  http://twitpic.com/7fatyf     
    
    
    @ordend ¡Suerte!    
    
    
    When using shaders don't forget to set all the uniforms on your GL code. All kind of weird unrelated things could happen if you don't.    
    
    
    Parallax mapping, first take. Working on tangent space. http://twitpic.com/7hff37     
    
    
    Some specular added to enhance the effect. Wet bricks all over the place. http://twitpic.com/7hipqv     
    
    
    City lights at night http://twitpic.com/7hywg4     
    
    
    New planet atmosphere shader. Cheap scattering simulation. Color and opacity configurable via 1D texture. http://twitpic.com/7i23u7     
    
    
    @kikogolk Descargando las tengo ya.    
    
    
    Java generics are so ill-conceived that are almost unusable, except for the most trivial cases.    
    
    
    When using alpha-blended camera-plane-oriented billboards sort by distance to the plane instead of distance to the camera.    
    
    
    The information on random point picking at MathWorld is very useful for particle emitters creation and random sampling http://mathworld.wolfram.com/topics/RandomPointPicking.html …    
    
    
    Fire, Snow, Explosions... the brand new particle system is working ^_^ http://twitpic.com/7m8v3q     
    
    
    @ID_AA_Carmack Drink more water!    
    
    
    Live_ISS_Stream - NASAtelevision http://www.ustream.tv/channel/live-iss-stream …    
    
    
    I, for one, #hate when after following a tutorial I get completely different results    
    
    
    Inside Search: Showing some love to math lovers http://insidesearch.blogspot.com/2011/12/showing-some-love-to-math-lovers.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Dilbert Daily Strip: 2011-11-04: http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2011-11-04/ …    
    
    
    #Android "Starting with 2.2, the #NDK enables debugging native code on production devices" Yepee!    
    
    
    The first time you copy code from one class to another one you know you have to refactor and extract this reusable piece of code.    
    
    
    I've just finished the stand alone scene graph renderer. Different types of scene graphs can be changed on demand.    
    
    
    #youtube #vevo "who has blocked it in your country on copyright grounds" FUUUUUUUUUUUU!    
    
    
    Here's What People Look at on Facebook Brand Pages http://mashable.com/2011/12/14/eyetracking-facebook-brand-pages/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Daily Wrap: Microsoft's Apology for IE and More by @duzins http://rww.to/rsaqDC  via @RWW    
    
    
    The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey – See the trailer http://trailers.apple.com/trailers/wb/thehobbit/ …    
    
    
    Static Code Analysis http://altdevblogaday.com/2011/12/24/static-code-analysis/ …    
    
    
    FindBugs has shown some not noticed hard to find bugs in our code base. And it's free.    
    
    
    Mi calle parece Vietnam    
    
    
    Integrar Google Chrome en KDE http://goo.gl/fb/muqNR    
    
    
    #ComparteCultura: http://wp.me/pfKuH-298     
    
    
    Fog is supported now (exp2). No impact in performance so far.    
    
    
    I underestimated the amount of work to be spent on content creation tools.    
    
    
    Tools: Material Creator. 12 hours coding sprint. http://twitpic.com/85qii5     
    
    
    @idaho06 It's a tool to define parameters for the generator wich resides in the Android engine. Shaders are generated & compiled on demand.    
    
    
    L.A. Noire: The Technology Behind Performance http://www.gametrailers.com/video/developer-diary-l-a-noire/708504 …    
    
    
    The #Android Matrix.invertM() method internally allocates 448 bytes. Several uses per frame in real time and the GC goes crazy.    
    
    
    @ruben3d My previous post is no longer true on Android 4.0.    
    
    
    Discarding fragments early on alpha test reduces the performance impact of the branch. Still too costly to use on the full scene. Use wisely    
    
    
    WebGL now in Beta: here comes the 3D web! http://bit.ly/dOX0tq    
    
    
    Tools: Model Viewer. http://twitpic.com/87yo7j     
    
    
    A autoemplearse: http://www.navegapolis.net/content/view/1050/53/ …    
    
    
    I support #wikipediablackout! Show your support here http://tinyurl.com/7vq4o8g     
    
    
    New Blender free and open short film. Help the project! http://www.blender3d.org/e-shop/product_info_n.php?products_id=143 …    
    
    
    #Chrome 9 #WebGL Aquarium 1000 fishes 50+ FPS http://www.chromeexperiments.com/detail/webgl-aquarium …    
    
    
    In-game graphic level modification is working. It freezes 200ms while compiling new shaders. Now the framerate vary between 18 and 55 fps.    
    
    
    The heavy fragmentation of #Android devices is driving me nuts. Can't find two GPUs with the same load of issues and bugs.    
    
    
    @kikogolk http://identi.ca/     
    
    
    The GalaxyS2 graphic driver does a pretty good job removing death code from shaders. Sadly it forgets to notify which uniforms were removed.    
    
    
    View frustum culling has dramatically improved performance in some situations.    
    
    
    With multitouch support the soft feature freeze finally arrived to the engine. Bugfixes and urgent small changes from now on.    
    
    
    Facebook Files for $5 Billion IPO http://mashable.com/2012/02/01/facebook-files-ipo/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Misteriously the Nexus S is limited to 300 GL drawing calls per frame. After that the ZBuffer fails. Could not reproduce on other devices.    
    
    
    Ended up building my own GL based widget toolkit.    
    
    
    Listening to the album Irish Jig by Gwendal #nowplaying #tunesday http://tny.gs/zOYVAf     
    
    
    Coder facts! http://coderfacts.com/post/15503997383/analista-sr-experiencia-en-uml-ms-project … via @coderfacts    
    
    
    The XML Schema editor in Eclipse is great. Editing XSD files never was so fast.    
    
    
    Working again...    
    
    
    @XaV1uzz Yo fui de http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/ZXSpectrum48k.jpg …    
    
    
    I tried to watch Game of Thrones and this is what happened - The Oatmeal http://theoatmeal.com/comics/game_of_thrones … via @Oatmeal    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/0YpcacekDSY?a  TRAILER DE JESUCRISTO 2009    
    
    
    @ddavity ¿Qué terminal es?    
    
    
    @ddavity Una app    
    
    
    @ddavity Pasame un mail por privado.    
    
    
    @alberticomf No tiene mala pinta    
    
    
    Just fixed a bug in the perspective matrix calculation that went unnoticed for 11 months :O    
    
    
    I wish you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!!    
    
    
    Emprender o emigrar http://www.equiposytalento.com/noticias/2012/03/30/espana-vive-una-fuga-de-ingenieros-informaticos-debido-a-sus-malas-condiciones …    
    
    
    The hardest decision of my childhood http://randomgag.com/funny-image/6183/lol.html …    
    
    
    My Nexus S got the official Android 4.0 ICS update. Lots of eye candy.    
    
    
    Menus almost ready for release http://twitpic.com/9621mf     
    
    
    He marcado como favorito un vídeo de @YouTube. http://youtu.be/qURei6svd90?a  Doom II OST - Map 01,15 - Running from Ev    
    
    
    C'mon, who else does this? http://randomgag.com/funny-image/32509/lol.html …    
    
    
    The in-game tutorial is working. Everything almost ready for release.    
    
    
    Hard code freeze! Urgent bugfixes only from now on until release.    
    
    
    The PowerVR SGX 530 fails painting alpha-blended non-square mipmaps.    
    
    
    @kikogolk @elpixelilustre Spectrum 48k forever <3    
    
    
    City Lights - http://bit.ly/hPS4hE (via @NASA)    
    
    
    According to @klout, my Klout score is 45. How influential are you? http://klout.com/user/ruben3d/score-analysis?n=tw&v=klout_score …    
    
    
    Fibonacci spiral http://bit.ly/JxLxSc     
    
    
    An update for Aerial Wild Adventure is in the oven... #android    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video from @bass_boss_ http://youtu.be/Hppky-V77B8?a  Patten Live @ LEV Festival 2012    
    
    
    Preparing a course on Windows Phone 7 #wp7    
    
    
    Carmageddon: Reincarnation by Stainless Games — Kickstarter http://kck.st/IFBdGm  via @kickstarter    
    
    
    Something is cooking in the oven. Smells like... Chapter 2 with 10 new levels! https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tapasinteractive.aerialwildadventurefree … #android #free #game    
    
    
    I'm greatly surprised. The nvidia Tegra 3 executing complex shaders on complex scenes at 720p is astonishing. @NVIDIATegra    
    
    
    The Tegra 3 GPU driver crashes when using gl_FrontFacing on a shader on the Asus Transformer Prime.    
    
    
    I just backed Carmageddon: Reincarnation on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/IFBdGm     
    
    
    #KDE SC 4.5.0 released!    
    
    
    Carmageddon Mobile http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jKjEfS0IRT8&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Awesome http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hgll-XTqcS4 …    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/XHmf_WWFLWg?a  Aerial Wild Adventure - Trailer #1    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/32fRW5AIcwk?a  Aerial Wild Adventure - Trailer #2    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/nIwrgAnx6Q8?a  O Fortuna Misheard Lyrics (Animated)    
    
    
    Defending Free Software against Oracle's attack http://bit.ly/crviSQ    
    
    
    631. Mea culpa http://shar.es/svM8J     
    
    
    About Microsoft Surface and Ipad. So true. http://yfrog.com/mgkcjxlj     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/tTXUuDiThzA?a  Hooverphonic - Vinegar & Salt (live @ Benicàssin Festival)    
    
    
    Arithmetic for Beginners http://abstrusegoose.com/474     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/P5_GlAOCHyE?a  Planet Earth seen from space (Full HD 1080p) ORIGINAL    
    
    
    Love making games pic.twitter.com/UhwEL7YM    
    
    
    Say god particle one more time http://shar.es/t1DXi     
    
    
    #Tron Legacy: Avoid watching it at all cost    
    
    
    Aerial Wild Adventure http://goo.gl/fb/Qguzh     
    
    
    Random terrain and cave generator, first take. http://twitpic.com/a68lgm     
    
    
    "This video contains content from UMG. It is not available in your country." FFFUUUU-    
    
    
    Just discovered my 6 year-old C++ build system doesn't work anymore with gcc 4.6.1. The order of parameters matters for the linker. Easy fix    
    
    
    It appears that the cellular automata wasn't necessary after all for pleasing results on the random terrain generator.    
    
    
    Physical assault by McDonald's for wearing Digital Eye Glass http://eyetap.blogspot.com/2012/07/physical-assault-by-mcdonalds-for.html … @McDonalds    
    
    
    Testing Windows phone 7    
    
    
    @ChickenTyping Moby Dick    
    
    
    Microsoft reports first public loss. Google reports stronger than expected earnings http://gu.com/p/396ef/tw     
    
    
    My Nexus S has been updated to Android 4.1 Jelly Bean. Better widget management, some performance improvement, Google Now.    
    
    
    Developer console crash reports: "java.lang.RuntimeException: eglSwapBuffers failed: EGL_SUCCESS" What the...?? Makes no sense.    
    
    
    Earth from space (#Blender 2.63 #Cycles) http://flic.kr/p/cDmFeJ     
    
    
    Amazing showcase of #HTML5 capabilities: http://bit.ly/aUFV3d (Google Chrome experiment)    
    
    
    Android beats iPhone in number of total users for first time http://androidcommunity.com/android-beats-iphone-in-number-of-total-users-for-first-time-20110107/ …    
    
    
    @iverona ¡Evitalo si puedes!    
    
    
    Android 2.3 Gingerbread Ported to iPhone 3G http://androidcommunity.com/android-2-3-gingerbread-ported-to-iphone-3g-video-20110108/ …    
    
    
    46-inch panel accepts unlimited touch inputs http://www.engadget.com/2011/01/08/multitouch-ltds-46-inch-panel-accepts-unlimited-touch-inputs-w/ …    
    
    
    Ya llegó mi Nexus 7 pic.twitter.com/3BMl54ij    
    
    
    Google Nexus7 tablet: Connect Nexus 7 to Linux via MTP using USB http://www.nexus7tablethelp.com/2012/07/connect-nexus-7-to-linux-via-mtp-using.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The World http://twitpic.com/3okgse     
    
    
    @ddavity Suerte, y que se dé bien :D    
    
    
    @notch I felt a great disturbance in the Force, as if millions of clean coders suddenly cried out in terror, and were suddenly silenced.    
    
    
    @Sosowski @notch If this is java he can't to that.    
    
    
    @Bitomule @gamevelop "Modern C++ Design: Generic Programming and Design Patterns Applied", Andrei Alexandrescu #LibrosDeveloper    
    
    
    @AnaMathius ¡Menudo robo!    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/-txDHDxklmc?a  Ben Prunty Music - FTL - 24 Rockmen (Battle) FTL Soundtrack    
    
    
    Developers Fork Mandriva Linux, Creating Mageia: http://bit.ly/dluWpb    
    
    
    Modern browsers in real-world benchmark: http://bit.ly/b5YEix    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/GZynD4bx-V8?a  Lluis Llach - L'estaca    
    
    
    That's no moon #iOS6 http://twitpic.com/axxa1j     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/SQngoCBvq3Q?a  Andromeda Software Development - Happiness is Around the Bend    
    
    
    He subido un vídeo de @YouTube (http://youtu.be/hGdx_82GFSM?a  - Earth from space - Blender 2.64 RC2 - 1080p).    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/JE2muDZksP4?a  8.Mozart's Requiem-Lacrimosa (lyrics+translation)    
    
    
    217 points http://html5test.com/ #Chrome 6.0.472.63 #HTML5    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/ExJShWGsAB0?a  Wizorb music - Slime Forest    
    
    
    @kikogolk Ya te daré envidia cuando me pueda descargar mi copia :D    
    
    
    He subido un vídeo de @YouTube (http://youtu.be/UKe2Wa9linU?a  - Earth from space HD 1080p - Realistic Version - Blender 2.64 Cycles).    
    
    
    He subido un vídeo de @YouTube (http://youtu.be/MlQKLZgCjLE?a  - Earth from space HD 1080p - Vintage Version - Blender 2.64 Cycles).    
    
    
    Depth of field implemented! http://flic.kr/p/dnyYKe 
http://flic.kr/p/dnyYQk  #raytracer    
    
    
    The Blender Foundation releases the open movie project Sintel: http://bit.ly/9RDaZH    
    
    
    Horn, published by @zynga, was so poorly localized into Spanish that I wanted to play the English version. Shame I can't choose the language    
    
    
    @kikogolk Yo lo dejé a mitad cansado de padecer.    
    
    
    @gamevelop Mejor    
    
    
    @eleizel ¿Pero qué te ha pasado?    
    
    
    #Windows Vista source #code leaked: http://bit.ly/cnUeWY    
    
    
    #IE marketshare falls below 50% http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/tech/news/internet/IE-marketshare-falls-below-50/articleshow/6692281.cms …    
    
    
    http://Amazon.com  recommends me books I've already purchased from them.    
    
    
    Space scenes created using #Blender #Cycles http://flic.kr/s/aHsjCKpXRd     
    
    
    "This video contains content from WMG and UMG. It is not available in your country." Okay. It's Grooveshark then.    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Zk-q4RD2fP4?a  Santana - Maggot Brain - Kaiser Gold Sounds 96 - São Paulo    
    
    
    CARL SAGAN: Make the most of this life  http://zenpencils.com/comic/carl-sagan-make-the-most-of-this-life/#.UJztEtNDVEQ.twitter …    
    
    
    Cross-Platform C/C++ Development with Eclipse CDT http://twb.io/MpnOZM     
    
    
    "Mathematics for 3D Game Programming and Computer Graphics" by Eric Lengyel is one of the most useful books I've ever had.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/h_gmX9  Both APIs can achieve the same results, but OpenGL. got my vote thanks to cross-platform compatibility. With...    
    
    
    Coded support for VBOs and the FPS are the same. So the bottleneck is still in the fragment shaders and we have space for tons of geometry.    
    
    
    Top+5+reasons+you+should+love+your+ternary+operator+http://wp.me/p10053-1P    
    
    
    Useful tip: you can enter unicode characters within the Inkscape Text Tool by pressing Ctrl+U, the code and then Enter.    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/OD0vMWg1ULE?a  Luciano Pavarotti "Recitar...vesti la giubba" Pagliacci    
    
    
    Sometimes when drawing diagrams you never know if they are easily understandable by other people or not. pic.twitter.com/HrsHqpnz    
    
    
    Cherry coke! pic.twitter.com/g7bvt8Fj    
    
    
    Averaging last frames time deltas for current solved lots of FPS issues but on demand shader compilation is still noticeable on some devices    
    
    
    @gamevelop Veo que todavía no podemos registrarnos :(    
    
    
    Testing my brand new Samsung #NexusS    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/aFjR5t #GoogleDocs launches new #chart maker    
    
    
    Most contradictory comment ever: 5 stars "Is f***ing great never download it piece of s**t unstall this!!!" #android #googleplay    
    
    
    @guxlightyear Yep    
    
    
    @buguibuguibuda Looks great! Make the menus show on mouse over, instead of showing them on mouse click.    
    
    
    @buguibuguibuda The menus at the navbar. I'll take a look into meteor.js when I have some spare time, it looks interesting.    
    
    
    Just upgraded to Fedora 14    
    
    
    @damianfm @elmundoes Menudo fail    
    
    
    @idaho06 Si te sirve, a mí me ha pasado eso a todas las edades.    
    
    
    Apple Promises To Fix Glitches In Map Software By Rearranging Earth's Geography   http://www.theonion.com/video/apple-promises-to-fix-glitches-in-map-software-by,30616/ …    
    
    
    Why Eric Schmidt Left As CEO of Google?: http://bit.ly/fvziqg    
    
    
    @TheJare It happened to me. It turned out that using the real deltatime every frame was a bad idea. Averaging past frames solved it.    
    
    
    @TheJare I keep the GC away from running. It appears that the time between calls to onDrawFrame varies greatly on sequential similar frames.    
    
    
    "Math for Game Developers" series teaching the basics http://www.youtube.com/user/BSVino/featured …    
    
    
    @ddavity Ha durado 10 minutos escasos.    
    
    
    @ArtX365 Great lighting!    
    
    
    Major Samantha Carter creates a virus for Goa'uld controlled Stargates, uses C# #microsoft #msdn cc/@JuanKRuiz pic.twitter.com/irKwplmR    
    
    
    #Android SDK Tools r9 and #ADT 9 just launched... now that's speed coding!    
    
    
    I scored 34 of 50 on the #MSDOS #screenshot challenge: http://tinyurl.com/dos-quiz  @StarfieldSoftUK    
    
    
    WolframAlpha - zoidberg curve http://wolfr.am/XeETK8     
    
    
    @Algunenano ¿Tras completar The Secret of Monkey Island?    
    
    
    Enjoying the new SimCity thanks to @LuisMorens    
    
    
    @aitorciki ¿Chrome zampar memoria? ¡Calumnias! pic.twitter.com/kt2H1M1v5x    
    
    
    #KPackageKit in #Fedora 14 tested on some computers... unstable in all of them.    
    
    
    Camera depth of field running in real-time on an Android device :D http://twitpic.com/cgi224     
    
    
    @MRLia ¿qué te ha pasado?    
    
    
    My raytracer is working now on Windows :D http://twitpic.com/cozn5p     
    
    
    @ID_AA_Carmack Compilation time, and keeping all these data on the application memory data segment at the same time, unless using DLLs.    
    
    
    FTL for $2.49 on gog! http://www.gog.com/gamecard/faster_than_light …    
    
    
    Android Fragmentation Report July 2013 http://opensignal.com/reports/fragmentation-2013/ …    
    
    
    This is geek on some many levels http://codepen.io/TimPietrusky/pen/eHGfj …    
    
    
    Intel CEO: Nokia Should Have Gone With Android http://tech.slashdot.org/story/11/02/18/1535257/?sms_ss=twitter&at_xt=4d5fc25d0365042d,0 …    
    
    
    Ya han llegado mis Sennheiser 439 ^_^ pic.twitter.com/yIEQSLAJDi    
    
    
    @Cibeles_ "This video contains content from NBC Universal, who has blocked it on copyright grounds." u_u    
    
    
    Nokia Sells Qt: http://bit.ly/gOH8Fl    
    
    
    Khronos Releases Final WebGL 1.0 Specification - Khronos Group Press Release http://shar.es/3iDl9     
    
    
    My #SVN is slowly rotting... again    
    
    
    Opinion: How the PC is making consoles look out of date http://www.pcauthority.com.au/?250462    
    
    
    #IE9 still lagging behind http://bit.ly/dYkqlK    
    
    
    What Happened to #Nokia?
http://mobilesoftware.tumblr.com/post/3565611897/what-happened-to-nokia    
    
    
    Game developers want DirectX to 'go away,' says AMD man http://www.engadget.com/2011/03/21/game-develops-want-directx-to-go-away-says-amd-man/ … via @engadget    
    
    
    Carmack: Direct3D is now better than OpenGL http://www.bit-tech.net/news/gaming/2011/03/11/carmack-directx-better-opengl/1 …    
    
    
    Rendimiento IE9-Chrome 10-Firefox 4-Opera 11.01-Safari 5 http://www.muycomputer.com/2011/03/23/comparativa-ie9-chrome-10-firefox-4-opera-11-01-safari-5 …    
    
    
    On Graphics APIs - http://www.gamedev.net/blog/42/entry-2249692-on-apis/    
    
    
    ISO C + Committee Approves C++0x Final Draft: http://bit.ly/fKRTWz    
    
    
    Nokia - No More Symbian Phones After 2012: http://bit.ly/gu2WDj    
    
    
    Coder facts! http://coderfacts.com/post/4216866300/a-todos-se-nos-ha-pasado-por-la-cabeza-alguna-vez … via @coderfacts    
    
    
    I'm very tired of #PHP    
    
    
    Facebook To Be 'Biggest Bank' By 2015: http://bit.ly/e8drud    
    
    
    Dating too Expensive? Get a 'Cloud Girlfriend'  http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2383485,00.asp … via @pcmag    
    
    
    Preview: #webOS 3.0 Beta 1 emulator leak http://www.precentral.net/preview-webos-3-0-beta-1-emulator-exclusive …    
    
    
    Stable #Blender 2.57 released! http://bit.ly/ezCvgL    
    
    
    How to fix any computer - The Oatmeal http://theoatmeal.com/blog/fix_computer … via @Oatmeal    
    
    
    My transformation pipeline for OpenGL ES 2 on #Android is working now :D    
    
    
    Preallocating large static buffers for many short-lived small objects reduces the GC overhead on #Android for real-time applications    
    
    
    After 50 hours of work, my multi-threaded 3D engine prototype for #Android 2.2+ is working :D    
    
    
    "The 30 people who dislike this can deep throat a cactus" Best comment I've read on #Youtube    
    
    
    CryTek For Free: CryEngine 3 SDK and Editor: http://bit.ly/hNP8GX    
    
    
    #PHP Passing and returning hashmaps as parameter lists should be outlawed. Maintenance is driving me crazy    
    
    
    I love debugging concurrent code on Saturday morning    
    
    
    Single-pass smooth transition between frames for animated textures is working now :D    
    
    
    It appears that using a frame of reference (pos,front,up) for cameras and actors is working better than using Euler angles. Easier dynamics.    
    
    
    Google Engineers Deny Hack Exploited Chrome: http://bit.ly/mTbkJu    
    
    
    Coder facts! http://coderfacts.com/post/4561743096  via @coderfacts    
    
    
    Rendering of multiple viewports, cameras and scene graphs is working now ^_^    
    
    
    Ubuntu Switches To OpenStack For Cloud: http://bit.ly/lrQegt    
    
    
    Just finished the OBJ loader. Optimizing the mesh was easier than expected but way slower on my NexusS. Will have to use a custom bin format    
    
    
    Models exported from Blender, downloaded from Blender Swap. http://twitpic.com/50q8sg    
    
    
    Simple phong lighting is working now! http://twitpic.com/522cyc    
    
    
    Specular maps are working.  http://twitpic.com/52nzdi    
    
    
    When working with multiple lights, it is way faster using a shader for each light count than using branching or looping on a single shader.    
    
    
    Microsoft Windows after 25 years: A visual history http://www.networkworld.com/slideshows/2010/110810-microsoft-windows-visual-history.html?ap1=rcb …    
    
    
    8 Free E-Books on C# http://rww.to/lIpieV  via @RWW    
    
    
    Per-pixel. Up to 3 lights + ambient. Performance is better than expected and there's room for some improvement. http://twitpic.com/54aauv    
    
    
    Microsoft has received five times more income from Android than from Windows Phone http://www.asymco.com/2011/05/27/microsoft-has-received-five-times-more-income-from-android-than-from-windows-phone/ …    
    
    
    Doom on the Web http://mzl.la/j2WAvM  via @mozhacks    
    
    
    Building "Windows 8" - Video #1 http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p92QfWOw88I&feature=share …    
    
    
    Debuging math code...    
    
    
    The set of lights contributing to each object is computed and the optimized shader for that set is used. http://twitpic.com/56famt    
    
    
    I felt in love with Thunderbird 5    
    
    
    @ddavity http://www.mozillamessaging.com/en-US/thunderbird/5.0b1/releasenotes/    
    
    
    13 Reasons Why One Developer Dropped Google App Engine http://rww.to/i7FhwA  via @RWW    
    
    
    Silverlight developers rally against Windows 8 plans http://www.itnews.com.au/News/259910,silverlight-developers-rally-against-windows-8-plans.aspx … via @itnews_au    
    
    
    If using quicksort, move to insertion sorting when your subarrays left after pivot selection are small (10-20 elems).    
    
    
    Very useful: http://www.touchtrigonometry.org/     
    
    
    “If I had six hours to cut down trees, I’d spend the first three hours sharpening my axe, and the last three cutting down the trees.”    
    
    
    Common sense http://imgur.com/eoi3d     
    
    
    Pedir http://www.linuxhispano.net/2011/06/21/pedir/ …    
    
    
    Ortographic camera working http://twitpic.com/5exjkm    
    
    
    Simple HUD test http://twitpic.com/5fnzdk    
    
    
    Rendering multiple scenes on multiple viewports http://twitpic.com/5hat08    
    
    
    @ddavity ¡Gracias!    
    
    
    When going mobile, manually unroll all your loops on #shaders. The branch penalties are really high. Got a 5x speed up on Nexus S.    
    
    
    Designing a flexible input system that integrates with 3D picking    
    
    
    @Blag oh my... tell me you have some spare invitations ^_^    
    
    
    Testing #Google+    
    
    
    Source Engine SDK To Be Free: http://bit.ly/j8bnIe     
    
    
    9 Reasons to Switch from Facebook to Google+ http://soc.li/id0fhAL     
    
    
    Just finished the implementation of the Unproject function. Given 2D screen coords produces 3D rays ready for scene intersection checks.    
    
    
    Full screen landscape layout http://twitpic.com/5n3k0o    
    
    
    Dilbert Daily Strip: 2011-07-07: http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2011-07-07/ …    
    
    
    Just substituted my 3 years old Fedora with a fresh Ubuntu install. I'm liking it so far.    
    
    
    Bruce Campbell Confirms New Evil Dead Movie: http://bit.ly/oLF8kT     
    
    
    Adobe Released 64-bit Flash For Linux: http://bit.ly/nWh5e0     
    
    
    Entrevista con Rafael Sanches creador de Recipe Search, Craiglist Notification y Asteroid Tower Defense http://and.roid.es/entrevista-con-rafael-sanches-creador-de-recipe-search-craiglist-notification-y-asteroid-tower-defense.html … via @androides    
    
    
    @ClaudiaTrasto ¡Qué te ha pasado?!?    
    
    
    Wikileaks Moves to Amazon Web Services by @klintron http://rww.to/ewpOhF  via @RWW    
    
    
    @unclebobmartin "Good idea but we don't have time for that" they usually say.    
    
    
    Cambiando de base http://goo.gl/fb/EU1g1    
    
    
    Google Open-Sources NoSQL Database Called LevelDB by @klintron http://rww.to/qrqOLN  via @RWW    
    
    
    The new input system is working for screen events (tap, hold, drag). Now debugging scene and entity events. Won't be ready before vacations.    
    
    
    Android takes almost 50% share of worldwide smart phone market | Canalys http://www.canalys.com/newsroom/android-takes-almost-50-share-worldwide-smart-phone-market …    
    
    
    @ClaudiaTrasto Angry Birds http://www.rovio.com/index.php?page=angry-birds    
    
    
    