Long Run pic.twitter.com/FcZAejUZn0    
    
    
    Tidal Bay before the Betfair Chase. pic.twitter.com/nmIKS4VNIy    
    
    
    Dynaste. Ran a cracker! pic.twitter.com/YADUMrxtev    
    
    
    Another of Dynaste. pic.twitter.com/YsiGytZKww    
    
    
    Barry Geraghty and Bobs Worth pic.twitter.com/Yl2tp0HJJa    
    
    
    Joe Tizzard and Cue Card pic.twitter.com/FXBlLAYEiP    
    
    
    Tom Scudamore and Dynaste pic.twitter.com/HHyLT8cWI7    
    
    
    SWC and Long Run pic.twitter.com/ms4XnkHL6m    
    
    
    Roi Du Mee and Jason Maguire pic.twitter.com/WO4WJ3x4MN    
    
    
    Noel Fehily and Silviniaco Conti pic.twitter.com/HbeGhS213f    
    
    
    Denis O'Regan and The Giant Bolster pic.twitter.com/9QgHvPu4Up    
    
    
    Sam Twiston-Davies and Tidal Bay pic.twitter.com/oV2FJP85eJ    
    
    
    @HarryCowmilker @AP_McCoy unfortunately that's the closest I got to him.    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo cheers. There's one further on with Scudamore I like, seemed to turn round at the perfect moment.    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo did you back Dynaste EW? Over the final fence I thought he had it.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli need to catch up with today's. Was it a dominant win?    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo that's alright then. You were right about BW surely there was something wrong with him. Only beat one home. Cue card great >    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo run but wouldn't have had him in my shortlist.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli she is in my 'Jumps coupon' with William Hill. Zarkandar is a superstar. Somehow missed this race on course.    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo that would have been a  wry nice return.    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 and you adam somehow missed @LauraMckib    
    
    
    @robynfrommars he will get heavier as the race goes on with all that birch.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib @AdamWebb121 haven't got anything planned yet but would love to do the Becher money dependant.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum broke a leg by the looks of it hobbling around. Bad side of jumps racing with the screen up in seconds.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum too true. I think that was the only fatality of the Haydock card. Couple of falls but luckily they got up.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum fantastic day out though. Roll on the next one    
    
    
    @dahlsmum have a good one! I'm sure you will. Never been Ludlow, have to get myself round more of the NH courses.    
    
    
    Hannah please pack your bags and piss off. You are shit.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib looked like he broke a leg. Was worried for Mac Eada in the last but read on here that he got up.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib that should have been Mac Aeda but guessed you'd know that.    
    
    
    Go on Rough Copy! Loved this tune back in the day.    
    
    
    How many times does she want to forget the words.    
    
    
    Put a sock in it Annabel. Fuck sake    
    
    
    What a con! Its a world title fight you utter cunt    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 @SpoilerTV Oh God that episode looks AMAZING!!!!    
    
    
    Need 1 horse to complete the '9 other horses' so far; Al Ferof/Annie Power/Big Bucks/Champagne Fever/Dynaste/Quevega/Simonsig/Sacre tips?    
    
    
    Also who the hell is going to be my stable star???    
    
    
    #TheCrew for #PS4 looks one hell of a game :o    
    
    
    Roll on Friday, after seeing trailers for PS4 games (and having Fifa14 here already) it is killing me.    
    
    
    Do I get my arse in gear and get to the Becher at Aintree 7th Dec?    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 seriously thinking about it now.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 I'd still rather be in your position than ours.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 honestly have no idea but we play WBA tomorrow, seriously fallen out of love with the game and didn't renew ST this year.    
    
    
    Fellaini to score first a price boost. Are you kidding me??    
    
    
    Fucking hell come on All Blacks.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 Thats pretty much the same as me.    
    
    
    Ireand are going to make history here. This sounds like one hell of an atmosphere.    
    
    
    They've only gone a done it. Best team in the world for a reason.    
    
    
    @reluctantnicko Think you need to borrow my glasses.    
    
    
    Won 14/14 throughout the year.    
    
    
    Roooooooooooooney. That was always going to happen with the controversy from earlier.    
    
    
    God Utd are crap. They won't win this.    
    
    
    Season finale of Boardwalk Empire tonight, cant wait to watch that tomorrow.    
    
    
    Dracula not on in the States yesterday??    
    
    
    2 weeks in a row an injury time goal has crippled my acca. Wankers    
    
    
    @jak812 @AP_McCoy cracking photo Jackie.    
    
    
    Mary J you used to churn out some crackers but what the flying fuck was that.    
    
    
    Gary and the Meerkats. ❤️    
    
    
    @JayneKenniford @Jamie_ak_bfc what a fag!!!    
    
    
    Goodbye Hannah/Tamera.    
    
    
    How? That is a farce. Forgot her words more than once. At least Hannah is going home.    
    
    
    @KingSimonsig yeah you have to pick 9 horses and one stable star (the stable you have a choice between 8 horses) 10 horses in total.    
    
    
    @KingSimonsig it's part of a coupon through William Hill called the jumps. Hard to explain in 140 characters.    
    
    
    @KingSimonsig hahaha if only it was that easy.    
    
    
    If rough copy don't go through judges heads need testing.    
    
    
    @Steven__1991 looks a fantastic line up so far. Doubt they will all remain though    
    
    
    @Steven__1991 haha you'd settle for that if it was The New One, Zarkandar, My Tent Or Yours and Melodic Rendezvous turning up.    
    
    
    @Steven__1991 @AASherratt not sure, just looked at the big race meet cards. Can never tell until final decs on the Thursday.    
    
    
    @BoardwalkEmpire #teamchalky    
    
    
    FFS can't believe I'm saying this but I'm starting to warm to Joey. 😱😱😱    
    
    
    @PollyRodgers before he went in thought he was a right prick. Vincent is annoying me no end.    
    
    
    Trying to avoid twitter today until I've seen the finale of Boardwalk Empire. It's not working as I'd planned.    
    
    
    What the hell is Sauls plan with Brody??    
    
    
    @craigelwell just watching it now.    
    
    
    Nobody does a series finale better than @BoardwalkEmpire. Nobody.    
    
    
    The people I thought were dead certs to be killed off only one of them was. Didn't expect the last scene at all. Gutted. #BoardwalkEmpire    
    
    
    Lambert had prepared Steve Clarkes team talk with his comments the past week. Glad I've got better things to do.    
    
    
    @bazfitz1982 I wouldn't go on the #BoardwalkEmpire hashtag for a while as that's all that's being talked about Very good season all I'll say    
    
    
    @bazfitz1982 that too was a shock. Can't wait for season 5.    
    
    
    £23 for season 3 Boardwalk Empire Bluray. That's a steal surely.    
    
    
    @Alky007 one of the best tv programs I've ever seen. Just watched the finale of season 4 tonight. Wow.    
    
    
    @Alky007 no haven't seen that. Will have to add that to the list    
    
    
    @Alky007 I've got so much tv from America on my list but will add those to the lists. Can't beat a good boxset    
    
    
    Another top class episode from #TheBlacklist it just gets better and better. Love Red and Keen.    
    
    
    #sleepyhollow time. Loving Ichabod and Abbie    
    
    
    @dahlsmum up to Episode 9 now. I'm loving it. You got far with it? How was Ludlow?    
    
    
    @dahlsmum can't go wrong with that. Can't beat a good American series. Few more coming up within the next month 😃    
    
    
    @dahlsmum have fun. You got a lot of catching up to do?    
    
    
    @dahlsmum hahaha I have to make a list of what to watch on which days to keep me up to date.    
    
    
    Have you seen this weeks Sleepy Hollow @Footychick25? Think @shortchick77 is in for a nice surprise!!    
    
    
    @shortchick77 congrats. :)    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 you've got to be kidding me. Fuck sake. Hate these mid season breaks. Tonight's blacklist was brilliant.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 where you working/what you doing?    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 haha it has to be done. Think I've just seen episode 9.    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 what is the point in these mid season breaks? When do they air again?    
    
    
    @shortchick77 Good luck. When do you start?    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 the following starts 14th Jan or something like that. Then there's True Detective and more 👍    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 only seen one episode of that so far.    
    
    
    Episode 3 of The Bridge.    
    
    
    @roryjiwani @stanjames Countrywide Flame. #newcastle #fightingfifth    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 will be putting it on shortly. Can't wait.    
    
    
    Anybody else order their PS4 with Amazon? Have you had a despatch confirmation email yet? I'm getting edgy.    
    
    
    Person of interest was superb @Footychick25 @shortchick77    
    
    
    Loving @MichaelEaly character in #AlmostHuman    
    
    
    Anybody not watching Almost Human needs to get involved with it.    
    
    
    And now an episode of The Bridge before I'm a Celeb starts.    
    
    
    England tickets for the 2015 World Cup are a bit pricey aren't they!!!!!    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 superb. Have you seen any of Almost human yet? That is very good. Also started watching the bridge been v. good    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 the opening have me goosebumps. Great way to end the 3 episode event    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 it's easy once you make a list ;)    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 haha you must watch some rubbish 😃    
    
    
    @mytentoryours rats and snakes. And I'd have a real go at trying to overcome them.    
    
    
    Off to Weatherby racecourse in a couple of weeks (December 7th ish) for the birthday (with thanks to Auntie and Uncles phone call tonight).    
    
    
    @mytentoryours hahaha I am shit scared of them.    
    
    
    Haha Delroy Facey that guy was fucking dreadful at Burnley    
    
    
    Come on Amazon, Despatch my PS4.    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf you had an email from them? Still says it's down to be delivered tomorrow but I'm now getting edgy.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ZionistWolf still down for delivery tomorrow but still says not yet dispatched :( I'm nervous!    
    
    
    @EddWalsh Fifa, Killzone, camera and 2 controllers Didn't think it was bad for the price considering I was offered an upgrade on single unit    
    
    
    @EddWalsh think the single unit was £389    
    
    
    The tunnel has gone up one or two gears. 👍    
    
    
    @BetRacingNation Countrywide Flame    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x I watched it earlier. Very good ending 👍    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x I'm watching something similar at the minute that was on in America called the Bridge, that's very good as well.    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x kind of similar, was based on original from Denmark/Sweden but changed to suit American audience. It's been good so far    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf yes, all my accessories have been dispatched now I'm waiting for the big one!!! 😃    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf like this? I've ordered a bit with Amazon so no idea what package it is. Says still not desp on web tho pic.twitter.com/CKfscZkCe0    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf never had one of them before been a desp email and that's it. Still down for delivery tomorrow so not sure what to expect now    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf keep your fingers crossed for me haha.    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf so far only ones I've got are FIFA and Killzone, will be getting some for Xmas though. You?    
    
    
    Amazon have annoyed/pissed me off today.    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf at least yours has been delivered :(    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf nope. Gutted. Everything else I've ordered has come but still ps4 less.    
    
    
    My Tent Or Yours and At Fishers Cross double looks obvious today doesn't it?    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x yeah ones called My Tent or Yours (Newcastle 2:05) and another called At Fishers Cross (Newbury 2:25)    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x no week off this week, birthday weekend. Off to meet up with Aunt and Uncle next week at Weatherby to go racing.    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x have fun. :)    
    
    
    @LauraMckib what have you got?    
    
    
    @LauraMckib nothing wrong with that. How long you had it    
    
    
    @LauraMckib very nice! 👍    
    
    
    My Tent or Yours ❤️    
    
    
    All turns to @BarryJGeraghty now, come on At Fishers Cross.    
    
    
    Typical. Bookies will be laughing cocks off now with so many MTOY/AFC doubles down.    
    
    
    Mine included.    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf nope. Have had an email from Amazon apologising. So frustrating as it was pre ordered months ago pic.twitter.com/aOLK8Ew4oJ    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf is it good?    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf couple of accessories came on Friday the controller feels amazing. Can't wait to get my hands on it now!    
    
    
    Merry King here for me, no bet though.    
    
    
    I think Id prefer last seasons Villa. This seasons Villa is boring as fuck. zzzzz    
    
    
    Homeland season 2 Blu ray selling for £19 on Amazon at the minute in their lightning offers if anyone is interested.    
    
    
    @Mat_avfc superb.    
    
    
    Don't like Nicole's short hair.    
    
    
    Birdy shits all over this version.    
    
    
    Cowell needs to come back and rescue this show. Bring Cheryl back with him. Sharon is getting on my nerves.    
    
    
    Sam has easily won this.    
    
    
    Rough Copy should be sailing through after that.    
    
    
    @ianewen that as well.    
    
    
    Matthew is one massive knob head.    
    
    
    Now we can all start putting up Christmas trees and playing Xmas songs.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes :)    
    
    
    Come on Luis. Step up.    
    
    
    Now fucking cut your hair Tom.    
    
    
    Needed a Suarez goal today. Useless bellend    
    
    
    @craigelwell Monday nights in America, I watch it on Tuesdays. Yep that's where I'm up to now, only 1 maybe 2 more and it breaks for xmas    
    
    
    Love my cards from everyone and present from mum and dad. That is quality.    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x yeah it's tomorrow but opened cards and present from mum and dad while we were all together tonight.    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x thanks. 28 tomorrow 😱    
    
    
    Has there ever been a more boring x factor contestant than Rebecca Ferguson??    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC rough copy favs to go home tonight    
    
    
    @pavilla73 snap!    
    
    
    @pavilla73 Happy Birthday for tomorrow then bud!    
    
    
    Hopefully Tamera goes tonight as Luke was 12/1 last night and I bottled it.    
    
    
    This is Luke's best performance    
    
    
    @GaryBarlow shithouse grow some balls!!!    
    
    
    Analifet at 10s for the Triumph Hurdle. Worth a few quid?!!    
    
    
    Yes. Piss off Annabel    
    
    
    28 today.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli thanks Mark.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib thanks Laura.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC thanks Jenbo!!!!    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x thanks Liz. Hope it's a good day for you as well.    
    
    
    @Haroon_62 thanks.    
    
    
    @GarDeady Cheers Gar.    
    
    
    @Adameffo cheers Adam. 🎂    
    
    
    @dahlsmum thank you Jo! Hope your having a good day. X    
    
    
    And Amazon have delivered my PS4 😀. Only problem is I'm stuck at work until 5 at the earliest 😞    
    
    
    @Jamie_ak_bfc thanks!    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 cheers Adam. I'm off to Wetherby races this weekend to meet up with Aunt and Uncle but off to Haydock 21st. Are you there?    
    
    
    @Liz_NessaAVFC thank you Liz! It's getting better now I've finished work for the day!!!    
    
    
    @AngieSouth @Liz_NessaAVFC thanks Angie :)    
    
    
    @Nik_South haha the stakes, like it! Cheers Nik.    
    
    
    Anyway to change your PSN name on PS4? Still the same as my info for PS3. Needs to change!!!    
    
    
    Next Gen Fifa is very good. Graphics looks quality.    
    
    
    @StueyG2009 cheers Stuey!! Fingers crossed    
    
    
    @lukegthomas26 Cheers Luke.    
    
    
    It's okay when you're doing it though eh Lucy. 2 faced bitch.    
    
    
    I've sworn over 91 times on Twitter, so I'm on Santa's naughty list. Sad face. Have you been naughty or nice?  http://socialsanta.co/     
    
    
    Xmas tree is up. Round of applause for Julie. pic.twitter.com/o4l5tppayC    
    
    
    @AngieSouth Thanks. Love this time of year    
    
    
    @AngieSouth we used to go for real ones but mum decided to change last year. Ollie seems to like the synthetic one better too.    
    
    
    Can't wait to play on this beaut. Thank you @JayneKenniford pic.twitter.com/sE6kZnfKf6    
    
    
    Woah. That episode of the Blacklist was brilliant.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday for tomorrow @Liz_NessaAVFC🍻🎂    
    
    
    @Liz_NessaAVFC yeah it was very good thanks.    
    
    
    @Liz_NessaAVFC I'm only a week ahead of you (well you catch up on Friday). I've just seen how it all ends. Superb program.    
    
    
    I love this @ap_mccoy birthday card. pic.twitter.com/XsbmsHnJVj    
    
    
    Lucy is getting on my tits!!!    
    
    
    Fair play to Joey Essex changed my opinion about him while he's been in the jungle.    
    
    
    Where's Kian been in the recent VT's @imacelebrity    
    
    
    What the hell happened for 3 red cards!!! pic.twitter.com/M7ySYwpC7F    
    
    
    I thought the blacklist was originally a 22 episode series??? I'm confused.    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 thanks, just keep seeing tweets saying it has been renewed for a 2nd season totalling 22 eps etc    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 and Megan Boone tweeted something like see you for season 2.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 cheers, always rely on you two 👍. POI tomorrow 😃    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 oh FFS stop fucking with my brain America. Too many season breaks :(    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 thanks. Hope they do one of those every month! Could just highlight the ones I watch and I'm sorted!!    
    
    
    Fuck off Lucy. Stupid bitch    
    
    
    Can we all vote Lucy out tonight. What a bitch. She's so envious of Amy it's embarrassing    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC hate her! What a bitch    
    
    
    @mytentoryours nope Lucy. Annoys the crap out of me    
    
    
    Joey Essex haha. He's turning into legendary status.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 How's work going Nat? Enjoying it?    
    
    
    #AC4BlackFlag what a game!    
    
    
    Catching up with last nights #TheTunnel    
    
    
    After watching the bridge (US version) I have an idea of what is on its way with the tunnel.    
    
    
    @NicolaP74 I think I know what's going to happen, it's similar in many ways to something I watched in America called the bridge.    
    
    
    Good ending but knew that was coming.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC no not yet, couple more episodes. I'd say the bridge is probably better at the moment.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC it's the American version of the tunnel. That was very good. Loads of new tv coming from US soon.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC I'll have a look but last time they were all single files. S04 started In UK recently. I'm up to about e10 from US.    
    
    
    RIP Nelson Mandela.    
    
    
    @beckybfc if you do take me with you in your suitcase!!!    
    
    
    Italy Uruguay and Costa Rica. Not the best of draws.    
    
    
    Don't hug her Dave floor her! Can't stand her anymore at all.    
    
    
    @mytentoryours no Sunday    
    
    
    @mytentoryours No. Meeting up with Aunt and Uncle at Wetherby.    
    
    
    @mytentoryours and you bud! Any fancies from the Wetherby card.    
    
    
    Wetherby tomorrow, anyone got any strong fancies?    
    
    
    Well that was a shocker    
    
    
    @StuartJBrown I expect better from you!    
    
    
    @StuartJBrown haha count me out. I will be wearing a nice Christmas hat though.    
    
    
    What a day at Wetherby. Few winners across the cards. Roll on the next outing!!    
    
    
    How did Leighton Aspell hold on when deep trouble jumped the last. Fantastic ride!    
    
    
    @dahlsmum good luck for tomorrow Jo, if I can run 10k with these knees I'm sure you can. 🏃🏃🏃    
    
    
    @dahlsmum my time was 1hr 24mins go out there and smash it to pieces!! 👍    
    
    
    @dahlsmum Few months ago now did the Manchester 10k. Was the first time I'd ever run 10k. Adrenaline and support from sides got me through    
    
    
    @dahlsmum you'll have to let me know how you get on. Good luck. 😃    
    
    
    How many more chances is Mad Moose going to get??    
    
    
    Sire De Grugy powered home up that Sandown hill. Unfortunately for him he's around in the same era as the beast Sprinter Sacre.    
    
    
    @Andy_Wilson87 superb performance, back to his best after Cheltenham last outing. Shame but that's why we love racing I suppose.    
    
    
    Rough Copy deserve to be in the final next week.    
    
    
    @wbavicki😱    
    
    
    Is that the same Steventon Star that was trained by Hannon?? When did he get sold?    
    
    
    @Steven__1991 thanks for that. Wish i'd have seen that earlier. Was quite a big price considering.    
    
    
    @wbavicki haha, who you think will go this week?    
    
    
    @wbavicki think Luke will go as well. Not up to the standard it was years ago needs Cowell back and a couple of better judges now.    
    
    
    After that I think Luke should just pack his bags and not turn up for the results tomorrow.    
    
    
    Don't think I'll bother with the 6am start for the Fugue race. Moonlight Cloud at 13/8 looks a bit big surely she wins.    
    
    
    Yes!!!!!! Fuck off Lucy, should have happened days ago.    
    
    
    Waking up to see that Moonlight Cloud finished 6th and will now be retired. Any problems with her or was the ground too quick?    
    
    
    @_tips4punters_ that's a shame. After all she's done this year to go and retire after that must be frustrating.    
    
    
    RIP Jwala    
    
    
    Des Champs or Arvika??    
    
    
    @Steven__1991 I like SDC. Would love him to win the Gold Cup. Shame there's only 3 racing in said race    
    
    
    @Timeform1948 Arvika SDC Rubi Light    
    
    
    Is that the first time SDC has fallen? Can't remember many if any    
    
    
    Quite funny how shit this is. Being destroyed by a woeful Fulham side.    
    
    
    I turned Assassins Creed off for this shit.    
    
    
    @The_Warlock You're not the only one! Im also giving thought to going back on AC!    
    
    
    @dahlsmum Great effort!!! Well done Jo.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum Enjoy. You'll feel a bit sore tomorrow.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum Woah, must have been running years for that time. Get some deep heat, worked wonders for me haha.    
    
    
    Is Faugheen really a 20/1 shot for the @SkyBet Supreme?    
    
    
    Analifet at 10's for the Triumph Hurdle. I could easily get involved with that    
    
    
    Rough Copy have nailed this!!    
    
    
    Sharon's going to bottle it.    
    
    
    Shitout!!    
    
    
    This is the worst final 3 in X Factor history.    
    
    
    Both deserve it. Happy whoever wins this. Kian most likely.    
    
    
    And that's that for another year. 😥    
    
    
    Homeland season finale is going to be brilliant judging by that episode.    
    
    
    Jesus how is this clown still going? He was shit years ago. #JogonHarry    
    
    
    @Rebeccery love it!!! ❤️    
    
    
    He is the ultimate showman. Love that guy.    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC had to turn it off after an hour. Poor mans Boardwalk empire    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC I'll try it again but just smacked of that while watching.    
    
    
    @YorkshireRacing @WetherbyRaces Scooby Ruby #griystmas    
    
    
    Happy retirement Binocular. @skysports_ed will be gutted by that news I'd expect.    
    
    
    Man City playing Barcelona now according to that knob jockey Quinn.    
    
    
    Typical, Utd score minutes after City lead. Welcome to the one club letting you down Accas again.    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC How has he still got a job at Sky?    
    
    
    Come on Pep, lets see how good these really are.    
    
    
    @NicolaP74 @WeLovePR_MrsB @StuartJBrown @Jenni_BFC hahaha    
    
    
    Is Gerard Butler for real? Not willing to do the time, don't commit the crime.    
    
    
    Followers, after spending the day out in Manchester I have run out of ideas for my mum for Christmas, what should I be looking to buy her??    
    
    
    @dahlsmum I wouldn't have a clue if shed like it or not. Normally struggle for dads presents but this year it's the opposite.    
    
    
    @OneManchester unfortunately too late, as we are now on our way home, the Xmas markets were fantastic though.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum Occasionally. And I'd have to check with sister if she's bought her one. Sis has pinched all my ideas this year :(    
    
    
    @nickhobbs039 dad bought her a kindle last year mate. She loves it, just so hard to buy for this year, normally I'm struggling for Dad.    
    
    
    @AmazonUK how would I sort out an issue from non delivery possibly lost in post?    
    
    
    That was a penalty? Are you kidding me??    
    
    
    Go on Danny!    
    
    
    This is why Arsenal won't win the league. Just not got it when they come up against the big teams.    
    
    
    @Coral where is the price bomb at evens for The New One? Can't get on to the page    
    
    
    @Coral all I'm getting is this? pic.twitter.com/FbndxtRtaD    
    
    
    @Coral what is the point of price bombing if not many customers can take advantage of it? pic.twitter.com/5deT5pu9Z0    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum this is all I got with the links they sent me. Shambles pic.twitter.com/18Db4v9pQX    
    
    
    @Coral @jamiefrombrum bloody hell all right for some.    
    
    
    More of That did it with ease at Haydock as well under AP. Genuinely looking forward to seeing how he progresses.    
    
    
    Real Madrid 4/1 should I go in?    
    
    
    @bazfitz1982 Half hour left 2-1 down. Seems too big but just seen Ramos was sent off.    
    
    
    @beckybfc 2-0 down, highly unlikely now.    
    
    
    Real Madrid equalise. Fuck sake. Grow some bollocks Liam.    
    
    
    @bazfitz1982 Nope. Real Madrid/Draw double chance was 5/2 didnt even bother with that. I want to cry.    
    
    
    You'd think after 3 months they'd finally find Luke some pants that actually fit him.    
    
    
    WTF was that. Well and truly murdered that one didn't you Nicholas.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC remind me how he made the final?    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Nah Sam has won this hands down surely.    
    
    
    Both lads making this so easy for Sam to win this.    
    
    
    @MagnifiqueEtoil Louis has cocked up massively tonight.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC @SimonCowell if he had any sense he'd come back and save his show over here.    
    
    
    How's he managed to get Ellie Goulding to duet with him! Lucky bastard!!!!    
    
    
    Well that's just confirmed Sam had pissed this.    
    
    
    @wbavicki #avramforWBA    
    
    
    @wbavicki who would you like to replace him?    
    
    
    @wbavicki plenty of up and coming ones around. Some odds up already. Think you'd be disappointed with any of these pic.twitter.com/96eoCx0LM3    
    
    
    @Mat_avfc @wbavicki never going to happen that one though.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC no chance. Sam pissed this.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC nah. Think you've got an Xmas bonus. How much will you win?    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC yipeeeee!!!    
    
    
    Gillian Anderson is quite fit for a 45 year old.    
    
    
    Becks ❤️❤️    
    
    
    @AngieSouth one of my heroes. Gave me one of my fondest memories in 2001.    
    
    
    Sir David Beckham. Has a nice ring to it doesn't it.    
    
    
    Leona 💤💤💤💤💤💤💤    
    
    
    @cathygannon353 Congratulations Cathy    
    
    
    @Jamie_ak_bfc Happy Birthday    
    
    
    @wiggledotdot Had to check her page before confirming how old she was. Defo 45.    
    
    
    Watching Homeland Season 3 finale.    
    
    
    Wonder if the Real CIA are like this. Full of back stabbing fuckers.    
    
    
    Holy shit. That's a jaw dropper of a finale. #homeland #seriesfinale    
    
    
    Think there is going to be a few pissed off Homeland fans in the coming weeks.    
    
    
    Still shit I see.    
    
    
    When Welbeck scores 2 against you you then realise you are dog shit    
    
    
    This is a Manchester United team in turmoil. They haven't had to get out of first gear yet after 20mins they've won the game 😂😂    
    
    
    @WillHillBet haven't you missed a couple of zeros from Villas odds?    
    
    
    @WillHillBet nope me either.    
    
    
    The thing that's making this a lot worse is Man Utd were close to even money. Didn't quite manage to get money on. Printing money    
    
    
    2 for Welbeck and 1 for Cleverley. Give up lads.    
    
    
    @Adameffo For good. No where near good enough for the Premier League.    
    
    
    @craigelwell Couldnt get on in time or Christmas would have been on William Hill.    
    
    
    @Adameffo Its clear nothing is working. So why are we persevering with it? Young players are no where near good enough.    
    
    
    @craigelwell Looked this morning saw price, watched Homeland season finale and totally forgot, about to go in big when Welbeck scored first.    
    
    
    @Adameffo This the first time this season its been sold out? I know I keep getting hassled with emails and text messages about ticket combos    
    
    
    @craigelwell It airs tonight but it has been leaked over internet, its a jaw dropper!! Use torrents?> http://torrentz.me/d728fb44446e6c16eafe2bbd2932dce10e272c87 …    
    
    
    @craigelwell or this one http://rarbg.com/torrent/apvgfbx     
    
    
    @craigelwell No worries. Let us know what you think. Dying to have a conversation with someone else who's seen it.    
    
    
    @craigelwell hasn't finished starts again in America mid Jan just on a break for Xmas, already renewed for season 2.    
    
    
    @StanCollymore @talkSPORT positives there's only 2 minutes left. Negatives the 88+ minutes before hand.    
    
    
    Luis!!!!!!!!! £££££££    
    
    
    @bet365 Jonny Wilkinson #bet365XmasCountdown    
    
    
    Thats a great finish from Henderson.    
    
    
    Fuck all wrong with that. Too much protection on GKs    
    
    
    Limited myself to bare minimum stakes this weekend. Not being greedy but could do with a few more weeks like this. pic.twitter.com/ji6Tz2LnBi    
    
    
    Goodbye AVB.    
    
    
    The Tunnel is going to end exactly like the bridge did judging from that trailer.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC 2 and 3 Assists.    
    
    
    Would love AP McCoy to win SPOTY but highly unlikely given the year Murray has had. 2nd place up for grabs though.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC she's won already.    
    
    
    @racingkate is there a market for betting without Murray Kate? Can't find it if there is.    
    
    
    @racingkate thank you. :) #comeonAP    
    
    
    @LauraMckib hahaha    
    
    
    @LauraMckib Murray has this sewn up surely. Hopefully AP 2nd.    
    
    
    Well Nicholas you've well and truly fucked your chance up here.    
    
    
    Well done Sam. Best act won.    
    
    
    @SamPreen congrats buddy :)    
    
    
    Warren Gatland had to win that    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC finale even better.    
    
    
    As much as I hated the guy, he was a great manager and deserves this.    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC earlier today. Was leaked on Internet, check my timeline from a few hour ago. Link should be on there.    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC get ready it's a shocker!!    
    
    
    AP 3rd.    
    
    
    Well in Leigh Halfpenny. Didn't expect that result.    
    
    
    Cant believe Im seeing tweets asking who Leigh Halfpenny is. Gobsmacked!!!    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC Disgusting.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 He's the main reason the British & Irish Lions won the series in Australia in the summer.    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC Its an hour long, very good though. Jaw dropper though.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 He was like a man possessed! Nerves of steel.    
    
    
    @DarrenBirdie Happy Birthday Darren.    
    
    
    Anyone else seen the series finale of Homeland yet? What did you think?    
    
    
    Who do you want now then @shortchick77? Heard any rumours?    
    
    
    Would Capello leave Russia before the World Cup? 2/1 next Spurs boss looks enticing.    
    
    
    Anyone know when season 2 of The Bridge (US Version) airs??    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli has a great chance though if it does run.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli What else have you had on?    
    
    
    About time Vitali Klitschko vacated his WBC title. Hadn't defended it for over a year.    
    
    
    Anyone backing Cue Card for the KG? Can see Dynaste reversing form Boxing day.    
    
    
    @calummadell Didn't know that, you had anything Ante-post?    
    
    
    @Lukeelder13 Fairytale Of New York    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli Cant wait to see Analifet in the flesh! Haven't had any Ante-posts (yet) but that would be my main one.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli @LeicesterTigers £22 fuck me, didn't realise rugby games were priced that reasonably.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli your talking at least double that as an average for football games. Enough was enough.    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum @WillHillBet fucking hell Jamie. Have you heard the Chelsea team or something?    
    
    
    @EPDS_Racing @_Schmutzli that's the dream one day!    
    
    
    @villaclarkie ditto, didn't renew in the summer. One of the best things I've done. Thought I'd miss it but haven't missed going one bit.    
    
    
    @thelucylocket @Adameffo congrats #teametheridge    
    
    
    @villaclarkie didn't watch WBA game and turned Man Utd game off after 20 mins when It was game over. You soon realise how much £ you save!!    
    
    
    What are the Chelsea fans singing (to the tune of feel the noise)    
    
    
    @MitchHuxtable Hahaha brilliant. Cheers for that.    
    
    
    Well done Chelsea.    
    
    
    2 wins and the shortest priced lets the treble down. How many times does that happen. Fucked over by another late goal.    
    
    
    @craigelwell Annoying as fuck. Had Villarreal, Levante and Chelsea. Chelsea 8/15 and the shortest price go and fuck me over.    
    
    
    Watching Person of Interest. Missed this show!!!! Have you seen it yet @shortchick77 @Footychick25    
    
    
    Missed seeing @onlysarahshahi on my tv screen. #PersonOfInterest    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 it's a good one.    
    
    
    Trapped my finger earlier today between two 70+kg rolls. Ripped the skin quite deep it's been painful ever since. Fuck sake.    
    
    
    Hoping the tunnel can take my mind off it.    
    
    
    For those who have just watched the tunnel, get onto the bridge (the fox america version) would say that was better.    
    
    
    The class of 92- great film @GNev2 @fizzer18 @NickyButt    
    
    
    Simonsig out for the season. Sickner    
    
    
    Wish I'd have seen this one earlier (Southwell 1:40). pic.twitter.com/I7y8xtp6WH    
    
    
    @AtTheRaces #getingeraghty Classy Trick, neck.    
    
    
    @bet365 (The King) Kauto Star #bet365XmasCountdown    
    
    
    Hope Puffin Billy can battle through this.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum which ones do you need Jo?    
    
    
    @dahlsmum 1/2 pic.twitter.com/rtpKrMG5bb    
    
    
    @dahlsmum 2/2 pic.twitter.com/fL5pgxUyLI    
    
    
    @dahlsmum no problem.  Haha I'll get the portable one in a sec. Down to 5% now 😱    
    
    
    @dahlsmum no worries👍off to any racecourses over xmas?    
    
    
    @dahlsmum boooooooooooo!!!!!!!    
    
    
    @dahlsmum looking forward to watching Kempton. Have a fancy for the KG yet?    
    
    
    @dahlsmum ouch, iphone/iPad app? Seems to be working fine on both this end.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum good luck with that.    
    
    
    @JimBrierley1 went for surgery for colic recently, Oliver Sherwood tweeted earlier about it.    
    
    
    @JimBrierley1 hopefully he pulls through.    
    
    
    Haven't watched Corrie for months. Watching tonight- my god it's shit.    
    
    
    @lau7 new job?    
    
    
    @lau7 oh sounded like that. Good luck with whatever, sure it will be one a great decision.    
    
    
    I've spent 740.4 hours on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    @Thomoncfc @OptaJoe les sealey.    
    
    
    @Thomoncfc @OptaJoe Paul Ince another one?    
    
    
    Who's at Haydock tomorrow then?    
    
    
    Horrible watching these bullying stories.    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 hahaha probably even money shot as well    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 you at Haydock tomorrow?    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 yeah I'm there. Will say Hi if I see you around the paddock.    
    
    
    What Horse could I put in a double with Pendra?    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 I've gone for Safran De Cotte in that race.    
    
    
    @PollyRodgers wasn't impressed with that last time out (Wetherby 7th Dec)    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 is that your nap? If so I'm afraid I'm leaving well alone haha    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 *goes to changes my choice in that race to Ahyaknowerself.*    
    
    
    @PollyRodgers will hack up now I've said that.    
    
    
    #Curseofthewebbnap @AdamWebb121    
    
    
    Pendra was poor.    
    
    
    @PollyRodgers told you this morning it would hack up after I slated it. 👎    
    
    
    Good day @HAYDOCKRACES again added with a couple of winners.    
    
    
    What's happened to At Fishers Cross?    
    
    
    @SamPreen will have to look out for that one. Will more than likely be there.    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo You're starting to feel how I did this time last year. Now I'm no longer interested. All about horses now    
    
    
    @SamPreen good luck. You'll have to keep us updated if Haydock is the destination    
    
    
    Gutted to hear the news about Silver by Nature. #RIPSilverbyNature    
    
    
    @LauraMckib Great photo Laura. Such a shame    
    
    
    117,000 there to witness #Orfevre romp home. Some way to bow out.    
    
    
    Decided its Al Ferof or Dynaste for the KG. Probably cursed both of them now.    
    
    
    @wiggledotdot after much debating it's between those 2.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib think i'll just end up putting money on both. If not can guarantee the one I side with will be beaten by the other one I opposed    
    
    
    I need a Gigginstown scarf for Cheltenham Gold Cup day. #SirDesChamps #Analifet    
    
    
    @WillHillRacing #WHKG 1- Dynaste 2- Al Ferof    
    
    
    @SamPreen torn between Dynaste and Al Ferof.    
    
    
    What a strike.    
    
    
    Where are the idiots that said Martinez would struggle now??    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Managed to get The Tunnel for you. Cant find a complete BlueBloods S03 at all. Got some more for you if you want them!    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC I have replacements for you. ;)    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC I'll send you a photo by text.    
    
    
    Can anybody find #BlueBloods season 3 complete series for @Jenni_BFC???    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Haha deal.    
    
    
    RIP Chatterbox    
    
    
    @dahlsmum Had to be put down last night.    
    
    
    Pray to God PSG don't find a winner now.    
    
    
    No racing to look forward to until Thursday now. Some good races coming up after Xmas now.    
    
    
    @wiggledotdot very nice.    
    
    
    Thank you PSG.    
    
    
    Is Arvika racing in the Dial-A-Bet chase?    
    
    
    @Footychick25 Congrats Nic.    
    
    
    Giroud is crap. Arsenal need a top class CF If they want to win the league.    
    
    
    @villabone 18 month contract.    
    
    
    Giroud 💩💩    
    
    
    Arrived before Christmas. Now I'm ready for Cheltenham. pic.twitter.com/R0YjvqI1m1    
    
    
    Christmas can officially start as of 10:30 this morning. Bit strange they had us in for 2 hours, but not complaining.    
    
    
    @Andy_Wilson87 luckily can use mine for Analifet and Sir Des Champs that day.    
    
    
    @bet365 Tony Yeboah, Lucas Radebe, Tomas Brolin #365Flashback    
    
    
        
    
    
    Istubble Shaver only stays on for about 3 seconds now. Any ideas why? Its fully charged etc.    
    
    
    @BaBylissUK My #IStubble only stays on for approx 3 seconds now before turning back off. Its fully charged etc. Any ideas??    
    
    
    @NeilSledding At £50 a throw, not a chance!!!!    
    
    
    @NeilSledding Now I know you're joking.    
    
    
    @NeilSledding These suggestions aren't helping at all Mr. Sledding.    
    
    
    @BaBylissUK thank you. Email sent.    
    
    
    What time are you out Jenbo @Jenni_BFC    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Jayne is already out, dad will be later on. I'm getting to the stage where I can't be arsed haha.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC I'm only going for my glass collection.    
    
    
    Reverse forecast on My Tent or Yours/The New One is surely giving away money??????    
    
    
    @NeilSledding last tweet? Horse racing Kempton Boxing Day. Printing money!!    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC #FairyTaleOfNewYork pic.twitter.com/pYz4gtd1MM    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC you're home then-?    
    
    
    Probably the best Xmas present this year @JayneKenniford?? pic.twitter.com/fao6mczbsF    
    
    
    Made up with my presents. Got some real crackers!!    
    
    
    Who wants to come to my race night. Bugger Kempton, this is the place to be this Xmas! pic.twitter.com/K5WP4zNU2y    
    
    
    @robynfrommars seriously 😱    
    
    
    Also get to see Sprinter Sacre for the whole month of December, they must have known it was month of my birthday pic.twitter.com/tFgbNdpvzD    
    
    
    @robynfrommars hopefully that was a joke then haha.    
    
    
    I'm dreaming of a white (or grey) Christmas when either bolt up in the  #kinggeorge #dynaste #alferof    
    
    
    @JimBrierley1 got Dynaste at 4s on Betfair.    
    
    
    @JimBrierley1 nah that's a fair price. I'm happy with 4s anyway doubt he will be that big tomorrow.    
    
    
    Christmas dinner was superb. Compliments to the chef @NicolaP74 from all the family    
    
    
    Elf Brown. @StuartJBrown pic.twitter.com/0Pnz2zeaz9    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC @StuartJBrown @JayneKenniford @Jamie_ak_bfc @NicolaP74 well done Stu!!!    
    
    
    @PPOffers Dynaste, 24    
    
    
    Great day/night @Jamie_ak_bfc @StuartJBrown pic.twitter.com/qioIamEs7r    
    
    
    @StuartJBrown @Jamie_ak_bfc great effort.    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo antepost? Surely there will be rule 4 deduction if not.    
    
    
    Whats going on with your in-plays @bet365    
    
    
    Haha well done lads.    
    
    
    @bet365 most of the games just said kick off instead of what was happening in the game.    
    
    
    And here's to you Vincent Kompany...................... @StuartJBrown    
    
    
    @StuartJBrown You've got some fair catchy terrace chants    
    
    
    Wetherby owners and trainers tomorrow. Flementime running.    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x given the circumstances it's better waiting a couple of weeks to see what Tan does with Mackay and pick him up on the cheap.    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x either way, Lambert won't be going anywhere mid season.    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x not sure. Has Cardiff playing some decent stuff with the team at hand and is a realistic target.    
    
    
    @stuartjharper @LizAnne_x fair enough. Only seen them on tv this season. At home they looked decent.    
    
    
    What happened with Analifet? Just seen some of the results from today. Hope she's ok.    
    
    
    @Steven__1991 Damn. Had big bet on her for Triumph. Like you say not life threatening thankfully.    
    
    
    @Steven__1991 I was looking forward to seeing her that day. Gutted.    
    
    
    What time will tomorrows minor cards be priced up? Starting Price galore.    
    
    
    Racing fans, take a look at the last 2 at @WetherbyRaces tomorrow and tell me who you'd back.    
    
    
    Wetherby not happening now weather is piss poor, gutted.    
    
    
    Is £20.80 a month worth it for RacingUK?    
    
    
    Can't believe the Kempton card with the beast Sprinter Sacre is only being shown to subscribers. What happened @Channel4Racing    
    
    
    Doctor Dolittle or todays Kempton card. Tough decision Channel 4.    
    
    
    Would have had the first 2 winners at Wetherby had I been there today. Absolutely typical.    
    
    
    Make that 3/3 at Wetherby. Guaranteed now that my only bet of the day doesn't win now    
    
    
    Surprise surprise it doesn't.    
    
    
    @BaBylissUK hi. I emailed on Xmas eve but heard nothing so far, is that normal over this period?    
    
    
    Why couldn't I have been at Wetherby 4/4. I could cry.    
    
    
    Anyone found a nice link for the Superstar Sprinter Sacre race?    
    
    
    @JimmyKed Brilliant Cheers mate    
    
    
    Sprinter pulled up.    
    
    
    Gobsmacked.    
    
    
    @JimBrierley1 pulled up very quickly after 7 fences. Still waiting to see if he's okay.    
    
    
    @JimBrierley1 Barry hasn't dismounted they are saying surely that's a good thing.    
    
    
    Come on lets hear some news from Barry/Nicky hope nothing serious.    
    
    
    Irregular heartbeat for Sprinter Sacre. BG right to pull up.    
    
    
    No more heroes has done that with absolute ease.    
    
    
    @SeanPrestonHair @Channel4Racing Great effort today, hopefully one day we will get to see a SDG vs SS race.    
    
    
    Three Kingdoms wins, what a finish!    
    
    
    Anybody taking a chance with Sir Des Champs in the Lexus after the couple of days Willie Mullins has had.    
    
    
    @camillahendo praying for good news and a speedy recovery.    
    
    
    Totally lost track of time. Spent the last few hours engrossed in Fergie's book.    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf just got up to the Van Nistelrooy chapter. Really enjoyable read so far. Planning Redknapps next.    
    
    
    @ZionistWolf only started it earlier today. Normally don't read for that long but couldn't put it down.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC getting lots and lots of boxsets on your iPad will help.    
    
    
    Anyone on the Des Champs double (Sir and Tour) paying about 64/1    
    
    
    @StanCollymore @PeopleSport Burnley/Villa?    
    
    
    @BarryJGeraghty great handling of Sprinter Sacre today. Hopefully he will be back to his best and give you some more memorable days.    
    
    
    No movie comes close to The Shawshank Redemption. Absolutely quality, could watch everyday and still not tire of it.    
    
    
    @bazfitz1982 @villabone definitely in my top 3    
    
    
    What a finish. Awaywiththegreys very tough.    
    
    
    The 20/1 about Faugheen will be long gone after that    
    
    
        
    
    
    What a run from Tidal Bay.    
    
    
    Get in Bobs Worth.    
    
    
    What happened to him at Haydock Park in the betfair chase then?    
    
    
    Villa have scored at home. 😱😱    
    
    
    SDC at 10s.    
    
    
    @StanCollymore That would imply playing football Stan.    
    
    
    Wonder if he knows he's fucked up with his kids philosophy.    
    
    
    All eyes on Leopardstown at 2pm tomorrow. Despite only 5 being entered what a race in store.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum Ran his heart out today off top weight on that ground.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum Bobs Worth's back to his best as well after today.    
    
    
    @JimBrierley1 Interesting. You on it?    
    
    
    Read this in 2 days. Couldn't put it down. pic.twitter.com/t97kwuJlJB    
    
    
    @PollyRodgers I don't read but got that Redknapps and McCoy's books for Xmas.    
    
    
    @NeilSledding Neil, I am a man of many talents.    
    
    
    Now do I go with McCoys Taking the fall or Redknapps always managing.    
    
    
    @NeilSledding Yeah, as much as I hated him, its a quality read.    
    
    
    @NeilSledding Yeah no worries. Think mum wants to read it then you can.    
    
    
    Thank fuck there's only one more episode of Mad dogs left. Got ridiculously stupid now.    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC that was like me all way through season 3.    
    
    
    Great ride from @_Davy_Russel_ on Sea Light.    
    
    
    Justified favouritism with that.    
    
    
    This is quality pic.twitter.com/U0InkLw1Ot    
    
    
    Go on The Fly!!!!    
    
    
    18 Grade 1 wins is some going. What a champion. Get Bryan Cooper back on Our Conor.    
    
    
    How far is Cheltenham racecourse away from Cheltenham Spa train station??    
    
    
    @calummadell Planning way ahead for GC day, getting in at 12:24 should be ok or try for earlier?    
    
    
    @calummadell Can get one getting in at 11:24, sorted. Thanks for help. You going?    
    
    
    @calummadell Im sure will find out/see on here if you end up changing your mind.    
    
    
    @ianewen Cheers mate, sure there will be a shuttle bus knocking around.    
    
    
    Just booked my train tickets for Gold Cup day. Getting excited about it now.    
    
    
    @ianewen Legend.    
    
    
    How has Giroud missed that?    
    
    
    @PaulLovesBeer World class striker would have put that away, or done much better with it. Can you tell I dont rate him?    
    
    
    @JPFestival Cheers, found out they will be running a bus service.    
    
    
    @racingkate 4/1 on HF after today, brave. Shaping up to be a cracker.    
    
    
    Etooooooo    
    
    
    Hahaha Mourinho    
    
    
    Racegoers club membership worth doing?    
    
    
    @jak812 oh easily do that. Never heard of it before to be honest.    
    
    
    @wiggledotdot never heard of it before tbh.    
    
    
    @jak812 @wiggledotdot £25 seems like a bargain then.    
    
    
    That was shit #MadDogs    
    
    
    @jak812 @wiggledotdot I'm in!    
    
    
    @mjyharris what a great photo of a true champion!    
    
    
    @mjyharris joined the racegoers club tonight heard of it?    
    
    
    @mjyharris oh sweet! Not sure how it all works to be honest.    
    
    
    @mjyharris look forward to that being delivered.    
    
    
    @AP_McCoy Briliiant read #takingthefall pic.twitter.com/ViSGW12pwI    
    
    
    What the hell is wrong with me, normally I don't read yet past 4 days read 2 books back to back.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Becoming? Haha, not like me is it Jenbo.    
    
    
    @StuartJBrown @Jenni_BFC (Fergies) Fantastic read Stu, you want to borrow it at some point? Will start on Redknapps at some point    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Cash it in. Over £100 there.    
    
    
    My Golden followers this year. #3 @Jenni_BFC #2 @Footychick25 #1 @shortchick77    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC It all goes off at Sugar Mill Square.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 True. Only about 8 tweets difference from the top 2.    
    
    
    Hidehidehidehi (Hidehidehidehi)
Hodehodehodeho (Hodehodehodeho)
Hedehedehedehe (Hedehedehedehe)
Hidehidehideho (Hidehidehideho)    
    
    
    Robbie Williams at the Palladium is quality viewing. #Legend    
    
    
        
    
    
    Annie Power vs Zarkandar again tomorrow. Surely a formality for Annie with Zarkandar carrying an extra 7 pounds. Love both.    
    
    
    @BetVictor where is the link that will take you to it on mobile?    
    
    
    @BetVictor thanks but this link only takes me to this page pic.twitter.com/PpyVaJZeJz    
    
    
    @Coral I'd want a few more zeros on the end of that.    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum £31 fucking hell 😱    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum haha where's that? I get moaned at for spending £16 on a pizza takeaway feast here.    
    
    
    Somebody take me to Sydney next year for new year    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum haha it's shit New Year's Eve, I've escaped Burnley for the night it's that bad    
    
    
    Did Lukes Benefit win earlier just seen Boston Bob won and my phone has decided to turn its self out with a 1/4 of my battery left....    
    
    
    @beckybfc fantastic thanks for that 👍    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum quality read. Couldn't put the book down.    
    
    
    Just encountered my first ever steam room. Fuck knows how jockeys can put themselves through that possibly every day.    
    
    
    Bryan Cooper has landed on his feet if that news is confirmed.    
    
    
    @78lizzibeth I've been in an ice bath. After a few mins you get used to it, that was absolutely relentless.    
    
    
    @78lizzibeth steam room? About half an hour-45 mins in total.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Jenbo I have no idea!! Staying in the Norbreck Castle for the night seeing in the new year.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC mum and dad. Last minute decision as bugger all happening in Burnley.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC come over! I'll let you sneak in my room hahaha    
    
    
    @78lizzibeth I came out for about 2mins in between.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC didn't realise you weren't doing anything. :(    
    
    
    @beckybfc haha where are you staying?    
    
    
    Shortlist of 5, 1 of them from UK, wonder who they could be. Surely it's Bryan Coopers gig now.    
    
    
    Ruby 1/8 for Gigginstown gig. Surely not.    
    
    
    @hodges_c2kauto my money would be with Cooper. Like Davy but deep down think they're doing the right thing. Cooper will be a class act.    
    
    
    @hodges_c2kauto totally read it wrong. Slashed Coopers odds to 2nd fav behind 1/8 shot Walsh for Irish Jockeys championship.    
    
    
    And people wonder why I'd rather not drink. Some cock heads around.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib haha who's next in line?    
    
    
    Once somebody has taken me to Sydney for new year the year after we can go to Dubai. Your treat of course!    
    
    
    Gone and won something on the raffle, some cheeky bugger tried claiming it before I did.    
    
    
    @mickfitzg Would Ruby possibly walk away from Willie in your opinion?    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC I had no idea you were alone tonight. You never said over Xmas    
    
    
    @McIlroyRory congratulations Rory    
    
    
    Singers pretty fit! 👍    
    
    
    @92bryan92 by the sounds of it 2014 will start with a bang if rumours are true.    
    
    
    Happy New Year legends. Hope you all get what you ask for in 2014, and we get to see some top class racing!    
    
    
    @_Davy_Russel_ happy new year Davy! Sure you'll be snapped up in no time.    
    
    
    Taking bets on how many wise guys there are (when as soon as it hits 12) moaning theres no signings 💤💤💤💤    
    
    
    @ianewen you might have given the surprise away there.    
    
    
    @ianewen pretty sure it was some Argentinian whizz kid since you've let the cat out.........    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli tbh I'd have sacrificed everything I've done tonight to be there tomorrow.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli there was quite a few of the Mullins crew I want to see. Devastated Analifet missing the Triumph. I was going GC day    
    
    
    Happy new year sis @JayneKenniford    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli oh definitely. Will have to start saving to see more of these superstars.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to all the horses!!!    
    
    
    Is Oscar Whisky going to win today? pic.twitter.com/BgYiXepZmJ    
    
    
    @GetYourTipsOut that was first choice. Think is better if avoided then. Will more than likely regret it later on    
    
    
    @aliceplunkett Looks soaked at Cheltenham    
    
    
    Annie!!!!!!    
    
    
    Anyone had trouble with iPhone 5 not being able to hear making/receiving calls, can't even hear the tone waiting for person to answer.    
    
    
    However I can hear email notifications, music and the ringtone...    
    
    
    Ohhhhhhhhh Michael Van Gerwen...... @StuartJBrown    
    
    
    @StuartJBrown Cant see it. You covered Wright so your quids in either way?    
    
    
    MVG is taking the piss.    
    
    
    @dmc1305 Class.    
    
    
    @mytentoryours Treve's arc win. Dawn Approach vs Toronado, Lethal force golden jubilee from start to finish. I could go on and on.......    
    
    
    Jesus MVG.    
    
    
    @StuartJBrown getting nervous?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Stupid question but can you book tickets online in advance with this voucher book? Haven't read any of it yet. pic.twitter.com/AAIWEGnmL7    
    
    
    @jak812 look forward to seeing you. Will try and head to a couple of the stable visits.    
    
    
    @jak812 thanks. Will have to read up. Better use all my rewards for racing points up now then :)    
    
    
    @jak812 Didn't think you could do that, result!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jak812 I assume you add a date, add racecard to order then delete said date? Or is there a better way around it?    
    
    
    Is he for real?? Football's all about winning trophies. Fuck being a mediocre prem side year after year http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/25579811 …    
    
    
    @ChezCon69 That smacks of being happy being boring club with no ambition. Clearly made a great choice not renewing in the summer.    
    
    
    Ol loves my new rug better than her basket. pic.twitter.com/oyEH8hYIKv    
    
    
    Btw think I fucked up massively. It's absolutely huge!!!!!    
    
    
    Sprinter Sacre is back by the sounds of it. How long will even money last?    
    
    
    Sir Des Champs out for the season. Wounded. Another was looking forward to seeing gold cup day.    
    
    
    @mjyharris it is now SDC out for the season.    
    
    
    @mjyharris think it would have been closer than last year. Certainly makes it a bit easier for Bobs Worth without now. Wish I'd have taken>    
    
    
    @mjyharris a price on him after the Betfair chase at Haydock. Think he went to about 8s in places. That seems huge now.    
    
    
    @jak812 congrats on the 2 placings.    
    
    
    @mjyharris it was a weird race to work out that. Conti reversed with Cue Card. Shame a couple I was looking forward to seeing won't be there    
    
    
    @wbavicki :( Thats shit.    
    
    
    @PaulLovesBeer Sharm El Sheikh is brilliant. Quality scuba diving there if you're into that kind of stuff.    
    
    
    @_tips4punters_ Unfortunately it wont while idiots keep watching    
    
    
    Top 4 ante-post bets for Cheltenham festival in your opinion are..............    
    
    
    No idea where that rogue 4 came from.    
    
    
    Top ante-post bets for Cheltenham festival in your opinion are..............    
    
    
    Villa style defending from Wolves.    
    
    
    @Andy_Wilson87 EW wouldnt be a bad shout.    
    
    
    @Andy_Wilson87 I did go big on Analifet for the Triumph before her injury. Mendip Express looks a beast after seeing last race in NH Chase    
    
    
    Yeah looks like the barrel is being scraped now.    
    
    
    Kill Bill is over 10 year old. Fuck me!!    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC @beckybfc Burton game called off. You've placed 5x five folds meaning out of the results you need 5 teams to win for a return.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC I'd guess at 4 as one of them (Burton leg) will now be void- games been called off.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC haha what or where is that? Burnley 2-0 down.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC villa are losing against Sheff U. Blackburn drew with City.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC no think they were down to draw.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Come on Huddersfield get a grip.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC you'll have to look when your next over. Looks nicer    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC I may have something for you as well    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC unfortunately not.    
    
    
    @beckybfc were you on the Ings jay rod double?    
    
    
    @beckybfc boooo.    
    
    
    @beckybfc is he playing?    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Burnley 2-4 villa 1-1    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC no about 10-15 mins remain. You need a draw in villa game.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC Jenbo not happening Leeds losing. Villa losing again. Leicester losing. :(    
    
    
    Haha no worries we can now focus on finishing 17th. where's the ambition gone?    
    
    
    @delibobble they are incredible!!!    
    
    
    @delibobble tbh I have no idea. The graphics are insane. Which games did you get?    
    
    
    @delibobble FIFA 14 is quality. I got that Assassins creed and kill zone. Haven't played kills one yet but the other 2 are amazing    
    
    
    #RIPEusebio    
    
    
    Bye Sam.    
    
    
    @craigelwell Jason Lee?    
    
    
    Delighted West Ham getting twatted, disrespect the FA cup- you get what you deserve.    
    
    
    Get in Routledge.    
    
    
    Well done David Moyes... He's fucked up Fergies boys.. We'll go wild wild wild....    
    
    
    Come on Swansea. Winner please.    
    
    
    Get in Bony!!!!!    
    
    
    Moyes looks like he could cry. Turned champions into the most average Man Utd team in years.    
    
    
    Woah, I need to watch PSG Ladies from now on. @laureboulleau stunner!!!!    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum @laureboulleau You seen her in the PSG away shirt. Wow.    
    
    
    Going to give Strike Back box set a watch.    
    
    
    Have no idea what I'm going to do with my phone now. Apple won't entertain fixing it. I'm pretty fucked with no chance of upgrade until sept    
    
    
    I can still text those who have my number but can't make/receive any phone calls. Apparently all 3 microphones have gone at the same time.    
    
    
    Which is very rare. Battery has fucked up and last on the list the power button is on its last legs. Phones only just out of warranty jokers    
    
    
    @piav86 I'd still like to keep with iPhones as I love them. Just pisses off with what's happened today.    
    
    
    @The_Warlock I have a nano sim. Will only fit into an iPhone,    
    
    
    Wouldn't fix it yet wanted me to buy a new one.    
    
    
    @piav86 Will keep a look out for that. Cheers    
    
    
    @The_Warlock can still hear all my music etc. text messages, ringtone but once answer or try to make calls- nothing, :(    
    
    
    Anyone got their tickets for the Grand National through the post yet?    
    
    
    Strike Back is amazing.    
    
    
    @craigelwell yeah v.good started watching few days ago as box set seasons 1-4s on Sky. I'm loving it mate.    
    
    
    @LukeGBantam Villa or Burnley mate?    
    
    
    Short change hero as it's opening credit. This show gets better and better.    
    
    
    @LukeGBantam cheers mate.    
    
    
    @ctfcMatt yeah Sunday night. Into S2 now. Love it.    
    
    
    @ctfcMatt was shocked at how S2 started with Porter. Gripped after 1-2 episodes is great when starting a new box set. Thankfully all on sky    
    
    
    @ctfcMatt on demand at the minute. That's the only reason I started to watch Sunday night tbh.    
    
    
    @ctfcMatt will do mate.    
    
    
    @craigelwell will Dm you something my uncle text today in a sec. Don't shoot the messenger.    
    
    
    @craigelwell did you get involved with strike back? What you think?    
    
    
    I want to be Damien Scott in Section 20. The guy has it all....,,    
    
    
    @craigelwell nah. On with Person of Interest, Dracula, Blacklist, Almost Human and strike back. All good so far.    
    
    
    @craigelwell haha. Dracula will probably end the same as I've read it's unlikely to be renewed for S2.    
    
    
    @craigelwell I've never seen lost. 24 was ace, watched that last summer. Didn't like GOT.    
    
    
    @craigelwell haha I watched first 4 when it started- didn't enjoy it so cancelled series link.    
    
    
    @craigelwell starts back at America on 13th.    
    
    
    Mad Moose forced into retirement. Probably for the best.    
    
    
    @LizAnne_x haha I saw him at Royal Ascot give the leaders such a lead then didn't come last. Last couple of races were farcical.    
    
    
    Strike Back season 2 done. Very good 👍    
    
    
    Agent Shaw, marry me. She can do everything. POI again delivers..... Reese is back.    
    
    
    Fuck sake. Season 5 of Boardwalk Empire will be the last.    
    
    
    @mjyharris Wetherby.    
    
    
    @mjyharris I'm there in Owners/trainers again with uncle tomorrow.    
    
    
    @mjyharris will do. Nice course to be honest.    
    
    
    @mjyharris surely you'll be off to Kempton?    
    
    
    Fantastic day @WetherbyRaces in the owners and trainers even managed to find a few winners, only one let me down for the place-pot.    
    
    
    Had a quick chat with Brian Ellison in there. That guy is sound as.    
    
    
    Haydock next week for the Peter Marsh chase.    
    
    
    Strike Back season 3 finale time.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC yeah should be. Text before coming and will confirm.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC I have Boardwalk Empire S4. 1-3 (on Bluray) should be easy to download though. Very violent, but I love it.    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC they've added a few more boxsets to on demand. Can you get that?    
    
    
    @Jenni_BFC yep got that.    
    
    
    Also got talking to Henry Cecil/Lady Cecil's right hand man (Guy) yesterday. Bought the winner of the bumper for 3k looked good (Molly Cat).    
    
    
    Champion Hurdle is going to be some race if they all turn up at their best.    
    
    
    Gouffran moves away from the ball, he stays where he is it hits him. Therefore surely gaining an advantage.    
    
    
    @mirak_eel @SimonBCFC He could but fact is he didn't which is why we're all debating this.    
    
    
    @Gibbo2292 think thats for Jordan Clarke    
    
    
    @Gibbo2292 cheers for that.    
    
    
    The more I see that tackle the worse it gets. Red card for me.    
    
    
    Alvaroooooooooooooooooooooooo!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @robynfrommars If its definitely gone down as Shawcross OG then they will pay out on 2nd goalscorer as 1st goalscorer.    
    
    
    ''The simple fact is that Daryl has never given me the impression that he was mad keen to ride Big Buck's.'' Fuck me.    
    
    
    2-0 Suarez, get in. If only Negredo had scored first my double would have been in and I'd be laughing.    
    
    
    Fucking hell Liverpool    
    
    
    Nicky is annoying as fuck in Blue Bloods.    
    
    
    Banshee Season 2. Anyone else seen this yet?    
    
    
    @dahlsmum have you seen season 1? Ended brilliantly, high hopes for season 2. Just put on now    
    
    
    @dahlsmum season 1 was on Sky Atlantic few months ago. Season 2 started last night in America. It's pretty violent.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum it might be on demand in the boxset sections of catch up through Sky.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum no problems. I'm sure @skyatlantic will inform you if they plan to repeat season 1 of Banshee.    
    
    
    Nice twist already. 👍    
    
    
    Tempted to go to Doncaster for the sky bet chase. Anyone else be there?    
    
    
    Scott and Stonebridge time. #StrikeBack    
    
    
    @SteveyAsp on the last season now. Managed to watch up to this point in a week, so addictive. Love it.    
    
    
    Major Dalton is stunning. Fuck me. ❤️    
    
    
    @paulhenriques80 onto series 4 now. I'm loving it.    
    
    
    @paulhenriques80 gutted it's going to be the last one.    
    
    
    @DarrenBirdie @CheltenhamRaces £9 will definitely be having some of those.    
    
    
    Did #TrueDetective live up to the hype??    
    
    
    @dahlsmum will let you know when I'm home. V. Hard to explain in 140char but 'Hood' (sheriff) is not who he says he is.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum if you have a spare 20 mins you could go to Imdb and search for Banshee. It gives a quick synopsis of what happened each episode.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 either of you 2 seen true detective yet? About to put on in next half an hour.    
    
    
    @Lukeelder13 Happy Birthday Luke. Had a good one??    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 when's it on Sky Atlantic? Just started watching will let you know if it's good.    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 the following starts next week in US doesn't it? Blacklist back tonight with Sleepy Hollow 👍    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 will keep with US so I know where I am. Need to get back to using my download list.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 anymore starting soon I should be looking out for? You started Almost Human/Banshee/Dracula?    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 no haven't seen that. Oohhhhh! More than 13 eps for Sleepy sounds good. When is season finale, can't be far off?    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 mixed emotions over that one, season finale :( 2 hour long sleepy :)    
    
    
    @BetVictor seem to be having problems trying to deposit money through app. All I'm getting is this? pic.twitter.com/P2xrauDKIR    
    
    
    @BetVictor great stuff. Seems to have worked.    
    
    
    Dracula before watching headless chickens in claret and blue chase a football.    
    
    
    Turns Sky Sports on. Sees we're 2-0 down already (predictable). Turns off! Think I'll finish Season 4 of #StrikeBack off.    
    
    
    @MJ39VillaFC watched it earlier. Good.    
    
    
    Haha barrel scraping at its best. http://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/transfer-news/aston-villa-transfers-grant-holt-3019664#.UtRSRP02RII.twitter …    
    
    
    If we have to sell our soul to be competent then so be it. These cunts wouldn't make it into most Championship sides.    
    
    
    @ChrisHiggy34 pump City style millions in and I couldn't care less.    
    
    
    Have 3-1 Arsenal so it's not finishing that score.    
    
    
    “@GraemeBailey: We understand Grant Holt will have medical at Aston Villa on Tuesday morning ahead of loan move from Wigan.” Barrel scraping    
    
    
    “@EmmaThommo: Still can't believe we've managed to offload Holt #wafc” says it all. :)    
    
    
    @EmmaThommo sounds like me haha.    
    
    
    Rip St Nicholas Abbey. What a warrior.    
    
    
    Red is back! My God how I've missed The Blacklist.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @StuartJBrown the tv series Stu. It's brilliant.    
    
    
    @StuartJBrown this is the synopsis. It's very good. Series finale next week. pic.twitter.com/4ldPweQn57    
    
    
    @NicolaP74 it was on last night in America was just on a mid season break for Xmas. Not sure when it airs over here.    
    
    
    @NicolaP74 Blue Bloods already back in US. Nothing has really happened this season. Normally a bigger storyline running in background    
    
    
    Should finish all 4 seasons of strike back tomorrow. Don't want it to end, I love Scott and Stonebridge.    
    
    
    Anyone know why twitter decided to follow another 200 people without my consent last night? Was a ballache trying to delete that.    
    
    
    @Villa_Fan cheers. Managed to get it to what it was better not happen again.    
    
    
    Did you managed to get upto date/find out what happened previously with Banshee @dahlsmum?    
    
    
    What have Newbury done now? Saw a few tweets from you all around dinner but haven't seen anything else.    
    
    
    Twitter stop fucking following people without my consent!!!    
    
    
    Holy fuck that's a huge huge huge twist. Season finale of strike back will be immense now.    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum you need to get involved.    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum just quicker than saying final episode of the season.    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum haha it's on sky demand. Watch it on your own, been brill.    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum No, I don't. Just plug Ethernet cable into router and back of hd box and bingo!    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum I'm still getting them for nothing. Have to pay for movies but get boxsets downloaded free    
    
    
    @jamiefrombrum have everything with hd package surely it can't just be because hd.    
    
    
    And it's finished 😢gutted but roll on season 5.    
    
    
    Should I get involved with revenge? Any one seen it..    
    
    
    I want 6. I want 6. I want 6!!!!!    
    
    
    reynaldothewizard to carry on the great C&D form??? #Meydan    
    
    
    Who else is going Haydock on Saturday? Made my mind up.... I'm going.    
    
    
    Buzzing for this to start again. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ob4ZZ94nx2Q …    
    
    
    Cant get the Clean Bandit tune out of my head.    
    
    
    Wonder why Mullins is not sending any of his horses over here at the weekend.    
    
    
    Next box set to get in to.... Scandal.    
    
    
    @eileeno10 looks good first 10 mins. Always a good sign.    
    
    
    @NeilSledding cut out the shit from UK tv then Neil, bingo! Haven't watched likes of corrie for about a year.    
    
    
    @eileeno10 good. Hopefully get upto speed quickly.    
    
    
    @SeanPrestonHair good luck for tomorrow Sean. #ComeonTheGrugy    
    
    
    Arrived @HAYDOCKRACES. Anyone else here yet? Bring it on!    
    
    
    That's why AP came here. Taquin destroyed them.    
    
    
    This is what £450k worth of horse buys you. (Un Temps Pour Tout) pic.twitter.com/SDc0uikmmY    
    
    
    #sireonfire #siredegrugy 11/8 easy easy easy money    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great day @HAYDOCKRACES. Found a few winners to keep me warmer. Question is do I get to Doncaster next week now??    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 @mulldog @jak812 great to see you and Steve too.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib think there was a huge weight swing in the end. Very impressed today.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib were you at Haydock today?    
    
    
    @LauraMckib Taquin was seriously impressive in the end. Great day, think it's the National trials next meeting :)    
    
    
    @robynfrommars you'll still win though. We're crap.    
    
    
    @robynfrommars nope. Normally it's shit haha, granted I've only seen us on tv this season, previous seasons have been dreadful tho'    
    
    
    @craigelwell cash out!!    
    
    
    That didn't take long.    
    
    
    Ollie enjoyed her long walk this morning. She won't enjoy her bath though pic.twitter.com/g20eXOGPRD    
    
    
        
    
    
    Get in there!!    
    
    
    Hat-trick!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @craigelwell Haha that was a long time ago.........    
    
    
    3-1    
    
    
    2 last minute goals in Portugal in the Rio Ave (1-0) and Academica (1-0) games. Love it. £5- £90 4-fold.    
    
    
    @Jamie_ak_bfc it is.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @NicolaP74 yeah. You can get seasons 1&2 on sky on demand through the box sets section.    
    
    
    Did the following season 2 air yesterday in the states?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @shortchick77 Scandal is fantastic. I'm loving it, first season only 7 eps but 2nd 22. Midway through 2nd at the moment. Back on end of Feb    
    
    
    @shortchick77 in America. You could say its a tiny bit like Person of Interest.    
    
    
    @shortchick77 haha you have got to make time. You won't regret it. Was the Following on yesterday in States?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @shortchick77 crap! Should be ok though. Only have about 10 episodes to get through.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Footychick25 will be watching the following very shortly, then true detective then back to my scandal marathon. You seen scandal?    
    
    
    @Footychick25 haha you sound just like @shortchick77. Just put the following on.........    
    
    
    Fucking hell those Joe Carroll masks are scary    
    
    
        
    
    
    I can't get the following raven from my profile pic. However I need a Joe Carroll mask. @TheFollowingFOX    
    
    
    The following is back with a bang!!!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Footychick25 wow, back with a bang.    
    
    
    Superb acting from Woody Harrelson and Matthew McConaughey in True Detective. Deserves lots of awards......    
    
    
        
    
    
    @eileeno10 very addictive. It's class. Just watching S2 E13 now. You up to date with it?    
    
    
    @eileeno10 I'm guessing this all blows up and Fitz finds out about Cytron etc in the next few episodes.    
    
    
    @eileeno10 sure is. Can't wait to get upto date with it all.    
    
    
    You do not fuck with Olivia Pope.    
    
    
    @Footychick25 the Joe Carroll masks kind of freaked me out but I now want one.    
    
    
    @Footychick25 it did with me while they were on the train. Roll on next Tuesday now for E2.    
    
    
    One of these days I will make a decision with my own initiative you don't comment back on whinging, Shouldn't have to put up with this shit!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    That Blacklist was awesome. Anyone know when it comes back over here (asking for mum and dad).    
    
    
    Now I did not expect that ending 😱#TheBlacklist    
    
    
    Time for Sleepy finale.    
    
    
    Sleepy Hollow finale, woah! That was quality...... What a curveball.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Abdomlahor you've got something to look forward too. Loved it.    
    
    
    How good was Sleepy final? @shortchick77 @Footychick25    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 the curveball at the end..... Wow!!!    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 when's S2 airing?    
    
    
    How much did City get Negredo for? Money well spent.    
    
    
    @Footychick25 @shortchick77 POI not on last night?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 any idea when it's back then? Seen they've done the same with Almost Human.    
    
    
    Coming towards the end of Scandal S2. Love this program!!!    
    
    
    @craigelwell yeah seen both episodes so far. Another HBO classic!    
    
    
    Should have had the Barney Curley lucky 15 on today. I'd have been able to retire at 28.    
    
    
    You don't mess with @BellamyYoung character Mellie in Scandal.    
    
    
    @mattgarstang haha, it's about time you made one... You can make up for it tomorrow morning.    
    
    
    S2 of Scandal done.    
    
    
    Anyone know what was being sung few minutes ago. Sure it was something like Fergie time...Fergie time    
    
    
        
    
    
    Get the fuck in    
    
    
    @EddWalsh oh well maybe it is    
    
    
    De Gea bound to have the final say in this now. It's how football works isn't it.    
    
    
    Get in. Enjoy Wembley @safclyndz    
    
    
    Well in Moyes.    
    
    
    Fuck me the retard @garypiper1155 has joined twitter.    
    
    
    @garypiper1155 put a picture up retard! Stop being an egg.    
    
    
    @garypiper1155 change your picture bellend    
    
    
    @garypiper1155 have a look at Kempton 5pm. Back it!!!    
    
    
    How good is it when other people start seeing what you have been for months!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mytentoryours I wouldn't have been able to talk to anyone for weeks if it happened to me.    
    
    
    Street Power won. Uncle will be happy.    
    
    
    @mytentoryours good luck mate! If it gets to the last leg back every single other outcome hahaha    
    
    
    Abby looks well different in S3 of Scandal.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Long Run pic.twitter.com/FcZAejUZn0    
    
    
    Tidal Bay before the Betfair Chase. pic.twitter.com/nmIKS4VNIy    
    
    
    Dynaste. Ran a cracker! pic.twitter.com/YADUMrxtev    
    
    
    Another of Dynaste. pic.twitter.com/YsiGytZKww    
    
    
    Barry Geraghty and Bobs Worth pic.twitter.com/Yl2tp0HJJa    
    
    
    Joe Tizzard and Cue Card pic.twitter.com/FXBlLAYEiP    
    
    
    Tom Scudamore and Dynaste pic.twitter.com/HHyLT8cWI7    
    
    
    SWC and Long Run pic.twitter.com/ms4XnkHL6m    
    
    
    Roi Du Mee and Jason Maguire pic.twitter.com/WO4WJ3x4MN    
    
    
    Noel Fehily and Silviniaco Conti pic.twitter.com/HbeGhS213f    
    
    
    Denis O'Regan and The Giant Bolster pic.twitter.com/9QgHvPu4Up    
    
    
    Sam Twiston-Davies and Tidal Bay pic.twitter.com/oV2FJP85eJ    
    
    
    @HarryCowmilker @AP_McCoy unfortunately that's the closest I got to him.    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo cheers. There's one further on with Scudamore I like, seemed to turn round at the perfect moment.    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo did you back Dynaste EW? Over the final fence I thought he had it.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli need to catch up with today's. Was it a dominant win?    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo that's alright then. You were right about BW surely there was something wrong with him. Only beat one home. Cue card great >    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo run but wouldn't have had him in my shortlist.    
    
    
    @_Schmutzli she is in my 'Jumps coupon' with William Hill. Zarkandar is a superstar. Somehow missed this race on course.    
    
    
    @Theoooooooooo that would have been a  wry nice return.    
    
    
    @AdamWebb121 and you adam somehow missed @LauraMckib    
    
    
    @robynfrommars he will get heavier as the race goes on with all that birch.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib @AdamWebb121 haven't got anything planned yet but would love to do the Becher money dependant.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum broke a leg by the looks of it hobbling around. Bad side of jumps racing with the screen up in seconds.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum too true. I think that was the only fatality of the Haydock card. Couple of falls but luckily they got up.    
    
    
    @dahlsmum fantastic day out though. Roll on the next one    
    
    
    @dahlsmum have a good one! I'm sure you will. Never been Ludlow, have to get myself round more of the NH courses.    
    
    
    Hannah please pack your bags and piss off. You are shit.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib looked like he broke a leg. Was worried for Mac Eada in the last but read on here that he got up.    
    
    
    @LauraMckib that should have been Mac Aeda but guessed you'd know that.    
    
    
    Go on Rough Copy! Loved this tune back in the day.    
    
    
    How many times does she want to forget the words.    
    
    
    Put a sock in it Annabel. Fuck sake    
    
    
    What a con! Its a world title fight you utter cunt    
    
    
    @shortchick77 @Footychick25 @SpoilerTV Oh God that episode looks AMAZING!!!!    
    
    
    