@misspennylilian Back off, groupie    
    
    
    @Skysportswebed It was that goal that made me fall in love with football    
    
    
    DUNG NEWS: http://bbc.in/1fSewTO     
    
    
    I love it when foreigners write beautifully about London http://nyti.ms/1ba8xEk     
    
    
    Oh this piece is just brilliant: "Geography starts to feel like destiny."    
    
    
    @CarleanneGwen #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    An iPad Mini 2, in the same range of colours as the iPhone 5C, would surely become to the most stylish tablet on the market this Christmas    
    
    
    Christ, terrible grammar in my last tweet. Soz.    
    
    
    @hollyseddon @shiftyhorse Sonic is weeping :-(    
    
    
    @rmitty @_AmandaFoley Aw. Maybe we should organise a meet-up! (Not sure my mum would like that.)    
    
    
    A fan writes... "RT @BETTYKHAN4: @DaveLeeBBC you should not be allowed on twitter."    
    
    
    Today I have the misfortune of being a) really quite hairy b) employed at the BBC and c) called Dave Lee.    
    
    
    @BETTYKHAN4 Aw, that's ok. Don't worry.    
    
    
    BBC4's Storyville prog has commissioned @VICE to make a documentary on the Silk Road drugs site. Should be a belter, I hope!    
    
    
    @JmsDmnd Nobody's safe, Jim. Nobody's safe.    
    
    
    @Krsjn @flemingsean "Unbearable" !! You sound like my first girlfriend.    
    
    
    @piersmorgan You also wanted him to get the sack, you daft bucket!    
    
    
    Great series - portraits of young women in their bedrooms http://bit.ly/1bSJfLR     
    
    
    @nualaloves Hot    
    
    
    @nualaloves Oh Daily Mail. "If you love this dress we're taking the piss out of... click here to BUY BUY BUY!"    
    
    
    Oh my word, this is sublime, via @mattdanzico. SHAKE. http://bit.ly/15YpZvw     
    
    
    @SeanBlanda The inventor said so himself!    
    
    
    Everyone talks about writers block. But no-one mentions video editor's block. It's much worse.    
    
    
    @ThatPaulCoxon Absolutely does exist. But it's more writer's overload, rather than block. Hard to formulate.    
    
    
    @UberFacts Source for that?    
    
    
    @WillDRoberts @UberFacts Well indeed!    
    
    
    @TonyHarper @WillDRoberts ...  *sigh*. And so the PR churn continues! (Thanks for the link)    
    
    
    Boy who made girlfriend unwilling porn star has fine reduced; judge suggests it is "socially acceptable" nowadays http://bit.ly/1a99NHw     
    
    
    My mood today re:Apple is reflected accurately here: http://bit.ly/17fDPg8     
    
    
    Does anyone have reliable figs for iPhone sales in the UK?    
    
    
    @GraffitiBar Always one... ;-)    
    
    
    Haven't seen anything about #MUSTARDPRFifa14 on Sky Sports News yet.    
    
    
    I bet Fox News are feeling a little inadequate right now... http://bit.ly/1bhC4fb     
    
    
    @DP_Walsh @_JamesR I don't think I am ready :'-(    
    
    
    @Khurtizz @dp_walsh @_jamesr Don't beat yourself up mate. In a way, we're all losers.    
    
    
    @hannah_goes @reuters YOU'LL BE HEARING FROM MY LAWY... oh, no, that's ok. Go ahead.    
    
    
    @hannah_goes #professional    
    
    
    @larakiara Looks a lot more sinister written down.... :-|    
    
    
    @larakiara Which I am. Now.    
    
    
    @criley2008 @ruskin147 10 points, first to say that today. Took 3 weeks to get everyone on tape!    
    
    
    @benjaminbunny @dgoneill Siri was my favourite. I'm pleased British Siri is an extremely well-spoken, charming man sporting a waistcoat.    
    
    
    @hannah_goes Bloody hell, that is slow. I had you in my 'quick wit' bracket!    
    
    
    London prices getting you down? Move to, and commute from, Barcelona! http://huff.to/1fZoPWs  (Well...)    
    
    
    @Kathryn_Hearn @DaveLeeBBC Cheers!    
    
    
    @cward1e You've moved to Spain?!    
    
    
    Just seen Mark Morrison taking his laptop back to the Apple store...    
    
    
    @christhall Top of the worldddd    
    
    
    @AdamWestbrook @cward1e There's a joke here about French people that I'm far too professional to make    
    
    
    @mofgimmers I can see you, Mof, writing that one down    
    
    
    @AdamWestbrook That, Wobbly, is bloody awful.    
    
    
    @LJRICH No.    
    
    
    @2MattScott @JoshHalliday The skull is standing in for me today.    
    
    
    @flashboy @jamesrbuk @scottygb Love the solitary comment on that piece. It's as if we've collectively decided he's not worth it.    
    
    
    @hannah_goes Quick twit more like #hahhahahahahah #hahhahhahhahahhahahh #hahahahahhha #ha #Friday    
    
    
    @OctoberJones Still want to interview you for BBC, sir. Told you're not keen to do on camera? Booo, hissss etc    
    
    
    So, @iankatz1000 has told the newsroom to "bang his door down" with ideas for Newsnight. Refreshing open door approach, certainly!    
    
    
    Newsnight for too long seen as mostly untouchable for journalists not in the 6/10 world.    
    
    
    @gnei11 Runner up! Slaughtered (twice) by @LeeStobbs06    
    
    
    @davidrbaxter Corrs that are regulars on the top spots -- so, the six and ten o'clock news (+Today prog)    
    
    
    @flashboy I just like to cause aggro, ennit    
    
    
    It should be illegal to sell SD cards without a little SD card case.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle Saw this and thought "Chris Mandle might laugh at this" http://bit.ly/1ahUOes     
    
    
    @olivia_solon Fanks!    
    
    
    Brilliant read from @NabilHassan79 on talent scouts in football http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/24653124 …    
    
    
    Nothing quite like that feeling of checking your bank account after three weeks of blissful ignorance    
    
    
    Like a UK Boyz II Men. It's "little Lenny Henry" all over again. #XFactor    
    
    
    Grant Shapps want to cut off money to an organisation that had held him to account multiple times. I see.    
    
    
    It'd be like me calling for immediate relegation of Peterborough United, and being taken seriously.    
    
    
    @stevelee23 two easy home games needed then a big 3rd round for the coffers    
    
    
    Does this MOTD Extra thing show any highlights?    
    
    
    Lovely work from @easyJet. Arrive on time for flight. Told they've sold my seat. Can't travel until tomorrow now. What the hell?    
    
    
    @easyJet you're not following me...    
    
    
    @easyJet I can't DM - you're not following me!    
    
    
    Went with easyjet to save our budget. Looks like it will now cost £100s more thanks to them overbooking.    
    
    
    Irony of tweeting this while sat under their ad that says "we love business customers!" is also highly enjoyable.    
    
    
    @dangillmor happens all too often. In gaming too - FIFA 14 £40 in the shops,£60 as a download!    
    
    
    I've squeezed on a diff @easyjet flight, so Berlin is *go*. Unless it's too windy.    
    
    
    Only bonus from @easyjet fiasco... bumped into Last.fm founder Martin Skitsel! Also on his way to Disrupt.    
    
    
    @benjaminbunny oh really? I quite liked it. The Forsyth thing was MENTAL.    
    
    
    On my way to talk to the man behind Tinder. Any fans out there? What do you make of it?    
    
    
    @jasongoodman rushed with interviews this morn - but perhaps a beer this eve or coffee 2mo? Be good to catch up.    
    
    
    God bless the EU. £3 for 100MB of data in Berlin. I remember paying £5 for 10MB    
    
    
    The first edition of @BBCRosAtkins’ new show Outside Source is on @BBCWorldService at 11GMT today live from the BBC newsroom. #BBCOS    
    
    
    Feels like a good time not to be in London.    
    
    
    That awkward moment you realise your mum's twitter account (@textsfrommum) will very soon have more followers than yours.    
    
    
    Anyone at #tcdisrupt *not* launching a Kickstarter campaign? Man alive.    
    
    
    Saw a lot of tech at #tcdisrupt , but @Lock8_me stood out. Very smart.    
    
    
    24-hour hotel bar appears to be closing.    
    
    
    @HamBevan heh, my expenses certainly don't cover my in-the-field booze intake, Shapps or no Shapps    
    
    
    @HamBevan unless you mean he's talking my ex-girlfriends away... in which case he's welcome to them.    
    
    
    @IndelibleFudge @dansumption heard a bloke wind up his missus about there once. "Why's it called Guy's hospital?!" "they treat the men 1st!"    
    
    
    Feeling rather uninspired by #tcdisrupt. A lot of people functioning on hot air and little else    
    
    
    It's easy to be the cynical journo, of course, and I admire the energy. But too many firms' strategy = Kickstarter, yay!    
    
    
    When they don't get the funding they'll blame it on a lack of coverage, rather than a cack idea #tcdisrupt    
    
    
    Also - no noticeable vetting of exhibitors here. Besides terrible, I've seen one start-up that is downright dangerous #tcdisrupt    
    
    
    Thankfully I bumped into a similarly fed-up journo here in the shape of @benjrooney. #tcdisrupt is exhausting, for all the wrong reasons.    
    
    
    @Dan_Martin Kickstarter has lowered the entry bar. It means terrible ideas don't require any support to feel like they've 'started'    
    
    
    @Dan_Martin Before Kickstarter, you'd need some money. Either your own, or an investors. It's a good filter of bad ideas.    
    
    
    @Dan_Martin @benjrooney I have been impressed by a couple of companies, yes. Published here: http://bbc.in/1gXQmJk     
    
    
    @benjrooney @Dan_Martin Precisely. To not be would be cruel - it'd be like the audition rounds of the X-Factor.    
    
    
    @benjrooney @Dan_Martin Think we can all agree I was born to be Barlow.    
    
    
    Trying what I'm told are Berlin's best burgers, under a railway bridge. Cold. http://instagram.com/p/gEBSUGjO5D/     
    
    
    @VFritzNews you're too posh for me sometimes, Fritz!    
    
    
    Trying a few German beers. There's one called "CLAP", but I've already had that.    
    
    
    A glimpse of web filtering future in UK: T-mob (roaming) blocks the Guardian as harmful and for over 18s only.    
    
    
    I mean I find @JoshHalliday's work as offensive as the next man, but that's a bit much.    
    
    
    @andylivingston eh?    
    
    
    @andylivingston One paper did - The Mail. I'm in favour of filters existing, of course, but only as opt-in, not opt-out as the PM wants.    
    
    
    @andylivingston I don't recall that. Link?    
    
    
    Operation Get Whalloped in Berlin was a resounding success. Stick a fork in me twitter, I'm done.    
    
    
    Massive numbers for the brilliant @UsVsTh3m - 3m uniques expected for October (2m more than Sept) http://www.theguardian.com/media/2013/oct/30/daily-mail-quiz-usvsth3m-users-mirror-buzzfeed?CMP=twt_gu …    
    
    
    @WillardFoxton eh? It's nothing like Buzzfeed at all...    
    
    
    @WillardFoxton it's about the delivery method - going directly into tweets rather than expecting people to come to us    
    
    
    @WillardFoxton if reaching a bigger audience that wouldn't normally find us is the "worst" idea, I'm an astronaut.    
    
    
    @WillardFoxton we use twitter, aye, but we don't *broadcast* on it - as in, everything at the mo requires people to visit our site    
    
    
    @cgalbraith very much a flying visit, so others will know better - but start at Burgermeister and work from there!    
    
    
    @Varuka @brokenbottleboy why are you both putting the "." before the username?    
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy It's what I do, Mic, it's what I do. Didn't realise it had reached 'classic' status, though. I'm pleased.    
    
    
    @ProfJeffJarvis @brokenbottleboy indeed! Question is, Fake Jeff, will I ever use my powers for good?    
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy you're too sensitive, chap. Tweets and stones... etc    
    
    
    @clareasmud @textsfrommum who said that?!    
    
    
    Looking through the Berlin Wall http://instagram.com/p/gIYcwHDO5m/     
    
    
    Someone needs to open a massive currywurst place in London before I get back or there'll be trouble.    
    
    
    @IanDouglas I'll import it by the barrel    
    
    
    @chris_mandle prepare my horse!    
    
    
    Lots recommending Herman ze German for a London currywurst fix. Will check it out!    
    
    
    @OwsWills @row @JayneKitsch @clareasmud @textsfrommum @lukelewis Aw, you guys!    
    
    
    Irish pub at Berlin airport: Two massive German barmen, no Guinness and Buffalo Soldier ringing out. Nailed it.    
    
    
    @LittleScotty that's the one!    
    
    
    @davidschneider Only the Brits    
    
    
    @coffee_dad have a coffee chap!    
    
    
    @GatwickExpress back at 1905... how's it looking after that?    
    
    
    @GatwickExpress London bridge, with lots of bags. Will it still be shorter trains by then?    
    
    
    @FirstCC ah ha! Just making sure it's all running ok ... have just landed.    
    
    
    @Dakaix Gatwick me old chap - sorry!    
    
    
    Blimey, Gatwick, you've had a stormer. From plane to train in less than 20 minutes. Top that.    
    
    
    @lydialeavitt hope she crashes    
    
    
    Just witnessed the most fantastic dad joke moment ever on the train from Gatwick    
    
    
    Fella lets out little fart as he strained to lift a suitcase. Daughters horrified. "Trick or treat!" he says. Magic.    
    
    
    Followed by him gesturing at me saying "well he found it funny". Yes sir, yes sir I did.    
    
    
    Sadly searches for tweets with "dad farted" in the text has yielded no leads.    
    
    
    The "best Halloween costume ever" tweet to rule them all. Patrick Stewart, everyone: http://i.imgur.com/PCEmlGF.jpg     
    
    
    @adamblenford remind me to tell you my favourite lobster joke next time I'm at work...    
    
    
    @itsanitarani Brilliant programme. I worried it would be typical poverty-porn, but it's been so so much more. Congrats.    
    
    
    @Dakaix Two pieces!    
    
    
    @LewisWiltshire @alextrickett Chaps - what's that stat of no. of prem league players on Twitter again?    
    
    
    @adamblenford Enough.    
    
    
    @LewisWiltshire @alextrickett @TwitterUK Lovely stuff, cheers chaps.    
    
    
    @Trinifood @LewisWiltshire @alextrickett @TwitterUK I'll be a journalist for some years yet, Franka!    
    
    
    @Trinifood @LewisWiltshire @alextrickett @TwitterUK a Although am off the chips, I must point out. #slimline    
    
    
    @danwhitejourno he says no contact has been made. Hoping it's just rumours!    
    
    
    @chris_mandle I've "been off"    
    
    
    @bryonosaurusrex I'm here with @getawaytricycle talking about Cambridge. She's pretending to care. Bless.    
    
    
    @bryonosaurusrex @getawaytricycle well quite. Great work on the centenary celebrations!    
    
    
    There's a superb 'please take me off this list' reply-all fest doing the rounds right now.    
    
    
    @bexlewis361 Last time I did that I got a severe telling off from our infosec team... (!)    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy Has he got his keys?    
    
    
    Can anyone think of one of those silly local news stories that has gone mega after spreading on Twitter?    
    
    
    Ah ha! RT @essexalliehb: @davelee the Essex lion!    
    
    
    Ha, great suggestions re:local stories gone viral. Thanks all.    
    
    
    @The_Dolphin_Pub Gosh, just in time. Thank you.    
    
    
    Smart PR > RT @BoingBoing: Amazon discounts Kindles to commemorate FAA devices-during-takeoff/landing rulechange http://bit.ly/18TaClj     
    
    
    @CarleanneGwen @guardian Heh - posted it on my Facebook this morning! Brilliant. Raises the bar for a great night out.    
    
    
    A while ago someone kind - a follower - offered to help code a simple wordpress site for me. Can't for the life of me remember who it was.    
    
    
    If it was you, please get back in touch! (And forgive me...)    
    
    
    Who came up with "mudchute"? I mean really.    
    
    
    @Trojan7Sec @adrianshort which store is that? @Tesco can you confirm?    
    
    
    @Trojan7Sec @adrianshort @Tesco I see.    
    
    
    @VFritzNews why do I get the feeling I'll be seeing that bloody advert with the kid on the bike all day today...?    
    
    
    Something very delightful about this pic of a small boy, his dog, and his effigy of Guy Fawkes: http://dailym.ai/1baKC6f     
    
    
    TIL the word "dude" originated from "doodle". As in, Yankee Doodle Dandy http://bit.ly/17aY1Qh     
    
    
    @rickygervais This one, beautifully animated, is up there: http://bit.ly/18sYBmY     
    
    
    Seem to remember a band on the X-Factor saying "hashtag-something" last year. Who was it? Am I going mad?    
    
    
    Thanks all re: hashtag question. It was Eurovision, not X-FActor! Thanks @danforys    
    
    
    Liking this comment in response to @ruskin147's blog on whether Britain could've made Twitter http://bbc.in/16Gy8Fw     
    
    
        
    
    
    Now for the latest from the Google Barge... http://bit.ly/1gtbCFu     
    
    
    @NickPullar @crazycolours @pauljchambers Gosh, quite right - have amended, cheers. (And sorry!)    
    
    
    @DP_Walsh Aw, shucks.    
    
    
    @JennyTheolin Who's the Disney princess?!    
    
    
    @CWMLeo Thanks Chris, that's nice of you to say.    
    
    
    @JennyTheolin But which princess?!    
    
    
    @JennyTheolin I'm far too excited about this.    
    
    
    @JennyTheolin That's... kinda strange. Ha. I was hoping for Jasmine, just saying.    
    
    
    There's a young NUJ (under 27) conf coming up. On the agenda - "how to get a job". Depressing.    
    
    
    Great news! RT @gillis: What a joy to have @alanconnor back in @BBCNewsMagazine.    
    
    
    @crazycolours @NickPullar @pauljchambers Aye - have changed the piece. So sorry about that! (Congratulations!)    
    
    
    @davidcuen Thanks David!    
    
    
    @kgittleson @BBCNewsUS think you're missing a digit! $45.10    
    
    
    @MattHartley100 Cheers!    
    
    
    Love the injuries fact box in this piece by @HonestFrank http://bbc.in/1cXmnLD     
    
    
    @ruskin147 They should have the dog in shot! BBC News Dog would be an instant international celeb.    
    
    
    @ruskin147 Monkey Tennis is my BIG big idea, but sure.    
    
    
    Seeking inspiration for a possible future project. What are some of the most innovative podcasts/radio shows covering tech today?    
    
    
    @karlwoolley Cheers mate!    
    
    
    @MrYahhYahhh Think you've misunderstood my meaning! See here: http://bit.ly/1esH4Ty ! :)    
    
    
    Superb, yet again >> I'm 20% NORTHERN according to the #northometer! That's somewhere around London. http://toys.usvsth3m.com/north-o-meter/     
    
    
    Probably more fashionable to say Lady Gaga is crap - but while Prince remains asleep, she's the most interesting popstar out there.    
    
    
    @Moosola Pretty sure @stevelee23 has pulled worse in the local    
    
    
    @Moosola @stevelee23 not this week. (Been busy)    
    
    
    @nualaloves that's like one of those "u ok hun?" Facebook statuses. COME ON.    
    
    
    @louis_louis less words, more awesome dog. Cheers.    
    
    
    @louis_louis YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE WE ONLY SEE EACH OTHER AT CHRISTMA... oh. Bring the dog or GTFO.    
    
    
    @misspennylilian what in the world?!    
    
    
    @misspennylilian oh well that's lovely... :'-(    
    
    
    Off to @stevelee23's for some important brother bonding. With FIFA, naturally.    
    
    
    Great afternoon at British Museum gawping at this chap http://instagram.com/p/gmIc4IDOxc/     
    
    
    Badabing! > RT “@JonnieMarbLes: Roadrunner is so selfish sometimes. It's all meep meep meep.”    
    
    
    Oyster tap-in broken at Greenwich... so @Se_Railway gives me the option of more expensive ticket or fine. Cheers.    
    
    
    NUJ branch meeting in the "Dimbleby" room tomorrow. Worried they'll make me get a tattoo.    
    
    
    @bowlesy Heh, happens every now and then, sadly.    
    
    
    @katiemcp 2012 rang, it wants its viral site back    
    
    
    Huge welcome back to @ITVLauraK, returning to BBC to join Newsnight. Massive news!    
    
    
    @psmith And a 'talent exodus'....    
    
    
    News of a significant technological achievement in the Philippines should break tomorrow - will be prepping a story first thing in the morn    
    
    
    @tomgara @WillardFoxton Define good guys...    
    
    
    @katiemcp oh for god's sake... You're one of *those* people    
    
    
    @katiemcp cry me a river!    
    
    
    @katiemcp It's part of my stalker toolkit.    
    
    
    Loving this no-nonsense guide to getting a flight upgrade from @shandypockets. Includes: pretend to be dead. http://bit.ly/1bnV8an     
    
    
    At risk of sounding a bit kiss-ass, I really wish more editors here were as brave as @iankatz1000 - publicly standing behind his prog    
    
    
    Too many that get promoted from within are too afraid to dip into the audience like that. Takes a (former) outsider to turn that around.    
    
    
    !!! RT @Andrew_Adonis: Fact of the day: golf courses occupy more land than all the housing in England put together (today's City AM)    
    
    
    Considering using the phrase "musical legend Justin Bieber" so I can make the BBC complaints inbox explode.    
    
    
    @Pocketlint Looks only a mother could love!    
    
    
    @thelondonblog @Viber Greatm thanks - will perhaps work this into the story later.    
    
    
    @BBCUnion Thanks for your DM - keep up the good work    
    
    
    "Help us" - well curated collection of pictures from the Philippines http://lat.ms/1gJVmAa     
    
    
    Macbook charge stuck on 98%... whasallthatabout?    
    
    
    @nevali Erm. Might need to enlist a non-colourblind person to answer that one :-(    
    
    
    @nevali nice one, will do that. Cheers!    
    
    
    No bloody hot water. Kill me now.    
    
    
    @VFritzNews I'm out on a shoot!    
    
    
    @VFritzNews Managed to scream my way through 5 mins + shave. That'll do it. Ha. #glamour    
    
    
    The One Direction fan I interviewed for a feature has just found out she's meeting the band. I think she's excited.. @STYLATORARMY Congrats!    
    
    
    @lydialeavitt Because you prefer Boyz II Men.    
    
    
    @TheRealJoeCox Partly! http://bbc.in/19UsXPy     
    
    
    ANDREW GILLIGAN BACK ON THE BBC. (For a moment, talking about cycling safety.)    
    
    
    Spent a fantastic morning at the National Museum of Computing at Bletchley Park today. Shamefully, my first visit.    
    
    
    What I wonder -- so many companies here owe so much to the innovation in the museum, yet it lives hand-to-mouth on donations.    
    
    
    Come on ARM, Google, Facebook et al -- is it not time to put your hands in your pockets and support the history that led to your creation?    
    
    
    @tomwarren iOS emulator    
    
    
    @timoncheese Also: doodle of a willy on the inside cover.    
    
    
    @timoncheese Oh cheers mate! Finally starting to get the hang of it, I think. Get me on with Vine for #bantz and #lolz    
    
    
    @wonky_donky For some reason I didn't seem to following you. No idea how that happened!    
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy You strike me more as a Joe Pesci in Moonwalker    
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy What?! I was actually being jovial.    
    
    
    @markfrankel29 With a name like Frankel you'd fit right in, no?!    
    
    
    !!! RT @BuzzFeedUK: #ff: @textsfrommum    
    
    
    @k_a_f_f That's very sweet!    
    
    
    @Nero @lukemcgee85 If it's not Harry I'm unfollowing you all.    
    
    
    Does anyone know if ProPublica has anyone based outside of US? (On a timezone allowing them to be awake...)    
    
    
    @shindles @securityninja Aye, they've sponsored a room, so that's a start!    
    
    
    This is 2013, where you add your cab driver on twitter on the way. Cheers for the lift, @fab10r !    
    
    
    Best one yet! RT “@WHS_Carpet: A picture is worth a thousand words (via @Fudgee1980) pic.twitter.com/6KNv56Pcj2"    
    
    
    Live on BBC Radio Wales in a moment if you're in that neck of the woods    
    
    
    Currently editing a clip that shows a spot on my chin at extreme close up. Enjoy your lunch.    
    
    
    The next tweet I post might get me fired.    
    
    
    I don't like Doctor Who.    
    
    
    @FoIManUK I don't like any of your blog posts    
    
    
    @FoIManUK Kiddinggggg    
    
    
    @FaySadro Thanks for favouriting that, you weirdo.    
    
    
    VJs of Twitter, do you have something nice to keep your SD cards in? My approach of "probably in this pocket" is starting to fail.    
    
    
    @misshannahtuck @UL_Journalism glad you enjoyed it. If there's anything I can do to help :)    
    
    
    Spare us the Hull jokes everyone, please.    
    
    
    Three letters to accompany this story about 'dwarf bouncers' at the Hippodrome: WTF. http://bit.ly/IfNEP8     
    
    
    Just did an actual LOL to this: http://onion.com/1cG8wsk     
    
    
    BBC lift having a bit of a mid-life crisis pic.twitter.com/uw39zpH2Be    
    
    
    Don't know why, lucky thing gets ridden every day! #heyooooo    
    
    
    Cc @chris_mandle RT “@TakeaBraek: **Tragic Lives**
How Girl Raised By GAMMON Overcame Fear Of PINEAPPLE”    
    
    
    @Nahidur No word of a lie, it cleared up 3 days later, as the app said!    
    
    
    @alexwoodcreates @TechCityUK @TechCityNews How many website relaunches is that now?    
    
    
    @elenacresci If your name's not down you're not co.... EXTERMINATE!!! .... blimey.    
    
    
    LAD http://dailym.ai/1cGkC4L     
    
    
    It's freezing in the office. Process is: ring facilities desk, they'll file a report, engineer reads said report, visits desk (cont)    
    
    
    (cont) takes temperature, returns to facilities desk, decides what to do. A process that takes hours.    
    
    
    How about this revolutionary idea, folks: a thermostat.    
    
    
    @mikejjennings It's my fingers!    
    
    
    What's left behind after a locket... http://bit.ly/Iga82u     
    
    
    @ProfJeffJarvis Did he do Through the Wire Copy?    
    
    
    Delightfully opportunistic press release from SPAM, pegged to Monty Python comeback. Bravo!    
    
    
    @olivia_solon @natelanxon I LOVE what you've done with the place!    
    
    
    @MichaelDMillar It's depressing how right you are.    
    
    
    @TheMediaTweets @LewisWiltshire Currently being updated to reflect that it was a "legacy" follow, as it were, from auto-follow days    
    
    
    @racheythompson Ha! It was you! Well played.    
    
    
    @racheythompson The last time I had spam I puked all over four of my school friends. True story!    
    
    
    @TheMediaTweets back when everyone was learning, I guess.    
    
    
    Anyone out there with SkyGo use it to get onto Apple TV? Plotting a bit of Ashes watching later...    
    
    
    How's @theashes these days?    
    
    
    As if North Korea didn't have enough problems, there are now concerns (from the US) of a meth epidemic in the country http://on.wsj.com/1ejzisE     
    
    
    @JonathanEx I'd commission that.    
    
    
    Final Cut Pro making me lose the will to live.    
    
    
    @richardkendall Boom boom    
    
    
    @dgoneill Sadly the powers that be here have decided we all should edit on FCP7 (at least for the time being...)    
    
    
    NUJ FoI reveals that the News division has the more unhappy teams than any other part of the BBC: http://bit.ly/1b9OdH3     
    
    
    @Nero Your fee is merely compensation for subjecting me to the sight of @brokenbottleboy's arse... ;-)    
    
    
    Interviewing a very divisive figure later today: the boss of the most popular online ad-blocking software    
    
    
    Thoughts on the model and ethics of adblock software?    
    
    
    @danjsaunders But is restricting the revenue streams of sites that rely o ads a concern to you?    
    
    
    Incredible bravery - woman calmly drives bus with bomb on board, defies terrorist demands http://bit.ly/1fm8Hy7     
    
    
    I take your R Kelly improv sex songs, and raise you Elton John singing about a cooker: http://bit.ly/1fmaeUP     
    
    
    @ChocolateSoul @riptari How did this become a debate about Blackberry?    
    
    
    @riptari @ChocolateSoul I've been here a while :)    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy @YahooTech @gilbertjasono You can do the same thing with the little button on normal Apple headphones!    
    
    
    Delighted @readmatter is now free, but slightly disappointed that we won't get to see how its model played out long term    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy @YahooTech @gilbertjasono Try it!    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy @gilbertjasono @YahooTech pic.twitter.com/onEuQkTKbk    
    
    
    @LauralizHibbard @JessicaKRoy @gilbertjasono @YahooTech If this was Reddit I'd so be getting gold right now :(    
    
    
    @bobbie Ah ha! Sounds great - look forward to reading it.    
    
    
    @iankatz1000 @TimHarford Inspired by lifts at NBH, by any chance?!    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy ASL?    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy woah.    
    
    
    Just got an absolute belter of a @textsfrommum    
    
    
    #ff @dougalshaw. He delivered a pizza to my desk for lunch. He is a hero. (He's also on the ace @BBCTrending team)    
    
    
    @Motorwayviewer @stevelee23 @textsfrommum Don't worry, we do. Plenty of them!    
    
    
    Really glad I took my phone out to read this. Pfft. pic.twitter.com/vSs52O9GlN    
    
    
    I think he's interested in some dogging... http://instagram.com/p/hDsEnWDO5S/     
    
    
    @RyHunt19 Planned scruffy! Hahaha    
    
    
    Where's the best Student Union bar in London? Want to film a vox pop with lots of students at lunchtime tomorrow...    
    
    
    @malavadhia Ah! Good idea!    
    
    
    10 points if anyone can recognise this hero from my childhood... pic.twitter.com/IjPraN52se    
    
    
    @RichEvans Yes! Blimey, that was quick.    
    
    
    @RichEvans Cash them in! (I've not thought this through...)    
    
    
    @viewmagazine Ooof! No thanks.    
    
    
    @FrasSmith Wrong, try again!    
    
    
    @louisebolotin Nope! It's the Tiger Who Came To Tea. Amazing.    
    
    
    Pulled out all the stops for Dad's birthday. pic.twitter.com/uEsB2X10ms    
    
    
    BBC Sport style dictates all goal scorers be mentioned in first 4 pars. Expertly done here by @MandeepSanghera http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/24976958 …    
    
    
    @ajhalls1 @danwhitejourno I haven't.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle @ajhalls1 @danwhitejourno #ladsontour ?    
    
    
    @danwhitejourno @chris_mandle @ajhalls1 You said you were coming back....    
    
    
    Made the fatal mistake of ringing an SU bar to ask if I could film. Should've just gone down there. Schoolboy.    
    
    
    @Blonde_M Large Australian chain, you say? Shall I just turn up and Walkabout?    
    
    
    @SOTMario @victoria111 I'm still sobbing    
    
    
    BBC production systems have made my life 3 years shorter tonight. Or @FaySadro might kill me sooner.    
    
    
    @HenryCP Hang in there HCP. (Not literally.)    
    
    
    @mikebutcher find the train on trainline, then buy it on http://nationalrail.co.uk     
    
    
    @johncthompson @pressgazette @AJReid it was a friendly office...    
    
    
    @chris_mandle "out"    
    
    
    @chris_mandle #apparently    
    
    
    @chris_mandle where's the open quote mark?    
    
    
    @JoshHalliday @rachelkennedy84 Statement reads: "Awwooooooooooooo..."    
    
    
    @Nero @AquilaAngels so what's the complaint exactly?    
    
    
    @louisebolotin ha! Has been a while now. It's so they can link to it without fear of me saying shit, balls and bollocks without warning :)    
    
    
    @RLoyall @faysadro @hewleith There's a reason I feel awful this morning. This is it.    
    
    
    As someone a bit fed up with boring phones, the Jolla is a pleasant surprise: http://bit.ly/XA9rru  Best looking phone and OS?    
    
    
    @michaeltweed Made by a team of ex-Nokia employees... so that figures.    
    
    
    @michaeltweed It *looks* quick and lightweight -- hoping to give one a go this week.    
    
    
    @Linguagroover It's "yol-la", apparently...    
    
    
    @Trinifood Ex-Nokia team. It's 399 euros, sim free!    
    
    
    @AMTomchak @textsfrommum Ha! Glad you like it. Mum is enjoying her fame.    
    
    
    How Bitcoins work (a quick primer): Bitcoin is often referred to as a new kind of currency. But it may be (cont) http://tl.gd/n_1rsdrqp     
    
    
    @andrewlee02 Badass!    
    
    
    I'd just like to publicly congratulate myself on making a reference to Baldrick in a newsroom-wide email. I'm taking the rest of the day off    
    
    
    @christofflennon @rachelabartlett It's a good skill to have, but not essential anymore, really.    
    
    
    "The bear and the 'are... couple-a mugs." -- quite right, Danny Dyer. http://bit.ly/197funM     
    
    
    @christofflennon @rachelabartlett For what, exactly? Court reporting, yes, but most journo positions don't need that.    
    
    
    @christofflennon @rachelabartlett It's desirable, not essential. Like an extra language.    
    
    
    @christofflennon @rachelabartlett Well that's just a question of preparedness. Like having a spare pencil.    
    
    
    @christofflennon @rachelabartlett But I agree -- it is preferable, but it's not essential anymore.    
    
    
    @mattwhitehorn Hi Matt - can you drop me a line on dave.lee@bbc.co.uk asap? Cheers!    
    
    
    Subtle: http://bit.ly/1glADjr  (h/t @jonathanhaynes )    
    
    
    @danwhitejourno I agree!    
    
    
    @ShamoonHafez It links to my "official" one. Just keeps things professional... none of my aimless twaddle from this account!    
    
    
    @ShamoonHafez I'll send you a postcard next    
    
    
    Woah: RT @CourtNewsUK: Hey trainee reporters! How d'you think your shorthand would have stood up to this little baby?
http://bit.ly/1bry7sq     
    
    
    "New concert for Aswad" ... well played, Songkick. Well played.    
    
    
    Ah Apple Maps, where Marks & Spencer is given more prominence than Kings Cross station.    
    
    
    Eagerly awaiting  @James_morgan's crap story later...    
    
    
    Deep... RT “@GreenwichMean: It's 6.31pm. Your parents don't love you.”    
    
    
    Amen brother RT “@benjrooney: I swear the next PR company that sends me release about "Black Friday" in the UK is going on my spam list    
    
    
    @JoshHalliday ...happy birthday.    
    
    
    @OnlineLivesC4 You're not following, so can't DM. Drop me a line - email's in bio.    
    
    
    Peckham has a "Nigel Road". Please tell me there's a famous Nigel.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle loooooligel    
    
    
    Free the Dolphin 1. RT “@BBCWorld: 'Death sentence' for tiny dolphin http://bbc.in/1imr7ks ”    
    
    
    Just bought some teeny bits of bitcoin. Am I a millionaire yet?    
    
    
    @jamiembrown Well indeed!    
    
    
    Bought $42 worth of bitcoin earlier. Now they're worth $51. BRING ON RETIREMENT.    
    
    
    @londonDLR Drunk bloke shouting and threatening people on the bank train pulling into heron quays now. Front carriage. Get rid?!    
    
    
    @PerveenAkhtar @darrenwaters lies    
    
    
    The BBC News party is the last pillar of abject misery.    
    
    
    @scosteloe 8 minutes! Visit my drunk self at this table. I'm far too drunk to move.    
    
    
    @GregCochrane BUT YOU STILL MISS IT, GREG. Don't you? No? Oh balls. Sending you my CV.    
    
    
    @ginandting Thanks for the pick-me-up    
    
    
    @NonLeaguePaper 10/10 punning    
    
    
    @kezamacdonald For me, AC easily the most impressive PS4 title. Pure joy to play - unlike the stop-start of COD and Killzone    
    
    
    @shivamLM One must learn to love one's self, young warrior.    
    
    
    "I have a Word file that's 200 pages long that's just stray bits of Alan." - Armando Iannucci talks Partridge http://bbc.in/19gsPKO     
    
    
    Spam is getting more adorable: http://bit.ly/1g5Am70     
    
    
    @MichaelDMillar Economic recovery will cost you an arm and a... just an arm. Well played, Nelson.    
    
    
    @BrianHonan @helpnetsecurity Sounds suspicious...    
    
    
    Turning into quite the year for @CambridgeUtdFC. 5 points clear at the top (w/ game in hand), and into F.A Cup 2nd round. Delicious.    
    
    
    Ok, Thinkstock, give me something decent to illustrate a botnet story. ... .... http://bit.ly/1bfXwns  Great.    
    
    
    @Trinifood Just two :-(    
    
    
    @pagefair Looking to talk to someone at Pagefair asap for BBC News online story. Please drop me a line - email in bio. Cheers!    
    
    
    @FaySadro STRAP IN, we're getting burgery    
    
    
    Great news: RT @SPINmagazine: 'Black Panties' man @RKelly will liberate new 'Trapped in the Closet' chapters in 2014 http://bit.ly/1eWm8SM     
    
    
    Can anyone suggest a website that's utterly covered in horrid ads?    
    
    
    @jonnybradford Well that's just perfect! haha    
    
    
    I do love a multi-layered pun! RT @suttonnick: "The long ranger" #tomorrowspaperstoday #bbcpapers pic.twitter.com/MPPvfEiBTW”    
    
    
    @LINGsCARS @securityninja heh, you know what - I realised that immediately after tweeting that. No ads, just... busy :)    
    
    
    @LINGsCARS @securityninja did laugh at your "message" re: cookie directive, too...    
    
    
    Up next on Buzzfeed: "17 cockatoos freaking out about the BBC website" ... possibly.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle Ha! Like it. Reminds me of this (which I'm sure you'll have seen) .. http://bit.ly/Wxaai     
    
    
    @jackschofield @jangles Cheers    
    
    
    Loving @Drawing_daily. Phenomenal.    
    
    
    @drawing_daily I'm already pretty monsterish, to be fair.    
    
    
    Do you need to book a genius bar slot to bring in a broken Macbook?    
    
    
    @BBCFarayi What a great grudge match that would be!    
    
    
    @Journalisti @jaredbkeller @fleetstreetfox Please... let's not get distracted by idiots on Twitter.    
    
    
    +1 >> RT @fergalkeane47: #Mandela Outstanding contribution by @nomsa_maseko on BBC Ten News.    
    
    
    Simplicity of the Ten tonight has really worked - measured, genuine anchoring from Huw Edwards. Two brilliant guests, all key details.    
    
    
    A sign of Madiba's fight: When "Life in pictures" story was first being prepared on BBC site, it was story no. 10651690. (cont)    
    
    
    Tonight's story announcing his death? No. 25249520.    
    
    
    @jiiimmyw See follow up tweet -- news of his death was story number 25249520    
    
    
    Special programme on Mandela's death now airing on BBC1.    
    
    
    @TonyChurnside Not quite like that, unfort - started at 10000000, and jumped a few to 20000000 when new CPS was rolled out.    
    
    
    @TonyChurnside But it's a LOT of stories.    
    
    
    Wonderful live pictures of South Africans dancing in the streets tonight    
    
    
    FW De Klerk live on BBC now.    
    
    
    FW De Klerk: "He's a remarkable man. His biggest legacy will be emphasis on reconciliation. He lived reconciliation."    
    
    
    I will! RT @BrettTechLawyer: @davelee pass on thanks for removing the geo-blocking to the news 24 online output.    
    
    
    International broadcaster in "broadcasting world news" shock. Come on, Spectator: http://bit.ly/1iEhUUP     
    
    
    @Linguagroover @spectator Ridiculous, isn't it. The full stop in the headline makes me wonder if very few people saw it before it went live.    
    
    
    Past and present Africa corrs for the NYT reflect on Mandela on this stylish page: http://nyti.ms/1gIgiot     
    
    
    "He had his part in life, and he did it very well. It's fine he goes. He was old." - touching vox-pop from streets of Soweto.    
    
    
    Mandela 1918-2013 - BBC News Online special report in full: http://bbc.in/1iEkqKQ     
    
    
    Taking bets on whether the Metro's frontpage will be hampered by a wraparound for the new PlayStation...    
    
    
    Eng and Aus teams will wear black armbands for today's play in the Ashes, reports @bbctms + minute's silence.    
    
    
    Oh wonderful > RT @suttonnick: Quite a cartoon by @BrookesTimes in tomorrow's Times http://bit.ly/1gIiV9V     
    
    
    @alexhuds evens    
    
    
    The pic! RT “@Toure_yaya42: I am the master of my fate.. I am the captain of my soul pic.twitter.com/bOqu7RUGfj”    
    
    
    Missed this - a "new" Michael Jackson track was leaked this week. A cover of Horse With No Name:  http://bit.ly/1iG1AD9     
    
    
    Recorded in 1998, around the time of the History album (i.e. when his voice was still holding up a bit)    
    
    
    @scottgoodacre Ah it's alright. Just a studio outtake, really.    
    
    
    @scottgoodacre The 'Jackson Estate' isn't known for its subtlety in milking whatever they can.    
    
    
    @scottgoodacre Plus Sony's continued feeling that MJ shortchanged them with his 5-year deal which only led to one cack album and a lawsuit    
    
    
    @charlesarthur Hater    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy GET OUT    
    
    
    @alexhuds That's libel. I'll take a settlement of £3.    
    
    
    @alexhuds Check your email please chap    
    
    
    "The proof is in the pudding, and the pudding, in this case, is a football." Still the best World Cup build-up: http://bit.ly/1iGTYQP     
    
    
    I preferred these when Wogan did the commentary    
    
    
    Group E please!    
    
    
    @woodybarber @karlpilkingtonq TAKE MY MONEY    
    
    
    In line for a @MotherFlipperuk masterpiece.    
    
    
    Cambridge out of the cup. Very unlucky. Three very strong penalty appeals. Oh well.    
    
    
    @Liberationtech @Techlicious my piece isn't about surveillance tech at all.    
    
    
    @Liberationtech @Techlicious that's the point I make in the last line.anti-ad people say relevance is the answer, but that requires tracking    
    
    
    @Liberationtech @Techlicious which I pointed out is contentious.    
    
    
    @Liberationtech I did, actually - but the ethics question is about hindering revenues, not tracking. I've purposefully not made the link    
    
    
    @Liberationtech Internet ads *can* be a form of surveillance, but not always. As I said, my piece was about a diff debate.    
    
    
    @Liberationtech purely: should you block revenue streams for free sites. Tracking debate is separate to that    
    
    
    @kellyrose love a bit of bubes, so I'm flattered    
    
    
    Anyone else get a press release about Sterling Moss's new bathroom? Mesmerising.    
    
    
    Rush hour on the Thames clipper. Empty. £6.50 one way. What a waste of effort all round.    
    
    
    Great announcements though: "The next pier is London Eye. Disembark here for the London Eye."    
    
    
    Great positive mental attitude, I like it RT “@Owlinflowers: @davelee Yes but Dave you now have your own personal boat.”    
    
    
    I've written 43 drafts in Medium. I've published one of them. Christ, there's your procrastination problem right there.    
    
    
    @KatStorrSky Well that's my night's sleep ruined    
    
    
    @KatStorrSky He's... terrifying.    
    
    
    @charlieemmeline Brains doesn't have enough admirers    
    
    
    Ben Whishaw tipped to play Freddie Mercury in upcoming biopic http://bit.ly/1cmemhi     
    
    
    @hannah_goes Where have you BEEN    
    
    
    @hannah_goes Just here, on this chair. You never call. You never visit.    
    
    
    Looking for hi-tech inspiration for cooking Christmas dinner. Anyone? #journorequest    
    
    
    Ha! Wearable fatigue... I'd avoid our CES coverage ... RT @lws_clrk: @davelee please nothing on wearables, whatever you write    
    
    
    @JocelynMedhurst Ooh, interesting! Thanks    
    
    
    @DanaHashem @virginmedia Heh, nice try.    
    
    
    @Poynter @carr2n Lucky students!    
    
    
    @stevenblum Thanks, will take a look    
    
    
    Terrific explainer on the #CAR crisis. Our website should be crammed with these http://bbc.in/1hKpoEk     
    
    
    Beginning of the end? N Korea flogs its gold reserves in 'sign of economic collapse' http://bit.ly/18AYExI     
    
    
    The view from the top of the Burj Khalifa... looking down. Terrifying. http://bit.ly/1jMcOUp     
    
    
    @TonyNewsCamera Have replied!    
    
    
    @JonathanEx @gmedia LAD. Well in, congrats.    
    
    
    Mash-up: Fake Mandela sign language man vs Kanye West http://bit.ly/1bW6QPd     
    
    
    Brb, just looking for Mary Poppins RT @matt_cav_: The view from London Bridge, looking east along the Thames. http://bit.ly/1f6ZeHT     
    
    
    @ktm_film Would be great to see it screened in London. @frontlineclub ?    
    
    
    Protest ban needed to prevent "violent" behaviour. http://bit.ly/IKPJTk  How about: use the law as it is to arrest violent people?    
    
    
    @PollyTT ...They posted it to you?!    
    
    
    @PollyTT ew    
    
    
    @ktm_film @frontlineclub Nice one, will look out for it.    
    
    
    It irritates me how talented @timoncheese is. It's greedy, if anything.    
    
    
    @tomwarren COME AND HAVE A LOOK AT OUR MOUSE MAT    
    
    
    Actually rather remarkable: Here's a crow having a bit of a laugh sliding down a roof on a mayonnaise lid http://bit.ly/1iXiwVL     
    
    
    @flashboy I just love the idea of nature just larking about --- wonder what the scientific explanation of this would be?    
    
    
    @evilchili get on the roof, lad! Get on the roof!    
    
    
    @priyal I... I've heard it. It's evil.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle let's have lunch there on Saturday?    
    
    
    @BBCRosAtkins that tweet deserves to be in some kind of hall of fame    
    
    
    @chris_mandle that's a shame "geez"    
    
    
    @spidoux84 @MichFrenC4 That git!    
    
    
    @JoannaUK Not sure about this. It's an advert for Woolworths, no? Far too many logos in it not to be.    
    
    
    It's headlines like this that make technology journalism so utterly depressing sometimes: http://read.bi/18Egdx0     
    
    
    @JoannaUK I'm feeling pretty cynical -- true -- but I still think it's a little tacky    
    
    
    @JoannaUK Fair point    
    
    
    Bit of plinky-plonky Adele before Instagram event. MAYBE IT'S A CLUE.    
    
    
    (It's not. Obviously. Just fancied doing a spot of LIVE TECH BLOGGING)    
    
    
    Ray Charles now playing. Wanted to use a bit of Ray in a BBC piece once - was ridiculous to get the rights. Doubt Instagram have paid...    
    
    
    Sod the announcement, let's just listen to Ray all afternoon. Just an old sweet songgg    
    
    
    @ajdomanico Source?    
    
    
    Boooooo! Put Ray back on! Booooooooooooo    
    
    
    @benjrooney What do you mean?! I'm a natural.    
    
    
    "it's about moments" ... is something he's about to say.    
    
    
    While we wait, I'm going to start doing a few reviews.    
    
    
    Cardigan: 6/10, poor button distribution.    
    
    
    Foliage: 9/10    
    
    
    Promise I'll tweet news if/when it happens at the Instagram thing. I'm not just dicking about.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle Can confirm there are no pockets #breaking    
    
    
    Dog: 3/10    
    
    
    First thing: Google+-style groups to share pictures with certain people.    
    
    
    "Moments"... told ya. Credit where it's due - beautifully designed.    
    
    
    Instagram direct available today on iOS and Android    
    
    
    @chris_mandle Apparently so    
    
    
    Instagram have cut off the livestream for the Q+A. The interesting bit. Poor form.    
    
    
    And they won't let journos there film it either.    
    
    
    Who's at the #instagramdirect presser? Ask them why they're not letting us see the livestream anymore. Ta.    
    
    
    @TheOnlyGuru None. Might dock a point for that, actually.    
    
    
    @LydiaBreakfast @anjalimullany Happy to give you the other side - guilt-ridden, but prohibitively busy reporter...    
    
    
    "Checking facts is important, because facts are important." Too right. @bobbie on the money: http://bit.ly/IRERmW     
    
    
    I laughed too hard at this: RT @davelee1968: Non-ironic graphic spotted on tonights Look North. http://bit.ly/Jbqs5x     
    
    
    There's a subreddit where people just count together. They've just got over 100k. http://bit.ly/18I8NvS  .. no, me neither.    
    
    
    @RafaelHwang Hi Rafael -- trying to get hold of an Egg Minder to feature in BBC TV piece. Can you help?    
    
    
    @RafaelHwang Do you have any in the UK?    
    
    
    @RafaelHwang That'd be great -- I've tried the pr@quirky.com address, but no luck so far. Direct email for Tiffany would be good, thanks!    
    
    
    Great storytelling in this piece: RT @BBCNewsMagazine: The tragic death of film-maker who chose to be homeless: http://bit.ly/18IC2ys     
    
    
    Is there a way to download your own clips off YouTube without using some dodgy plug-in?    
    
    
    As in, clips I've uploaded myself...    
    
    
    @JonathanEx Lovely, ta    
    
    
    @caro_milanesi Thanks for all your comments/quotes/advice! Good luck with new horizons    
    
    
    Quick survey: experiences of using Uber in London, anyone? Good, bad?    
    
    
    @leydon Hit and miss... how so? Bad cars/drivers?    
    
    
    @leydon Great, thanks - I'll put that to them.    
    
    
    @cathywhite10 Ha... do expand....    
    
    
    @rmitty You're very bad in Dalston    
    
    
    This is great: big number-crunch looking at how far teams will need to travel to win the World Cup http://bit.ly/ITUTfY     
    
    
    London Bridge station. Has it ever not been completely knackered? Trains never on time. Miserable.    
    
    
    @Owlinflowers ha, don't get me started on the bloody boats    
    
    
    If you're not watching Boyzone on ITV1 you're dead inside.    
    
    
    @PerveenAkhtar I'm so disappointed in you Perveen.    
    
    
    Ha. Fair enough. RT “@gnei11: @davelee Bowie night on BBC four ffs!”    
    
    
    @MartinBelam 67% for me. *sticks mophie up arse*    
    
    
    That awkward moment you accidentally order a curry to @chris_mandle's house and have to cancel it before he scoffs the thing.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle Turns out Hungry House "remembers" where you live better than I do...    
    
    
    @chris_mandle Yeah! I think it was that night we ordered so many nuggets they thought we were lying    
    
    
        
    
    
    @lucyknighton My theory is that he buried himself... ;-)    
    
    
    "He's my friend, he's your friend..." .. reminds me of Joey's hand song ... "oh wait that's your hand, no wait it's my hand..."    
    
    
    @EmilyBarron89 Pull yourself together Baz!    
    
    
    @RichLeighPR Your wifi is clearly a genius!    
    
    
    @RichLeighPR WIFE! I meant wife. Jesus. I need to change jobs.    
    
    
    Who are these people who get so excited?! I just don't understand.    
    
    
    Some odd sound issues in that performance, no?    
    
    
    @tomwarren Sound issues during Nicole's performance last year too.... OOOH... conspiracy. I need to go out.    
    
    
    Figured it out ... RT @thesundaypeople: Is that the ghost of Chrisopher Maloney I can hear?    
    
    
    Was it Jedward?! RT @mrjamieeast: Hahaha Jedward testing their mics!!!    
    
    
    Quite enjoying Jedward actually.    
    
    
    WAGNER YES    
    
    
    Went out dressed as Wagner once. Amazing. Never been such a hit with the girls. #lobshack pic.twitter.com/qjD0yU6nRE    
    
    
    @STYLATORARMY I intend to do all of those things anyway....    
    
    
    Get nervous when people favourite a "funny" tweet. Feel like they're taking down evidence. Looking at you, @beccacaddy .    
    
    
    @RyHunt19 Shirt cost me £70 from a vintage shop. Mental. Kept it.    
    
    
    @beccacaddy My boss fav'd a tweet sent at 2am once. Was bricking it.    
    
    
    @LewisWiltshire You might have to take that back... this is awful.    
    
    
    Frost/Nixon, Paxman/Howard, O'Leary/Flowers    
    
    
    Cracking Wossy line-up later    
    
    
    @chris_mandle @AccidentalP Noooooooooo    
    
    
    Few women in the world sexier than Gillian Anderson!    
    
    
    @darrenwaters The truth is out there    
    
    
    Making a showreel. Might pop in that clip of me performing as Michael Jackson at the school talent show, summer 2003.    
    
    
    "Sure, I lack gravitas, but look at that moonwalk..."    
    
    
    @JonathanEx Bloody good point that    
    
    
        
    
    
    @sarabenwell Why's that harsh?!    
    
    
    @nualaloves Me too, Nuala. Me too.    
    
    
    My theory is that Victoria has always pulled the strings with Dave. He's only ever played for clubs in cities with global fashion weeks...    
    
    
    @mrjonkelly At least it's not Lawro    
    
    
    This has to be one of the best Beckham interviews ever - a man retired gently into family life. Good on 'im.    
    
    
    Leona what have you done    
    
    
    @nualaloves Well that was a given    
    
    
    @luke_morton Hanger in there    
    
    
    @jessbrammar you'd expect more from the drivers    
    
    
    @NatashaClark92 I love how the "have fun in real life" night has, er, a hashtag...!    
    
    
    @NatashaClark92 What is this 'real life' you speak of?!    
    
    
    @abbiquinn I've no time for poetic niceness at 04:49am. P    
    
    
    @ShaunPlatt Yeah - confused though, have changed pw and revoked a few apps... But hasn't stopped them. Hmm    
    
    
    So - malware that posted tweets from me earlier also followed 50 people. Haven't seen that before...    
    
    
    Much preferred #SPOTY when it was the small, intimate do. This is a bit pants.    
    
    
    @tomwarren i love the ingenuity, though. Well played.    
    
    
    Inspired by @uefacorruption , thinking about what else we could "predict".    
    
    
    @peterbradwell @BBCTech very interesting, thank you    
    
    
        
    
    
    Is there a new Anchorman film out?    
    
    
    Me: "which train is going to greenwich?" Guard: "Maybe the next one" Me: "maybe?" Guard: "Or the one after that." ... great.    
    
    
    @NFFCbarker well in lad. Keep up the fight.    
    
    
    @wonky_donky @flashboy I have a blog post titled "Technology journalism faces extinction -- good"  drafted, but it needs the right moment...    
    
    
    @stevelee23 ...?!?    
    
    
    @stevelee23 Even more confused that @chris_mandle fav'd my reply! Nutter.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle I'm keen to hear your "analysis", Nelson!    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy Please tell me you said that.    
    
    
    Writing the BBC's round-up of the viral year. I've got a shortlist of about, er, 30 things. Suggestions welcome.    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy Text her    
    
    
    @RichStanton Hahahhah. Yes. Can't believe I'd left that off!    
    
    
    @penelopeloves Stop hitting the oven with a stick    
    
    
    @BrettTechLawyer That was last year, no?!    
    
    
    @chrishams .. ? Link?    
    
    
    @chrishams Oh of courseeeee    
    
    
    @chrishams Ha, very nice. Like a tuneful version of the Old Spice campaign    
    
    
    Love @vitt2tsnoc's bio: "All views my own, not BBC's. Probably because I don't work there."    
    
    
    Odd request of the day: anyone know a great barber shop quartet in London?    
    
    
    @barbershopogram Hello there -- I've just dropped you guys an email with an idea. Please take a look when you have a moment!    
    
    
    @Sebussy Looking for help on a rather bonkers idea. Any YouTube clips I can check out?    
    
    
    @Sebussy Possibly my favourite song ever. Taking a look now.    
    
    
    @Sebussy Can you DM me your email addy? cheers!    
    
    
    @WillardFoxton Oi oi!    
    
    
    @chris_mandle Takes time.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle @ajhalls1 Sod off Lego    
    
    
    @nmalinarich Cracking sign-off    
    
    
    @hirstmike Ta!    
    
    
    @lydialeavitt why I oughta    
    
    
    Expecting this debate to come up at the next #PMQs... http://bbc.in/1bZU5kY     
    
    
    New banknotes will be Churchill fiver in 2016, and then Jane Austen tenner a year after that.    
    
    
    Like the idea of a fiver being dubbed a "Churchill" now. Or even a "Sir Winston".    
    
    
    @EmilyPurserSky "Lend us a Sir Winston, Em, I fancy a pint"    
    
    
    @EmilyPurserSky It works!    
    
    
    @DKCrewe I'm stopping that right now before it catches on    
    
    
    Oh this is good too... RT @UkieAndyT: @davelee A 'Winnie', surely?    
    
    
    "The press service cannot answer questions about individual cases, judgements and decisions." - useful Swedish courts press office, there.    
    
    
    @Blonde_M I'm just trying to ascertain what a ruling was... bit crap, really.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Spelt out my name over the phone. Got to E. "Is that E, for evil?" ... well I guess...    
    
    
    "Hundreds of young men from Britain [fighting in Syria]". Great story here: http://bit.ly/19wvjsj     
    
    
    @Trinifood @NiciC @Owlinflowers @bensutherland OH GOD YES    
    
    
    @decath10n @JNETTEKWAKYE Maybe she understood perfectly...!    
    
    
    @dmuper Do you want a job mate? Looks like you're having a tough Christmas.    
    
    
    Urgh. "Quietly" in tech headlines again. Spotify "quietly" updates app. What does that even mean?!    
    
    
    What's the opposite? "Pyrotechnics and chorus of kazoos herald Spotify app update"    
    
    
    Always a blast > RT @Poynter: See who topped @CraigSilverman's annual best/worst errors and corrections list for 2013 http://bit.ly/1hkGKoL     
    
    
    Wow, looking forward to this: an intimate documentary about Mitt Romney (a Netflix original, no less) http://bit.ly/IV6Q5J     
    
    
    Apple has piddled all over John Lewis' chips, no?    
    
    
    via @staceybartlett - Look at the URL in this Daily Mail piece about Watkins: http://dailym.ai/1bQt1Uy     
    
    
    That's not one of those hoaxed URLs... that's the actual hard-linked url from the Mail's homepage.    
    
    
    I mean I get why that's been generated like that -- but still !    
    
    
    @flashboy I just think, for reasons of context, you'd edit that out    
    
    
    @Nero @flashboy I think it's the way the Mail's CMS drops words like 'as' that makes the context a bit brutal, is all.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Who needs an office when you can just work from an iron storage container?! Ace work from @kprescott ... http://bbc.in/1i3qN98     
    
    
    Terrible PR pun of the day: "1 in 5 Christmas hosts are a Webeneezer Scrooge"  ... I actually quite like it.    
    
    
    @chris_mandle You wouldn't!    
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy Wasn't she just drawing attention to a brilliant piece in the Village Voice? Awareness raising...?    
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy I was surprised as to the extent of the allegations against R Kelly - the point of the piece isn't that they're new    
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy But that very little has happened as a result. That was Caitlin's surprise (and mine too....)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MandaMindie Email is in my bio. Cheers!    
    
    
    @MandaMindie Haha, don't worry. No-one noticed. Apart from EVERYONE    
    
    
    @marklittlenews Hi Mark - please get in touch, keen to talk to you for BBC News piece. Email in bio.    
    
    
    @nravitz Hi Natalie -- BBC News here. Can we use this pic?    
    
    
    @nravitz No prob! Cheers. What's the credit? 'NewsCorp' ?    
    
    
    Might make a start on the Christmas shop. What's Oxford Street like today? (Besides windy as hell...)    
    
    
    @WillardFoxton quieter than Friday, then. Good good.    
    
    
    @MsSaraKelly Camden Market will be blown over any moment now, I'm sure of it    
    
    
    @getbentsaggy Are you planning any Christmas tricks for your neighbour, Chris?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ffgqc Hi Francis, have something to ask - what's best email for you?    
    
    
    Christmas break now truly in sight. Now playing this on repeat: http://bit.ly/19nofQI  #beerbeerbeer    
    
    
    @chris_mandle racist    
    
    
    @dhrutishah @lucyburton @peter_page That... that has to be sarcasm    
    
    
    Do feel slightly sorry for the ISPs getting grief for blocking sites. None of them wanted blocking in the first place.    
    
    
    Then again, none had the bottle to oppose it on the record...    
    
    
    @GreenwichMean it's Christmas you miserable old sod! Stop tormenting me!    
    
    
    @maggieshiels merry Christmas :)    
    
    
    Merry Christmas to all - particularly friends working in the newsroom today and tonight.    
    
    
    Stick a fork in me    
    
    
    Seeing out the day with a bit of reading. First: "Is Google Wrecking Our Memory?" by Clive Thompson  http://www.slate.com/articles/health_and_science/science/2013/09/are_search_engines_and_the_internet_hurting_human_memory.html …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @katiemcp you look lost    
    
    
    This is great > "Think Again: Mexican Drug Cartels" by Evelyn Krache Morris http://www.foreignpolicy.com/articles/2013/12/03/think_again_mexican_drug_cartels …    
    
    
    Watching football with my Nan. "Why aren't they English?" ... here we go.    
    
    
    "He's got a funny name, hasn't he? Tor-ey yar-yar" #footballnan    
    
    
    @DanCloughLT Ha, no. Might get me arrested.    
    
    
    Need @LewisWiltshire round here to explain to my mum that I can both watch TV and use my laptop at once. That's the point.    
    
    
    @cgalbraith MONEY    
    
    
    @theJeremyVine That's Stratford!    
    
    
    Great backstory to Johnny Cash's A Boy Named Sue http://mentalfloss.com/article/30082/johnny-cashs-boy-named-sue-was-written-shel-silverstein …    
    
    
    @markstencel What a treat - thanks for this. Love reading classics from the archives    
    
    
    Hi @FirstCC, what kind of service are you running out of Huntingdon tomorrow?    
    
    
    So smart - Oyster-like card in Singapore tells traffic lights to give elderly extra green man time http://www.onemotoring.com.sg/publish/onemotoring/en/on_the_roads/traffic_management/green_man_plus.html …    
    
    
    @FirstCC but you're charging full peak prices...?    
    
    
    "Are you charging full peak prices today?"
"Yes."
"Are you running a full peak service?"
"No."

Bravo.    
    
    
    @Phooto Too soon. I'm hurting.    
    
    
    @WillardFoxton My thoughts exactly. Research like that adds very little to the debate    
    
    
    @chelleajohnson Ha! Sorry to disappoint. Try something else? I hear meth's quite lucrative.    
    
    
    @textfiles Hi Jason - Dave from BBC News in London here. Keen to chat about console archive. Can you drop me a line on dave.lee@bbc.co.uk?    
    
    
    @internetarchive Hi there - hoping to speak to someone asap for BBC story on console archive. I'm on dave.lee@bbc.co.uk . Cheers!    
    
    
    @benjrooney By day's end you'll be both broke and broken.    
    
    
    The license fee covers a lot of things, but one thing's for sure, it doesn't quite stretch to heating at New Broadcasting House.    
    
    
    Might go outside to warm up a bit.    
    
    
    @ruskin147 during the Christmas break...? Rarer than the dodo... ;-)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Popcorn that looks like Donald Trump pic.twitter.com/sl7mIhmOEN    
    
    
        
    
    
    @BoobsRadley @robdelaney "sex thicket"    
    
    
    @adamblenford @nmalinarich Research = dicking about on the internet for the past 12 months...    
    
    
    @hannah_goes keep working hard and one day dead brollies might make it in there ;-)    
    
    
    @Cohen_Goes_HAM @christianhern @mikebutcher @jemimakiss RT rarely means an endorsement. Otherwise thousands of us endorsed Ed Balls.    
    
    
    "If you're later than 8 there is a good chance you'll start the year with a lamb cutlet up your arse." .. should probably be on time tonight    
    
    
    @kenyanpundit lovely turn of phrase. I'm stealing it for myself :)    
    
    
    @flashboy have you been reading my mum's texts?    
    
    
    So slow to this, but utterly addicted to Papers, Please. Why's it not on iOS?!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @charlesarthur months ago sadly - maybe he's given up. Shame - such a smart title.    
    
    
    @charlesarthur @dukope feel bad now - people asking him about it constantly!    
    
    
    Happy new year all!    
    
    
    @chris_mandle I wanna plonka plonk with you Christoph Mand! 2014.    
    
    
    @jamesrbuk square!    
    
    
    @chris_mandle much sorry. So remorse.  wow    
    
    
    Whatever I said whatever I did I didn't mean it want you back want you back want you back for goooooooood    
    
    
        
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy New Years resolution for Mic: don't worry, be happy    
    
    
    @brokenbottleboy awooooo ooo ooo ooo ooo do be doooo be doo, ooo be doo be doo be doo, ooo be do be do    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Odd goings on this morning. Not even 8am and I've seen four blokes having a pint in the local, and one guy with a big Chinese takeaway.    
    
    
    WHAT DOES IT ALL MEAN?!    
    
    
    Has to be... RT “@claireshiels: @davelee have we had the 3 min warning or something?!”    
    
    
    @WillardFoxton We had to already! Honestly, the morning rush can sometimes get violent.    
    
    
    Brilliant news everyone - Spaceballs has been added to Netflix! http://flip.it/WPyXR     
    
    
    All the "that's not the real tube!" irritations condensed nicely here: http://bzfd.it/1apUSb7  #sherlock    
    
    
    Although - why don't people get just as wound up about "Baker Street" ...?!    
    
    
    T-Mobile trying to pull an Apple with a pre-CES mysterious invite. New Sidekick or GTFO    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ruskin147 Pills? Blimey. We *are* going to have fun    
    
    
    @benjaminbunny Forkin' 'ell    
    
    
    That's quite something... RT @EverydaySexism: A sad snapshot from the Tate website #EverydaySexism http://bit.ly/19KJfLW     
    
    
    +1 RT @flashboy: why doesn’t tweetdeck have an option to block that spider vine    
    
    
    Surprised @waltmossberg + co didn't launch Re/code with a blistering story to put it on the map straight away. Still, best of luck!    
    
    
    @JamesCridland Indeed -- but give it a day or two.    
    
    
    Genuinely fascinating AMA session on Reddit with a guy that has two penises. No, really: http://bit.ly/Kkj6O7     
    
    
    @skyboximaging Hi there, really keen to talk to you. Please get in touch - dave.lee@bbc.co.uk    
    
    
        
    
    
    Is it technically luggage if a suitcase is empty?    
    
    
    @hannah_goes Why not draw a comical double-willy on a post-it note...    
    
    
    @wonky_donky @hollybrocks If this kicks off a "statues who think they're in music videos" meme I'll be bloody delighted.    
    
    
    Annoying that CES allows all the companies to spam journalists en masse, but not the other way round. Would be far more productive!    
    
    
    i.e. I'm trying to email as many fitness companies at the event at once. Proving time consuming    
    
    
    But this is where @charlesarthur pops up and says he's created a small robotic monkey to do it for him    
    
    
    @charlotteahenry aye!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @charlesarthur http://bit.ly/1d1tzd4     
    
    
    @charlesarthur Flippin' 'eck - between that and the spider vine, this has been a terrifying day.    
    
    
    If you’re a fitness tech enthusiast, join @BBCTech’s Las Vegas fun run this Sunday! Sign up here… http://bit.ly/bbcfunrun     
    
    
        
    
    
    Contemplating hiring an Elvis impersonator to join our BBC tech fun run in Las Vegas. Or might just dress up myself.    
    
    
    Al Qaeda is brilliant at bookkeeping, apparently: http://bit.ly/1cfhKcZ     
    
    
        
    
    
    Exactly! RT “@ajhalls1: @davelee why would you need two?”    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Why's the 1931 cancelled?"
"Dunno. Engineering probably."
"When's the next Greenwich train?"
"Probably the 41."

#Probably    
    
    
    @JessicaKRoy "piddles"    
    
    
    This explains EVERYTHING RT @YahooTech: Science: Men who use smiley faces online get hit on less http://bit.ly/KmQpiW     
    
    
    @BenBajarin My laptop is coming - but staying at the hotel. iPad Air and keyboard for me at the event    
    
    
    @danwhitejourno I've never had a dig at you for anything    
    
    
    No-one saw that coming... RT @gigaommobile: Alicia Keys fallin’ out of creative director role with BlackBerry http://bit.ly/KmT5ND     
    
    
    @CarleanneGwen Sort of (John Lewis)    
    
    
    @c4sparks Terrific piece on Brits in Thailand this evening.    
    
    
    @charlesarthur As long as http://bit.ly/c1qsIs  is still working hard at Intel, all is well.    
    
    
    @charlesarthur Was it Intel? Maybe HP. Oh who cares.    
    
    
    @charlesarthur It'd be great if all tech conferences had some kind The Voice format with spinning chairs. "Internet of thi..." *oh sod this*    
    
    
    Problems that don't need solving #31: RT @Gizmodo: This mug lets you harness a hot beverage to warm your hands http://bit.ly/1cLybT1     
    
    
    @stuartmiles I hear you're joining us?    
    
    
    @stuartmiles Mark has 10k in mind, but it's up to you how long you join him for...    
    
    
    @jonfildes Great range of people signed up so far!    
    
    
    @DavidClinchNews Yep!    
    
    
    @DavidClinchNews @marklittlenews A pint to toast your recent news, no less! Let's sort something out. Busy schedule, but can make it work    
    
    
    @tomwarren Very strange, isn't it? The point of that post is to have a go at the security firm, not apologise to users. Bad move, imo.    
    
    
    @tomwarren Growing pains, if I'm being kind.    
    
    
    @mikebutcher Constantly. And so predictably I sometimes do it on purpose as a way of closing the thing.    
    
    
        
    
    
    4) Kick Bishop Brennan up the arse    
    
    
    Tempted to ask my dad - a tube driver on the Victoria line - to do a Reddit AMA. Would anyone care, do we think?    
    
    
    Or this?! Ha RT @willguyatt: @davelee I'd read a texts from mum AMA.    
    
    
    @willguyatt Well quite - I'd have to see about that    
    
    
    @willguyatt And I've clearly just buggered up any chance of doing it anonymously. Dammit.    
    
    
    Regarding London Underground AMAs, here's one that happened a year ago: http://bit.ly/1cMU58p  via @richjm    
    
    
    Colleague: "I can't tell if your tweets are supposed to be funny." .... encouraging.    
    
    
    @maryammaruf FAME    
    
    
    More BBC World Service programmes should be like #BBCOS. Far more relaxed and fun than traditional WS news shows.    
    
    
    @charlesarthur @ProfWoodward 2014's best social media strategy (for companies especially) is cheekiness. @O2 being another good example.    
    
    
    @charlesarthur @ProfWoodward Which is great, cos some poor soul will get it way off the mark and be wildly offensive/racist etc etc. #NEWS    
    
    
        
    
    
    @charlesarthur @williammarriage @pmaher http://bit.ly/1cN8j9o     
    
    
    Another shout-out for the BBC fun run in Las Vegas on Sunday. Please RT and spread the word. Sign up here: http://bit.ly/bbcfunrun  #CES    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Nero That one's terrible    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wow .. virtual currency, in 1999! RT @paulmutton: @davelee @MendzappJames Do you remember Beenz? http://bit.ly/JNPSGn     
    
    
    