Are you a #coffee lover? Then, you'll love Café Culture #Pinotage! Check out Dave's vlog on this fascinating new arrival: http://ht.ly/5Wwoj    
    
    
    tickets left for "Summer Sippers and Picnic Pairings" - August 24 7-8:30pm $20 - don't miss out!    
    
    
    Pinot Evil Sparkling Pinot Noir on the Tasting Bar today - 2-6pm - Delicious new summer wine!    
    
    
    today on the tasting bar: Sottano!! special guest Sebastian Olalla all the way from the winery in Argenting will be pouring from 3-6pm!    
    
    
    @LeVieuxPin @Yaffler @CSWS_Inc both Feenie's Blends  are in stock @EWineNV!    
    
    
    It's Sangria Sunday in North Vancouver!! Join us from 2-6pm and enjoy three different home-made recipes!    
    
    
    @cheritravelgeek have yet to encounter a great iPhone app for record-keeping. Cellar Tracker seems to be the best web-based so far.    
    
    
    Cheers! RT @cheritravelgeek: Follow @EWineNV for excellent wines - huge wine store, tastings etc.    
    
    
    It's our #LabourDay #Wine #Sale! Stock up on some fabulous wines at amazing prices! http://bit.ly/n0QX87  @EWineNV/everything-wine-2    
    
    
    We are now SOLD OUT of My Cousin Vino Chianti! Never fear, however, as we have a great backup Italian Rosso at the same price:...    
    
    
    ...Castel di Maranfusa Rosso, Sicily is $3 off! An unreal $6.99 until Tuesday! http://ht.ly/6kQPO #wine    
    
    
    We've sold out of the #MyCousinVinoChianti and have dropped the price of our #CasteldiMaranfusaRosso to $6.99 - another amazing #wine    
    
    
    Today on the Tasting Bar: 1-4pm "Five Under $15" - 4-6pm "Vina Koyle" with  Export Director Patricio Torres (all the way from Chile!)    
    
    
    Patricio Torres from Chile is in-store pouring Vina Koyle NOW until 6pm - don't miss out!    
    
    
    Viva Italia! Join us today from 2-6pm in North Van for a taste of Italy - Cantina di Negrar's Amarone, Bardolino, and Ripasso!    
    
    
    Sorry, not carried here. RT @Astra_PT: @erin_ireland @Cibo_Uva @Viti_Wine_Lager @balbinaknight have you tried @ewinenv or @edgemontfinewin?    
    
    
    today on the tasting bar: Five Under $15! Budget and Flavour-friendly wines!    
    
    
    Thanks again to @NatHunter953 and @DrewSavage for the coffee and treats this morning! Much appreciated on this rainy Thursday!    
    
    
    Save a buck on this gem of a Malbec! $11.99 until Sept. 22 (or while supplies last). http://ow.ly/1xcxyC     
    
    
    Cheers! RT @NatHunter953: @EWineNV @DrewSavage You guys are my new favourite store! When I'm out of money can I live in your stockroom?    
    
    
    Likewise! Never a dull moment! RT @DrewSavage: @EWineNV Great to meet you guys today - you're amazing enablers ;) @NatHunter953    
    
    
    Cheers for the shout out! Back at you! @Cibo_Uva: #FF day!    
    
    
    Today on the Tasting Bar: Sacred Hill Sauvignon Blanc and Pinot Noir! Some of New Zealand's Finest! 2-6pm    
    
    
    Osoyoos Larose Winemaker Pascal Madevon joins us in-store today from 3-5pm to pour a lineup of his award-winning wine!    
    
    
    Nice job! RT @shabbydog: I just ousted Rob B. as the mayor of Everything Wine on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/b5witV  @EWineMX    
    
    
    http://www.vancouvernow.org/event.php?id=671 …    
    
    
    Need the perfect turkey wine? Our Thanksgiving Weekend Sale starts NOW! http://ht.ly/6Pyoi FREE delivery in BC on orders over $200!    
    
    
    Just in time for the holiday: Burrowing Owl Chardonnay, Merlot and Syrah are in stock now! #BCWine    
    
    
    Do you have tickets for the West Coast Wine & Food Festival yet? Just $25+HST! Pick up a ticket this weekend while you're in for the #sale.    
    
    
    #Turkey pairing alert: Valentin Bianchi Pinot Noir is $2 off and @Team1040's Wine of the Week! http://ht.ly/6PyYO.    
    
    
    Need the perfect turkey wine, #Vancouver? Our Thanksgiving Weekend Sale is on! http://ht.ly/6PU38 FREE delivery in BC on orders over $200!    
    
    
    A late, but deserved, #FF to @PerseusWine - our 1,000th follower!    
    
    
    Yes, we are OPEN! 11:00-6:00 Sunday and Monday for your last-minute wine needs. Happy Thanksgiving, Vancouver!    
    
    
    Cute #dachshund! RT @paintedrockjohn: 18 family members, 5 big dogs & this guy...who's running the show? http://yfrog.com/nwv4kcbj     
    
    
    Thanks! RT @TheAmandaWest: I'm at a store called Everything Wine. Best. Store. Ever.    
    
    
    We're open today until 6pm for your last-minute #turkey wine. AND our sale is still on! Happy Thanksgiving, #Vancouver! http://ht.ly/6SSWd    
    
    
    Just over a week left before the West Coast Wine & Food Festival! Don't miss out on this great evening! - $25+hst    
    
    
    Only 6 tickets left for the "Battle of the Grapes" tasting event THIS WEDNESDAY - only $30+hst - call the store for tickets and details!    
    
    
    There are still a few tickets left for tonight's "Battle of the Grapes" tasting event in North Vancouver! Call 604-929-7277 for tickets!    
    
    
    today from 3-6pm we're pouring Cupcake Wines and serving mini Cupcakes from "Cupcakes" to the first 50 customers who join us!    
    
    
    Tonight! RT @SS_LiffordBC: Wed night @EWineNV West Coast Wine & Food Fest- Come taste some #CharlesSmithWines @KVintners Tix: bit.ly/p3K2Wl    
    
    
    Cheers for the RT, but note, Blasted Church tasting is Friday RT @DianneChow: 3-6pm, @EWineNV, Blasted Church tasting: http://ow.ly/6ZaDH     
    
    
    Can't wait! RT @amykleckner: Looking forward to this tonight - Wed night @EWineNV West Coast Wine & Food Fest Tix: http://bit.ly/p3K2Wl     
    
    
    Such a great night. Thanks to everyone who came out! Lots of new faces & lots of big smiles. Cheers!    
    
    
    Long Shadows Winemaker Release - November 16 - 5-8pm in our Vintage Room! http://www.vancouvernow.org/event.php?id=1013 …    
    
    
    Our Halloween Wine Sale is on now! Shop these scary-good deals in-store or online today and tomorrow! http://ht.ly/7dmy8     
    
    
    TODAY from 2-4pm, we'll be pouring samples of 2010 Black Hills Syrah right out of the barrel! An EWine first, don't miss out!    
    
    
    TODAY: @BlackHillsWine is here from 2pm pouring their killer wines, incl. a barrel tasting of Syrah 2010! Don't miss this rare opportunity!    
    
    
    @winesofcanada @EWineNV, North Vancouver!    
    
    
    We have @HaywireWine pouring their exciting new #BCWine at the tasting bar from 2-5pm today. Drop by & check them out! It's free!    
    
    
    Everything Wine Inventory Blowout Sale starts now! @EWineNV @EWineVictoria @EWineMX http://ht.ly/7pki8     
    
    
    We are open today at 11:15 am, after a moment of silence & respect.    
    
    
    Today from 5-8pm, Long Shadows winemaker Giles Nicault will be in our vintages room pouring through his 7 award-winning wines! Dont miss it!    
    
    
    Beaujolais Nouveau Day begins now @EWineNV!    
    
    
    today at our tasting bar from 2-5pm - California Cabs! Don't miss out - we're opening some real gems!    
    
    
    Try this delicious new single-vineyard Sauvignon Blanc! You can find it on our 90+ Points wall: http://ht.ly/1AQPIA     
    
    
    Save $2 on @vinatarapaca Gran Reserva Cabernet & GR Carmenère until Monday (or while it lasts)! Nice, big reds for rainy Vancouver weather!    
    
    
    Your holiday party red: @WOSACanada Obikwa Merlot 2010 ~ $9.99 @EWineNV. http://ow.ly/1AQVBS     
    
    
    Who loves white Burgundy? We have 2 great 09s from Joseph Drouhin for the holidays: Mâcon-Villages ($22.99) & Pouilly-Fuissé ($34.99)!    
    
    
    Save 30%! Tisdale Merlot and Chardonnay are on sale for an amazing $6.99/bottle. Save an extra 5% on a case! Now through Monday.    
    
    
    @sdacre Andeluna Grand Reserve is great, as are Decero Remolina Vyrd, Luca, Alta Vista Premium, Jean Bousquet Grand Reserve. What price?    
    
    
    It's Day 2 of our biggest #wine sale of the year!  http://ht.ly/7UfYk  Free Shipping on orders over $200. Shop in-store 10-9 or online 24/7    
    
    
    Perrin & Fils 'Les Cornuds' Vinsobres '09: 93 pts, Wine Advocate & $4 off! Winemaker Thomas Perrin tastes & chats: http://ht.ly/7Ugrw     
    
    
    Today! RT @EWineMX: Give @TEAM1040 & @TDMulligan a listen to find out what the latest Wine of the Week will be!    
    
    
    So glad we can help! RT @mrsrhino: I just have to say, I love @EWineNV. Let the wedding begin.    
    
    
    Holiday Wine Sale on NOW until Monday December 19! "try before you buy" at our tasting bar from 2-6pm!    
    
    
    Last minute gift ideas? We have some great wines on sale until Wednesday! http://ht.ly/83af3  Gift baskets, too! http://ht.ly/83ahO     
    
    
    Be sure to tune in to @bt_vancouver tomorrow morning to see our own Sharon McGavin to learn about bubblies for #NYE2011    
    
    
    Happy New Year to all our friends & followers! Thank you 4 your support in 2011. Looking forward to the new wines & new challenges of 2012!    
    
    
    Snow in the forecast? This delicious organic Monastrell from Yecla, Spain is the perfect match 4 winter stew & $2 off! http://ht.ly/8sRJb     
    
    
    Check out this article by @KurtisKolt on the excellent wines of @FraserGallopEst http://ht.ly/8ytWf  - avail. @EWineNV!    
    
    
    Closing up shop @ 5pm for EW staff party @Glowbal_Group Italian Kitchen 2night! You can still shop online 24/7: http://ht.ly/8Cd8M     
    
    
    Evans & Tate Margaret River Cabernet Sauvignon 2005, only $21.99! RT @Shelleyhj: @EWineNV Got any good recommendations for #AustraliaDay?    
    
    
    Is it Torrontes season yet?!  A #wine for grilled halibut or sea bass topped with a chipotle cream sauce... http://ht.ly/8Kj7z     
    
    
    @spookysquirrel Congratulations!    
    
    
    90 points in @robertmparkerjr's The Wine Advocate for $16.99! That's Cubo Tempranillo, our Wine of the Week: http://ht.ly/8Kjgj     
    
    
    Avail. @EWineNV RT @TDMulligan: WineDiva Review: Ganton & Larsen Prospect Shiraz, Okanagan 2008 http://ow.ly/1FfM5x  1 of our SuperBowlWines    
    
    
    Today at the tasting bar, two tasty values from Mendoza, Argentina: @FincaelOrigen Malbec Rosé and Syrah. $13.99/$14.99, respectively.    
    
    
    FREE! RT @diannechow: Thur, Feb 2: 2-6pm, @EWineNV (998 Marine Drive, North Van)
 Three Under $13 wine tasting.    
    
    
    Cheers! RT @ALMURDOCH: Thanks to the staff @EWineNV for recommending '09 Trapiche Broquel Malbec $21.99. Wonderful to drink just on its own!    
    
    
    Enjoy! RT @craig_nvan: @EWineNV Sherry Seminar http://instagr.am/p/GuqEFqNmTT/     
    
    
    “@craig_nvan: Noé : my new favourite #sherry, available at @EWineNV http://instagr.am/p/Gu3DCytmUZ/ ” Our staff's new favourite! Should arrive this week    
    
    
    New arrival: The phenomenal Poggiotondo Chianti Superiore 2007 http://ht.ly/8YIAC  $28.99 - North Vancouver only. (cc @trialto)    
    
    
    Need something for your sweetie? Valentine's Day Wine Sale is on! Shop these great deals (& more) today thru Tuesday: http://ht.ly/904nr     
    
    
    @almurdoch #BCWine Pinot Noir: We like @FoxtrotVineyard, @CedarCreekWine Platinum & @HaywireWine! Any to add, @TDMulligan @TheSpitter?    
    
    
    @ALMURDOCH @TDMulligan @TheSpitter ...also try @MissionHillWine Reserve, @Stoneboat, @CastoroWinery #BCWine Pinot Noir    
    
    
    Cal Y Canto (ES) & Santa Alicia Cabernet (CL) are big hits so far this weekend! Those wines, & many more, on sale now! http://ht.ly/91pjt     
    
    
    Perfect for Valentine's Day! Take your pick of great sparklers from FR http://ht.ly/91q5O  or ES http://ht.ly/91q7R  both just $12.99!    
    
    
    1 Litre Format! #Spanish Red Blend #Wine $2 OFF http://bit.ly/w5FJlY  #sale at @EWineNV @EWineMX @EWineVictoria    
    
    
    Our latest blog is from our own John McLaughlin @athirstynomad http://bit.ly/AfaKtq  on his recent trip around the #Australia #wine country    
    
    
    Join us today any time between 12 and 1 for a complementary lunch and wine tasting in our vintages room with Casa Lapostolle!    
    
    
    Lunch is served @Everything Wine in North Vancouver today from 12-1pm! Casa Lapostolle is here for a complimentary wine tasting and luncheon    
    
    
    Join us from 12-1 in our Vintage Room TODAY for a complementary lunch and wine tasting with Lapostolle Winemaker Andrea Leon Iriarte!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar: Desert Hills! Ian Ross will be here from 2-6pm - Don't miss out!    
    
    
    @miss_sarahng @PaintedRockJohn Red Icon 2009 is in-stock in our Vintages Room @ $54.99/bottle. Come & get it!    
    
    
    Join us today from 2-6pm to experience the outstanding value, flavour, and variety that Spanish wine has to offer! Free!    
    
    
    Still a few bottles on the shelf! RT @traceyleebarr: @liffordnicole Loved it! (bought it!) Heard a rumour I can buy more @EWineNV #decero    
    
    
    Happy St. Patrick's Day! Our March Madness sale continues today with fresh oysters from @ToTheBoathouse & $1 off Oyster Bay Sauvignon Blanc!    
    
    
    Shop our March Madness sale this weekend and find a new favourite! Big savings until Monday, in-store and online! http://ht.ly/9Isek     
    
    
    “@EWineMX: While they might not be Irish, we've got fresh oysters on the bar today, 3-5 pm from the Boathouse, pairing with Oyster Bay SB”    
    
    
    @athirstynomad well done John! Looking forward to your nextb #vlog    
    
    
    Cheers, @georgiastraight readers, for the 3rd place in #GoldenPlates 4 Best Wine Shop! It's gr8 that so many of u make the trip 2 N Van!    
    
    
    @NorthVanHomes sounds great! Let me know if you need anything!    
    
    
    #NowPouring the BEST of #BC wines. Stop by our Tasting Bar today from 2-6. See you soon!    
    
    
    Back by popular demand: #Aussie Skulls Shiraz & #USA Wha Cha Ma Call It Chard are finally back it stock. Get it in store or order online!    
    
    
    Hey #Alberta! Did you hear Everything #Wine & More is coming to town? Follow their #FB page for exciting details --> http://on.fb.me/GUBSqi     
    
    
    @localfoodwine Heyo! Please feel free to ask us if we have a certain #wine you or your followers are looking for! #local #Vancouver #blog    
    
    
    Looking forward to hearing about all your success in your upcoming grande opening in #Lethbridge #Alberta @EWineAndMore    
    
    
    “@ewineandmore: Is there a favourite #wine or #beer that you've been looking for, #Lethbridge? Let us know & we'll try to find it!"    
    
    
    #FYI We will be closing our stores this evening at 5:30pm for our annual full store inventory count. Thanks for understanding!    
    
    
    Our April #wine #events calendar is out! Check out all the fun we're gonna have! http://bit.ly/fZK9Yq  Hope to see you there!!    
    
    
    today at our tasting bar: BLASTED CHURCH!! Delicious wines from 2-5pm    
    
    
    #Easter #Wine #SALE on now until Monday at @EWineNV, @EWineMX & @EWineVictoria, or order online --> http://bit.ly/HbOlDA     
    
    
    Easter Wine Sale is on! Download our sale flyer: http://ow.ly/d/zkn  and shop online, too! http://ht.ly/a5zoW     
    
    
    @DianneChow thanks for the mention!    
    
    
    Lost your dog? We have a pretty & well-mannered black lab-x(?) at the store. We'd love to keep him, but he wants his family back!    
    
    
    Such a cutie! Call or DM if he's yours! RT @joecorkscrew: Here he is! Lost Dog North Vancouver @EWineNV pic.twitter.com/tTEnZx5k    
    
    
    #Canucks fans down under! what time is it there?! “@SRusling: loving the live telecast of the @VanCanucks v LA in Adelaide, Australia”    
    
    
    Join us from 2-6pm today to celebrate World Malbec Day! we'll have loads of tasty malbecs to try, paired with tasty empenadas!    
    
    
    The Empanadas are here and the Malbec is open! Drop by for a free sip and sample until 6:00pm! #MyMalbecWorldDay    
    
    
    Good to hear, cheers! RT @jasonccook: Fabulous service @EWineNV yesterday. Went in for a couple of bottles & left with 6! #happenseverytime    
    
    
    Join us today at our Tasting Bar from 2-6pm as we Celebrate Chile! 5 fantastic wines will be open - don't miss out!    
    
    
    @EWineNV's @craig_nvan just posted a blog about his recent experience at @athirsynomad's #NZ #Wine Tasting - http://bit.ly/HPIkMf  #new #blog    
    
    
    Now in stock @ewinenv! $29.99 http://instagr.am/p/I0hyd-lLz8/  http://www.everythingwine.ca/product/El-Enemigo-Malbec-750-mL …    
    
    
    @gossipsquirrel nice! Be sure to follow the surrey store, too @ewinemx!    
    
    
    “@ewineandmore: 11 days til store open!...". Like our FB fan page for more info! - http://on.fb.me/GUBSqi ” #wine #lethbridge #Alberta    
    
    
    8 tickets left for Wednesday night's French Classics tasting! 7-8:30pm - $30 +hst - call 604-929-7277 for tickets!    
    
    
    Something VERY exciting is being launched tomorrow on-line .... Interested? Get on our #VIP #WINE LIST here - http://bit.ly/J7ZPXl     
    
    
    #Deal of the Day! 6 #wines, 2 each, all 90+pts, a $300 value for $250! Quantities are limited so order yours today! http://bit.ly/IbmU1B     
    
    
    The Everything Wine Experience is back! Three consecutive Wednesdays in May $25 per class --  http://www.localwineevents.com/events/detail/421974/twitter … via @worldwineevents    
    
    
    Save over $50 on this great selection of 90+ point wines! Limited quantities! This case offer offer expires May 1! http://ht.ly/aztpe     
    
    
    1-time buy, get it while it lasts! “@joecorkscrew: Semillon lover, @KurtisKolt; this is now avail. @EWineNV: http://instagr.am/p/KBMu3zFLwf/  $27.99!”    
    
    
    Winemaker Michael Fragos from @chapelhillwine is here pouring two of his outstanding wines from 5-7pm! Drop by and say Hi!    
    
    
    Nothing is more exciting than opening day! RT @ewinemx: Congrats and best of luck to our newest store @ewineandmore in Lethbridge, AB!    
    
    
    Our Spring Wine Sale is on now! Shop in-store or online until Monday: http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Spring-Wine-Sale …    
    
    
    Only 5 tickets left for tomorrow night's Everything Wine Experience!!! 7-8:30pm - $25 for one or $50 for all 3 evenings! Call 604 929 7277    
    
    
    Just arrived: @MarimarTorres Cristina Pinot Noir 2007! Maybe Russian River's best Pinot. 95 points, @WineEnthusiast. http://ht.ly/aMG8Y     
    
    
    @athirstynomad anything outstanding?    
    
    
    Join us today from 4-6pm - Australian Winemaker Bill Hardy will be here pouring a brand new lineup of wines!    
    
    
    This killer Marlborough Chardonnay is our Wine of the Week! Vibrant, lively and complex. Great for al fresco dining! pic.twitter.com/0SuXvTcz    
    
    
    Just Arrived: Be the first to try the fabulous new Pinot Gris from @YWCollection! Now in-stock @EWineNV! #BCWine    
    
    
    It's 5 o'clock somewhere! Come on in for an early sip of @LandmarkWines selections from Young & Wyse, Veramonte & Cycles Gladiator til 2pm.    
    
    
    We have a full slate of tastings today at the Tasting Bar: @LandmarkWines until 2pm, Oyster Bay Wines from 2-4 & @Road13Vineyards from 4-6!    
    
    
    Tasting Bar 2-4pm Oyster Bay Wines! We've got all bases covered: bubbly for Mom, crisp whites for the patio and great BBQ reds.    
    
    
    CORRECTION: No @Road13Vineyards this afternoon. Sorry! Watch our blog for a video from yesterday's tasting with Joe to be posted soon!    
    
    
    Happy Mother's Day! Need a last-minute gift? We've got you covered: our Mother's Day gift baskets are still in-stock and ready to impress!    
    
    
    @EWineMX: your new mayor! RT @shabbydog: I just became the mayor of Everything Wine on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/b5witV     
    
    
    Cheers! Come again soon! RT @mallorywatt: I'm at Everything Wine (North Vancouver, BC) http://4sq.com/KTt3en     
    
    
    Good luck with your first #wine sale in #Lethbridge this long weekend, @ewineandmore !    
    
    
    Just partnered up with @CoscaRestaurant for our annual Summer Solstice Wine Festival! We can't wait for June 20th! Tickets available now!    
    
    
    Excited to have @whistlerwater on board for our annual Summer Solstice Wine Festival June 20th!    
    
    
    We're a huge fan of @SmallVineyards ! They recently did a tasting with our staff - read about it here: http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Whats-Sippin …    
    
    
    drop by any of our three locations all weekend and pick up some fabulous wines on sale! try before you buy at our tasting bar!    
    
    
    in-store or by phone! for event details, visit http://ht.ly/b0HZH  RT @phoenix220402: @EWineNV where do we buy the tickets from??    
    
    
    You bet! @EWineMX event details here: http://ht.ly/b0I4f  RT @marlinladner: @EWineNV Will this event also be happening at Morgan Crossing?    
    
    
    Remember @MaipoWines Viognier? Well, it's back and on sale for $9.99! You won't find a better-value Viognier than this: http://ht.ly/b0Im6     
    
    
    Happy we could contribute! RT @van_bellysplash: A very big thank you to @EWineNV in North Vancouver for the #BellySplash2012 sponsorship    
    
    
    Come on down for a sip of wine and stay for the BBQ to support @CampArtaban! We've got great deals and good causes all day long!    
    
    
    the BBQ is on outside and there's wine and cheese at the tasting bar! Come on down to the store this sunny Saturday - Wine Sale on Now!    
    
    
    Wine Sale and BBQ on now! Support @campartaban and stock up on some outstanding summer wines!    
    
    
    BBQ is on in full force! Only a few more hours to come down and support @campartaban in North Vancouver! 998 Marine Dr pic.twitter.com/Kv1xe9RL    
    
    
    We're open all weekend and the sale is on through Tuesday! Check out our great deals here: http://ht.ly/b1gr6     
    
    
    Don't miss out on our 4th annual Summer Solstice Wine Festival, June 20th at all three locations! Tickets only $30+tax pic.twitter.com/8yV3gSBw    
    
    
    We're happy to have it! RT @tugwellcreek: I'm excited to have our #mead at #Everything #Wine in #North #Vancouver!  #YVR #BCWine    
    
    
    Were you out of town this weekend? You didn't miss our sale, it's on until Tuesday! Drop by or shop online: http://ht.ly/b1gsP     
    
    
    Enjoying the sunshine, #Vancouver? Enjoy it even more with a nice bottle of white or rose from our big cooler!    
    
    
    & @EWineMX in Surrey! RT @divafish: Yowzah! @EWineNV sponsored a $4500 wine cellar for BC Centre 4 Ability fundraiser. http://ow.ly/i/Emst     
    
    
    @finnsspace @paulrickett i appreciate the referral! still have the caymus ss magnums in stock. may have to pass on the '82 petrus, though ;)    
    
    
    Including @hopeangracewine Pinot Noir and @FincaDecero Cabernet! RT @bc_cork: #NewWorld Wine Tasting @EWineNV #PremiumSunday 2:00-6:00pm    
    
    
    Be sure to follow them @ewineandmore! RT @joe_fiddler: New fancy wine store!!  @ everything WINE and more http://instagr.am/p/K_LAj3ExOd/  #Lethbridge    
    
    
    Need something new this weekend? $2 off this grill-worthy Italian red: http://ht.ly/biDT6  The sun is coming, #Vancouver!    
    
    
    @LeftFieldCider: we're interested in carrying your ciders @EWineNV! DM me an email address and we can discuss. Cheers!    
    
    
    Today at the Tasting Bar: @SelectWines_BC is pouring Bonterra Organic Vineyards Viognier, Chardonnay & Cabernet Sauvignon 3-6pm. Free!    
    
    
    #FF new rose wines available from: @drinkriverstone, @lfngwine, @missionhillwine, @angovewine & soon @domainedenizas!    
    
    
    Exciting tasting coming up on Thursday in North Van! Matt Mavety from @BlueMtnWinery will be here from 4-6pm! http://scoutmagazine.ca/2012/05/31/goods-blue-mountain-vineyards-cellars-hosting-two-free-tastings-in-vancouver/ …    
    
    
    @BlueMtnWinery will be @EWineNV tomorrow from 4-6pm! Don't miss it http://www.nsnews.com/entertainment/Food+calendar/6737300/story.html …    
    
    
    2 weeks left until #SummerSolstice !! Get your tickets for our annual Wine Festival, Wednesday June 20th 7-9pm https://www.facebook.com/EverythingWinePage#!/events/243338505766044/ …    
    
    
    Excited for the @BlueMtnWinery complimentary tasting at @EWineNV today from 4-6pm!    
    
    
    Matt Mavety from @BlueMtnWinery is in-store NOW until 6pm pouring his delicious wines! pic.twitter.com/4Q1S9q5T    
    
    
    Matt Mavety from @BlueMtnWinery is in-store NOW until 6pm pouring his delicious wines! pic.twitter.com/q06usF0P    
    
    
    Matt Mavety from @BlueMtnWinery is in-store NOW until 6pm pouring his delicious wines! pic.twitter.com/n5sORCfh    
    
    
    Matt Mavety from @BlueMtnWinery is in-store NOW until 6pm pouring his delicious wines! pic.twitter.com/4VKYRDL7    
    
    
    Good Luck! RT @lazy_susan27: I just entered the $5000 Alaskan Cruise Contest with Everything Wine! #enter now! http://n.3tl.ca?p=TJD772AUJUn.3tl.ca/?p=TJD772AUJU     
    
    
    Cute! RT @lfngwine: Row 24 Malbec block had a little surprise for me today! #gottalovefarming pic.twitter.com/rTyPvYO3    
    
    
    I wonder who will #win the $5000 #Cruise trip to #Alaksa for two with @TheSpitter Anthony Gismondi??!! Like us on #fb! http://on.fb.me/NWurQN     
    
    
    Come on down to the store NOW until 6pm! Tim Martiniuk from @stoneboat is here pouring a lineup of his outstanding wines at our tasting bar!    
    
    
    today from 2-6pm at our tasting bar we will be sampling wines from the Southern Hempisphere! Australia, NZ, Chile, Argentina and S.Africa!    
    
    
    Tickets still available in North Van for our Summer Solstice Wine Festival next week! @hurricanegrill will be on-site serving mini burgers!    
    
    
    Excited to have @whistlerwater and @PinnaclePier on board for our Summer Solstice Wine Festival next week! Tickets still available!    
    
    
    Summer Solstice Wine Festival in a week!!! @EWineNV call 604-929-7277 for #tickets - only $30 plus tax, nearly sold out!    
    
    
    Excited to have @TommyCaters on board for our #SummerSolstice #Wine #Festival!! Delicious selections, we can't wait! Tickets still available    
    
    
    Hey, @Miss604! Your followers can win a $5000 Alaska Cruise for 2 w/ @TheSpitter! Click the link & like us on Facebook! http://ht.ly/bz8um     
    
    
    Hey, @vancitybuzz! Your followers can win a $5000 Alaska Cruise for 2 w/ @TheSpitter! Like us on Facebook! http://ht.ly/bz8um     
    
    
    In-stock, and cold! http://ow.ly/i/H9V6  RT @LeftFieldCider: Hello #northvancouver Left Field Cider now available @EWineNV.    
    
    
    Hey, @yelp_vancouver! Your followers can win a $5000 Alaska Cruise for 2 w/ @TheSpitter! Like us on Facebook! http://ht.ly/bz8um     
    
    
    6 days until our #SummerSolstice #Wine #Festival!! Call us for tickets today - we still have a few left! Only $30 plus tax. Wed June 20 7-9    
    
    
    Three wines under Thirteen dollars at our tasting bar today until 6pm!!    
    
    
    Hey, @VIAwesome! Your followers can win a $5000 Alaska Cruise for 2 w/ @TheSpitter! Like us on Facebook! http://ht.ly/bz8um     
    
    
    It's here! @DomainedeNizas Languedoc Rose is the prettiest pink you'll try this summer! $22.99 http://ht.ly/bAPat  pic.twitter.com/nFs4fA23    
    
    
    Hey, @vanmag_com! Your followers can win a $5000 Alaska Cruise for 2 w/ @TheSpitter! Like us on Facebook! http://ht.ly/bz8um     
    
    
    Spoil Dad this weekend with our #FathersDay Wine Sale! On now thru  Monday. http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Fathers-Day-Wine-Sale … pic.twitter.com/fgqXPMmI    
    
    
    #FF our Alaska Cruise contest team: @TheSpitter, @VancouverSun, @VanSunLife & @3TierLogic! Like us on Facebook 2 enter: http://ht.ly/bBGbs     
    
    
    Hey, @wherevancouver! Your followers can win a $5000 Alaska Cruise for 2 w/ @TheSpitter! Like us on Facebook! http://ht.ly/bz8um     
    
    
    Hey, @bt_vancouver! Your followers can win a $5000 Alaska Cruise for 2 w/ @TheSpitter! Like us on Facebook! http://ht.ly/bz8um     
    
    
    .@WeslaWong said it: it's a great day for wine tasting! Drop by to sample a few picks for #FathersDay and take advantage of our great sale!    
    
    
    only 25 tickets left for our #SummerSolstice #Wine #Festival this Wednesday!!! Call 604-929-7277 to reserve your spot!    
    
    
    Happy #FathersDay! Have a gift for Dad yet? Our sale is still on, ends Monday. http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Fathers-Day-Wine-Sale … pic.twitter.com/fgqXPMmI    
    
    
    Our #SummerSolstice Wine Festival is now SOLD OUT!!!    
    
    
    Mark DeVere, Master of Wine, is at our tasting bar NOW until 7pm pouring Robert Mondavi wines!    
    
    
    Another successful #SummerSolstice Wine Festival last night!! Thanks to all who made it out, we hope you enjoyed yourselves!    
    
    
    and a giant thank you to our sponsors @Rockford_Grill @PinnaclePier @hurricanegrill @whistlerwater @TommyCaters    
    
    
    that was quite the show in our vintages room last night at our #SummerSolstice wine festival @LandmarkWines - you really outdid yourself!    
    
    
    Stop by on your way home today for samples of Australia's own Angove wines! Rose and Cab Sauv open to start your weekend off right!    
    
    
    photos from our #SummerSolstice Wine Festival now up!! https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10150880352451402.399502.366292181401&type=3 …    
    
    
    Rained out, #Vancouver? Make it an 'inside' night with a nice bottle of red wine. We're open until 9pm!    
    
    
    Old World Gems from Gabbiano, Tesch, J-P Moueix, Carpineto & more at the tasting bar and in the Vintages Room today until 6pm! #Free!    
    
    
    Heighten your senses, one sip at a time with John & Sean at our Blind Wine Tasting! July 25 @ 7:00pm, $25. http://ht.ly/bN9Fu     
    
    
    Thanks for stocking up! RT @erica_sop: Stocked up thanks to Everything Wine in North Van. Hello Saturday night.    
    
    
    Thanks for being there! RT @wlorganics: Thanks Everything Wine for your sold out Summer Solstice event! We were thrilled to be a part of it!    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar 2-6pm: Fish Eye wines! Pinot Grigio and Shiraz, perfect for a mid-week pick-me-up!    
    
    
    All of our sale wines are open to try at our tasting bar NOW until 6pm! Choose any 3 and get an early start to your #CanadaDay long weekend!    
    
    
    Our #sale #wines are open all afternoon until 6pm! Stop by on your way home from work to "try before you buy"! Lots of brand new wines!    
    
    
    @TheSpitter Tony Gismondi and Kasey Wilson will be broadcating LIVE from our store 12-1pm on AM650 - drop by and enter to win $100 basket!    
    
    
    Happy #Canada Day!! We're celebrating with #sale wines, open to try before you buy at our tasting bar 10-6! Stock up for #summer today    
    
    
    last day of our Canada Day #sale!! Several sku's are now sold out, but we still have LOTS of great value #wine left! Tasting bar open 2-6pm    
    
    
    We're celebrating our American neighbours today with delicious American wines on our tasting bar 2-6pm! Cheers to the sunshine!    
    
    
    Then cross Marine 4 a btl for home! @hurricanegrill: This is patio weather Vancouver! Join us tomorrow & enjoy the sun! pic.twitter.com/8UesHNLh    
    
    
    From @beaucastel, Famille Perrin Vinsobres 'Les Cornuds' 2009 is a deep, impressive CdR. 91 points (RP) and $2 off! http://ht.ly/c4lIL     
    
    
    A can't-miss! RT @diannechow: Fri, Jul 6: 2-6pm @EWineNV (998 Marine Drive, North Vancouver) @SmallVineyards tasting of Italian wines.    
    
    
    Good luck! RT @ceciliaflaming: I just entered the $5000 Alaskan Cruise Contest with Everything Wine! #enter now! http://n.3tl.ca?p=TJD772AUJUn.3tl.ca/?p=TJD772AUJU     
    
    
    Our $5000 Alaska Cruise contest with @VancouverSun & @TheSpitter ends Monday! Like us on @Facebook to enter: http://ht.ly/c4mnO     
    
    
    Now Pouring: 5 great @DrinkChile wines, including a blockbuster Concha y Toro @granreservawine Carmenere! Free tasting until 6pm.    
    
    
    Beautiful new release from @SigVin, richly layered and textured, but with great freshness. Only 6 bottles! $100. pic.twitter.com/vir2TdE3    
    
    
    Staff Favourites @ our #tasting bar today from 2-6pm! See Ya Later Gew, Dirty Laundry Rose and J Lohr Valdigue - perfect #summer #wines !!    
    
    
    Today at our #tasting bar until 6pm: Vino Cacao #chocolate wines!! Absolutely delicious dark chocolate-infused white and red #Bordeaux    
    
    
    @DianneChow thanks for the support and tweets of our events!    
    
    
    Derrick from Blasted Church Vineyards will be at our tasting bar from 2-5pm today pouring #summer whites from his portfolio! Don't miss it!    
    
    
    wow, thanks for saying so! “@KristonDean: @EWineNV I love your stores! I love the way you merchandise and share wine knowledge!”    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar: Vive La France! French wines open from 2-6pm!    
    
    
    Today at our #tasting bar - our Wine of the Week, Perez Cruz Cabernet! On Sale for $16.99 - such a deal! Also pouring a delicious Torrentes!    
    
    
    Today from 3-6pm at our Tasting Bar: BC's own Black Widow Winery!! Pouring two outstanding white wines, drop by on your way home from work!    
    
    
    Our #Sale wines are open now until 6pm at our #tasting bar!! We've got incredible deals all weekend long, come stock up for the summer!    
    
    
    BBQ is fired up and smells great! Come on over to @EWineNV for a free hot dog! #customerappreciation    
    
    
    4 kinds of dogs - ready for you to eat them!! @EWineNV #BBQ (and a giant wine sale inside!) pic.twitter.com/oW2EIp9q    
    
    
    @CaroSpoline celebrate with wine and hot dogs! we have veggie dogs, too :)    
    
    
    Despite the rain in #vancouver, our giant Summer Sale is still on! Drop in to sample & save! Spanish Shiraz for $7.99 ($3 off) & lots more!    
    
    
    We have @RobertMondavi wines open on our tasting bar NOW until 6pm! Absolutely delicious, stop by on your way home! pic.twitter.com/EDjSXmgk    
    
    
    Perfect BBQ red for under $10! http://ht.ly/cy6Xb  Save $3 on Don Leon Tempranillo/MerlotShiraz until August 2!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar: Jeff Curry from @winesyndicate will be here pouring Punto Final Malbec and Renacer Enamore Red Blend! 3-6pm!    
    
    
    Jeff Curry from @winesyndicate is at our Tasting Bar NOW until 6pm pouring some delicious #Argentinian red #wine!    
    
    
    Today from 2-5pm we'll have 7 outstanding Italian wines open for you to try! Sparkling, white and red - all perfect for #summer!    
    
    
    Glad to hear it! You're welcome to drop by any time! “@FenskePeg: My new favourite place: Everything Wine Superstore. http://instagr.am/p/Ne1e37xxrS/ ”    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar: New World Gems & Premium Sunday! Join us from 2-6pm for samples of wines from Aus, Chile, US and BC!    
    
    
    @BodegaRenacer @winesyndicate We certainly did! They were a hit at the tasting bar - staff and consumers loved your wines!    
    
    
    New Tasting @EWineNV - Celebrating the Finer Side of Chardonnay! Wed Aug 29 7-8:30pm, $50+tax, hosted by Chris Sharpe http://www.everythingwine.ca/events/vancouver-events-calendar …    
    
    
    We're pouring Pieza El Coll Red Blend from #Spain today at our tasting bar! $19.99 - outstanding deal!    
    
    
    Out of town this weekend? No worries, our giant BC Day sale is on for 6 days! Stock up before you hit the highway! http://bit.ly/KjD6YP     
    
    
    @stephfowler_ please follow us so we can DM you instructions for donation requests!    
    
    
    Tasting bar is open! You know you're going 2 need something for the patio - drop in & sample wines from our sale flyer! http://ht.ly/cJSbc     
    
    
    Don't miss out on our LIVE broadcast of the Donnafugata Harvest TODAY at 3:30pm! Wine and Cheese served https://www.facebook.com/EverythingWinePage/events#!/events/251740084929236/ …    
    
    
    Today at our #tasting bar from 3-6pm: Wagner Family Wines! Belle Glos, Meiomi & Conundrum! 3:00-6:00pm - don't miss it!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting bar from 2-6pm, we'll be pouring BC's own @TherapyWines!    
    
    
    Our newly-expanded @winesofchile section. 33% larger! Dozens of new wines enroute! pic.twitter.com/xd8Ex6nh    
    
    
    Our August in-store sale has begun! Check out some great deals here: http://ht.ly/cUT5g 
Shop in-store or online!  http://ht.ly/cUT7n     
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar we have @LeftFieldCider pouring their delicious ciders until 6pm! Come cool off on this scorching hot day!    
    
    
    Missed our @LeftFieldCider tasting today? Check out our "What's Sippin'" page for our thoughts! *hint - deeelicious! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Whats-Sippin …    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar - Cameron Hughes Wines! Matt Thirlwell from Vintage West will be here from 3-6pm pouring 5 of @chwine's best Lots!    
    
    
    Sunjinder Juneja is here at our Tasting Bar pouring Domaine de Cabasse Seguret and Sablet NOW until 6pm! Drop by on your way home from work!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Theresa Pederson from @LeftFieldCider visited us last week! Check it out! http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/VLOG--Left-Field-Cider-Co- …    
    
    
    Our tasting bar is open! Come by NOW until 6pm and try some awesome Spanish Wines! @CSWS_Inc    
    
    
    TWO events going on today! Premium tasting from 2-5pm in our Vintages room, and BC's own Calliope Wines at our tasting bar 2-6pm!    
    
    
    Another Long Weekend, another giant sale! Shop in-store or online for some great back-to-school deals! http://ht.ly/dmbag     
    
    
    If you want to see @SloanMusic and have dinner at the gorgeous @TinhornCreek, stay tuned for a rapid-fire contest. Starts in 1 hour!    
    
    
    Our @TinhornCreek @SloanMusic RAPID-FIRE CONTEST starts in 30 minutes and ends at 5:00pm PST! Get ready, tweeps!    
    
    
    CONTEST: For a chance 2 see @SloanMusic at @TinhornCreek & dinner at @MiradoroResto, reply 2 this tweet w/ ur favourite wine from @EWineNV!    
    
    
    Thank you all for the great response to our contest! Our first round of (random) qualifiers have been notified. There may be more to come!    
    
    
    Great response 2 our @Sloanmusic @TinhornCreek @MiradoroResto contest! Winners have been notified, but if any can't attend, we'll re-draw!    
    
    
    We're pleased to announce our 2nd annual Everything Wine Food & Wine Festival! Contact your local store for tickets http://www.everythingwine.ca/Events/FoodWineFestival2012 …    
    
    
    @DeeWuu are you our Facebook friend, Debbie Walker? Follow us so we can DM you!    
    
    
    @BillSanford1 I sent you a quick note - can you DM me?    
    
    
    Fabulous #sale on now at all three EWine locations! Shop until Tuesday instore and online http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/WeekendWineSale …    
    
    
    Our tasting bar is open until 6pm! Drop by on your way home and stock up on some of our great #sale wines!    
    
    
    “@HardRow: @grapehwy John and Taylor are here checking out Lake Chelan wines.” sounds like fun!    
    
    
    What are you having for #WineWednesday tonight? We're open for business from 10am-9pm. Stop on by & we'll help you find the perfect #wine !    
    
    
    Tickets for our Fall wine festival are now available at all three locations! Check out this video for a sneak peak! http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=ljYCA_zy-p4 …    
    
    
    #SAVE $10 off our #WineOfTheWeek - Masi Seregro Alighieri Anniversario Red Blend - http://bit.ly/TrnLiE  - #wine #sale    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar: #Wines of #California! Join us from 2-6pm for samples of some of the Best from the Golden State!    
    
    
    "There's Always time for #Gruner" - check out our latest #wine #blog from @EWineNV's own @AThirstyNomad - http://bit.ly/P1U5o9     
    
    
    1 hour until we start pouring a great range of @plwines! Drop by to sample the new Art series and a couple other gems.    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar: Three Under $13 Thursday!! Join us from 2-6pm for samples great valued wines!    
    
    
    Jamie from Summit Fine Wines is at our tasting bar until 6pm pouring #delicious wines from California and Chile! Drop by on your way home!    
    
    
    Tickets are selling fast for our annual fall festival! Call your local store to reserve your ticket now! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Events/FoodWineFestival2012 …    
    
    
    Thanks again to @LandmarkWines for bringing @HelenatAtaRangi from @Ata_Rangi to our store this summer! http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/Vlog--Helen-Masters--Ata-Rangi-Winemaker …    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 2-6pm - @PerseusWine from BC! Liza McAuley from @DelfGroup will be joining us this afternoon, don't miss out!    
    
    
    4 tickets left for our tasting event next week "Let's Broaden Our Wine Horizons" $25 plus tax Wed Sept 25 7-8:30pm hosted by @Kady_Smith    
    
    
    6 tickets left for tomorrow night's "Let's Broaden Our Wine Horizons" #event at our North Van store! $25 +tax - call 604 929 7277 #wine    
    
    
    Tomorrow from 3-6pm we will be pouring @Stagshollow wines! Check out our latest Vlog  for a sneak peak!http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/Vlog--Stag-s-Hollow-visits-Everything-Wine- …    
    
    
    @Stagshollow wines today @ our tasting bar from 3-6pm! Check out this sneak peak http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/Vlog--Stag-s-Hollow-visits-Everything-Wine- … and stop by on your way home!    
    
    
    Brendan from @Stagshollow is here at our #tasting bar NOW until 6pm! Stop by on your way home! Delicious BC #wines pic.twitter.com/mMWOOHc1    
    
    
    Elizabeth from @dreamwines is at our tasting bar NOW until 6pm pouring @BodegaAndeluna wines! #malbec #chardonnay #pasionado    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 2-5pm, Monica from Vino Allegro will be here pouring @DonnafugataWine ! Amazing value #italian wines!    
    
    
    Tickets are half-way sold out for our Wine & Food Festival on October 17th!! They're going quick, so call 604 929 7277 and get yours today!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar - our Wine of the Week! We'll also have some delicious @Yalumba wines from Australia open to try from 2-6pm    
    
    
    We're over half-way sold out for our Fall #wine #festival taking place in TWO WEEKS! October 17, 7-9pm, $30! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Events/FoodWineFestival2012 …    
    
    
    Two weeks till our Everything Wine Food & Wine Festival!! Tickets still available - 604 929 7277 http://www.everythingwine.ca/Events/FoodWineFestival2012 …    
    
    
    Tickets are selling fast for our Fall Food & Wine Festival!! Call 604-929-7277 for tickets for our October 17th event! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Events/FoodWineFestival2012 …    
    
    
    @swichcafe - Pretty excited to have you guys on board for our annual Fall Food & Wine Festival! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Events/FoodWineFestival2012 …    
    
    
    New tasting @EWineNV - Wednesday October 24 - 7:00-8:30pm "A Walk through the Rhone Valley" with Chris Sharpe $50+tax http://www.everythingwine.ca/events/vancouver-events-calendar …    
    
    
    Thanksgiving Wine Sale on NOW! Shop in-store or online until Tuesday night. Special #thanksgiving treats at our tasting bar at 2pm too!    
    
    
    We have #Thanksgiving treats at our tasting bar today! Turkey, brie and cranberry sliders from @swichcafe !!! #pumpkin pie #cheese #wine    
    
    
    Turkey, brie and cranberry mini sandwich sliders from @swichcafe on our tasting bar today! #thanksgiving #sale on now! pic.twitter.com/w5QTzwag    
    
    
    We're down to the final 50 tickets left for our festival next Wednesday night and they're selling fast! 604 929 7277 pic.twitter.com/JmwTKeSL    
    
    
    Exciting news!!! The team from @COBSBread in #Edgemont Village will be on-site at our food & wine festival next week!    
    
    
    We've got 40 tickets left for next Wednesday's food & wine festival! Don't miss out on this awesome event! 604 929 7277 pic.twitter.com/NnsSDiGJ    
    
    
    @swichcafe @TommyCaters @whistlerwater @COBSBread @rogerschocolate @eatgonecrackers - 6 days to go until our wine & food festival!    
    
    
    Drop by on your way home today for samples of Brumont wines from #France! Export Manager Benoit Valery is here until 6pm signing bottles!    
    
    
    Outstanding #California wines on our tasting bar today until 6pm! @LaCremaWines @KJWines @FreemarkAbbey    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 2-5pm, Alice from @RenWine will be pouring samples of #Cooralook from #Australia!    
    
    
    Only 20 tickets remaining for our 2nd annual Fall Food & Wine Festival this coming Wednesday night! 604 929 7277 pic.twitter.com/xsaaoHq4    
    
    
    Check out this awesome new #blog by @athirstynomad from last month's wine tasting hosted by @Kady_Smith http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/Broadening-Your-Wine-Horizons-Tasting …    
    
    
    Only 10 tickets remaining for our Fall Wine & Food Festival coming up this Wednesday evening! Call 604 929 7277 to reserve your ticket! $30    
    
    
    Today @ our Tasting Bar: The Boxer from @MollydookerWine in Australia! Winemaker Sparky Marquis visited us this morning and we had to share!    
    
    
    Our North Vancouver location's Wine & Food Festival is officially SOLD OUT!! Ticket-holders, we'll see you Wednesday evening at 7pm!    
    
    
    We're getting excited for tomorrow night's SOLD OUT Wine & Food Festival! @swichcafe @whistlerwater @COBSBread @rogerschocolate @TommyCaters    
    
    
    Another successful #WineFestival last night! Were you there? We hope you had as much fun as we did!    
    
    
    Many thanks again to our #WineFest sponsors @swichcafe @whistlerwater @tommycaters @COBSBread @rogerschocolate @eatgonecrackers @SpiritCool    
    
    
    Today @ our Tasting Bar: @8th_Generation wines! Join @sujindertakeaim from @Quaffwines from 3-6pm here @EWineNV    
    
    
    Check out our latest #vlog with Ezra Cipes from @summerhillwine! http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/Vlog--Ezra-Cipes-presents-Summerhill-Pyramid-Winery … @sujindertakeaim @RenWine    
    
    
    Thanks for the shout out @TammyBogdan! We're so glad that we can help make your day a little easier!    
    
    
    #November #Events @EWineNV posted! Exciting stuff coming up! http://www.everythingwine.ca/events/vancouver-events-calendar …    
    
    
    Missed our Fall #Festival last week? Check out photos from the event and don't miss the next one! https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10151087875226402.426564.366292181401&type=1#!/media/set/?set=a.10151087875226402.426564.366292181401&type=1 …    
    
    
    Join us today from 2-6pm at our #tasting bar for our #wineoftheweek! Three delicious selections for you today from #chile #italy #australia    
    
    
    Do you love #Sparkling wine as much as we do? Come to our #Champagne #Dreams tasting on Wed Nov 21 from 7-8:30pm! Only $30 plus tax!    
    
    
    Today at our #Tasting Bar from 2-6pm, we have @TherapyWines from BC! Absolutely delicious, award-winning wines - don't miss out!    
    
    
    @TherapyWines are open now until 6pm at our tasting bar! Stop by on your way home and try a new #favourite today!    
    
    
    Do you love #Champagne and Sparkling Wine as much as we do? Join us Wed Nov 21 from 7-8:30pm for our Champagne Dreams tasting event! $30+tax    
    
    
    #Champagne #Dreams tasting event and many more exciting tastings coming up @EWineNV in #November! Check it out http://www.everythingwine.ca/events/vancouver-events-calendar …    
    
    
    Happy #Halloween! Today from 2-6pm we're pouring @mooncurser wines from BC to celebrate - staff dressed up and mini chocolates for all!    
    
    
    We've got @mooncurser wines from BC open to taste until 6pm! If you can't make it down, check out our thoughts: http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Whats-Sippin …    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 2-6pm: Three Under $13 Thursday! Great value #wines that suit your budget without compromising on flavour!    
    
    
    @craig_nvan So glad you like your shirt! We'll pass along the thanks to Alice from @RenWine and @mooncurser - Enjoy!    
    
    
    Today at our #Tasting Bar we welcome Sandi Hubner London from 3-6pm pouring delicious #French #Wines!    
    
    
    Our annual Port Extravaganza tasting event is so popular that we've added a second evening! Tuesday December 4, 7-8:30pm, tickets $75+tax    
    
    
    Today at our #Tasting Bar: Vive la France! David Smyth from @DirectWinesltd will be here 2-5pm pouring delicious Rhone and Bordeaux wines!    
    
    
    Today at our #Tasting Bar from 2-6pm we'll be pouring the award-winning wines from Oyster Bay! Introducing the brand new Pinot Grigio #Yum    
    
    
    We'll also be #tasting our brand-new Stark Raving red and white wines today - such cool labels, and a phenomenal price at $15.99! Open 2-6pm    
    
    
    Our annual inventory blowout sale is on now until Tuesday night! Shop in-store or online at http://www.everythingwine.ca     
    
    
    Only 8 tickets left for next week's Champagne Dreams tasting! Only $30+tax, join us from 7-8:30pm for a delicious event celebrating bubble!    
    
    
    It's Beaujolais Nouveau Day! George Dubeouf & Joseph Drouhin available now @EWineNV. Get it while it lasts!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar from 3-6pm we have BC's own @ClosduSoleil wines! Delicious, great value wines - stop by on this sunny day! #bcwines    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting bar from 3-6pm, Desirae from Summit Fine Wines will be pouring some #delicious wines from #California!    
    
    
    Kendall Jackson Grand Reserve Cabernet Sauvignon, La Crema Chardonnay, and Cambria Pinot Noir open 3-6pm at our #Tasting #Bar    
    
    
    David and Cynthia from @lfngwine Laughing Stock Vineyards are at our tasting bar NOW until 5pm! Delicious, award winning #BC #wines    
    
    
    Great deals on Great Sips: a $7.99 red, an $8.99 white & a $15.99 90-pointer! Big savings on all 3! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Great-Sips …    
    
    
    Tomorrow night's #Champagne #Dreams tasting is now SOLD OUT! Ticketholders, we'll see you at 7pm!    
    
    
    Also in @EWineNV holiday gift baskets! “@Yaffler: Loving this. Hardly any around... Serious #riesling < $20 pic.twitter.com/FLgGblN3”    
    
    
    Come by on your way home from work - Jessie from @CSWS_Inc is here pouring delicious BC wines from @soaringeagle75 estate winery until 6pm!    
    
    
    We also have our #sale wines open at our tasting bar all weekend from 2-6pm! Try any three before you buy them, and discover a new favourite    
    
    
    Join us on Saturday afternoon from 2-3pm - Author James Nevison of @HADAGLASS will be in store signing copies of his new 2013 edition!    
    
    
    Author James Nevison will be here from 2-3pm signing copies of his 2013 edition of @HADAGLASS - excellent gift idea and stocking stuffer!    
    
    
    James Nevison, Author of @HADAGLASS will be here 2-3pm signing copies of his 2013 edition! Don't miss out - perfect stocking stuffer idea!    
    
    
    Our Winter Wine Sale continues... http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Winter-Wine-Sale … Prices from $6.99!    
    
    
    As featured in today's @TheProvince: Our Winter Wine Sale runs 'til Tuesday! pic.twitter.com/KFQhRN9G    
    
    
    We have ONE ticket left for tonight's Introduction to #Port ! Only $30 plus tax, call 604 929 7277 to reserve your spot!    
    
    
    Vito from Galileo Imports will be at our tasting bar from 3-6pm pouring delicious #Italian wines! Perfect gift wines for friends or for you!    
    
    
    Stop by on your way home from work tonight for some delicious #Italian wines! We've got them open till 6pm - #cheese and #treats out too!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar from 3-6pm we have Annie Lau pouring SIX delicious #Italian wines! We are so excited to share these with you!    
    
    
    @skytrainprez @hadaglass used as fining agents in wine for some time, recently wineries have been required to include them on labels.    
    
    
    @skytrainprez @hadaglass more here via @nzherald: http://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&objectid=10349188 …    
    
    
    @skytrainprez any time! fire your wine questions our way, we'll get you answers!    
    
    
    Today from 2-5pm we're hosting our annual Oyster Bay holiday event! Oysters on the half shell paired with sparkling, sauv blanc and pinot!    
    
    
    In just under an hour, the Oyster Bay team will be at our tasting bar serving up fresh oysters paired with their delicious wines! Drop by!    
    
    
    Our Holiday Wine Sale has something for everyone! It's a great weekend to stock up for the holidays! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Holiday-Wine-Sale …    
    
    
    Today from 12-1pm Tony & Kasey's Best of Food & Wine AM650 radio show will be broadcasting LIVE from our North Van location! Come on down!    
    
    
    Today from 3-6pm at our Tasting Bar Jessie from @CSWS_Inc Christopher Stewart will be here pouring some #outstanding #Spanish wines!    
    
    
    Check out our latest #vlog with @MollydookerWine Winemaker Sparky Marquis! http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/Vlog--Sparky-Marquis--Mollydooker-Winemaker … @EWineNV @EWineVictoria @EWineMX    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar from 2-6pm, Len and Linda Wiebe will be here pouring @VinoCacao chocolate wines! Perfect stocking stuffer ideas!    
    
    
    Come on by our Tasting Bar NOW until 6pm for samples of @VinoCacao chocolate wines! Perfect gift ideas and stocking stuffers, and delicious!    
    
    
    Baby, it's Chile outside! Today at our tasting bar from 2-6pm, we'll have a fantastic selection of #Chilean wines open for sampling!    
    
    
    Check out our latest Vlog post featuring @MollydookerWine winemaker Sparky Marquis! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9sn15So7Cx4&feature=player_embedded … #mollydookershake    
    
    
    Today from 3-6pm we'll be pouring wines from BC's @platinumbench estate winery! Delicious wines perfect for gifts or weekend dinner parties!    
    
    
    Guests coming during the holidays? Stock up today! These last-minute deals run thru Monday! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Last-Minute-Deals …    
    
    
    Snowing in your metro- #vancouver  neighborhood? Shop our sale from the warm comfort of your home! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Last-Minute-Deals …    
    
    
    Last Minute Wine Sale! Check out these great deals in-store or online. Sale ends Monday: http://ht.ly/g8TBD     
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 3-6pm, Jeff Curry from the @winesyndicate will be pouring "Big Reds" from #argentina and #italy    
    
    
    Tomorrow at our tasting bar, Matt Thirlwell will be pouring @chwine Cameron Hughes wines from 3-6pm! Buy 3 bottles, receive Reidel glasses!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar 3-6pm, Matt Thirlwell will be here pouring Cameron Hughes wines! Free Riedel glasses with purchase of 3 CH bottles!    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar we'll be pouring premium #California wines from 3-6pm! Last minute gift ideas, great holiday buys - dont miss it!    
    
    
    At our tasting bar until 6pm: 90 Point Wines & Staff Favourites! Delicious wines, outstanding deals - come by, we're open until 6 tonight!    
    
    
    We're open today until 6pm! We have some great deals on in-store, and will have a few of the #sale wines open from 2-6pm at our tasting bar!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Morning, sunshine! Get out of the house & shop our New Years Eve Sale - When 2012 ends so do these deals! http://bit.ly/WdO9t0     
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar we have some delicious German, Australian, and French wines open to taste from 2-6pm! Stop by on your way home!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar: Discover New Zealand! Outstanding value and incredible flavour, these wines are sure to impress! #sauvignonblanc    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar from 2-6pm: Three Under $13 Thursday is back! Great value wines under $13, don't miss out!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar from 2-6pm: Spanish Sensations! 5 of our favourite Spanish wines will be open to sample all afternoon.    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar from 2-6pm we'll be pouring @Joelgott wines! #Riesling #Chardonnay #Zinfandel    
    
    
    Our January Wine Clearance is on now! Obikwa Chenin Blanc or Merlot is $6.99/btl! + lots more in-store or online:http://bit.ly/XncOfu     
    
    
    Three Under $13 Thursday at our Tasting Bar in North Vancouver today from 2-6pm! Delicious wines that suit your budget!    
    
    
    Join us today at our tasting bar from 3-6pm! Alice from @RenWine will be here pouring three delicious wines from her portfolio!    
    
    
    Today from 2-6pm at our tasting bar, we'll be pouring Australia's @mcguiganwines! Outstanding value, flavour, and perfect for the weekend!    
    
    
    $3 off a big, juicy 90pt. Cabernet for Game Day, plus a killer sticky, spicy grilled wing recipe & 2 more party wines! http://bit.ly/WYM866     
    
    
    Our first ever February Long Weekend Sale is on! Great deals and a ton of clearance & bin-end wines: http://bit.ly/UKvET4     
    
    
    WINE SALE ON NOW! Big hits so far: Somerton Shiraz/Cabernet/Merlot & Chardonnay. 2 South Australian gems, $8.99 each! http://bit.ly/UKvET4     
    
    
    Congratulations to the newest member of the #EverythingWine Family @EWineMoreSWPark!! They just opened their doors in Edmonton - good luck!    
    
    
    Today we have two special treats! Valentine wines at our tasting bar, and a special premium event in our vintage room from 4-6pm!    
    
    
    @KurtisKolt us too! See you soon!    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 2-6pm - Taste Australia! We'll be pouring some #delicious Aussie gems for you to sample while you shop!    
    
    
    Only 8 tickets left for John McLaughlin's "A Wander through #Washington" wine tasting next Wednesday! $25 tickets, contact 604 929 7277    
    
    
    It's Wine of the Week Wednesday @ our Tasting Bar! Today from 2-6pm we'll be pouring Perrin & Fils Vinsobres, and Judge & Jury Red Blend!    
    
    
    Only 7 tickets left for next Wednesday's tasting event, "A Wander Through Washington" with host John McLaughlin! $25+tax, call 604 929 7277    
    
    
    It's 3 Under $13 Thursday at our tasting bar! Open now until 6pm, join us for this week's selections!    
    
    
    Our Weekend Wine Sale is on NOW until Sunday night! Shop in-store or online http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/WeekendWineSale …    
    
    
    Jessie from @CSWS_Inc is at our tasting bar now until 6pm pouring the brand-new @bench1775 wines from Naramata! Stop by on your way home!    
    
    
    Oscar weekend and #VanWineFest week - time to stock up at our Weekend Wine Sale! Ends tomorrow! http://bit.ly/XTaAV0     
    
    
    @ShooterMc19 That's what we like to hear! Glad you enjoyed the visit. @EWineMoreSWPark    
    
    
    Only 3 tickets left to tomorrow night's "A Wander Through Washington" wine tasting! $25+tax, 7:00-8:30pm - don't miss out! 604-929-7277    
    
    
    Award Winning Winemaker Walter Schug from @SchugWinery joins us at our tasting bar from 4-6pm tomorrow in North Vancouver! Come say hi!    
    
    
    Award winning Winemaker Walter Schug of @SchugWinery is at our Tasting Bar NOW until 6pm! Stop by, say hi, and pick up a signed bottle!    
    
    
    Happy Vancouver International Wine Fest! Today at our tasting bar from 2-6pm we'll have some delicious #California wines open to celebrate!    
    
    
    World-renowned Winemaker Charles Smith will be visiting us in North Vancouver from 1-3pm tomorrow at our #tasting bar! Exciting stuff! #yvr    
    
    
    We're celebrating #California wines and #Chardonnay in honour of #VIWF today at our tasting bar from 2-6pm! @KJWines #SonomaCutrer    
    
    
    @craig_nvan So glad you had a great time at @athirstynomad 's #Washington tasting on Wednesday night! Thanks for coming out! #yvrwine    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar we're celebrating #Chile! Join us from 2-6pm to sample some outstanding Chilean wines, including a new #moscato!    
    
    
    @LiffordBC @KVintners Thanks for stopping by our tasting bar yesterday! We had such a great time - the wines were fabulous! #Cheers    
    
    
    Tickets for our next tasting event, "The Grape Divide" are on-sale now! Only 16 seats left, don't miss out - call 604-929-7277 for details!    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar it's Wine of the Week! Try the outstanding gPG Garganega Pinot Grigio blend from #Italy today from 2-6pm!    
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar from 2-6pm, it's Three Under $13 Thursday!! Wines that suit your budget without compromising on flavour!    
    
    
    Delicious wines under $13 at our tasting bar NOW until 6pm this evening! Don't miss out, we're pouring some new gems!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    On sale this weekend for $7.99! RT @liisklasen: Special buy @EWineNV #Kressmann Merlot! pic.twitter.com/e3AVzzByyL    
    
    
    Beware the Ides of March, but behold our March Madness Sale! Try-before-you-buy in-store or shop at home online: http://bit.ly/WLOo52     
    
    
    Go MAD this March with great savings on wine. Sale Ends Monday! http://bit.ly/WLOo52  #MarchMadness    
    
    
    Fantastic #MarchMadness wine savings on through Monday! Don't miss out; shop in-store or online: http://bit.ly/WLOo52     
    
    
    It's not too late to shop our March Madness wine sale! In-store until 9pm or online until midnight at http://www.everythingwine.ca ! #yvrwine    
    
    
    Everything Wine is now a @ShawInfo #ShawGoWiFi hotspot! Browse wine reviews & food pairings while you shop! http://www.shaw.ca/internet/wifi/     
    
    
    Today at our Tasting Bar from 2-6pm, it's our Wine of the Week! Delicious California Pinot Noir, 2009 Cambria "Julia's Vineyard" on sale now    
    
    
    Join us today from 3-5pm to try some of our DELICIOUS Oyster Bay blends and eat some oysters!! pic.twitter.com/Nj9sRK9t3y    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 2-6pm we have the team from @platinumbench estate winery in Oliver, BC! Delicious wines, don't miss out!    
    
    
    Try this fantastic new #BCWine Rosé! Exclusive to Everything Wine and available for a limited time only! http://bit.ly/123bdB3     
    
    
    Tomorrow! Celebrate @MalbecWorldDay at Everything Wine with great wine, food & fun! http://campl.us/oBxn     
    
    
    Drop in this afternoon and sample the great value French wines of @LaVieilleFerme. Red, white and rosé are all open! Santé!    
    
    
    Try before you buy! Our tasting bar is open early for your Saturday wine shopping convenience. http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Spring-Wine-Sale …    
    
    
    Staff fave: Mt. Monster Limestone Coast Cabernet 2010 is 90 points in @WineSpectator and on sale for $21.99! http://bit.ly/11rmxov     
    
    
    @Amateurdevins Thanks so much! See you again soon!    
    
    
    "Keep Calm and Think Pink" 
Come on in and pick up some bottles from The Delf Wine Group!! Featuring Rose Wines pic.twitter.com/PS2n8yOxzq    
    
    
    Nothing like Rhône wines on a rainy Sat. afternoon. 3 great values at our tasting bar until 6pm! @Beaucastel, Roche-Audran, @LouisBernard84    
    
    
    Exclusive Event! Winemaker Dinner with Paul Hobbs, May 27 @pier7restaurant in North Vancouver! Tickets $125+tax only avail @EWineNV 929-7277    
    
    
    It's gorgeous & warm; time for a crisp white or sparkling on the deck! We're open 11-6 today & the cooler is stocked! http://bit.ly/11HmV2b     
    
    
    Tickets for our #exclusive #winemaker dinner with  the legendary Paul Hobbs still available! Call 604-929-7277 for tickets @paulhobbswinery    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 2-4pm we welcome Javier Cortes from Vina Chocalan winery in Chile! @chocalan_wines Join us! #yvrwine #tasting    
    
    
    Today from 2-6pm UNSWORTH WINERY will be coming to pour 3 of their DELICIOUS summer wines! Come enjoy those locally made summer sippers!    
    
    
    On Sunday May 12- we have a special treat for all the mothers out there! From 2-6pm we will be pouring lovely varietals!  Bring in your mom!    
    
    
    Don't miss out on our #Blind #Wine #Tasting on Tuesday May 28 from 7-8:30pm! Tickets are only $25+tax. 604-929-7277 #yvrwine    
    
    
    VISIT ALL BC EVERYTHING WINE LOCATIONS THIS WEEKEND DURING OUR MAY LONG WEEKEND SALE! Yummy Treats to pair with delicious wines on sale!!    
    
    
    COME IN FOR OUR SALE WEEKEND!!!! ends on TUESDAY MAY 21 so you have plenty of time to come down and check it out!! pic.twitter.com/LDPEfyzmJz    
    
    
    Fantastic Wines= $6.99- 21.99
Cost of gas= $3.00-5.00
Tasting wines and food at our beautiful wine bar= PRICELESS!

AT ALL BC LOCATIONS!    
    
    
    Join us today in North Vancouver to try some Left Field Cider Co. Apple Cider! It is delicious and perfect for the weather today!    
    
    
    Only 85 tickets left for this year's Summer Solstice Food & Wine Festival in North Vancouver! Always sells out, so call 604 929-7277 now!    
    
    
    Join us today at our tasting bar from 3-6pm for samples of BC's own @mooncurser wines! Join Chris Tolley and kick start your weekend!    
    
    
    Tomorrow  at our North Vancouver Location in our Vintages Room Matt Thirwell will  be pouring California Premiums! Don't miss out!    
    
    
    Tomorrow-  Jodie from That's Life Gourmet will be visiting North Vancouver to pour delicious Italian and French wines! 2-6pm!    
    
    
    Today in North Vancouver in our vintages room, Matt Thirwell is pouring premium wines from California! 
from 2-6 PM 
DONT MISS OUT!    
    
    
    Today at the NORTH VAN location- At our tasting bar we will be pouring French and Italian wines with Jodie from That's Life Gourmet! 2-6pm    
    
    
    Come and discover New Zealand.... WINES!
Today at the North Vancouver location we will be pouring New Zealand classics! 
From 2-6 PM!    
    
    
    TOMORROW at NORTH VANCOUVER- Bob Johnson, the owner of Baillie Grohman winery, who will be pouring his outstanding varietals. 
Come from 2-6    
    
    
    Who doesn't love an amazing grilled cheese sandwich?!

 Who: TASER GRILLED CHEESE
 When: SATURDAY JUNE 15
 Where: Everything Wine North Van    
    
    
    THIS EVENING from 5-8 pm, join us for our @PenfoldsWine tasting in our vintages room! Cheese, Charcuterie, and delicious #wine @EWineNV    
    
    
    Today at North Vancouver, join Tak from Treasury as he pours different luscious varietals! Only from 2-6pm    
    
    
    Come try some of our staff favourites tomorrow and pair them with sushi from Gen Sushi! 
Sounds like a Sunday worth getting out of bed for!    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar, Tony Truchard pouring from his own divine wine selection. Be sure not to miss out on trying these varietals!    
    
    
    Join Matt Thirwell today in North Vancouver to taste wines from Cedar Creek's lovely winery. From 2-6- support our winery's here in BC!    
    
    
    Come EAT grilled cheese!
TASER GRILLED CHEESE IS HERE!
Our Father's Day Sale is on!
DONT miss out!! @Tasersandwich pic.twitter.com/zid0IKSi9n    
    
    
    @rachellai83 thank YOU for coming!    
    
    
    Let us whisk you away to Tuscany today, as we sample wines from the Ruffino Winery in Italy. Today from 4-6pm at our tasting bar!    
    
    
    Today we will be tasting 3 organic varietals at our tasting bar! Also Living Lotus is here to give out samples of their organic treats!    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar we will be pouring special samples in honour of our Wine Club! Join and get special offers on wine delivery! 2-6pm    
    
    
    Thursday July 11th from 7-8:30pm, join us for a White Haven portfolio tasting! Only $15 plus tax, enjoy delicious #NZ wines, cheese & treats    
    
    
    Our thoughts are with the Peter Lehmann Wine Family today - he was a Legend, and we're thankful for all he shared with us! @plwines    
    
    
    The favourite at our tasting bar so far this weekend - Wild Thyme Rose 750 mL  http://www.everythingwine.ca/product/Wild-Thyme-Rose-750-mL- … Stop by this weekend to try a sample!    
    
    
    Tasting Bar #fav today is the Castillo de Aguaron Cab Sauv from Spain! Only a handful of cases left!http://www.everythingwine.ca/product/Castillo-de-Aguaron-Cabernet-Sauvignon--750ml?pageID=7d4117a5-9231-81a9-b099-de1a6f80283e&sortBy=DisplayOrder& … @EWine_Inc    
    
    
    Canada Day BBQ on NOW at the store! Hot Dogs & Chips, donations going to the @HarvestProject in North Van! Shop our #sale instore and online    
    
    
    @WildThymeDogs awesome! We carry a #Gewurztraminer by Wild Thyme as well - what a great match!    
    
    
    @northsideof_red Aveleda Vinho Verde is a hit at the #tasting #bar today too! Outstanding value, on sale for $12.99 http://www.everythingwine.ca/product/Quinta-da-Aveleda--Vinho-Verde-750ml?pageID=7d4117a5-9231-81a9-b099-de1a6f80283e&sortBy=DisplayOrder& …    
    
    
    Come show your Canada Day Spirit like we are in North Vancouver today and pick up some delicious wines on sale!! pic.twitter.com/eU7Hj4GsMy    
    
    
    @EWine_Inc loving Tacora Reserva Pinot Noir! A fresh, light red perfect 4 summer. Think salmon+veggies on the grill! http://bit.ly/19N5wKe     
    
    
    HAPPY CANADA DAY! We ARE open today! Come celebrate with us by tasting our featured wines at our North Vancouver tasting bar!    
    
    
    Happy Canada Day! We're open until 9pm and our sale is still on! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Canada-Day-Wine-Sale …    
    
    
    🍁Celebrate Canada Day with a great #BCWine, Wild Thyme Rosé! Last chance to grab this EW exclusive!
http://www.everythingwine.ca/product/Wild-Thyme-Rose-750-mL- …?    
    
    
    It's still hot, #Vancouver! Cool down w/ a crisp, fresh Pinot Grigio. Last day to get Giacondi PG on sale for $9.99! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Canada-Day-Wine-Sale …    
    
    
    We've set up a feature wall of wines from our #SummerSolstice wine festival last month! Drop by and pick up a new Fav pic.twitter.com/Vi2gLqD680    
    
    
    @BurrowsLuongo Happy #WineWednesday to you! We're pouring our #WineoftheWeek at our Tasting Bar to celebrate! Fat Bird #SauvBlanc    
    
    
        
    
    
    @theranross great to hear! Enjoy :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Check out our upcoming tasting events on http://LocalWineEvents.com  --  http://www.localwineevents.com/events/detail/486387/twitter … via @worldwineevents    
    
    
        
    
    
    We're pouring our #wineoftheweek today as you enter the store! Trivento Mixtus Chardonnay/Chenin Blanc on sale $9.99! pic.twitter.com/ywLO1Y9lhp    
    
    
    Rose! Rose! Rose! Tomorrow at our tasting bar in North Vancouver we will be pouring different Rose from all over the world. 2-6pm    
    
    
    We have 6 tickets left for TONIGHT'S New Zealand tasting featuring White Haven wines! Tickets are only $15 plus tax! 604 929 7277 #wine #yvr    
    
    
    Join us from 2-6pm at our Tasting Bar for samples of award-winning Cameron Hughes wines from #California @chwine #delicious @EWineNV    
    
    
    Cameron Hughes Wine is open on our #tasting #bar for another hour and a half! Stop by on your way home and try new favourites! @chwine    
    
    
        
    
    
    Chocolate Chocolate Chocolate! Come to our bar today from 2-6pm to try some Purdy's chocolate paired with some of our delicious varietals!    
    
    
    We are offering $5 off our Aromas Workshop which is happening tomorrow July 17 from 7-8:30 pm! Call and get your tickets!    
    
    
    @TinhornCreek @wine_lass We still have stock! Swing by and pick up a few bottles!    
    
    
    We're OPEN! Our Summer Sale starts today, and our tasting bar is open for sampling! Choose any 3 to try before you buy. Stock up and #save!    
    
    
    Our #Tasting #Bar is hopping! Drop by all weekend for samples of our #summer #sale #wine! Stock up and save at all 3 BC locations! #yvrwine    
    
    
    Today at our tasting bar from 2-6pm we'll be pouring delicious #summer #wine from the Thomas Robert Agency. Delicious white, rose and more!    
    
    
    Today at North Van we have Plamen pouring tasty Chilean wine, Echeverria. Join us from 2-6pm at our tasting bar and spice up your afternoon!    
    
    
    Join us today in the vintages room to taste some delicious wine in honour of Peter Lehman poured by our special guest Ian Hongell. @plwines    
    
    
    Peter Lehman tasting with special guest Ian Hongell today in our vintages room! #everythingwine http://instagram.com/p/cSXuRbJmh0/     
    
    
    Sangria Sunday is happening today at our tasting bar in North Vancouver! Come down from 2-6pm and sample some delicious sangria!    
    
    
    Sangria Sunday! Join us at our bar for a splash of some refreshing sangria made with Belle Grove… http://instagram.com/p/cU69YTpmtf/     
    
    
    Our BBQ is still going strong! Come have a dog and support @HarvestProject, then pick up some great wines on sale!    
    
    
    Here's to 35 years of Pride! Cheers, Vancouver! pic.twitter.com/39Rl3fW2qY    
    
    
    New Vlog! Tom Barry from @Jimbarrywines in #Australia visited us last week. Here's what he had to say!
http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/Vlog--Tom-Barry-visits-Everything-Wine- …    
    
    
    Fallen into that summer craze? Well come get a dose of just what the doctor ordered.... Therapy! Therapy wines that is.  Samples from 2-6pm    
    
    
    @arthritictongue just arrived! $29.99 and it's in the cooler!    
    
    
    Old World Series tasting- Italy!! Our new paintings really brighten up the place! Only at… http://instagram.com/p/dDmYXvpmjs/     
    
    
    Derek from @BlastedChurch is at our tasting bar NOW until 6pm! Drop by for samples of this #delicious #BCWine @BlastedChurchDC    
    
    
    Visit us tonight at the @LonsdaleQuay farmers market from 5-10pm! We'll be set up near beer & wine garden! @CedarCreekWine @bailliegrohman    
    
    
    We are all set up at The North Shore Green Market beer gardens! Come visit us!! #everythingwine pic.twitter.com/8MfgNmE8AM    
    
    
    @TJordanArts Great to hear! Gotta squeeze every minute out of Summer - it's slipping away fast :(    
    
    
    Today is Australian Outback Day! At the bar from 2-6 sample some of Australia's finest varietals paired with special kangaroo burgers!    
    
    
        
    
    
    GIANT 6-day wine sale starts NOW! Shop in-store or online until Tuesday:  http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Labour-Day-Wine-Sale …    
    
    
    @the_pudgy_life @skozey we try! ;)    
    
    
    Join us today at our Tasting bar from 3-6pm for samples of delicious sparkling, white, and red wines from the @VinoAllegroBC portfolio! #yum    
    
    
    Jaime from Summit Fine Wines joins us at our #TastingBar today from 2-6pm, pouring some of #Califonia's best! #Zinfandel #SauvBlanc #CabSauv    
    
    
    The first 10 people to call today will receive $5 off our South American Showdown Tasting this Thursday, September 12 from 7-8:30!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Drop by on your way home from work this afternoon for a taste of #delicious @yalumba wines from #Australia! @kathrynLboyd is here until 6!    
    
    
    It's here! The Community Pizzeria truck is here! Come eat some delicious pizza. We will be paring wines at the bar as well all afternoon!    
    
    
    On October 4 in North Van and South Surrey we'll be hosting an Australian tasting featuring @PewseyVale and @VasseFelixWines @kathrynLboyd    
    
    
    Tomorrow we celebrate International Grenache Day at our tasting bar from 2-6pm! Don't miss out! #GrenacheDay pic.twitter.com/NTCEWrluQv    
    
    
    Don't forget! We're celebrating International Grenache Day from 2-6pm TODAY at our tasting bar! #GrenacheDay #yum #YVRWine    
    
    
    Our tasting bar is OPEN! Come celebrate International Grenache Day with us until 6pm! @EWine_Inc #GrenacheDay pic.twitter.com/8bYf0j81CV    
    
    
    Up early? Get a head start on the weekend by shopping our Birthday Bash Wine Sale online! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/BirthdayBash2013 …    
    
    
    Be the first 5 people to call in to our North Vancouver location and receive 10 percent off any event in September!    
    
    
    Happy 5th Birthday Everything Wine!! Come celebrate with us and have a piece of cake and try some of… http://instagram.com/p/eiOYkhpmmX/     
    
    
    We've got #Birthday #Cake at our tasting bar again today!!! Join us from 10-6 today at our tasting bar for samples of some #Sale wine too!    
    
    
    Today is your last chance to purchase tickets for our Back to School Basics class at our North Vancouver location! Don't miss out!    
    
    
    Proud to be sponsoring @LouisGervaisFFC 15th Anniversary gala tonight at the #Vancouver Art Gallery! #RooftopPatio pic.twitter.com/NGsO9nvioa    
    
    
    Setting up for our @JohnDuvalWines event tonight in our #vintage room! Proud to be hosting this #lengend pic.twitter.com/uDltlYHuhc    
    
    
    It's Cupcake Combo Sunday today! Come down this afternoon to the North Vancouver location to sample… http://instagram.com/p/e2t3f6pmhJ/     
    
    
    This Friday from 2-6pm we'll be featuring a double-bill of Australian wineries at our tasting bar! @VasseFelixWines and @PewseyVale    
    
    
    Do you love #Australian #Wine? Join us in North Van and South Surrey tomorrow from 2-6pm and sample @VasseFelixWines  and @PewseyVale wines!    
    
    
    FLASH Wine Sale! Shop these suprise deals in-store or online until Sunday! 
http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Flash-Wine-Sale …    
    
    
    Ticket Giveaway!!! We have 4 tickets to this great event at Park Royal on Oct 19. If you'd like to attend, tweet us! pic.twitter.com/H89I1kBVw2    
    
    
    @OceanScented - awesome! We'll enter your name in the draw and let the winners know by tomorrow morning. #GoodLuck!    
    
    
    Ticket Giveaway: We have two pairs of tickets to give away to the North Shore Rotary Wine & Food Festival on Sat Oct 19. Tweet us to win!    
    
    
    @w_archer We've entered your name into the draw! We'll let winners know tomorrow morning if they've won 2 tickets to the festival #GoodLuck    
    
    
    @salexander86 Great! We've got you entered into the draw! #GoodLuck    
    
    
    Congratulations @OceanScented and @RoseRedlich - you've both won a pair of tickets to the North Shore Rotary Wine & Food Festival!    
    
    
    @OceanScented - your pair of tickets are available for pickup at our North Vancouver location any time after 10am tomorrow morning #Congrats    
    
    
    @OceanScented We carry both! See you soon!    
    
    
    Exciting event coming up in #Vancouver with @plwinescanada, hosted by Athony Gismondi @TheSpitter on Oct 21! http://www.nationaltasting.ca/  for Info    
    
    
    Our #Thanksgiving #Sale is on NOW Until Tuesday night! Shop in-store or online now! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/ThanksgivingWineSale2013 … pic.twitter.com/l3NXNwE4yA    
    
    
    Interested in learning more about upcoming events, sales, and special offers? Like us on Facebook! https://www.facebook.com/EverythingWinePage …    
    
    
    Tickets for our annual #Champagne #Dreams tasting are now available at our North Van location! $30 plus tax #yvrwine pic.twitter.com/pdeBF3lbg4    
    
    
    We are open 11-6 Thanksgiving Sunday and Monday! Shop the sale in-store or online through Tuesday! http://www.everythingwine.ca     
    
    
    Interested in #California #Wine? We have a California Classics tasting event coming up on Wed Nov 6 at 7pm! Tickets are $25 - 604-929-7277    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tickets available for the North Shore Rotary Clubs Annual Wine & Food Festival on SATURDAY! http://www.northshorewinefest.ca/  pic.twitter.com/dIydSEB9YD    
    
    
        
    
    
    We have 2 more pairs of tickets to give away for tomorrow night's Rotary Wine Festival at Park Royal. Tweet us to win pic.twitter.com/19b1pHmoRa    
    
    
    Do you enjoy #California wines? Danielle from Appellation Wine Marketing is at our tasting bar till 6pm pouring Castle Rock wines! #yum #yvr    
    
    
    Conratulations to Kathy Krantz and Ray Van Driel, who have won two pairs of tickets to tomorrow night's Rotary Wine Festival. Congrats!    
    
    
    We have a special @VeuveClicquot tasting event on Monday evening with Chef de Cave Dominique Demarville. RSVP to evandriel@everythingwine.ca    
    
    
    Do you love @VeuveClicquot as much as we do? Then join us from 5:15-6:30 on Monday evening for your chance to meet the Winemaker! RSVP today    
    
    
        
    
    
    Giant wine sale on now! @ObikwaWines Merlot or Chenin Blanc for just $6.99! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/RedHotSale2013 …    
    
    
    Exclusive #Winemaker Event in our Vintages Room TONIGHT from 5:15pm with @VeuveClicquot's Dominique Demarville! RSVP! pic.twitter.com/0gSbERBI9s    
    
    
    Don't miss out on our Exclusive @VeuveClicquot Winemaker Event tonight from 5:15-6:30pm in our Vintage Room! RSVP now pic.twitter.com/I2RZpRn8dN    
    
    
    #Vancouver - if you're free tonight, join us @EWineNV from 5:15-6:30 for an exlusive @VeuveClicquot Event! RSVP now! pic.twitter.com/7yq0ZtLvA6    
    
    
    Our @VeuveClicquot event is in full swing! Drop by until 6:30pm to meet the winemaker and try the legendary champagne pic.twitter.com/0hRFddKFVu    
    
    
    We still have 15 tickets left for tomorrow night's Wine & Food Festival! Only $30 call 604-929-7277 #Vancouver pic.twitter.com/N3h8CE4VYF    
    
    
    @craig_nvan - We're so glad you had a great time at last night's @VeuveClicquot event! Thanks for coming out! #Wine #Vancouver #Champagne    
    
    
    We have 10 tickets available for tonight's Food & Wine Festival!! 7-9pm, $30, Call 604-929-7277 pic.twitter.com/txd7aUb49r    
    
    
        
    
    
    Join us from 5-7pm this evening for your chance to meet #Australian #Winemaker Sue Hodder from @WynnsCoonawarra! Great wines, great stories!    
    
    
    #Vancouver - Join us in North Van tonight from 5-7pm for your chance to meet #Aussie winemaker Sue Hodder! #yvrwine pic.twitter.com/unR4OykV7b    
    
    
    Join us from 5-7pm tonight for this exclusive #Winemaker #Event with Sue Hodder from Wynns Winery in #Australia!! pic.twitter.com/rrn2148LhD    
    
    
    Our Annual Inventory Blowout Sale is still on! Ends Tuesday! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Annual-Inventory-Blowout-Sale-2013 …    
    
    
    One of our favourites from this weekend's #Blowout #Sale -Wild Thyme Gewürztraminer from BC! $19.99 on Sale til Tues! pic.twitter.com/KRKD6HBaDd    
    
    
    The long weekend may be over, but our #sale isn't! Visit us today until 9pm for your chance to pick up some amazing #LastChance #wines!    
    
    
    @EWineNV Annual Inventory Blowout #Sale ends tonight! Shop online or visit us in-store until 9pm! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Annual-Inventory-Blowout-Sale-2013 …    
    
    
    Still a few hours left to go for our Annual Inventory Blowout #Sale! Shop in-store till 9 or online now! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/Annual-Inventory-Blowout-Sale-2013 …    
    
    
    @northsideof_red @LiffordBC Great Holiday buys indeed! The Map Maker Sauv Blanc is a particularly great white for all the #NewZealand fans!    
    
    
    Annie Lau from @VendemmiaWines is at our #TastingBar now until 6pm pouring #delicious #Italian wines! #Vancouver pic.twitter.com/J03cas3XNM    
    
    
    Today at our #TastingBar from 2-6pm we have Jamie from @SummitFineWines pouring #delicious #California and #Chilean #wines! #TGIF    
    
    
    Tomorrow from 7-9pm we're hosting an #exclusive #tasting with @FrescobaldiVini winemaker Nicolo d'Afflitto! Join us for #Italy's finest!    
    
    
    TONIGHT from 7-9pm we welcome Winemaker Nicoló d’Afflitto from @FrescobaldiVini in #Italy for a complimentary tasting event! #Vancouver    
    
    
    World-renowned winemaker Nicoló d’Afflitto from Marchesi de Frescobaldi will be pouring some of Italy's best at our tasting bar from 7-9pm!    
    
    
    Don't forget to drop by the store TONIGHT from 7-9 for your chance to try the delicious @FrescobaldiVini wines and meet the winemaker!    
    
    
    Our annual Winter Wine Bonanza Sale is here!! Shop in-store or online NOW until next Tuesday! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/WinterWineSale2013 … pic.twitter.com/mq15RMTHK8    
    
    
    Today's #favourite at our #TastingBar so far has been the Belle Grove Chardonnay! Only $6.99! http://www.everythingwine.ca/product/J--Garcia-Carrion-Belle-Grove--Chardonnay-750-mL?pageID=41c977b7-a231-9e83-b36d-594d98b7db06&sortBy=DisplayOrder&maxRows=10& … pic.twitter.com/12GGdgqwNg    
    
    
    We know it's still early, but the best part about our #Sale (other than the savings) is our Tasting Bar is open at 10am! Try before you buy!    
    
    
    .@JeremyDyson You bet! We have 3 to choose from, all under $17! Get them while they're fresh! #BeaujolaisNouveau    
    
    
    Our Winter Wine Sale is on! Great savings, like $5 off Belle Grove Shiraz & Chardonnay - just $6.99 until Tuesday! http://bit.ly/1ay90Cq     
    
    
    This morning's #TastingBar #Favourite has been the Niel Santofamia Garnacha, at $16.99! That's a $3 #savings! --> http://bit.ly/1ay90Cq     
    
    
    @northsideof_red @Gradywines Looking forward to Peter Lindlaub's visit to our Vintages Room this afternoon! #Caymus #MerSoleil #BelleGlos    
    
    
    Tonight in our #VintagesRoom from 5-7pm Peter Lindlaub from @CaymusWine is here! Don't miss it! #BelleGlos #MerSoleil pic.twitter.com/A9zq4Aa58q    
    
    
    Having a #great time with Annette from @Gradywines and Peter from @CaymusWine in our #VintageRoom! #WineTasting #yum pic.twitter.com/hgHgdtQdTT    
    
    
    We're OPEN! Day #3 of our Winter Wine Bonanza #sale is in full-swing, and we don't want you to miss out! Online --> http://bit.ly/1ay90Cq     
    
    
    Today's #Favourite at our #TastingBar is the Path Pinot Noir! New to the store $17.99! Save $4 http://bit.ly/1ay90Cq  pic.twitter.com/e4W4hkLZOs    
    
    
    Our #WineoftheWeek - the Niel Garnacha - is stealing the show today! Shop in-store or online! http://bit.ly/1ay90Cq  pic.twitter.com/2Chub5eXvd    
    
    
    #TGIF - Stop by on your way home for your chance to try some delicious wines at killer prices! http://bit.ly/1ay90Cq  #Weekend #Sale    
    
    
    Make sure you make it down to Everything Wine today! Along with our AMAZING Winter Wine Sale we have some delicious snacks! Hope to see you!    
    
    
    Happy Sunday! We open at 11:00 this morning for Day 4 of the Winter Wine Bonanza. All sale wines still in stock! http://bit.ly/1ay90Cq     
    
    
    Your weekend might be over but our sale is definitely not! We have amazing deals on AMAZING wines and there are still 2 days left!    
    
    
    Tomorrrow, @erinireland from To Die For will be at our store giving out samples of her delicious banana bread and lemon poppy seed loaf!    
    
    
    Lisa Hill visiting us from Christopher Stewart Wine Agency! She is here to pour two delicious wines from British Columbia! Come in from 2-6!    
    
    
    Today, Erin Ireland from "To Die For" will be at our store giving out samples of her delicious banana bread and lemon poppy seed loaf!    
    
    
    Our Holiday Wine Sale is on! Amazing wines for holiday giving and entertaining are on sale in-store and online. http://bit.ly/IuiuEk     
    
    
    Come on down this weekend to #StockUp on some incredible #Holiday #Wines!! Shop in-store or online Now! pic.twitter.com/NpGpr86II0    
    
    
    Hey @EWine_Inc , have you tried the Perrin Vinsobres lately? It's #outstanding as always! @EWineMX @EWineVictoria pic.twitter.com/Xvw9VHiYqy    
    
    
        
    
    
    It is Saturday of a sale! Do you know what that means!? yummy holiday treats! Pop in today to try wine on sale and eat festive snacks!    
    
    
    Our Holiday Wine Sale is still going on! Don't miss your chance on great deals! Taste any 3 on sale to make sure you like it before you buy!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Our delivery trucks just dropped off a fresh batch of Fat Bird Sauvignon Blanc and Perrin Vinsobres!! Stock up on these holiday favourites!    
    
    
    @louisemariewine it's delicious! We have a bottle open at our tasting bar to try if you're in the area. It's a steal of a deal at 19.99!    
    
    
    We're OPEN!!! Get your Holiday shopping off to an early start this weekend - we're open an hour earlier and close an hour later than usual!    
    
    
    Our #Exclusive Vina Maipo Viognier is BACK and on #Sale this weekend! $9.99 - save $3 a bottle!http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/FourDayWineSale2013 … pic.twitter.com/HnpyhsxlkG    
    
    
    Our #Tasting #Bar is OPEN! Try any 3 of our #Sale wines this weekend before you make your final decisions! #yvrwine pic.twitter.com/0OEeRjtl9x    
    
    
    This weekend, the #delicious 2009 Monte Hiniesta Spanish Red Blend is $10 off per bottle! 91 points Wine Advocate! pic.twitter.com/hY8DmNak0j    
    
    
        
    
    
    Today's #favourite at our #tasting bar so far has been the Niel Garnacha! Only $16.99, it's a perfect holiday gift! http://bit.ly/1bD7vCA     
    
    
    4 Day Wine Sale on NOW! In store and online --> http://bit.ly/1bD7vCA  Open until 10:00 tonight!    
    
    
    Need a few gift ideas? Along with a great selection of wines, we also carry accessories, glassware, and more! Shop our #sale 'til midnight!    
    
    
    Perfect #stocking #stuffer idea available now! @HADAGLASS 2014 - Top 100 wines under $20! #LastMinuteGifts @EWineNV pic.twitter.com/ITCNchPGUn    
    
    
    #Sale still on until tonight! Stores are open until 10pm, or shop online until Midnight! Don't miss out on the deals http://bit.ly/1bD7vCA     
    
    
    #SURPRISE! Our #wine #sale has been extended until we close on Wednesday!! Stock up today! http://bit.ly/1bD7vCA     
    
    
    Shop our #Last #Minute #Wine #Sale on NOW! http://www.everythingwine.ca/Wine-Shop/LastMinuteDeals2013 … Visit us in-store for these great deals and more! pic.twitter.com/kNt75N0O6Q    
    
    
    Santa sent us a helper #elf from head office! Sidewalks are all clear & ready for our #wine #sale on NOW! @EWine_Inc pic.twitter.com/8zCOkXRP6f    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great #gift and #craft ideas using leftover #wine bottles and #corks! There's still time to be creative this holiday! http://drinknectar.com/2011/12/22/12-merry-wine-christmas-decorations/ …    
    
    
    Don't let this happen to you this #Christmas - stock up today! We're open until 10pm, and we have a great #sale on! pic.twitter.com/PBKRl5gUNv    
    
    
    Running out time before the big day? Not only do we sell great #wines and #accessories but we also #wrap them too! pic.twitter.com/r0rQF9DKPe    
    
    
    Our #holiday #GiftWrap #Elf is getting busy!! Save yourself some time & impress your friends and family! #NorthVan pic.twitter.com/aV1YGo8pP2    
    
    
    Last-minute wine needs? We're open tonight until 10! Sale on NOW! At @EWineNV @EWineMX @EWineVictoria --> http://bit.ly/18XoR9Z     
    
    
    Only 3 days until the big day! Come visit us! We're open til 8! Complimentary wine tasting, holiday treats, sales and more! #NorthVan #wine    
    
    
        
    
    
    Only a few hours left before #Santa comes! We're open till 6 and have lots of wine and gift ideas left to choose from! #MerryChristmas    
    
    
        
    
    
    Today and for the next four days we will be having our last sale of 2013! Come down to buy some of our favourites for the NewYearsHoliday!    
    
    
    @VixenCoffee @8th_Generation @OkanaganWriting who can wait? happy new year!    
    
    
    hey, @VWWine - is there more Killka Malbec avail. in BC? Would love to get this staff fave back in! @benbolliger    
    
    
    Always something new in store! Ask about new stuff from @DeBortoliWines, @8thGenVineyard, @MichelTorino, @Tahbilk150, @LaFrenzWinery & more!    
    
    
    EW Buyer Dave features Molino Loco Monastrell in this week's vlog. Find out why this Spanish gem loves BBQ sausages: http://www.everythingwine.ca/blog/Dave-Features-Molino-Loco …    
    
    
    $5 off 5 Sale is on! 5 great reds reduced by a whopping $5! Limited quantities, North Van only! Check out the flyer: http://ow.ly/d/ho0    
    
    
        
    
    
    @lafrenzwinery a little bit, yes! going fast...    
    
    
    The tasty new @OKCrushPad #BartierScholefield wines are ordered! Made a nice little spot next to the @HaywireWine. #BCWine    
    
    
    Coming Soon! RT @joecorkscrew: @Deserthillswine Viognier, a light, floral, Muscat-like example of the grape. Perfect 4 the patio! #BCWine    
    
    
    Now in stock: @McWattersWine Meritage 2007 from the Black Sage Bench is the new must-try #BCWine! $25.99    
    
    
    Arrived: Más Amor Rosado and Zardetto Prosecco, 2 perfect summer sips from @Trialto / @LiquidArt_BC. Bring on the sunshine, #Vancouver!    
    
    
    Drop by 3-6pm today & try some great wines from @CHWine. We're opening Cameron Hughes Lot 188, Lot 212, Lot 62 & Lot 189! http://ht.ly/5F0dv    
    
    
    For Cabernet lovers only! LIMITED SUPPLY! Order your Perez Cruz Cab Sauv soon... this will definitely sell out! -  http://bit.ly/oVdcOu  #wine    
    
    
    Robert from @DreamWines is here today pouring killer reds from Cuvelier los Andes, Bodega del Desierto & Barrandica. 2-6pm. #Argentina #Wine    
    
    
    @Heather2020 @paulrickett you got one of the last bottles - we're out now, too. Glad you liked it!    
    
    
    Today on the tasting bar: Angove Artist Series Chardonnay  and Menduco Malbec!! Come into the store today from 2-6pm to give them a try!    
    
    
    only 16 tickets left for our "Let's Broaden our White Horizons" tasting! $30 - Tuesday July 26 7-8:30pm - Don't Miss Out!    
    
    
    Congrats #Japan! Nothing more exciting than a shootout. Drop by the store and pick up a bottle of sake to celebrate! #worldcupfinal    
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanks for the visit today, @SophieLui! What did you pick up? Next time I'll show you around the Vintages Room ;)    
    
    
    We love #Türkiye! @WineofTurkey @Turkishwine @WinesofTurkeyTR now available @EWineNV!    
    
    
    last chance to buy tickets for this Tuesday's wine event at the North Van location! Call 604-929-7277 for tickets! only $30 each!    
    
    
    Staying in town for the long weekend? We're here for your wine needs! Fri: 10-9, Sat: 10-9, Sun: 11-6, Mon: 11-6. Happy #BCDay, #Vancouver!    
    
    
    Today on the tasting bar: Mission Hill Family Estate Wines!! Start your BC Day Celebration early! 2-6pm    
    
    
    Yep! >> RT @QuenchWines: @WINEcouver @FairviewCellars I'm glad u liked it! @goodlifevan says it's avail @EWineNV    
    
    
    Great wine under $10 in #Vancouver? You bet! Buy this Italian gem by the case! http://ht.ly/5Wd89    
    
    
    Events for August are now posted! Some great #BCWine tastings coming up & lots more! http://ht.ly/5We5J #wine #Vancouver    
    
    
    Save $3 on this friendly, quaff-able French Pinot Noir: http://ht.ly/5WkA5 Now only $13.99!    
    
    
    #Rioja in 3 letters: LAN. #44 on the @WineSpectator Top 100 of 2010 list! Quantities are limited! http://ht.ly/5WdKF    
    
    
    Check out Dave's vlog on GH Mumm 50 Degree Riesling Kabinett, a stylish and versatile summer sipper! http://ht.ly/5Wejl    
    
    
    today on the tasting bar: Tinhorn Creek!! 2-6pm - yum!    
    
    
    Now Pouring: The well-made, well-priced wines of @TinhornCreek! #BCWine    
    
    
    Check out Dave's vlog on Vinos Sin Ley Puerta Bonita G5 Garnacha, 90 points by @RobertMParkerJr's The Wine Advocate. http://ht.ly/5WeeV    
    
    
    