The reason why Jesus Christ walked on the sea was to demonstrate to Christians that, the things we are afraid of... http://fb.me/27ehZkBkT     
    
    
    The phrase "Fear not" can be found 331 times in the Bible. This is certainly God's daily reminder in a year that... http://fb.me/2PgsOxmnH     
    
    
    AGREED! http://fb.me/NoUfcIrv     
    
    
    Your Destiny Is Determined by what you do with your hands, so put them to work. There is no substitute for hard... http://fb.me/6kBNYIdlt     
    
    
    Tell Them!! http://fb.me/28UKzpNln     
    
    
    Zinedine Zidane: "As a complete player, Steven Gerrard is better than Cristiano Ronaldo and Lionel Messi." #LEADER pic.twitter.com/qYUGTmkm6c    
    
    
    Talking about Business over Hunters... With my Boss. #WorkHard #PlayHard    
    
    
    "Being ignorant is not so much a shame, as being unwilling to learn." _ Benjamin Franklin  #Moron #AGREED    
    
    
    Tell Them!! http://fb.me/2byFZcPgQ     
    
    
    Psychology recommends that, Crush only lasts for a maximum of 4 months. If it exceeds, you're already in love.... http://fb.me/2FhsPaxvH     
    
    
    I Bet!! #AGREED http://fb.me/1Biy8ylBW     
    
    
    Psychology recommends that, Crush only lasts for a maximum of 4 months. If it exceeds, you're already in love.... http://fb.me/124Cga0Hk     
    
    
    "Sheer Bravery is to do things differently irrespective of the status quo - Bravery is not for the weak." - Isaac Atanley    
    
    
    "Sheer Bravery is to do things differently irrespective of the status quo - Bravery is not for the weak." - Isaac Atanley #FEARLESS    
    
    
    Hearts coach David Duncan defends 'slack' second half display http://www.ghanasoccernet.com/hearts-coach-david-duncan-defends-slack-second-half-display/ …    
    
    
    "For gold is tried in the fire and acceptable men in the furnace of adversity." - George Santayana #AGREED    
    
    
    Mark Zuckerberg Was Highest Paid U.S. CEO of 2012 http://on.mash.to/1a9aSzd  via @mashable    
    
    
    Top  Google   users    educated at Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology KNUST [1 - 11], total of 11 found    
    
    
    "In order to be irreplaceable, one must always be different." - Coco Chanel #BeOriginal #Rare #Genuine #OneHundred    
    
    
    AGREED! #WORD http://fb.me/OvMNcKCW     
    
    
    "You do not look for what you have." - Archbishop Benson Idahosa    
    
    
    A true leader does not command his followers but rather leads them to get the job done. You've got to always... http://fb.me/IYTw38hN     
    
    
    "The farther you see the more you desire. If your season is not due, do not complain but comply." - Archibishop Benson Idahosa #DEEP #WORD    
    
    
    What an interesting Truth!!! #Awesome http://fb.me/2KxfSoSDS     
    
    
    Ghana's 'Black Stars' putting African art on the map http://fb.me/1IOKhoukp     
    
    
    Great! http://fb.me/YZizfC2O     
    
    
    CABERNET SAUVIGNON... Vin Rogue!!! #1883 #BonVie #DMCV #CHEERS #OneHundred pic.twitter.com/FVqzNoLH4t    
    
    
    Here Did I Get Here... Haha #ELITE #ENGINEER #CHILLING #TIMBA #ONEHUNDRED #FEARLESSTEAM    
    
    
    They see me rolling... They Hatin'  #RIDIN #CrushDemAll #Damn    
    
    
    RT "@FIFAcom: 150 years ago today, modern football was founded in London. A very happy birthday to the @FA #FA150 - http://fifa.to/1gP6vAJ "    
    
    
    Steven Gerrard is set to play his 450th League game for @LFC today. He'll become the 9th Reds player to reach this pic.twitter.com/91YOwOkokQ    
    
    
    @Hill Club with my Boss. All Work and No Play Make #TIMBA A Very Dull Boy... Yaaaaaaay!!    
    
    
    @Hill Club with my Boss. All Work and No Play Makes #TIMBA A Very Dull Boy... Yaaaaaaay!!    
    
    
    @luis16suarez will surely scored a hat-trick today @D_Sturridge to also score a brace for @LFC #SAS #YNWA #RiseUp # pic.twitter.com/TrElK5ikHx    
    
    
    What a Goal... Suarez puts @LFC ahead.    
    
    
    What an Awesome Goal from luis16suarez... Yaaaaaay!! C'mon Suarez you da king of Nutmeg.    
    
    
    Suarez doubles the lead for Liverpool... Wow! What a player Luis Suarez has become. World Class!!!    
    
    
    Liverpool FC is definitely on fire... What a terrific build up towards the second goal. Great Team work and... http://fb.me/1jbFNts85     
    
    
    Super Free kick... What a goal against Man Utd.  #STOKE strokes pass united... Yaaaay!!!    
    
    
    Call me Timba the Octopus now... I predicted a hat trick for Suarez and he has cleverly done that. Well Done!!!... http://fb.me/2O2QxHbSV     
    
    
    Best Striker duo in the premier league... No doubt!! 14 goals together already between them. Wowza @luis16suarez and @D_Sturridge AKA SAS    
    
    
    Top of the Table Clash next week... Bring on Arsenal!! @LFC gonna definitely Beat dem to rise back on Top of #BPL Table. Coutinho will be...    
    
    
    Top of the Table Clash next week... Bring on Arsenal!!! @LFC gonna definitely Beat dem to rise back on Top of... http://fb.me/1X86nyv2r     
    
    
    RT"@FourFourTwo: Barcelona overcome Madrid at Camp Nou http://fft.sm/17kSkiN  ...as Ancelotti bemoans refereeing decisions #FCB #RMCF"    
    
    
    RT"@FourFourTwo: Rodgers praises 'tireless worker' Suarez after 'difficult summer' http://fft.sm/1g3vPS4  #LFC"#LS7 pic.twitter.com/Xnc33b6Bs7    
    
    
    RT"@kingofaccra: "@Boys_Kasa: Mogbe (Feat. Big Klef) [ http://hype360gh.com/2013/10/king-o … ] by King Of Accra"RT" #Dopest New Single... I luv it!    
    
    
    RT"@LFCFansCorner: Zidane believes the comments of former Manchester United boss Fergie about Gerrard in his autobiography are “strange.”"    
    
    
    EPIC!!! @luis16suarez header today was mind-blowing... Speed of 38mph over 17 yards outside the box. #Sensational pic.twitter.com/MpJGX4US6g    
    
    
    Rodgers hails 'magic' Suarez performance http://fb.me/PsoAxVRq     
    
    
    Sure James!! #YNWA http://fb.me/321e3hbt8     
    
    
    RT"@KingJames: Great solid win today @LFC!" The Best is Yet to come... YOU'LL NEVER WALK ALONE LEBRON!!! #YNWA pic.twitter.com/NM3zHLGGIp    
    
    
    Massive Win!!! "@CaroWozniacki: Holidays!! What better way to start them off? On my way to Liverpool to watch the game at Anfield!" #YNWA    
    
    
    AGREED!!! RT"@LFCTS: Luis Suarez & Daniel Sturridge have started in only 4 matches this season scoring 10 goals" #SAS #EPIC #DUO #LFC    
    
    
    Woke up very early this great morning... listening to audio sermons from Archbishops; Duncan Williams, Benson... http://fb.me/1ABdImHlP     
    
    
    Chillaxin' with my fellow ELITE Engineers over Hunters... Yaaaaaaay!!! Hardwork before Chiling. #ELITE #ENGINEERS... http://fb.me/2zMo5BUwX     
    
    
    Phew! Steam Boiler Installation is 96% completed awaiting fine-tuning by Gabby n co... FIRING of Boiler is... http://fb.me/2vq43EQFR     
    
    
    Psychologists have correctly said that, "when one is truly ready for a thing, it puts in its appearance" 
#100% #AGREE    
    
    
    "Nothing limits achievement like small thinking; nothing expands possibilites like unleashed imagination." - William Arthur Ward    
    
    
    @D_Sturridge is League's top goal scorer with 8 goals and @luis16suarez is joint second with 6 goals. Need i say more? Deadly Duo @LFC #SAS    
    
    
    I Bet!! #Ewww http://fb.me/Z8tOofbV     
    
    
    Its been a great year for me so far i think. Began the year as a Production/Maintenanace Senior Supervisor... http://fb.me/2l031jpgv     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2KACuOPKB     
    
    
    Safety Officer http://fb.me/2C2oYCJut     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1rxLN86Be     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/TopcinQE     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2k6T0IKrf     
    
    
    Don't Complain but Comply... Endurance is a prerequisite to Success. Make a Great week Y'all!!! #Decide #BeDiligent #StriveForGreatness    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2AS6YtgvP     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/YivXSQ2h     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2aqv7CAMu     
    
    
    oooh kk... That explains my situation. #EPIC #EinsteinLike http://fb.me/19Nm9z7LG     
    
    
    Once you go outside the Will of God for your life, you invite troubles unto yourself. #Proverbs 16:25 says that,... http://fb.me/Mu35Rexp     
    
    
    90% will Fail this Test on first Attempt... Try It!!! http://fb.me/1C58fC1lI     
    
    
    "In School of Engineering, they teach you how things work but in real situation, you must make things work -... http://fb.me/Lmfeqvze     
    
    
    "In School of Engineering, they teach you how things work but in real situation, you must make things work - Trained to Deliver." - Isaac A…    
    
    
    Suarez nominated for Ballon D'Or prize - Liverpool FC http://www.liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-news/148022-suarez-nominated-for-ballon-d-or-prize … via @lfc    
    
    
    Pathetic Team Arsenal... Nothing to show for herh!!! #Trophyless #Team http://fb.me/2SqFQZKeV     
    
    
    Sure! Hehe http://fb.me/3opN3Z3Bl     
    
    
    "If you're not willing to work for your success, you don't deserve it anyway. People don't luck in success. The... http://fb.me/276GEg1AW     
    
    
    Never hate people who are jealous of you, but instead respect their jealousy. At least, they are the only people... http://fb.me/YphB9JNL     
    
    
    God Favours Me... No Doubt about that!!!@IamLord_Zico @Kofi_Cylo @kingofaccra @ofoli_kwei @westman86 #GRACED #FAVOURED #JesusIsLord #Indeed    
    
    
    Have not i commanded thee? Be strong and of a good courage; be not afraid, neither be thou dismayed: for the LORD... http://fb.me/6JOmgCv95     
    
    
    I usually chat with our new office secretary @ work. My colleagues might be interested but i dont cuz she's way... http://fb.me/2elKPzkJA     
    
    
    Sure! @forbes Legendary Bill Gates of course. #askforbes    
    
    
    Seriously? @forbes Prez Mugabe i think...lol #powerfulpeople #askforbes    
    
    
    Wow! Real Madrid making a strong statement of intent here. CR7 scores a hat trick whiles a brace and 2 assists... http://fb.me/1afc6gwOK     
    
    
    CR7 Salutes... A reply to a bias Blatter who sees him a Commander. #EPIC #SALUTE #LoveThis #CR7 http://fb.me/6kNc8qiiI     
    
    
    Bring On Arsenal... We need to score 5+ goals against Arsenal this  weekend. #SAS #RiseUp #YNWA http://fb.me/2nsVDm6R4     
    
    
    Boston Red Sox will have won 108 of 178 games this season... That's so Remarkable!! Congrats to Fenway. #WorldSeries #RedSox #Fenway #Champs    
    
    
    "@BishopJakes: Creativity is born in the face of obstacles. Blessings aren’t convenient because God did not promise to put you in convenient    
    
    
    AGREED! @BishopJakes Bless You the for this great and timely Word!!! #Potter #Bishop #BlessU    
    
    
    @IamLord_Zico @Timbahood @westman86 Gradually, we getting there... God is grooming us into becoming World Leaders with a difference. #Arise    
    
    
    Really? "@BBCNews: Safety fears over bioenergy plant http://bbc.in/1bEW8Zl "    
    
    
    Liverpool of course! Watch us rise up to the top of the #BPL this Saturday. Unbelievable Combo #SAS are ready to... http://fb.me/15KWvqSQ1     
    
    
    Syria's chemical weapons production facilities destroyed, says watchdog http://www.theguardian.com/world/2013/oct/31/syria-chemical-weapons-factories-destroyed-opcw …    
    
    
    Coutinho given 'all clear' to return - Liverpool FC http://www.liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-news/148200-coutinho-given-all-clear-to-return?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter … via @lfc    
    
    
    LFC congratulate Red Sox on triumph - Liverpool FC http://www.liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-news/148181-lfc-congratulate-red-sox-on-triumph … via @lfc    
    
    
    Difference is Delightful - dare to be different! @DamnRightTweets Tell Dem!! @GirlfriendNotes AGREED! @Fit_Motivator Word! :p:p:p #Unique    
    
    
    Top  Google   users    educated at Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology KNUST [1 - 11], total of 11 found    
    
    
    Great are You Lord!!! #JesusIsLord    
    
    
    Ameeeen! @AJEnglish AGREED! @GreatestQuotes "Examine what is said, not him who speaks." - Arab Proverb  #WORD    
    
    
    Reinvent! "@Forbes: The generation of startup guys who want to change the way we dispose of the dead. http://onforb.es/1aK73AK " #REINVENT    
    
    
    Dieu Merci C'est Vendred... Yaaaaaaaaaaaay!!! #DMCV #BonVie #SALUT #Novembre    
    
    
    Can't wait... For the first time ever, i'm willing to put a 10,000 butts on this game. #Arsenal v #Liverpool... http://fb.me/1Jys0Ex5n     
    
    
    Cissokho wants win at Arsenal: Aly Cissokho has challenged his Liverpool team-mates to prove they ar... http://bit.ly/1dyV4bC     
    
    
    The Obamacare website mess underscores the first rule of good management http://onforb.es/1dY5ZOH  #Forbes @bamfodinho @westman86    
    
    
    Wow! 52 days more to An #EPIC Christmas. Shoppin' spree is imminent.... Yaaaaaay!!! Brace Yourselves my friends.... http://fb.me/2bFCjVwxJ     
    
    
    Christmas Countdown 2013 - Find out how many days until Christmas 2013 http://www.xmasclock.com/     
    
    
    Self-appointed Technical Tactician/ Director of Mandis Football Team. 3 weeks to go... Play against a formidable Community Team. #TeamMandis    
    
    
    RT"@MirrorFootball:Bonus Kenny Dalglish: Is Arsenal vs Liverpool a battle of title contenders? Just look at the table" #EPIC #KING @LFC    
    
    
    Missing Home Already... Awwww!! Stay Calm cuz my long awaited Annual leave is looming... Yaaaaaaaay!!! #Excited pic.twitter.com/2PttaO0C4K    
    
    
    AGREED!! "@MutomboDaPoet: Clear RT @kinnareads: @Kwabena GBC is to be disregarded, utterly useless. BBC is to be hated. @MutomboDaPoet"    
    
    
    Steven Gerrard Captains the Red Army 'Anfield Warriors' tonite. Let no team forget how menacing we've become as a... http://fb.me/2LZdJRI5S     
    
    
    EPIC COMBO!! @LFCFansCorner TRIO! @OptaJoe Suarez And Sturridge = #SAS   Suarez + COUtinho + SturridgE = SCOUSE  @luis16suarez @D_Sturridge    
    
    
    @westman86 sure bruv!! Its been awhile since i went. Work stuff u noe. Home is where the Heart is they say. #HomeSweetHome    
    
    
    AGREED! RT"@GreatestQuotes: "The most delightful surprise in life is to suddenly recognise your own worth." - Maxwell Maltz" #Onehundred    
    
    
    Greater Days Ahead guys... Brace Yourselves and Believe!!! #StayCalm #Faith #Believe #ENJOY #TIMBA #OneHundred #SALUTE    
    
    
    I Bet!! "@DietmarHamann: Fancy LFC to get a result today.Not sure whether Arsenal got the defensive weapons to stop SAS" @LFC    
    
    
    "@ParisHilton: Hey Moscow, see you all today at The June Shopping Mall in Mytischi. Can't wait to meet you all! See… http://instagram.com/p/gNF8KvK     
    
    
    Totally Deserved!! "@empireofthekop: Suarez named PFA player of the month for October http://liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-ne …" @luis16suarez #SALUTE    
    
    
    "@thisisanfield: Lots of excellent writing from our columnists ahead of today’s game at the Emirates: http://thisisanfield.com/tag/arsenal  #LFC #AF    
    
    
    GROSS! "@iTweetFacts: Gambrinous is a word that describes someone who becomes full from drinking beer." #Hehe    
    
    
    When Liverpool drew 2 : 2 with Newcastle, Chelsea fans be like... Typical Li'pool herh. Today Newcastle scored... http://fb.me/13qEMHpeN     
    
    
    The Coast is Clear for Liverpool to rise to the Top spot of the #BPL Table... All we need is an emphatic Win... http://fb.me/181HEjPPh     
    
    
    Luis Suarez has pipped the likes Wayne Rooney and Mesut Özil to be named as the PFA Fans' Player of the month of... http://fb.me/6ikiOagpC     
    
    
    STAY CALM LIVERPOOL!!! We got this.    
    
    
    DAMN! @iamlord_zico sure! We can't loose this game.    
    
    
    @splizidie I agree!    
    
    
    Sure! @splizidie Arsenal out-played i must say.    
    
    
    Arsenal 2 : 0 Liverpool ...  Arsrenal Play very well and won convincingly. Good nite guys!!! #NotGood    
    
    
    @iamlord_zico Well Done Gunners!!! #TOP #SALUTE    
    
    
    Football  #RIDDLE
I'm currently the top goal scorer in #CL with #7
I'm currently the top goal scorer in  #Laliga... http://fb.me/6wZqwU2cy     
    
    
    Top  Google   users    educated at Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology KNUST [1 - 11], total of 11 found    
    
    
    @Timbahood can't be friends with everyone... my only leverage is to choose them carefully. #HardTruth #PowerOfChoice #AGREED @IamLord_Zico    
    
    
    "The man who does more than he is paid for will soon be paid for more than he does." - Napoleon Hill  #Diligence is Key here  #Noted    
    
    
    Asamoah Gyan: I'm Rooting For Eaglets | NAIJA Lately - Read Nigeria Newspapers Online http://www.naijalately.com/news/asamoah-gyan-im-rooting-for-eaglets#.UnZEhaZP47s.twitter …    
    
    
    Romney: Obama 'dishonest' about Obamacare http://news.yahoo.com/romney-meet-the-press-140953473.html?soc_src=mediacontentstory … via @YahooNews    
    
    
    http://fb.me/6yFtUzUvR     
    
    
    Suarez dismisses Real Madrid link http://kopworld.net/lfc-news/suarez-dismisses-real-madrid-link/1682?utm_source=twitterfeed …    
    
    
    Have a great feeling this Christmas  gonna be so EPIC... Brace Yourselves Guys!!!  #EPIC #GREAT #TIDE #EVENTFUL #XMAS #CantWait @Christmas    
    
    
    "Formulate and stamp indelibly on your mind a mental picture of yourself succeeding. Hold this picture... http://fb.me/2rsOUu33B     
    
    
    #COMANDANTE_CR7
221 Goals for Real Madrid
22 Hat-tricks for Real Madrid
109 Goals in the last 100 games for... http://fb.me/2CW8X8cBx     
    
    
    One Hundred: Will a Glass of Red Wine a Day Keep the Doctor Awa... http://isaac-atanley.blogspot.com/2012/04/will-glass-of-red-wine-day-keep-doctor.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    http://isaac-atanley.blogspot.com/2012/04/follow-timbahood-functiondsidvar-jsfjsd.html …    
    
    
    "All that we are is the result of what we have thought. The mind is everything. What we think we become." - Buddha    
    
    
    "The man who does more than he is paid for will soon be paid for more than he does." - Napoleon Hill  #AGREED #DILIGENCE Is Key HERE!!!    
    
    
    There's now an app for STD testing http://onforb.es/183Ylef  @ameyaw112 #Wowza #EPIC    
    
    
    TOTALLY AGREE!! #EPIC #PIECE #SALUTE #YALL #ENGINEERS http://fb.me/PQxrUj24     
    
    
    A MUST READ #EPIC_PIECE
An engineer went to police station for filing
report for his missing wife:
Engineer : I... http://fb.me/232PiiQ8z     
    
    
    Ing. Timba #SALUTE http://fb.me/3lV5FUab1     
    
    
    Not By Might I must say... Spirit says the LORD!!!  #JesusIsLord http://fb.me/6ylvXUsVb     
    
    
    #BRAIN DAMAGING HABITS
1. No Breakfast
People who do not take breakfask are going to have lower blood sugar... http://fb.me/QGAroniA     
    
    
    "If your employers are happy with your work, that gives you the extra boost to do more for them." - Isaac Atanley  #Gratitude    
    
    
    "If your employers are happy with your work, that gives you the extra boost to do more for them." - Isaac Atanley  #Gratitude @latimes @LFC    
    
    
    En route to Accra... i'm being chauffeured by one of the finest grade A transporters in our pick up truck. I'll... http://fb.me/1TQMnduLI     
    
    
    Got Home Pretty fast. #DAMN    
    
    
    "I find it particularly difficult to understand people who do not want to take responsibility but want to be... http://fb.me/1sv15SNDq     
    
    
    "I find it particularly difficult to understand people who do not want to take responsibility but want to be... http://fb.me/3ieoYxJey     
    
    
    "I find it particularly difficult to understand people who do not want to take responsibility but want to be... http://fb.me/2WSngVQTn     
    
    
    "I find it particularly difficult to understand people who do not want to take responsibility but want to be success…http://lnkd.in/bbnXR6S     
    
    
    A wonderful morning in Accra... @christmas_clock is ticking pretty quick. Can't wait for this #EPIC SEASON to begin... Yaaay!!! #GreatTiding    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2Jiesyaq3     
    
    
    Tesla shares slide after earnings report http://onforb.es/1ehhyki  $TSLA    
    
    
    @nathanquao2211 True! Its amazing how shallow some soccer fans are innit? #Plastic fans i think. lol    
    
    
    China's Huawei to invest $600 million in 5G research over next four years http://reut.rs/1b7K1nv  #wow @ForbesTech    
    
    
    Google Glass Explorer invite $201.63 http://bit.ly/16F9c12  #glasses #video    
    
    
    Nokia Lumia 1520 Comes to AT&T on November 15 for $199 http://on.mash.to/17EqcaI     
    
    
    An impressive range of information being released publicly by governments around the world. Blog: http://wrld.bg/qwMkI  #opengov    
    
    
    How Walmart brought low-cost LEDs to the mass market http://onforb.es/1gquVPN     
    
    
    L. ive 
E. veryday to 
A. chieve your 
D. reams
#leadership    
    
    
    Cristiano Ronaldo achievements in 2013... Top goal scorer in 2013... #59. Messi is a good boy so give ballon d'Or.  #FifaLogic @blowingfact    
    
    
    One World Trade Center unveils new marketing offices to woo tenants http://onforb.es/1eg2KlU  pic.twitter.com/s6ysms4CBe #awesome    
    
    
    The more you have to wait for something, the more you appreciate it when you get it. #Worth_the_Wait #OneHundred #BlessGod    
    
    
    Six led to safety after building collapses in Southport http://dlvr.it/4Gh0Vq  #sosad    
    
    
    Monster Energy argued that "Dope!" granted it the right to publish copyrighted material. The court said nope. http://onforb.es/1egFqV5     
    
    
    Why most people are still suffering and struggling in this life is simply because they are not correct. Not doing... http://fb.me/MPPeV0AP     
    
    
    God Bless You REINHARD BONNKE!!! Welcome To Ghana http://fb.me/6sRAReGIw     
    
    
    Neither is there salvation in any other: for there is none other name under heaven given among men, whereby we... http://fb.me/2wgrcreEr     
    
    
    "I have a great dream, not to be rich and powerful like everyone else; but to be greater than the greatest here on... http://fb.me/ZBW1MPFm     
    
    
    AGREED! http://fb.me/LNbzWVa0     
    
    
    RT"@LFC: Your @StanChart Player of the Month for October is...@luis16suarez - http://liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-ne … pic.twitter.com/3C04NprL9X"    
    
    
    I Bet!! "@nytimes: "The city that never sleeps took an Ambien a long time ago." http://nyti.ms/17du78x "    
    
    
    Wowza!"@ForbesTech:The worldwide video game marketplace will reach $93 billion in 2013, up from $79 billion in 2012. http://onforb.es/1bbo3OQ "    
    
    
    AGREED! "@nytimes: DealBook: Price Cost Twitter Cash but Gave It Credibility http://nyti.ms/1evdZXM " @westman86 @IamLord_Zico @Timbahood    
    
    
    Not Good!! "@guardian: Top US navy intelligence officers suspended as bribery scandal widens:  http://gu.com/p/3k95q/tf " #Unacceptable    
    
    
    Yaaaaaaaay! "@GreatestQuotes: "Stop worrying about the potholes in the road and enjoy the journey." - Babs Hoffman" #RollerCoaster    
    
    
    Sure i think!!! RT"@latimes: Falling gas prices, a gift just in time for the holidays http://lati.ms/qE2iC " @Christmas    
    
    
    Glory Be To God!!! #BlessU http://fb.me/11BZM95bi     
    
    
    There is a very thin difference between people who are smart and people who get good grades. #HardTruth @blowingfact #AGREED    
    
    
    @Anfield in a bit... C'mon @LFC Lets Win massively today. What an Epic way to bounce back in style. #Warriors #Reds #YNWA    
    
    
    Liverpool wit a brace already... Can  we make it 5???    
    
    
    What A Goal... Suarez makes it 3.    
    
    
    Suarez With a brace... What a Gooooooooaaal #Golazo    
    
    
    Suarez u da mehn... Liverpool 4 : 0 Fulham. 3 more goals to go @LFC    
    
    
    West Brom Scores... Chelsea 1 : 1 West Brom    
    
    
    Chelsea getting their Ass whooped... Hehe   Chelsea 1 : 2 West Brom    
    
    
    #Comandante Cristiano Ronaldo scores another Hat-trick... Wow! #CR7    
    
    
    Shit! "@OptaJoe: 66 - Jose Mourino is unbeaten in 66 Premier League home games (W51 D15). Charmed."    
    
    
    What a thrilling Matchday... @LFC won Massively against Fulham and Real Madrid thrashed Sociedad... Helloooooooo! #Excited #Wowza #SuperSat    
    
    
    Goals this season:
Cristiano Ronaldo - 24
Ibra & Cavani - 23
Messi & Neymar - 18
#Comandante Cristiano Ronaldo... Ballon D'Or..:p @YaroLFC    
    
    
    A Muslim giving his life to Christ after being healed at a Crusade... Indeed Jesus Is Lord!!! :D #God_Bless... http://fb.me/2woZvm7Qt     
    
    
    Football Analysis #BPL #LFC
After 11 games last season Liverpool were 13th with 12 points and just 2 Wins. 
This... http://fb.me/11uierLHb     
    
    
    Liverpool v Fulham live football scores | Soccer scores and live video | http://ESPNFC.com  http://espnfc.com/uk/en/gamecast/367383/gamecast.html?soccernet=true … via @espnsoccernet    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/26YPdRSkp     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1S3T190JH     
    
    
    Hillary Clinton lays campaign groundwork in California http://lati.ms/qF7Tc   (She still won't say if she'll run... @BBCWorld @westman86    
    
    
    El Pistolero!! @luis16suarez rated ahead of Messi, Ronaldo and Ribery via @WhoScored @LFC #SALUTE pic.twitter.com/JXbvPbmZoh    
    
    
    The Best!!! "@FourFourTwo: FEATURE Saturday analysis: Is Luis Suarez the best player in the Premier League? http://fft.sm/1bhGCEJ  #LFC #EPL    
    
    
    List Of 20 Richest People In Ghana For 2013: http://www.spyghana.com/list-of-20-richest-people-in-ghana-for-2013/#.Un9tnDV_3B4.twitter …    
    
    
    AGREED! :D http://fb.me/N1lfdzU0     
    
    
    Sunderland Shocks Manchester City... What a league the #BPL is turning into? #EPIC_League #Excited #SuperSunday @BBCSports @Premierleague    
    
    
    Your harvest is in your seed. It is your giving that determines your financial stability in life - Archbishop... http://fb.me/27QqiaRtV     
    
    
    BBC News - Spanish police arrest 25 in 'Nigeria sex-trafficking ring' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-24890952 …    
    
    
    AGREED! "@Sports_HQ: Its not how you start... Its how you finish." #Endurance is Key here.    
    
    
    Remarkable! "@espn: You can't stop the @Saints offense. You can only hope to contain them... which is pretty much impossible." #EPL is Best.    
    
    
    Wow! "@Forbes: Weekend box office: 'Thor 2' sets Marvel record with mighty $86 million http://onforb.es/1dezsR4 " #Cant_wait    
    
    
    "You might well remember that nothing can bring you success but yourself." - Napoleon Hill  #Nothing    
    
    
    "I'm pretty much excited about what am becoming :D:D:D... World Changer. Glory Be To God!!!" - Isaac Atanley  #Magnate #TurnaroundSpecialist    
    
    
    "I'm pretty much excited about what am becoming :D:D:D... World Changer. Glory Be To God!!!" - Isaac Atanley... http://fb.me/6mb96Uwap     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2ugTezwli     
    
    
    Happy 102nd Anniversary To the Great @AccraHeartsOfOakGH  #SALUTE @IamLord_Zico @Timbahood We so very Proud of Ya. #KeepUp    
    
    
    @luis16suarez is Best of the Best in @Premierleague. This dude is totally Out of this World. We can't just get... http://fb.me/25zDlaGTH     
    
    
    "If you really want to do something, you'll find a way. If you don't you'll find an excuse." - Jim Rohn #YourCall    
    
    
    And That Says It All!!! Bless u #PaulaWhite http://fb.me/1X2udsZvZ     
    
    
    About 2 years ago, my colleague and I embarked on a journey to revamp a 'broken down' great facility. We prayed... http://fb.me/OBcKUaz5     
    
    
    #EpicTruth... Bless You Reinhard Bonnke!!! http://fb.me/39PS64cvJ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2AAk3wliB     
    
    
    @chiefmykheals AGREED!    
    
    
    @ofoli_kwei Powa Powa @de_2slo @iamlord_zico hehe @westman86 I clocked A to honour him wai    
    
    
    Like play like play @de_2slo he den Mr. Sagoe were key to my cloaking excellent grade way back u noe.    
    
    
    @westman86 Blame Paul for what? U never took the physics exam u remember? @de_2slo @iamlord_zico @ofoli_kwei    
    
    
    @westman86 i remember now. But who exactly did he cause ur afflictions eh??? @de_2slo @iamlord_zico @ofoli_kwei    
    
    
    Old habits... @ofoli_kwei You forget say we be Bl300 boys herh?    
    
    
    Sure! @ofoli_kwei ibi me noor!  @de_2slo i dey fool k3K3    
    
    
    "TOY GUN" @de_2slo Timba brought a rifle to skul? @iamlord_zico dis dude noe dey hear kraa oo @ofoli_kwei @westman86 hehe    
    
    
    "Nothing in this world can take the place of persistence. Talent will not, nothing is more common than... http://fb.me/R9dGkwcA     
    
    
    WhatsApp Sci4 Group @iamlord_zico Dubbed: TERROR CLASS @de_2slo Grp Members: Cubic, Cylo, Horror... @ofoli_kwei @westman86 Inbox TIMBA    
    
    
    Engineers Proved that:
OMG=WTF   #EPIC #Wow http://fb.me/37XZfERfP     
    
    
    EPIC FACTS!! http://fb.me/2tEwHUDm8     
    
    
    Dont Complain but comply. #Bless U Paula White http://fb.me/6M3veTVDD     
    
    
    You know what is waiting for me beyond that hurdle... IMMORTALITY!!!  #LEGGO #OneHundred @IamLord_Zico @nytimes @westman86    
    
    
    "Being a History-Maker and a World-Changer is about drive, determination, and courage - not talent!" #PaulaWhite #EpicFact    
    
    
    God Is A Good God!!! #SALUTE    
    
    
    My annual Leave officially begins Today... We Bless God for how far he's brought us. A strategic time to rest and... http://fb.me/2rXwIWX3B     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6sKwFtxwV     
    
    
    What an EPIC flying head to seal the Victory for Portgal... Comandante Cristiano Ronaldo is completely Out of this World. #OMG #CR7 #SALUTE    
    
    
    What an EPIC flying header to seal the Victory for Portgal... Comandante Cristiano Ronaldo is completely Out of... http://fb.me/3mVpveSdp     
    
    
    This Dude called Cristiano Ronaldo is gradually carving a niche for himself as the ALL-TIME Greatest ever Player... http://fb.me/QgEHwLZ1     
    
    
    En route to da GYM... No Pain, No Gain.    
    
    
    wit my bros @ a grande anniversaire... How Did We Get Here!!! #DAMN #Onehundred    
    
    
    A limited Edition of @Bordeaux Wine... Awwwww #Rare #1900s #VinRogue #Cabernet #Sauvignon    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6yA58E5Sf     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/PXJfAS9R     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/O7AlbWwj     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/20sgWG8gY     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/22TJeQIjJ     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2uGiKSgZl     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1S7BtYR7B     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6yJ5f2zMm     
    
    
    "The highest reward for a man's toil is not what he gets for it but what he becomes by it." - John Ruskin  #HardTruth    
    
    
    "Brace yourself for the race ahead... This race is not for the swift but the bold. This journey will never be forgotten. Endurance is key h…    
    
    
    "Brace yourself for the race ahead... This race is not for the swift but the bold. This journey will never be... http://fb.me/1aMF5cazG     
    
    
    Since childhood, i enjoyed fighting and beating people. Most people thought i had some sort of Supernatural... http://fb.me/10zevVyiT     
    
    
    I couldn't Agree with u more. @splizidie May the Best country win. @bbckomladumor    
    
    
    Why am i not surprised? #BadChef http://fb.me/2OILrDLQ3     
    
    
    Sometimes Life puts you down but u gotta get up... Stand Up!! #HardTruth    
    
    
    http://fb.me/3361vgtGU     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2k4ccvIG8     
    
    
    "The true sign of intelligence is not knowledge but imagination." - Albert Einstein :D:D:D  #Imagination #AGREED    
    
    
    Need i say more!!! @FIFAcom Portugal of course. They have a formidable squad... @Cristiano  and co.  #worldcup play-offs    
    
    
    "Nobody's a natural. You work hard to get good and then work to get better." - Paul Coffey #diligence    
    
    
    BREAKING: At least 23 people killed in dual blasts in front of the Iranian embassy in Beirut http://cnn.it/1dRkosK     
    
    
    Bill Gates and Bono talk about their alliance of fortune, fame and giving http://onforb.es/18jFQpX  pic.twitter.com/cKv1Jop1H3    
    
    
    Nothing in this world can take the place of persistence.    
    
    
    Now you can book hotels through Twitter http://onforb.es/1f9gE9Q     
    
    
    Ex #BPL striker and now Premier League TV pundit Iain Dowie picks his team of 2013/14 so far http://bit.ly/DowieXI  pic.twitter.com/kPt2ol1ucb    
    
    
    I'm going to 
☐ Paris 
☐ London 
☐ USA 
☑ Kitchen, I'm hungry... lol #KFC #EPIC    
    
    
    #Kuwait would grant $1 billion loans with easy terms to #African countries over the next five years - state news agency KUNA.@BBCAfrica    
    
    
    God is placing great opportunities in your life...pause and appreciate them.    
    
    
    Ghana XI v Egypt: F Dauda; H Afful, J Akaminko, R Sumaila, D Opare; A Ayew, M Essien, S Muntari, K Asamoah; A Gyan; A Waris    
    
    
    Check out my professional profile and connect with me on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/34g2M4  #in    
    
    
    Be strong & courageous. Do not be terrified or discouraged, for the LORD your God will be with you wherever you go. -Josh 1:9    
    
    
    Egypt v Ghana: 4pm GMT    
    
    
    Just one change to the #BlackStars as Harrison Afful comes in for Samuel Inkoom http://bit.ly/1fRuICq  http://fb.me/1cr1RXaP1     
    
    
    Eqypt 1 : 0 Ghana    
    
    
    Game Over!! Ghana Qualifies For Brazil on a dramatic 7:3 aggregate  at the expense of the pathetic Pharoahs of... http://fb.me/2v8kB0X5S     
    
    
    How Did We Get Here!!! Well Done Black Stars... Congrats to Asamoah Baby Jet Bl300bi Gyan for successfully... http://fb.me/34cv7kfP8     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/O2F5F6bQ     
    
    
    K-su paa!!! @ofoli_kwei hehe @de_2slo Confusion! @naa_achere    
    
    
    England of course!!! #Cmon Lions Roar!! http://fb.me/KpJkLdiZ     
    
    
    Suarez to return by private jet - reports http://fb.me/2FdS6ByO3     
    
    
    Just heard my High School Siren sound oo... Good old days i think.
School of No Regret remember? #EPIC #Sound #Memories    
    
    
    Cristiano Ronaldo edges out Zlatan  Ibramovich to qualify to Brazil World Cup with Portugal. This dude is... http://fb.me/30gGTHaAW     
    
    
    Liverpool's defender Mamadou Sahko scores a brace to send France to BRAZIL... impressive! #Welldone #France #Allez #Salut    
    
    
    FRANCE 3 : 0 UKRAINE #AllezLesBleus #coupedumonde2014 #SALUT    
    
    
    Liverpool’s Mamadou Sakho Scores Twice To Sends France To World Cup (VIDEO): Tweet http://bit.ly/1fehnqo     
    
    
    Congrats to @LFCFrance @mamadousakho3 #YNWA 축하합니다! #LFCKorea    
    
    
    Romania 1-1 Greece (Greece win 4-2 on agg) | World Cup play-off report http://gu.com/p/3kgdz/tw     
    
    
    @mamadousakho3: MotM vs Ukraine, Rating 9.8, Goals 2, Clearances 8, Interceptions 2, Pass Accuracy 95% http://www.whoscored.com/Matches/784920/Live …    
    
    
    TF1 attribue le troisième but de l'équipe de France à Mamadou Sakho, qui aurait donc marqué un doublé ce soir! #AllezLeBeus #LFCFrance #LFC    
    
    
    Exodus 3:7-8 (NIV)
[7] The Lord said, “I have indeed seen the misery of my people(ghana) in Egypt. I have heard... http://fb.me/2N6vUdw2N     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_profilepage&v=f82lmOZ_Zcg#t=37 …    
    
    
    Thank You To Barclays Premier League Fans Around The World. #YouAreFootball http://fb.me/6zmqZDjDf     
    
    
    Cristiano: I'm not obsessed with the Golden Ball and I don't respond to anyone. I do my talking on the pitch.... http://fb.me/3iU6W4Yve     
    
    
    Arguably the Best Player in the World now... Hell Yeah!! #Comandante Cristiano Ronaldo is totally Out of This... http://fb.me/2Oi07bTCW     
    
    
    ESPNsoccernet Podcast http://fb.me/6vZCOmHjO     
    
    
    ESPNsoccernet Podcast | Football Features | http://ESPN.co.uk  http://po.st/dFSaVx  via @espnuk    
    
    
    "Nothing in this world can take the place of persistence. Talent will not, nothing is more common than... http://fb.me/2ymY3BQG4     
    
    
    Searching for a Russian Babe to marry... Preferably an engineer of course!!! A Nikita type u noe... Will be in... http://fb.me/6BHEVw4Uf     
    
    
    Cristiano Ronaldo has now scored 26 career Hat-tricks:
Manchester United (1) -
Real Madrid (23) -
Portugal (2)... http://fb.me/29EQa4b9y     
    
    
    Need I Say More??? http://fb.me/NVmskeO7     
    
    
    Cristiano Ronaldo is on course to become the Greatest Football of All Time. Who does that? Comandante CR7 of... http://fb.me/2Dg6p7rdt     
    
    
    Cristiano Ronaldo is on course to become the greatest Footballer of All Time... He's just 28 now remember!!! @Cristiano @BBCSports @FIFA    
    
    
    Three of my Favourite Footballers of All-Time: Steven Gerrard> Cristiano Ronaldo> @luis16suarez ... @LFC @FIFA    
    
    
    It's official now. FIFA and France Football have decided to extend the  Ballon D'or voting till November 29th.... http://fb.me/YzPafuWt     
    
    
    Just go Back from the Gym... Pheew! How did I Get There. No Pain, No Gain Remember!!! #WorkOuts #BodyBuilding #Macho #TIMBA #Onehundred    
    
    
    Typical Blatter Logic huh? #GoodBoyLogic #Pathetic FIFA Prez @BBCSports http://fb.me/2MIbBo4Yn     
    
    
    From January To November 2013... December is imminent. http://fb.me/6yf3jYcHc     
    
    
    Who does That!!! @Cristiano #EPIC #OutOfThisWorld #SALUTE http://fb.me/3fsJopdSp     
    
    
    Ronaldo : I do not have to prove
anything to anyone.
Ronaldo : records are there to be
beaten and it was not my... http://fb.me/33w2XYBVZ     
    
    
    Let no man forget how menacing we are, we are Lions. #BringItOn #LEGGO #FEARLESS #TIMBA #Onehundred    
    
    
    You Deluded Cunt... Zlatan Ibrahimovic!!! #Pathetic #Loser http://fb.me/28h8z89nt     
    
    
    Future Gerrard... Hendo!!! #Believe @LFC http://fb.me/2vwmAf9zz     
    
    
    "Most of the problems we face in this life are man-made. Until we have understanding to deal with them; we are... http://fb.me/238iEfrSw     
    
    
    AGREED! #HardTruth http://fb.me/11tctmu0C     
    
    
    Why Liverpool must tell Real Madrid Luis Suarez is not for sale at any price |  http://metro.co.uk/2013/11/20/why-liverpool-must-tell-real-madrid-luis-suarez-is-not-for-sale-at-any-price-4194476/ … via @MetroUK    
    
    
    The only reason why i enjoy to pray these days is because, when i pray i see results. Its true that fervent... http://fb.me/PgXcXZOy     
    
    
    En route to Selma's engagement ceremony... Wow! I'm so very happy for her. Congrats Selma!!! #Excited #TYLJ    
    
    
    http://en.m.fifa.com/newscentre/news/newsid=2227293/index.html …    
    
    
    http://FIFA.com  - French future bright as starlets come to fore http://fb.me/1jtYSPtQM     
    
    
    Generous and Warmhearted, Creative and Enthusiastic.  Broad-minded and Expansive.  Faithful and Loving. #teamLeo #TIMBA #Onehundred #EPIC    
    
    
    Motivator @Fit_Motivator 
You'll never accomplish anything if you don't believe that you can do it #TellDem #GottaBelieve @latimes @ESPNFC    
    
    
    Consider these 10 affordable, food friendly Bordeaux reds for the #TDAY! Tomorrow, the whites http://bit.ly/TdayReds  pic.twitter.com/BjNKrpkYM1    
    
    
    Costco apologizes for labeling Bibles as "fiction" in a Southern California store http://lati.ms/r4box     
    
    
    Castro - Odo Pa (Feat. Asamoah Gyan & Kofi Kinaata) http://bit.ly/1gXdUhh  @ASAMOAH_GYAN3 @joyonlineghana #video    
    
    
    Good to know that... we coming on board soon. #BELIEVE #Onehundred http://fb.me/2XqgLVNjq     
    
    
    "The reason why Jesus walked on the sea was to demonstrate to the disciples that, the things that they are afraid... http://fb.me/2upCgK4Vn     
    
    
    #RULES http://fb.me/V6UG8DEM     
    
    
    Let no man forget how menacing we are, we are LIONS. Born Stubborn and very FEARLESS. #TeamLeo #TIMBA #FEARLESS #Onehundred    
    
    
    Its Pretty obvious #Comandante CR7 is the Hat-trick King. #SALUTE http://fb.me/2SmRhCJtz     
    
    
    @mubay2000  Isha Allah!!    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1tWv2854b     
    
    
    Can't wait!! http://fb.me/18ASamQk5     
    
    
    I'm Untouchable!!! Can't touch me except you have to touch Jesus Christ First which isn't gonna happen dickhead.... http://fb.me/6nSh3GfFd     
    
    
    Spend your life with those who make you happy, not who you have to impress.
Who does that? #Morons    
    
    
    Hell Yeah!! http://fb.me/2R5EjNxaW     
    
    
    Everton  v  Liverpool
 
Suarez and Sturridge have together scored 16 goals and Everton entire squad has only 14 goals in the #BPL    
    
    
    @iamlord_zico I shock give oo cuz u noe say if we win... We will go top of the table so u wan do against eh.    
    
    
    God has Empowered Us To Succeed @ Any Level... Walk In that realm today. What God has done for one person he can... http://fb.me/1YIupwSe3     
    
    
    Lawsuit Paid In Full: Samsung pays Apple $1 Billion sending 30 trucks full of 5 cent coins http://wp.me/p3ZU84-bo  via @BladeBrownShow    
    
    
    2014 Cadillac ELR, the electric luxury mashup: Motoramic Drives | Motoramic - Yahoo Autos http://autos.yahoo.com/blogs/motoramic/2014-cadillac-elr-electric-luxury-mash-motoramic-drives-184645268.html … via @YahooAutos    
    
    
    Stevie set to equal Carra's record - Liverpool FC http://www.liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-news/149633-stevie-set-to-equal-carra-s-record … via @lfc    
    
    
    Cant Wait to meet Ps. Paula White and co. @ Prayer Cathedral... See Y'all 
There!!!  #GreatAwakening... http://fb.me/1eeMeArbp     
    
    
    C'mon You Mighty Reds!!! #YNWA http://fb.me/3nRoKWQHi     
    
    
    What A Game!!! #MerseysideDerby http://fb.me/2Rq1neAxu     
    
    
    En route...    
    
    
    Travelling outside the country with my big Cousin... Yaaaaaaaaay!!! How Did We Get Here!!! See You Guys soon.... http://fb.me/2NucLV51u     
    
    
    BIENVENUE AU TOGO... WELCOME TO  TOGO!!! My Fatherland... Francophone Level!!!  #BonArrive #Chautaeu #Grande #MOPaO #SALUT @IamLord_Zico    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2v74Sv3Ww     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1O2yuQsAq     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2NEoohfbM     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/16udZxAVf     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/17ShJon1E     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2y8rYQGnW     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/3toIoHt60     
    
    
    3 Days Epic Visit To Togo... How Did WE get There!!! Mission Successful... En Route to Accra now.    
    
    
    My First Time Ever since i went off Facebook & Twitter 3 days in a row... DAMN! Had great Fun in Lome u noe with... http://fb.me/13erszIfY     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/Q18MfWLz     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2tYCuuCl5     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/37cX5wEnt     
    
    
    Finally @ Swanlake... We Bless God For a Super fast Journey. My Chauffeur is da best!!! Home  Sweet Home #OverDrive    
    
    
    Eating Chilly Pork + Limited edition Red Wine... Belle France Selection
Cabernet Sauvignon
Pays d'Oc
Issu de tres... http://fb.me/2BiuJNG3v     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2RdFGWlNh     
    
    
    Please Tell Dem... Thanks so very much Bonnke!!! #SALUTE http://fb.me/2y76iPcCp     
    
    
    "Create an environment for people to fail, to learn, and to grow. Their creativity and productivity will... http://fb.me/2vTtbZ2et     
    
    
    Began an Estate maintenance project @ Home and we intend to finish it this week... Work stuff!!  #LaMaison #Chateau    
    
    
    Gettin' ready to hit town... Ecobank in a bit den Lapaz for some consigment den Oxford Street. #LEGGO #Onehundred    
    
    
    Currently with my lawyers... Filing an Epic Lawsuit against my employers. They will regret it cuz they cannot... http://fb.me/2Blk2wQRr     
    
    
    Victor Moses tells Liverpool's Brendan Rodgers: Start me if you want to see the best of me http://fb.me/6uBJQtt5m     
    
    
    Somewhere in da Far east of the West... Grande Chateau!!! http://fb.me/6jy3Xr4X1     
    
    
    One Hundred!!! http://fb.me/1Hl07Yaq0     
    
    
    Relaxing @ Chateau de Atanley http://fb.me/28LIzInPj     
    
    
    Along the Year with my Boys... Yaaaaaaay!!! http://fb.me/2CzkV0zRE     
    
    
    Tim One HUNDRED!!! http://fb.me/2Ah4WKuzF     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2uL4PHvBu     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2GTPqekF9     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2u2D5qkhJ     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/3wuxWogGe     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2FLSAhm94     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6NLVlyoJ1     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/ZHLfhfJN     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6A2NpGvgV     
    
    
    And Then What!!!    
    
    
    Wow! CR7... Commander of Football Cristiano Ronaldo http://fb.me/1RCQf0OQj     
    
    
    Got Spiffy... Spiff'd Up!!! http://fb.me/1c0NKEzEi     
    
    
    10 People Who Only Show Up During the Holidays http://on.mash.to/1cPqLLX     
    
    
    Michelle Obama on being thankful for military families: "Their stories took my breath away." http://ti.me/1iKceWR     
    
    
    New African Magazine lists Komla Dumor among 100 Most Influential Personalities in Africa.    
    
    
    Americans will cook 736 million pounds of turkey this year. Thanksgiving, by the numbers: http://nyti.ms/1cOn8G8     
    
    
    A large quantity of 'cocaine' has been confiscated by authorities in the #Nigerian city of Kano as it was being smuggled out of the country    
    
    
    France divided over prostitution crackdown: http://yhoo.it/1bruTFy   Radical switch from the country's... http://fb.me/2C7MtnohI     
    
    
    Over 400 Retailers Are Offering Deals On New "Bitcoin Black Friday" Website http://tcrn.ch/1iiolg4   by @sarahintampa    
    
    
    Nutella and Go pic.twitter.com/DDDpI6auRk    
    
    
    Never give up on your dreams. You can make anything happen if you just work hard and believe in yourself. #agreed    
    
    
    I was always looking outside myself for strength and confidence but it comes from within. It was there all the time. - Anna Freud    
    
    
    Photos: Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade balloons, past and present: http://bit.ly/1aW9baP  pic.twitter.com/bapuukbLeR @BBCWorld    
    
    
    Never give up on your dreams. You can make anything happen if you just work hard and believe in yourself. #Agreed    
    
    
    The Best Black Friday Deals | Gadget Lab | http://Wired.com  http://fb.me/2GdJCcGCC     
    
    
    The Best Black Friday Deals | Gadget Lab | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/gadgetlab/2013/11/black-friday/ …    
    
    
    "The Problem in Africa is not Poverty but Greed. Most of our Leaders are self-centered and unintelligent; Its a... http://fb.me/1ajTodNfx     
    
    
    "The Problem in Africa is not Poverty but Greed. Most of our Leaders are self-centered and unintelligent; Its a... http://fb.me/3sSZ3vi4C     
    
    
    A MUST READ!!! http://fb.me/2WSSwut7F     
    
    
    I Bet! @iamlord_zico Just try hard and Win da EPL Trophy cuz its been abt a decade since u guys last won a trophy apart from ur Emirate Cup.    
    
    
    AGREED! @iamlord_zico But does not justify his hefty price tag he was bought... Anyways Gareth Bale is a promising talent i must say.    
    
    
    @iamlord_zico 18 times Champs against 13 times Champs... And u wanna mock us. Who does that???    
    
    
    Gareth Bale hat trick leads Real http://espnfc.com/news/story/_/id/1634424/gareth-bale-hat-trick-leads-real-madrid-atletico-win …    
    
    
    La Liga: Bale bags hat trick, Atletico win http://fb.me/2OqW9nJ2A     
    
    
    Gone Too Soon... Probably You Were Too Fast and Furious. lol #PaulWalker http://fb.me/2WAK9g55x     
    
    
    R.I.P Paul Walker!!! Too Fast, Too Furious... Gone But Never Forgotten. #FastSeven imminent http://fb.me/6vfMIW7C8     
    
    
    Back from da Gym, Basketball court installed @ Home n i'm aboutta rock it wit my injured hand... The only limitation is the Mind remember.    
    
    
    RT "@KalashnikLove: Suarez: "When I have confidence on the pitch, I speak with Stevie. Sometimes he shoots, sometimes I do #LFC #ElPistolero    
    
    
    RT "Suarez: "It's unbelievable. It's not only for me, for the Uruguay players and Liverpool, it's perfect! #LFC" @LFC #RiseUp #Legend    
    
    
    @LFC Suarez: "Against Everton, you hope for the perfect free-kick. I think it was a nice goal." #LFC #Awesome #Freekick #ElPistolero    
    
    
    Looks like Aaron Ramsey's myth continues... He scored a brace and Paul Walker of the Fast and the Furious Fame dies. #EPIC #Omg    
    
    
    "@LiverpoolWays: Gerrard has challenged his teammates to adopt a 'ruthless' mentality during the next seven days .. http://liverpoolfc.com/news/lat     
    
    
    SuperSunday Matchday... Can't wait. #BPL #LFC #SuperSunday http://fb.me/SB585swa     
    
    
    SuperSunday Matchday... Can't wait. #BPL #LFC #SuperSunday http://fb.me/2V1P7bOvc     
    
    
    En route to an Epic Event wit my troops... DAMN! How Did We Get Here. #EPIC_CONVEY #ELITE #Genuine_Rollers #Pro #SALUTE    
    
    
    BBC News - New York train crash: Metro-North derailment in Bronx http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-25176496 …    
    
    
    Liverpool must WIN Against Hull City... Nore More Draws if we wanna play in Champions League next season @LFC ... C'mon Mighty Reds. #YNWA    
    
    
    Seriously "@ESPNFC: GOAL!!!! @hullcityteam takes the 2-1 lead thanks to Meyler's rebound in the box."    
    
    
    Liverpool Losing 3:1 Away to Hull City... And that Really Sucks u noe. What Happened to my Liverpool eh... Did we sleep or what??? #NotCool    
    
    
    ASUS N550JV Laptop Review http://po.st/5Nx4F2  via @TrustedReviews    
    
    
    Wow! Totally Deserved... Living Legend. One of our very own. #Bl300bi #AccraAca #BL300 #DrVCCrabe http://fb.me/1ceN4GXfd     
    
    
    @livechonews @lfcts Will definitely be a great addition to our squad but as to whether he's our No.1 Priority... I gues not!!    
    
    
    EPIC Results!! @talksport Liverpool v AC Milan Champions League Final 2005 @Instanbul @LFC #MyClubsGreatestResult    
    
    
    Messi Injured >>>
Result : Barcelona 1 - 2 Ajax
Result: Barcelona 0 - 1 Athletic club
Where is Neymar ???????... http://fb.me/3uRuUxX27     
    
    
    AGREED!! "@LFCFansCorner: Still think Liverpool can get the Champions League, but Liverpool should buy two first team players in January.    
    
    
    Great News!! RT"@JamesPearceEcho: Rodgers - 'Coutinho will be fine for Wednesday. He has had no reaction. He has trained well today.'"    
    
    
    "@LFCFansCorner: Sakho, we paid £17m for him, he scored his first goal for France recently. Start him, his confidence is high.    
    
    
    Well Said Commander @Cristiano Ronaldo... Legend! #HalaMadrid #SALUTE http://fb.me/2VihDKlQe     
    
    
    POTS

Pot 1: 

Brazil, Spain, Germany, Argentina, Colombia, Belgium, Uruguay and
Switzerland.

Pot 2: 

USA,... http://fb.me/2QhG3ZD5J     
    
    
    @splizidie Sure! But Pastore looks so expensive u noe.    
    
    
    Infatuation is when you find somebody who is absolutely perfect. Love is when you realize that they aren't and it doesn't matter. #LoveFacts    
    
    
    "Nobody achieves greatness because everyone agree with them." - Bishop T.D Jakes  #DulyNoted    
    
    
    @splizidie nah hun, he's worth abt 30m to 4Om remember #PSG    
    
    
    @splizidie Hell No hun... Pastore is worth abt 30  to 4Om remember? #PSG    
    
    
    You must be spiritually, mentally, emotionally and physically strong to support @LFC #AGREED #YNWA    
    
    
    @luis16suarez to bag another Hat trick against Norwich tomorrow @Anfield @LFC
1 LIKE = Hat Trick    
    
    
    Gone But Not Forgotten... http://fb.me/26spnPpZB     
    
    
    "Living with integrity means: Not settling for less than what you know you deserve in your relationships. Asking... http://fb.me/2bVFCgTOp     
    
    
    "Develop an attitude of gratitude, and give thanks for everything that happens to you, knowing that every step... http://fb.me/11agKhFAl     
    
    
    "Develop an attitude of gratitude, and give thanks for everything that happens to you, knowing that every step... http://fb.me/OEHmI444     
    
    
    "Develop an attitude of gratitude, and give thanks for everything that happens to you, knowing that every step... http://fb.me/6iIuEvsye     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2Wgqr8vJK     
    
    
    Breaking!!! Michael Essien's mother just
mistakenly wished him a 42nd birthday
on
radio. Actually he's 31... http://fb.me/2kZUWvLwt     
    
    
    Breaking News!!! 
Michael Essien's mother just
mistakenly wished him a 42nd birthday on radio. Actually he's 31... http://fb.me/2EXJm6ErF     
    
    
    The Japanese prosthetics maker who reconstructs fingers (costing £2,000 each) for victims of... http://fb.me/2V9mME508     
    
    
    @splizidie Nawa oo... 'Football Age' i think.    
    
    
    Liverpool and Manchester United on alert for transfer of Pedro from Barcelona http://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/transfer-news/liverpool-manchester-united-alert-transfer-2880272#.Up5oe6DJ09s.twitter …    
    
    
    Liverpool and Manchester United on alert for transfer of Pedro from Barcelona http://fb.me/P0lmssYx     
    
    
    Philippe Coutinho set for Liverpool recall as Reds look to grab win over Norwich http://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/liverpool-team-news-philippe-coutinho-2878112#.Up5o_oHxbs0.twitter …    
    
    
    "Negaholics" are people who become addicted to self-doubt and negativity. They find the bad in most things and... http://fb.me/16iul4isw     
    
    
    "Negaholics" are people who become addicted to self-doubt and negativity. They find the bad in most things and hardly ever satisfied. #Nega…    
    
    
    Rodgers' targets for January window - Liverpool FC http://www.liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-news/150341-rodgers-targets-for-january-window … via @lfc    
    
    
    "Negaholics" are people who become addicted to self-doubt and negativity. They find the bad in most things and... http://fb.me/189mYpqnw     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2CuvCZm9i     
    
    
    Who is the Best for 2013? Messi or Ronaldo? View Facts and Figures below before you comment please. @Cristiano... http://fb.me/36wZPCT7u     
    
    
    Well Said Captain Casillas. #Legend #Hala Madrid http://fb.me/2LshdBXAk     
    
    
    Another Luis Suarez Hat trick imminent against Norwich tonite at Anfield as Liverpool need to bounce back from a... http://fb.me/1CxbGyJ8H     
    
    
    Final meeting with my Epic lawyers before we file a lawsuit against my unfaithful employers. Most of our leaders;... http://fb.me/1827Qxo7S     
    
    
    November Goal of the Month revealed !!!!
Standard Chartered Player of the Month Luis Suarez has completed a clean... http://fb.me/1UNHZ6dej     
    
    
    A Resounding Amen Bishop!!! #Believe http://fb.me/11ghGa6GP     
    
    
    Who will face Brazil? Guess the host's group and you could win a trip to the #WorldCup Final  http://fifa.to/1cVA9OA  pic.twitter.com/zRSxW4yCXE    
    
    
    TTI imminent... Yaaaaaaaay! http://fb.me/2JbyqU8As     
    
    
    "Действительно Бог и есть Бог"    
    
    
    @Cristiano Ronaldo is on course to Win the Ballon D'or for the second time. #Cmon #Comandante #Salute http://fb.me/2BwY9EWcO     
    
    
    Suarez made me proud indeed with another Hat trick... Luis Suarez remains the only player ever to score an hat... http://fb.me/110pJS08X     
    
    
    @luis16suarez... What a player!!! #ElPistolero #King #Fantastic http://fb.me/6muUq7u0l     
    
    
    Luis Suarez scores his Fourth of the nite... Amazing Super Free Kick.    
    
    
    Now dats what i'm talking abt... We've bounced back strongly. #RiseUp #WalkOn #MightyReds #YNWA http://fb.me/1PGuxjYDh     
    
    
    FT: Liverpool 5 : 1 Norwich  Suarez  scores 4 goal and 1 assist... This dude is out of this world. #Unplayable... http://fb.me/18seP0P6x     
    
    
    "Always looking towards what lies ahead of me because that which is behind is of the past and technically dead to... http://fb.me/2NF3tOSww     
    
    
    "Действительно Бог и есть Бог"    
    
    
    The past is behind, learn from it. The future is ahead, prepare for it. The present is here, live it. @DavidRoads Quotes    
    
    
    Brendan Rodgers places Luis Suárez in company of 'the Ronaldos and Messis' after four-goal haul http://gu.com/p/3yvz4/tw  #lfc    
    
    
    Premier League top scorers: #BPL

Suarez - (13) in 9 games
Aguero - (11)
Sturridge - (9)
Remy, Ramsey,... http://fb.me/2sMnWsj0Y     
    
    
    @luis16suarez Is definitely Out-Of-This World... Honestly, he's so very different and Priceless. God Bless Him MORE!!! @LFC @BBCSport    
    
    
    Joe Allen claims few teams in world football could have coped with @luis16suarez last night #Incredible #ElPistolero http://fb.me/6BJ4Duq1F     
    
    
    AGREED! http://fb.me/6nAJJ8Las     
    
    
    Good Afternoon!! @ocmesrl @hotandcoldglue @kazoupltd @littleseavideo    
    
    
    It is reported that FIFA’s official World Cup draw rehearsal took
place in Brazil earlier this evening, and it... http://fb.me/2LONkh9ox     
    
    
    Great Words from Suarez... Sure He'll Never Walk Alone. #Legend #ElPistolero #Incredible #OutOfThisWorld http://fb.me/6xOywmjKS     
    
    
    Great Words from Suarez... Surely He'll Never Walk Alone. #Legend #ElPistolero #Incredible #OutOfThisWorld http://fb.me/1HEPsFZ4T     
    
    
    http://fb.me/37UwyJJsf     
    
    
    Question: Where does Luis Suarez rank against
strikers you played with and against in the
Premier League? (From... http://fb.me/6pAhhXY7r     
    
    
    Need I Say More? @luis16suarez http://fb.me/17t8cxx7b     
    
    
    YNWA Mandela... A True Liverpool fan. #Legend #YNWA http://fb.me/2SP4xcFBb     
    
    
    RIP Great Nelson Mandela. A True Liverpool fan... You'll Never Walk On. Gone But Not Forgotten. ;(;(;( #Legend... http://fb.me/2P132voYD     
    
    
    RIP Great Nelson Mandela. A True Liverpool fan... You'll Never Walk Alone. Gone But Not Forgotten. ;(;(;( #Legend... http://fb.me/2JBSsyBpT     
    
    
    Great Leader!! "@BBCWorld: Nelson #Mandela: The death of a rare saintly politician http://bbc.in/1d0voDa  pic.twitter.com/nv41EdNPKq"    
    
    
    @oliviajwayne He was A True Liverpool Fan of course. #YNWA    
    
    
    @Pro Gym with my soldiers... Began professional training here 3 3 years ago. I'm da youngest Chap to still endure. No Pain, No Gain. #Pro    
    
    
    @Pro Gym with my soldiers... Bouncers, Engineers, Medics, Business guys, Police, Body-Builders. Began... http://fb.me/6yGZXKt1F     
    
    
    Fews Years ago before we began #ProGym, these Fearless Men born of a Woman inspired me. Now i'm part of the Squad. pic.twitter.com/d6IfGWt2wA    
    
    
    Few Years ago, before we began ProGym, these Fearless Men born of Women inspired me greatly. Indeed, How Did I Get pic.twitter.com/DILjFKf4rP    
    
    
    Few years ago, before we began Professional Gym, these Fearless Men born of Women inspired me greatly. Indeed,... http://fb.me/2Ee1mBFh9     
    
    
    FIFA President heaps praise on Nelson Mandela following his passing http://fb.me/22FFAmF9h     
    
    
    "Intelligence is not how well you excel in school but how useful you become. Grades alone can't measure one's... http://fb.me/X0WYmsOK     
    
    
    "Intelligence is not how well you excel in school but how useful you become. Grades alone can't measure one's intelligence. Intelligence is…    
    
    
    Seriously? Hackers on da rise... Becareful Social Media Freaks!!! #Hackers http://fb.me/122EwXA1U     
    
    
    13 - Luis Suarez (13) has scored one
more Premier League goal than West
Ham have as a team (12) this season.
Flourish.    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2yZnrm57K     
    
    
    Wow! @luis16suarez the record breaker. #BPL #LFC http://fb.me/PEwkQICG     
    
    
    Nelson Mandela quotes: 'Real leaders must be ready to sacrifice all for the freedom of their people' http://www.theguardian.com/world/2013/dec/06/nelson-mandela-life-quotes …    
    
    
    Nelson Mandela book of condolence opens in Liverpool http://www.liverpoolecho.co.uk/news/liverpool-news/liverpool-opens-nelson-mandela-book-6379472#.UqHFiuNzI8k.twitter …    
    
    
    Ballon d'or latest update:
3. Frank Ribery 72
2. Leonel Messi 109
1. Cristiano Ronaldo 126
We have to wait until... http://fb.me/6pSEywhV2     
    
    
    Group G: Germany, Ghana again... Back to back. This time we gonna finish dem... Yaaaaaaay!    
    
    
    Group G: Germany, Ghana, USA again... Back to back. This time we gonna finish dem... Yaaaaaaay!    
    
    
    Group G: Germany, Ghana, USA again... Back to back. This time we gonna finish dem all... Yaaaaaaay!    
    
    
    Group G: Germany, Ghana, USA, Portugal... Group of Death of course. Brazil 2014... Here We Go!!! #Wow #Excited #Yes #Brazil2014    
    
    
    Who says Ghana can't qualify through this Group eh? You Men of very little Faith. We triumphed over Czech... http://fb.me/6BRLqHtD5     
    
    
    Some of us, we don't just talk. The Grace of God upon us is very rare. We are born very Fearless in Christ Jesus.... http://fb.me/P2khcyb5     
    
    
    Some of us, we don't just talk. The Grace of God upon us is very rare. We are born very Fearless in Christ Jesus.... http://fb.me/10ep37ggE     
    
    
    Wow! Great news... HELL YEAH!! http://fb.me/2KYqTg0yQ     
    
    
    Liverpool plan ''amazing'' Luis Suarez contract offer in the New Year http://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/liverpool-plan-amazing-luis-suarez-2899591#.UqJSfey5cdU.twitter …    
    
    
    England World Cup group: Three lions face Italy, Uruguay and Costa Rica in tough draw http://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/england-world-cup-group-three-2897859#.UqJTBM_gvio.twitter …    
    
    
    Germany and Ghana will most definitely qualify to the next round.... Ghana will win against the USA as they've... http://fb.me/6pGDVUN3Y     
    
    
    Group G: Germany, Portugal, Ghana, USA... Group of Death. Ozil, @Cristiano, Gyan, Dempsey #GroupG @BBCSports #WC pic.twitter.com/uo0Yz1TQ9d    
    
    
    MATCHDAY... Cmon Liverpool, We got this against the Hammers. http://fb.me/2vAo7Blq5     
    
    
    Like Seriously!! @splizidie Martin Srktel with his second own goal for the week huh? That's not so cool i think. #YUCK    
    
    
    David Moyes is Tactically Not Correct. This dude is a Joke i think... The Glory Days of United now their Doom Days i reckon. #Pathetic    
    
    
    @luis16suarez is simply unplayable. What a goal that was. Already has 14 sensational goals. My Very Best Striker. #Incredible    
    
    
    Suarez is unstoppable... What a Striker. Almost scored his third goal of the game. #ElPistolero    
    
    
    And That Ends it all... Awesome! Liverpool 4 : 1 West Ham, Stoke City 3 : 2 Chelsea, Saints 2 : 2 Man City, Man Utd 0 : 1 Newcastle...    
    
    
    And That Ends it all... Awesome! Wouldn't have asked less u noe... Yaaaaay!!! 
 Liverpool 4 : 1 West Ham, Stoke... http://fb.me/1dde6Ixd1     
    
    
    @luis16suarez - Luis Suarez is the very Best Player in the Barclays Premier League so far this season. Best... http://fb.me/PLzzJpjx     
    
    
    Liverpool Overtake Chelsea and Man City... @LFC now 2nd on the #BPL Table. #Nice #YNWA http://fb.me/2CvkBTNxC     
    
    
    Liverpool overtake Chelsea and City http://espnfc.com/news/story/_/id/1643017/premier-league-liverpool-go-second-chelsea-lose-city-draw-newcastle-beat-man-united …    
    
    
    Only @Cristiano (17) and Diego Costa (15) have more goals than Luis Suarez (14) in the europe's top 5 league... Suarez missed 5 games.    
    
    
    Only @Cristiano (17) and Diego Costa (15) have more goals than luis16suarez (14) in the europe's top 5 league...... http://fb.me/36bqwEOZJ     
    
    
    Only @Cristiano (17) and Diego Costa (15) have more goals than @luis16suarez (14) in the europe's top 5 league...... http://fb.me/2dL3zWlOl     
    
    
    WE ARE LIVERPOOL WE ARE LIVERPOOL WE ARE LIVERPOOL WE ARE LIVERPOOL WE ARE LIVERPOOL WE ARE LIVERPOOL WE ARE... http://fb.me/2FPWF5YMe     
    
    
    Liverpool could offer Luis Suarez a deal worth £250k a week and a £100m release clause in his contract.    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2Rr8bK3RX     
    
    
    AGREED! http://fb.me/1iPnWcYNX     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2RVBw9q6m     
    
    
    Special Grace of God is upon my Life. #Greatness http://fb.me/1VngVXnJz     
    
    
    A Beautiful Monday Morning. We Thank God For Another Great week cuz Last week was so very EPIC. Make A Great Week Y'all #GodBless    
    
    
    Cool breeze buh dusty... harmattan remember? #YUCK    
    
    
    We Playing Basketball... LEGGO!!! #HomeSweetHome    
    
    
    http://fb.me/6AQAwYfPl     
    
    
    SALUTE! #Awesome http://fb.me/1PNwwPpfk     
    
    
    Sure! #BlessU http://fb.me/18xPEjl4I     
    
    
    Tell Dem!! http://fb.me/2MbZjqGVv     
    
    
    http://fb.me/19kan8Pu0     
    
    
    Pretty obvious i think. http://fb.me/2GKkzpjdv     
    
    
    http://fb.me/M72otb5y     
    
    
    http://fb.me/310y8Dzy5     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1EIoh8Ckx     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2tXueEFGm     
    
    
    http://fb.me/17442SuJF     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2dsDCU9cb     
    
    
    Hehe http://fb.me/10bnpEsa0     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1aMdz5CpJ     
    
    
    Monster Truck!! http://fb.me/1aR1fCPrf     
    
    
    Awww http://fb.me/2ytpV38x5     
    
    
    Choose? http://fb.me/2WTNFjC0W     
    
    
    Hell Yeah!! #ThatsIt http://fb.me/1Ykow1rpv     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3cNLObmKq     
    
    
    The Boss!! #SALUTE http://fb.me/2vBt6DBvW     
    
    
    Welcome Home my Canadian sis... Our Atanley Familly Reunion is imminent. #Excited #Atanley #Ethel    
    
    
    http://fb.me/243OoUm90     
    
    
    Tell Dem Robert!!! #Word http://fb.me/2TQXGJvMz     
    
    
    http://fb.me/16fdkvgwe     
    
    
        
    
    
    Wow! Another milestone reached @Cristiano Ronaldo #UEFA #EPIC http://fb.me/6mmUEeJIL     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2R0rQNw1w     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1LmehIEvm     
    
    
    #Cristiano_Ronaldo 
- Fifteen goals in his last eight games overall.
What a player.
Ronaldo has now broke the... http://fb.me/390U2sA48     
    
    
    I'm going for the KILL... Yaaaaaaaay!!! Let No Man Forget How Menacing We Are!!! Operation Code named 'KILL DEM... http://fb.me/6kz9k2YKU     
    
    
    #SALUTE http://fb.me/14GfstBTw     
    
    
    Need I Say More??? #EPIC_YEAR #BlessGOD #EXCITED http://fb.me/PDIej0KT     
    
    
    Year Highlights... How Did I Get HERE!!! #Diligence #Favour #Grace #Greatness #Prayers http://fb.me/RmGXpnXS     
    
    
    Hell Yeah!! #WatchAndLearn instead. http://fb.me/1JBNYGWEE     
    
    
    My Life... REPENTED!! http://fb.me/2y5BNYLq5     
    
    
    HELL RELL FT CORY GUNZ Dope Dealer Freestyle by ohboytopgunna via #soundcloud https://soundcloud.com/ohboytopgunna/hell-rell-ft-cory-gunz-dope?utm_source=soundcloud&utm_campaign=wtshare&utm_medium=Twitter&utm_content=https://soundcloud.com/ohboytopgunna/hell-rell-ft-cory-gunz-dope …    
    
    
    Birdman - Y.U. MAD ft. Nicki Minaj, Lil Wayne: http://youtu.be/jHgOvf7710k  via @youtube    
    
    
    How Did I Get Here!!! #Diligence #DivineFavour #Grace #Empowered by God #Blessed    
    
    
    “Intelligence is not how well you excel in school but how useful you become. Grades alone can’t measure one’s... http://fb.me/2GytF7ob8     
    
    
    Wanna get a white girl too... my life, my choice remember??? #Choice http://fb.me/29DlbdBve     
    
    
    Funny Video i think. lol #Enjoy http://fb.me/255gqfbtQ     
    
    
    Family Is Forever... Inspiring Video!! #Agreed http://fb.me/2AAbWeXt6     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2WTQXff3g     
    
    
    What an epic day... Phew! #Epic #MissionAccomplished #DoneDeal #Adieu    
    
    
    http://fb.me/6m0R9O24d     
    
    
    Enough for one day!!! #Adieu    
    
    
    God Bless this Atm... my very dependable machine friend. lol #LoyalAtm #SALUTE http://fb.me/2GPooDXgL     
    
    
    A Beautiful Morning... awww. Gym time den after basket ball    
    
    
    Let No Man Forget How Menacing We Are... I see whats coming and i'm Fearlessly ready to battle down completely... http://fb.me/6oHOnTkTy     
    
    
    Work in Progress... Yaaaaaay!!!  #SALUTE http://fb.me/2Wuh9T7fB     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2QdLFUHdy     
    
    
    Fresh Timba... Awwww!!! #Onehundred #Excited #Determined http://fb.me/2zt1P6TO9     
    
    
    AGREED! http://fb.me/3bkLNDDdx     
    
    
    "The man who does more than he is paid for will soon be paid more than he does." - Napoleon Hill    
    
    
    "All that we are is the result of what we have thought. The mind is everything. What we think we become." - Budda  #AGREED    
    
    
    Indeed Jesus Is Lord... I'm so very excited  cuz every piece of puzzle in my life seems to fall into place at the... http://fb.me/WyYwGZ4N     
    
    
    HOW DID I GET HERE!!!! #GRACE #DivineFavour #Intercession #Diligence http://fb.me/6BOgkdqwV     
    
    
    Wow! #BioEngineering http://fb.me/2Ngn2KAl7     
    
    
    Awww http://fb.me/2vxSSYMDK     
    
    
    EA Sports It Is... Yaaaaaaaay!!! http://fb.me/R1v9v1nu     
    
    
    Friday The 13th... Creepy Day i gues. #Horror    
    
    
    Is It Not Friday Yet?    
    
    
    Yummy! #ENJOY    
    
    
    Great Responsibility Ahead... Brace Yourselves guys!!! #Maturity #Endurance #Diligence http://fb.me/29QDTc8DH     
    
    
    Off to da Gym... No Pain, No Gain. #ProGym    
    
    
    Wow! Three of the finest lawyers in the country alongside other governmental agencies are on my case as both have... http://fb.me/Q2xPCMVp     
    
    
    Manchester City is showing us why they deserve to Win the #BPL this season. 

Man City 3 : 1 Arsenal    
    
    
    From henceforth let no man trouble me: for i bear in my body the marks of the Lord Jesus. #Galatians 6:17 #Declaration    
    
    
    Getting ready to go to church... Yaaaaay!!! #Excited #SuperCharged #Invinsible #Blessed    
    
    
    Church today was so Epic... Wow! #SuperAwesome #Blessed #Empowered http://fb.me/3stdB92mA     
    
    
    LIKE FATHER LIKE SON... SAME BLOODLINE!!! DANIEL KOFIGAH ATANLEY WILL NEVER BE FORGOTTEN. #SALUTE #DONNE http://fb.me/2uKn9jFsq     
    
    
    Tottenham Hotspurs have scored 15 goals in 15 Premier League games | Luis Suarez has scored 15 goals in 10... http://fb.me/3AGCyVr2M     
    
    
    Liverpool are playing so very well and should have been Up by a goal or 2 now i think... C'mon You Mighty Reds!!! #RiseUp    
    
    
    @luis16suarez is totally unplayable... What a goal by the Captain of @LFC . Hell Yeah!!    
    
    
    I Never Lost Faith in Jordan Henderson... What a clever goal from the lad. #THFC 0 : 2 #LFC    
    
    
    This is why I support my Fantastic Reds. I Never Once lost faith in Liverpool although sometimes i get... http://fb.me/2bXpdwx3S     
    
    
    Luis Suarez with his second goal of the season. Wow! 17th goals in 11 Premier league games... Who does that? #THFC 0 : 4 #LFC    
    
    
    WELL DONE @LFC for thrashing Tottenham Hotspurs @ White Hart Lane. What a lessons that was? The Reds were Ruthless!!! #THFC  0 : 5 #LFC    
    
    
    It's Finished!!! http://fb.me/TpkqxiWr     
    
    
    Passing thru    
    
    
    Luis Suarez: 17 goals in 11 games. No Penalties #BPL
Cristiano Ronaldo: 17 goals in 15 games. 4 Penalties included. #LaLiga    
    
    
    "Whatever course you decide upon, there is always someone to tell you that you are wrong. There are always... http://fb.me/3oelomfp4     
    
    
    Just got back from #ProGym. Playing basket ball now @ home. I'm running my own bizness now by God's grace and... http://fb.me/38ynDCKTz     
    
    
    Not By Might remember? Diligence is key. #ENJOY http://fb.me/1P3nrac8z     
    
    
    Mascot snubs Suarez: http://youtu.be/nk4f_2TxzGo  via @youtube    
    
    
    A Great Victory that was for my Liverpool... Enjoy the goals highlights. Luis Suarez is unplayable!!! Simply... http://fb.me/MwUUGX1d     
    
    
    Manic Monday i think... Awwww #ENJOY pic.twitter.com/Boru67zUR3    
    
    
    We Playing Basket ball... Yaaaaaaay!! #DANGIN #BANGIN #BAM http://fb.me/2ySLj5v2x     
    
    
    @luis16suarez since returning from his epic 10 match ban has scored 17 goals, 4 assists + 2 Hat tricks and also... http://fb.me/3z0UxrdSa     
    
    
    Somewhere in West Africa!!! #BiznessTour http://instagram.com/p/h_gRMUHafY/     
    
    
    2014 Is Almost Here But I Gotta Finish 2013 on High Y'all Know How We Do It!!! It's going down next week guys. Brace Yourselves & Lets Do It    
    
    
    Thou saith the Lord, 2014 Is My Year Of Great Increase... Hundredfold!! #Genesis 26:12 #GreatWealth #PropheticWord #2014 #TYLJ    
    
    
    Great Achievements Involve Great Risk Remember? #Courage #WillPower #Diligent #Trustworthy #Intelligent http://fb.me/2UGbVwkQM     
    
    
    Never underestimate some of us cuz it could get u killed remember? #Caution    
    
    
    ESSE QUAM VIDERI... TO BE IS BETTER THAN TO SEEM TO BE!!! SCHOOL OF NO REGRETS. #BL3OO #HONESTY #SALUTE http://fb.me/6y3m0yc6b     
    
    
    Moving Into My Self-owned Mansion @ Trassaco early next year & My First SUV - Cadillac Escalade Platinum Edition... http://fb.me/12IuAE9H9     
    
    
    "There is one quality which one must possess to win, and that is definiteness of purpose, the knowledge of what... http://fb.me/1LIoFDjw7     
    
    
    "There is one quality which one must possess to win, and that is definiteness of purpose, the knowledge of what one wants, and the burning …    
    
    
    Universal Serial Port - USB  #ENGINEER http://fb.me/35MPftmMX     
    
    
    Epic Circuit For Life. #Engineers http://fb.me/2qRBuG0np     
    
    
    I Can Feel the Christmas Season Now coupled with a dusty but Cool Wind in a Accra... Harmattan remember? Xmas... http://fb.me/LL2aCjIq     
    
    
    Need I Say More herh? @luis16suarez #ElPistolero #FinestStriker #Unplayable #Incredible #Epic http://fb.me/2eqsKyex4     
    
    
    Currently gotta choose from these 5 Adorable Babes... 3 Russian Babes, 1 Ukrainain babe, 1 Polish Babe. #Excited #DreamComeTrue #Russian    
    
    
    2014... Loading ~ 95% 
Brace Yourselves Guys. #MerryChristmas #GreatNewYear In advance to Y'all. http://fb.me/2JY3wENtB     
    
    
    I've been tryin' to Tell Dem this for a long time now Son. #EPIC http://fb.me/RpTzGRPu     
    
    
    Midday Live  - Discuss Job Cuts in Mining Sector - 17/12/2013 http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3_KOUHeVVio&sns=tw … via @youtube    
    
    
    Energy Drinks leading to heart attacks. #SERIOUSLY #IQuit http://fb.me/1ecYd1sIQ     
    
    
    Bonne Nuit guys!!! #SleepWell    
    
    
    @LFC    
    
    
    Particularly deserved!! @Forbes: Dwayne (@TheRock) Johnson is the top-grossing actor of 2013 http://onforb.es/1jbigm7  pic.twitter.com/zfmqI9HrAM"    
    
    
    Well Deserved!! I watched a couple of his 2013 movies... Great Acting. http://fb.me/RXZAtOqV     
    
    
    Well deserved!! @Forbes @TheRock Keep Up the great work Dude. You da mehn n you Rock. #Damn    
    
    
    "The highest reward for one's toil is not what one gets for it, but what one becomes by it." - John Ruskin    
    
    
    "The highest reward for one's toil is not what one gets for it, but what one becomes by it." - John Ruskin #Great    
    
    
    En route to #ProGym. Gotta do some workouts u noe. I think am putting up so much weight these days which aint healthy i believe. #LEGGO #Pro    
    
    
    ProGym http://fb.me/1L2xuGL1G     
    
    
    Seriously? #Weird #fb http://fb.me/14yqkSPmk     
    
    
    Gettin' ready for 2 high profile meetings this afternoon... Pretty much excited cuz i already know the overcome. Wow! #TYLJ #    
    
    
    http://fb.me/3fFsnzZfc     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6ADmPoVfW     
    
    
    https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rechner.road_race …    
    
    
    BBC News - UK unemployment rate at lowest since 2009 http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-25428119 …    
    
    
    I find the Unfriend buttom on facebook pretty useful these days u noe. Privacy is key in social networks my... http://fb.me/2NyLDRTi2     
    
    
    360 Mobile Security- Antivirus - Android Apps on Google Play http://fb.me/X2vbYQzM     
    
    
    "For I know the thoughts that I think toward you, says the Lord, thoughts of peace and not of evil to give you a... http://fb.me/24qZLulvg     
    
    
    @luis16Suarez Tops the list of Most Valuable Players in #BPL. #Incredible #ElPistolero @LFC http://fb.me/14WooVNFA     
    
    
    27 - Luis Suarez has scored 27 goals in 25 Premier League appearances in 2013. @LFC #Phenominal #ElPistolero    
    
    
    @LFC have scored 39 goals in 16 games this season. The last time they had as many was in their title winning... http://fb.me/1N49PdZtQ     
    
    
    #RelationshipTips
1. Don't Burden The Relationship With Marriage. Both Partners might not be ready and this may... http://fb.me/25TLLwK2N     
    
    
    #RelationshipTips
2. Cheating is a conscious choice and not a wrong mistake. #HardTruth    
    
    
    Robben on Ballon D'Or:
Because it's an individual award, I
think it will go to Ronaldo. He really deserves it.... http://fb.me/2Nmdhbdde     
    
    
    Brendan Rodgers wants to build his team around Luis Suarez in
the coming years. The Liverpool manager refused to... http://fb.me/2y0RUXiSH     
    
    
    Rockin' Basket Ball dans le Chateau... Get In!! #Damn #Lebron #PowerShots #EPIC    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6CwBwdbrs     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6AWLSHvic     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/3a0eOGI4g     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/39zGP0P54     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/29IVwvUVR     
    
    
    Hey Samsung, this TV is crazy... 105-Inch Ultra HD. #EPIC #SAMSUNG #HighTech http://fb.me/11k5aZ34L     
    
    
    Merry Christmas Guys!!! #ENJOY @ Barclays Bank (north k.) http://instagram.com/p/iHlWG_nabC/     
    
    
    10 Holiday gifts engineers will love - ABB Conversations http://fb.me/2hb9RrVCm     
    
    
    Check this out guys!!! #GetIn http://fb.me/2wZtKi3RC     
    
    
    "The starting point of all achievement is desire. Keep this constantly in mind. Weak desire bring weak results,... http://fb.me/35pp1nd66     
    
    
    Gettin ready to hit da gym... Yaaaaaaay!! No Pain, No Gain remember? #GetIn #ProGym #Workouts #EPIC    
    
    
    Is It Not Christmas Yet??? #GetIn http://fb.me/6vaFBLWQL     
    
    
    Is It Not Christmas Yet??? #GetIn http://fb.me/29JD46hrK     
    
    
    Is It Not Christmas Yet??? #GetIn http://fb.me/WetRyvbf     
    
    
    Is It Not Christmas Yet??? #GetIn http://fb.me/2UdYygZ7F     
    
    
    Luis Suarez!! No Comment!!!    
    
    
    Wow! What a lovely wedding it was. My fellow bl300 boy and Tech Engineer just got married. #EPIC #Bl3OObi #TECH #ENGINEER    
    
    
    Well Done Fellow Engineers. #Congrats #Sammy & #Sharon #Lovely http://fb.me/2Ia0757Bq     
    
    
    Don Tim @ an EPIC #Wedding http://fb.me/3i1EOXhxd     
    
    
    Don Tim @ an EPIC #Wedding http://fb.me/2huZSNa2z     
    
    
    Don Tim @ an EPIC #Wedding http://fb.me/3irpGLO5m     
    
    
    @luis16suarez is undoubtedly the Best Player in the World at the moment. Believe It or Die!!! @LFC    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2QprbrrF0     
    
    
    Slept like a baby last nite u noe... Its been a very long time in a while since i slept over 4 hours like i just... http://fb.me/2BQ7gdxGw     
    
    
    Hypocrisy is on the rise... Half of ya wont make it to heaven. Hypocrites are gonna rot in Hell for sure if they... http://fb.me/11qomoSA9     
    
    
    My Liverpool @LFC Is Top of the #BPL again. The last time they were top was in October. @luis16suarez is... http://fb.me/3xwabaFSP     
    
    
    Pellegrini: Suarez could make Man City suffer http://fb.me/17zsvr8yI     
    
    
    #YUCK http://fb.me/12nZPEg9i     
    
    
    The Incredible Luis Suarez
@luis16suarez is the top scorer in the top 5 leagues in the World with 19 goals and 2... http://fb.me/6mSt2q5b3     
    
    
    Beware City We Coming For You Guys This Christmas... Yaaaaaaay!! #Next #OnOurList #CrushCity #CmonLiverpool. http://fb.me/6r6GGPgnH     
    
    
    "Some of us can't just simply keep quiet because the seed of greatness has been birthed from within us. So instead... http://fb.me/Ren9rTrJ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/28GXI0ztz     
    
    
    Agreed! @eddygrey12 how many matches has he played as compared to @luis16suarez eh.    
    
    
    Vehicular Traffic in Accra today is so Sick. #Damn #NotCool    
    
    
    "Intelligence is not how well you excel in school but useful you become. Grades alone can't measure one's... http://fb.me/6nCQHkxSN     
    
    
    @LFC 3rd in Europe at the moment. Wow! Class they say is Permanent. #AGREED http://fb.me/1ctI9GeVH     
    
    
    http://fb.me/RMOvYDSe     
    
    
    # EPL – Result:
Arsenal 0-0 Chelsea
The Gunners remain 2nd on goal difference
while the Blues move to 4th.... http://fb.me/6qNJq6fKQ     
    
    
    My Relentless Reds @LFC Are Top of the #BPL For At least For Christmas. Wow!  Well Deserved!! @luis16suarez #YNWA http://fb.me/22xZ0dKD5     
    
    
    Yaaaaaaaaaay!!! @LFC #GetIn http://fb.me/XPthElOJ     
    
    
    We Can't Wait... Yaaaaaaay!!! #Movie_Freakz #FastAndFurious7 #EPIC #PaulWalker #VinDiesel http://fb.me/2EvmG2nt1     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3DlEPVEja     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1RcYgp0l4     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2PISZavNP     
    
    
    Like seriously... Hehe #EPIC #BreakingNews http://fb.me/181AYmXwQ     
    
    
    Merry Christmas Y'all Football Fanatics!!! #ENJOY http://fb.me/6x3ZpwWvg     
    
    
    Jose Mourinho:: "Liverpool is currently the most prominent and the favourite to win the title and that's becauce... http://fb.me/6CcXZwYVL     
    
    
    Liverpool FC cancel Christmas to stay focused on Premier League success - Liverpool Echo http://fb.me/21P9pelTN     
    
    
    Merry Christmas Everyone!!! 
May the Spirit of Christmas bring Us LOVE, JOY, HAPPINESS, FORGIVENESS, AND... http://fb.me/2xHIvFZkD     
    
    
    Merry Christmas Everyone!!!
May the Spirit of Christmas bring Us LOVE, JOY, HAPPINESS, FORGIVENESS, AND... http://fb.me/XlITs6b9     
    
    
    Merry Christmas Everyone!!!
May the Spirit of Christmas bring Us LOVE, JOY, HAPPINESS, FORGIVENESS, AND... http://fb.me/12yS8O1vU     
    
    
    Christmas Rumble 2013 #EPIC http://fb.me/2JA2iNKUj     
    
    
    Need I Say More herh!!! #Liverpool #Top #BPL #Christmas #Wow #Great #Win #Title http://fb.me/2UYM8W0hn     
    
    
    @iamlord_zico Merry Christmas @de_2slo ENJOY @ofoli_kwei #SALUTE #MissYall    
    
    
    Wow! What a year it has been for me so far. I sustained a very bad Industrial Injury (2nd Degree Burn) on my right... http://fb.me/RCl4VmAJ     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2zlTS5Pts     
    
    
    Wow! What a wonderful Christmas Sermon by #Bishop_Dag Heward Mills on John 3:16... Indeed, there is Light in That... http://fb.me/PzGvrwGV     
    
    
    #EPIC Stuff... Merry X-Mas http://fb.me/15SJWm131     
    
    
    Just got my 1Terabyte HDD 70% full with Movies and Games... Yaaaaay!!! Thanks to my Good Friend Charles Webb. #EXCITED #MovieFreakz #GetIn    
    
    
    Manchester City  v  Liverpool FC ... Boxing Day #EPIC_BPL Game is coming off Tonite @ Etihad Stadium... Liverpool... http://fb.me/VXUM2Bwl     
    
    
    Head To Head... Manchester City v Liverpool FC #ENJOY http://fb.me/6zqZSW8YJ     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2PCaU4meB     
    
    
    Crossover With Power. Finish Hard and End 2013 on a Good Note. Enough Is Enough!!! #Cmon #Fast #Pray #Enjoy #2014 http://fb.me/Sp5DpL89     
    
    
    #AGREED http://fb.me/2xYaclIwn     
    
    
    Can't Wait... C'mon @LFC lets Do this!!! @luis16suarez #ElPistolero #RiseUp #YNWA http://fb.me/2AeczQQbw     
    
    
    Bonne nuit guys!!! #ENJOY    
    
    
    Just Got back from #ProGym with my childhood friend... Bl300bi Abu. No Pain, No Gain!!! #SixPacks #SexyBody #Sweet    
    
    
    2013 Storms definitely coming to an Epic End. You Know what is waiting For Us in 2014... A Great Increase, Turning... http://fb.me/R1sUjq8M     
    
    
    A Good Friend of Mine. #ACASMA #TECH #BL3OO http://fb.me/6Dnjb4pcc     
    
    
    A Mark of Intellectual Friendship of course. #TECH #ACASMA #Wow http://fb.me/6x7av4fcc     
    
    
    Brothers on the Field... My Engineering Course mates now Epic #ENGINEERS. How Did We Get Here... Hardwork,... http://fb.me/12DHS7xCS     
    
    
    Wow! Now what? Hehe http://fb.me/2L2azFp8b     
    
    
    BREAKING NEWS:: Malky Mackay has officially been sacked by Cardiff City. #Farewell #BPL    
    
    
    U.S. sending missiles, drones to help Iraq government fight al Qaeda http://fb.me/2HWZ0ulJi     
    
    
        
    
    
    #EPIC Top Scorers 2013 http://fb.me/2xRkXikEr     
    
    
    Phew! I just had a Super busy day today converting Oxygen to Carbon dioxide... Hehe. What A Day!!!  #EPIC_Day #BonneNuit #Guys    
    
    
    "Its not what you go through that matters but how and what you come out with." - ArchBishop Nicholas Duncan Williams #DeepTruth    
    
    
    Our Last Saturday Workouts in 2013... En route to da Gym. #ProGym #NoPain #NoGain #Endurance    
    
    
    In attendance today was Mr. Armah... He was ranked 4th at the Ghana's Strongest Competition this year. We trained... http://fb.me/6jq08VukH     
    
    
    Wow! Bless U Pastor Paula White. #Confirmation http://fb.me/6nnxpKe5O     
    
    
    AGREED! #Engineering http://fb.me/2Ji73tZUz     
    
    
    Great Insight about Religion. God Bless You So Much!!! :D:D:D #Reinhard_ Bonnke http://fb.me/14UwEANwG     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6noeeFi9H     
    
    
    "This is what the past is for! Every experience God gives us, every person He puts in our lives is a perfect... http://fb.me/6jx9tTn0O     
    
    
    BEWARE OF COVETOUSNESS!!! Don't Take This into 2014... REPENT!!! Covetousness is without a doubt the "biggest"... http://fb.me/3DFM8lXkj     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2hJXnlnOD     
    
    
    And That's very Weird!!! 7 Epic Women Facts #Complicated http://fb.me/2nchwx5F3     
    
    
    Chelsea 2 : 1 @LFC ... Cmon Mighty Reds. #RiseUp #YNWA http://fb.me/14AZNpyr0     
    
    
    Chelsea 1 : 2 @LFC ... Cmon Mighty Reds. #RiseUp #YNWA http://fb.me/6BrfmOia7     
    
    
    http://fb.me/SONO4rM1     
    
    
    http://fb.me/30HZVwoeI     
    
    
    Confirmed Chelsea XI #CFC
Cech
Ivanovic - Cahill - Terry - Azpilicueta
Lampard - Luiz
Hazard - Oscar - Willian... http://fb.me/1eIbouxwS     
    
    
    What a Goal... Liverpool takes  the Lead!!! #Skrtel    
    
    
    Super Save from Mignolet... What a Save.    
    
    
    Howard Fuckin Webb... YUCK! #Pathetic    
    
    
    FT: Howard Webb 2 : 1 Liverpool 
Man of The Match: Howard Fuckin Webb #Pathetic    
    
    
    When you walk through a storm, hold your head up high And don’t be afraid of the dark At the end of the storm,... http://fb.me/6wfDMyUPQ     
    
    
    We Living The Life Right Here In Ghana and Africa. No need to travel to Dubai or Paris to upgrade your Lifestyle.... http://fb.me/UDukV3i7     
    
    
    We Living The Life Right Here In Ghana and Africa. No need to travel to Dubai or Paris to upgrade your Lifestyle.... http://fb.me/35c0scCya     
    
    
    Ewww... Disgusting Facts. #YUCKY http://fb.me/38aZzwvHs     
    
    
    http://fb.me/Uaf53MpV     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2AYjCvMtn     
    
    
    HAPPY 29th BIRTHDAY LEBRON JAMES... You da mehn!!! #SALUTE http://fb.me/12vr7cAFI     
    
    
    HAPPY 29th BIRTHDAY LEBRON JAMES... You da mehn!!! #SALUTE http://fb.me/2B7BWpMe7     
    
    
    HAPPY 29th BIRTHDAY LEBRON JAMES... You da mehn!!! #SALUTE http://fb.me/2bhXZ0pqo     
    
    
    HAPPY 29th BIRTHDAY LEBRON JAMES... You da mehn!!! #SALUTE http://fb.me/357jZGpfI     
    
    
    HAPPY 29th BIRTHDAY LEBRON JAMES... You da mehn!!! #SALUTE http://fb.me/6nF8JKJ6j     
    
    
        
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/14gYSFeZ9     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3jWzqgYYe     
    
    
    31st night Almost imminent and as usual friends of Dr. Mensah
Otabil will Cross Over, friends of Archbishop Duncan... http://fb.me/Rh89ZbAy     
    
    
    31st night Almost imminent and as usual friends of Dr. Mensah
Otabil will Cross Over, friends of Archbishop... http://fb.me/1Lyfbf7y0     
    
    
        
    
    
    Just Got Back from da Gym. Sipping one of the finest Cabernet Sauvignon Red Wines @ Home. #VinRogue #ProGym... http://fb.me/1GxlsIGFC     
    
    
    A Resounding AMEN To That Pastor Paula White!!! #AMEN http://fb.me/6Cfoig8Sr     
    
    
    http://fb.me/25BHUVs3z     
    
    
    Bonne Annee Mes Aimes... Le Vin Rogue de Cabernet Sa uvignon est bon pour la Sante! 
Ce Cabernet Sauvignon recolte dans les grandioses et …    
    
    
    Bonne Annee Mes Aimes... Le Vin Rogue de Cabernet Sauvignon est bon pour la Sante! 
Ce Cabernet Sauvignon recolte dans les grandioses et s…    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1uNYjslDQ     
    
    
    An Epic Sitting is going down in my neighbour @ an undisclosed location in Accra... An ELITE of Genuine and... http://fb.me/VK9x1j6S     
    
    
    Cmon @luis16suarez... Score a hat trick against Hull City this afternoon. @LFC #RiseUp #Anfield #ElPistolero #YNWA http://fb.me/2UUMcPOsi     
    
    
    WELCOME TO 2014!!! #HappyNewYear #EUROLEAGUE #FANZONE
#BPL Fixtures
12:45 GMT  Swansea v Man City
15:00 GMT... http://fb.me/6njLJguj5     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2zpYvqsib     
    
    
    Watching the lastest episode of Nikita S0406... So thrilling!! Nikita and Alex Udinov now gone AWOL. #DAMN... http://fb.me/302xzYsea     
    
    
    Finally Nikita, Alex Udinov, Sam, Michael, Brocuff got their Epic Freedom and Honoured courtesy Ryan Fletcher who... http://fb.me/2fYN6WqGB     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1RJFsIewb     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3AGhY6Mun     
    
    
    SUAREZ Scores his 20th goal... What a brilliant goal that was. @luis16suarez #Excellent #GetIn    
    
    
    Luis Suarez becomes the first Liverpool player to score 20+ goals league goals in successive seasons since Robbie... http://fb.me/QrPeE3A0     
    
    
    Well Done Liverpool!!! You really made my 1st January so memorable of course... What An Excellent well taken... http://fb.me/19trjM2J4     
    
    
    Luis Suarez becomes the first ever Player to score 20 Premier League goals in fewer matches (15) in the history... http://fb.me/1TwxLmGWu     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1yzUOGmKE     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://fb.me/6CrM4IxqG     
    
    
    "A Double Portion belongs to those who are relentless in their pursuit in the things of God and not people who... http://fb.me/1Qvz0DuVP     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6RTJufzlo     
    
    
    "Divine Intelligence is the highest level of intelligence man can ever attain and Jehovah alone is the source of... http://fb.me/2C9YDVDbl     
    
    
        
    
    
    Why on earth will any man be afraid if he has done nothing wrong? Who does that? Danger is looming i think...... http://fb.me/6s1X53THw     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2F5QzZyXK     
    
    
    Wow! #Deep Word!! http://fb.me/2yWLsgPwO     
    
    
    Watching Dracula 2013 movie Series alone @ Home... Creppy series!!! #Yaaaaaaaaaay #EPIC #Dracula #Series #HDTV    
    
    
    Have been watching Dracula season 1 all day u noe. Epic movie series and very creepy i must say. #DRACULA #HDTV #Series #Yaaaaaaaaaay    
    
    
    Wow! This is it... We've began 2014 on a good note. Nii Armah now the King of Progym managed to lift 250Kg of... http://fb.me/2GZCak4te     
    
    
    How you begin this year will determine exactly how you'll end it - Start right!! #ENJOY #Intent #Ambitious #Diligent #Prayerful    
    
    
    Ghana captain Asamoah Gyan was the sixth
most prolific striker in the world for the
year 2013.
The UAE-based... http://fb.me/1RAfTdsSg     
    
    
    "Hippopotomontrosesquippeddaliophobia" is the fear of long words. #CrazyFACTS #EPIC    
    
    
    Great Old Memories of our Alma Mata... ACCRA ACADEMY #BL3OO #SALUTE http://fb.me/24B2PIFMY     
    
    
    Who does that? :o #Nii_Armah #GhanaMostStrongest #ProGym http://fb.me/6yUbA3GwT     
    
    
    You've GottaTell Them Naeem Nasir!!! #HardTruth http://fb.me/3hitOaj4n     
    
    
    Wanna have less friends this year... The fewer, the merrier remember? #NewYear_Resolution    
    
    
    Wanna Pray more this year... A Prayerless Soul is a very unless one remember? #NewYear_Resolution    
    
    
    Wanna Stop Clubbing this year... Old habits die hard remember so help me God. #NewYear_Resolution    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wanna flee from dem Bitchy babes this year... Patiently waiting for my Russian Babe remember? #NewYear_Resolution    
    
    
    Finally Wanna Love Y'all... Gotta tolerate dem bullshit remember? #NewYear_Resolution    
    
    
    "Great spirits have often encountered violent opposition from mediocre minds." - Albert Einstein    
    
    
    Boxer of year: Floyd Mayweather Jr. http://fb.me/6zBedA8UN     
    
    
    A MUST READ!!! #Salvation is Free
Jesus saith unto him, I am the way, the truth, and the life: no man cometh unto... http://fb.me/12wgZBEhW     
    
    
    Anything you do which is not right, is definitely not correct. #HardTruth    
    
    
    Portugal legend Eusebio dies aged 71 http://fb.me/6s7eOWabk     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2fpzNbWgS     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2g3nvRytH     
    
    
    http://fb.me/3gVWKoQLK     
    
    
    Seriously? #MoyesOut http://fb.me/1ckKLlzEj     
    
    
    Seriously? #MoyesOut http://fb.me/6ssBtxJpM     
    
    
    Seriously? #MoyesOut http://fb.me/2dMcHt5j5     
    
    
    http://fb.me/34O4xtHLk     
    
    
    The Greatest Ever Portuguese Player of All Time... Eusebio Dies @ age 71.
Eusebio scored 319 goals in 313 matches... http://fb.me/2VDMxYRJa     
    
    
    Well Done @LFC ... Walk On!! Walk On!! #YNWA http://fb.me/2681e2srJ     
    
    
    AGREED! http://fb.me/1RZtIW8Lx     
    
    
    100% AGREED!! http://fb.me/6yUZpUoCE     
    
    
    This is very Deep. #PaulaWhite http://fb.me/Uii8EbJO     
    
    
    EPiC HALL... UNITY HALL #KNUST http://fb.me/2E4cS4xfj     
    
    
    Really Miss The Hall... Wonderful Fraternity #UnityPower http://fb.me/13vraVxGO     
    
    
    Duly Noted!! #Kim http://fb.me/19dbdAMcO     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2D7CqSjTu     
    
    
    The reason why Jesus Christ walked on the sea was to demonstrate to Christians that, the things we are afraid of... http://fb.me/27ehZkBkT     
    
    
    The phrase "Fear not" can be found 331 times in the Bible. This is certainly God's daily reminder in a year that... http://fb.me/2PgsOxmnH     
    
    
    AGREED! http://fb.me/NoUfcIrv     
    
    
    Your Destiny Is Determined by what you do with your hands, so put them to work. There is no substitute for hard... http://fb.me/6kBNYIdlt     
    
    
    Tell Them!! http://fb.me/28UKzpNln     
    
    
    Zinedine Zidane: "As a complete player, Steven Gerrard is better than Cristiano Ronaldo and Lionel Messi." #LEADER pic.twitter.com/qYUGTmkm6c    
    
    
    Talking about Business over Hunters... With my Boss. #WorkHard #PlayHard    
    
    
    "Being ignorant is not so much a shame, as being unwilling to learn." _ Benjamin Franklin  #Moron #AGREED    
    
    
    Tell Them!! http://fb.me/2byFZcPgQ     
    
    
    Psychology recommends that, Crush only lasts for a maximum of 4 months. If it exceeds, you're already in love.... http://fb.me/2FhsPaxvH     
    
    
    I Bet!! #AGREED http://fb.me/1Biy8ylBW     
    
    
    Psychology recommends that, Crush only lasts for a maximum of 4 months. If it exceeds, you're already in love.... http://fb.me/124Cga0Hk     
    
    
    "Sheer Bravery is to do things differently irrespective of the status quo - Bravery is not for the weak." - Isaac Atanley    
    
    
    "Sheer Bravery is to do things differently irrespective of the status quo - Bravery is not for the weak." - Isaac Atanley #FEARLESS    
    
    
    Hearts coach David Duncan defends 'slack' second half display http://www.ghanasoccernet.com/hearts-coach-david-duncan-defends-slack-second-half-display/ …    
    
    
    "For gold is tried in the fire and acceptable men in the furnace of adversity." - George Santayana #AGREED    
    
    
    Mark Zuckerberg Was Highest Paid U.S. CEO of 2012 http://on.mash.to/1a9aSzd  via @mashable    
    
    
    Top  Google   users    educated at Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology KNUST [1 - 11], total of 11 found    
    
    
    "In order to be irreplaceable, one must always be different." - Coco Chanel #BeOriginal #Rare #Genuine #OneHundred    
    
    
    AGREED! #WORD http://fb.me/OvMNcKCW     
    
    
    "You do not look for what you have." - Archbishop Benson Idahosa    
    
    
    A true leader does not command his followers but rather leads them to get the job done. You've got to always... http://fb.me/IYTw38hN     
    
    
    "The farther you see the more you desire. If your season is not due, do not complain but comply." - Archibishop Benson Idahosa #DEEP #WORD    
    
    
    What an interesting Truth!!! #Awesome http://fb.me/2KxfSoSDS     
    
    
    Ghana's 'Black Stars' putting African art on the map http://fb.me/1IOKhoukp     
    
    
    Great! http://fb.me/YZizfC2O     
    
    
    CABERNET SAUVIGNON... Vin Rogue!!! #1883 #BonVie #DMCV #CHEERS #OneHundred pic.twitter.com/FVqzNoLH4t    
    
    
    Here Did I Get Here... Haha #ELITE #ENGINEER #CHILLING #TIMBA #ONEHUNDRED #FEARLESSTEAM    
    
    
    They see me rolling... They Hatin'  #RIDIN #CrushDemAll #Damn    
    
    
    RT "@FIFAcom: 150 years ago today, modern football was founded in London. A very happy birthday to the @FA #FA150 - http://fifa.to/1gP6vAJ "    
    
    
    Steven Gerrard is set to play his 450th League game for @LFC today. He'll become the 9th Reds player to reach this pic.twitter.com/91YOwOkokQ    
    
    
    @Hill Club with my Boss. All Work and No Play Make #TIMBA A Very Dull Boy... Yaaaaaaay!!    
    
    
    @Hill Club with my Boss. All Work and No Play Makes #TIMBA A Very Dull Boy... Yaaaaaaay!!    
    
    
    @luis16suarez will surely scored a hat-trick today @D_Sturridge to also score a brace for @LFC #SAS #YNWA #RiseUp # pic.twitter.com/TrElK5ikHx    
    
    
    What a Goal... Suarez puts @LFC ahead.    
    
    
    What an Awesome Goal from luis16suarez... Yaaaaaay!! C'mon Suarez you da king of Nutmeg.    
    
    
    Suarez doubles the lead for Liverpool... Wow! What a player Luis Suarez has become. World Class!!!    
    
    
    Liverpool FC is definitely on fire... What a terrific build up towards the second goal. Great Team work and... http://fb.me/1jbFNts85     
    
    
    Super Free kick... What a goal against Man Utd.  #STOKE strokes pass united... Yaaaay!!!    
    
    
    Call me Timba the Octopus now... I predicted a hat trick for Suarez and he has cleverly done that. Well Done!!!... http://fb.me/2O2QxHbSV     
    
    
    Best Striker duo in the premier league... No doubt!! 14 goals together already between them. Wowza @luis16suarez and @D_Sturridge AKA SAS    
    
    
    Top of the Table Clash next week... Bring on Arsenal!! @LFC gonna definitely Beat dem to rise back on Top of #BPL Table. Coutinho will be...    
    
    
    Top of the Table Clash next week... Bring on Arsenal!!! @LFC gonna definitely Beat dem to rise back on Top of... http://fb.me/1X86nyv2r     
    
    
    RT"@FourFourTwo: Barcelona overcome Madrid at Camp Nou http://fft.sm/17kSkiN  ...as Ancelotti bemoans refereeing decisions #FCB #RMCF"    
    
    
    RT"@FourFourTwo: Rodgers praises 'tireless worker' Suarez after 'difficult summer' http://fft.sm/1g3vPS4  #LFC"#LS7 pic.twitter.com/Xnc33b6Bs7    
    
    
    RT"@kingofaccra: "@Boys_Kasa: Mogbe (Feat. Big Klef) [ http://hype360gh.com/2013/10/king-o … ] by King Of Accra"RT" #Dopest New Single... I luv it!    
    
    
    RT"@LFCFansCorner: Zidane believes the comments of former Manchester United boss Fergie about Gerrard in his autobiography are “strange.”"    
    
    
    EPIC!!! @luis16suarez header today was mind-blowing... Speed of 38mph over 17 yards outside the box. #Sensational pic.twitter.com/MpJGX4US6g    
    
    
    Rodgers hails 'magic' Suarez performance http://fb.me/PsoAxVRq     
    
    
    Sure James!! #YNWA http://fb.me/321e3hbt8     
    
    
    RT"@KingJames: Great solid win today @LFC!" The Best is Yet to come... YOU'LL NEVER WALK ALONE LEBRON!!! #YNWA pic.twitter.com/NM3zHLGGIp    
    
    
    Massive Win!!! "@CaroWozniacki: Holidays!! What better way to start them off? On my way to Liverpool to watch the game at Anfield!" #YNWA    
    
    
    AGREED!!! RT"@LFCTS: Luis Suarez & Daniel Sturridge have started in only 4 matches this season scoring 10 goals" #SAS #EPIC #DUO #LFC    
    
    
    Woke up very early this great morning... listening to audio sermons from Archbishops; Duncan Williams, Benson... http://fb.me/1ABdImHlP     
    
    
    Chillaxin' with my fellow ELITE Engineers over Hunters... Yaaaaaaay!!! Hardwork before Chiling. #ELITE #ENGINEERS... http://fb.me/2zMo5BUwX     
    
    
    Phew! Steam Boiler Installation is 96% completed awaiting fine-tuning by Gabby n co... FIRING of Boiler is... http://fb.me/2vq43EQFR     
    
    
    Psychologists have correctly said that, "when one is truly ready for a thing, it puts in its appearance" 
#100% #AGREE    
    
    
    "Nothing limits achievement like small thinking; nothing expands possibilites like unleashed imagination." - William Arthur Ward    
    
    
    @D_Sturridge is League's top goal scorer with 8 goals and @luis16suarez is joint second with 6 goals. Need i say more? Deadly Duo @LFC #SAS    
    
    
    I Bet!! #Ewww http://fb.me/Z8tOofbV     
    
    
    Its been a great year for me so far i think. Began the year as a Production/Maintenanace Senior Supervisor... http://fb.me/2l031jpgv     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2KACuOPKB     
    
    
    Safety Officer http://fb.me/2C2oYCJut     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1rxLN86Be     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/TopcinQE     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2k6T0IKrf     
    
    
    Don't Complain but Comply... Endurance is a prerequisite to Success. Make a Great week Y'all!!! #Decide #BeDiligent #StriveForGreatness    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2AS6YtgvP     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/YivXSQ2h     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2aqv7CAMu     
    
    
    oooh kk... That explains my situation. #EPIC #EinsteinLike http://fb.me/19Nm9z7LG     
    
    
    Once you go outside the Will of God for your life, you invite troubles unto yourself. #Proverbs 16:25 says that,... http://fb.me/Mu35Rexp     
    
    
    90% will Fail this Test on first Attempt... Try It!!! http://fb.me/1C58fC1lI     
    
    
    "In School of Engineering, they teach you how things work but in real situation, you must make things work -... http://fb.me/Lmfeqvze     
    
    
    "In School of Engineering, they teach you how things work but in real situation, you must make things work - Trained to Deliver." - Isaac A…    
    
    
    Suarez nominated for Ballon D'Or prize - Liverpool FC http://www.liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-news/148022-suarez-nominated-for-ballon-d-or-prize … via @lfc    
    
    
    Pathetic Team Arsenal... Nothing to show for herh!!! #Trophyless #Team http://fb.me/2SqFQZKeV     
    
    
    Sure! Hehe http://fb.me/3opN3Z3Bl     
    
    
    "If you're not willing to work for your success, you don't deserve it anyway. People don't luck in success. The... http://fb.me/276GEg1AW     
    
    
    Never hate people who are jealous of you, but instead respect their jealousy. At least, they are the only people... http://fb.me/YphB9JNL     
    
    
    God Favours Me... No Doubt about that!!!@IamLord_Zico @Kofi_Cylo @kingofaccra @ofoli_kwei @westman86 #GRACED #FAVOURED #JesusIsLord #Indeed    
    
    
    Have not i commanded thee? Be strong and of a good courage; be not afraid, neither be thou dismayed: for the LORD... http://fb.me/6JOmgCv95     
    
    
    I usually chat with our new office secretary @ work. My colleagues might be interested but i dont cuz she's way... http://fb.me/2elKPzkJA     
    
    
    Sure! @forbes Legendary Bill Gates of course. #askforbes    
    
    
    Seriously? @forbes Prez Mugabe i think...lol #powerfulpeople #askforbes    
    
    
    Wow! Real Madrid making a strong statement of intent here. CR7 scores a hat trick whiles a brace and 2 assists... http://fb.me/1afc6gwOK     
    
    
    CR7 Salutes... A reply to a bias Blatter who sees him a Commander. #EPIC #SALUTE #LoveThis #CR7 http://fb.me/6kNc8qiiI     
    
    
    Bring On Arsenal... We need to score 5+ goals against Arsenal this  weekend. #SAS #RiseUp #YNWA http://fb.me/2nsVDm6R4     
    
    
    Boston Red Sox will have won 108 of 178 games this season... That's so Remarkable!! Congrats to Fenway. #WorldSeries #RedSox #Fenway #Champs    
    
    
    "@BishopJakes: Creativity is born in the face of obstacles. Blessings aren’t convenient because God did not promise to put you in convenient    
    
    
    AGREED! @BishopJakes Bless You the for this great and timely Word!!! #Potter #Bishop #BlessU    
    
    
    @IamLord_Zico @Timbahood @westman86 Gradually, we getting there... God is grooming us into becoming World Leaders with a difference. #Arise    
    
    
    Really? "@BBCNews: Safety fears over bioenergy plant http://bbc.in/1bEW8Zl "    
    
    
    Liverpool of course! Watch us rise up to the top of the #BPL this Saturday. Unbelievable Combo #SAS are ready to... http://fb.me/15KWvqSQ1     
    
    
    Syria's chemical weapons production facilities destroyed, says watchdog http://www.theguardian.com/world/2013/oct/31/syria-chemical-weapons-factories-destroyed-opcw …    
    
    
    Coutinho given 'all clear' to return - Liverpool FC http://www.liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-news/148200-coutinho-given-all-clear-to-return?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter … via @lfc    
    
    
    LFC congratulate Red Sox on triumph - Liverpool FC http://www.liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-news/148181-lfc-congratulate-red-sox-on-triumph … via @lfc    
    
    
    Difference is Delightful - dare to be different! @DamnRightTweets Tell Dem!! @GirlfriendNotes AGREED! @Fit_Motivator Word! :p:p:p #Unique    
    
    
    Top  Google   users    educated at Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology KNUST [1 - 11], total of 11 found    
    
    
    Great are You Lord!!! #JesusIsLord    
    
    
    Ameeeen! @AJEnglish AGREED! @GreatestQuotes "Examine what is said, not him who speaks." - Arab Proverb  #WORD    
    
    
    Reinvent! "@Forbes: The generation of startup guys who want to change the way we dispose of the dead. http://onforb.es/1aK73AK " #REINVENT    
    
    
    Dieu Merci C'est Vendred... Yaaaaaaaaaaaay!!! #DMCV #BonVie #SALUT #Novembre    
    
    
    Can't wait... For the first time ever, i'm willing to put a 10,000 butts on this game. #Arsenal v #Liverpool... http://fb.me/1Jys0Ex5n     
    
    
    Cissokho wants win at Arsenal: Aly Cissokho has challenged his Liverpool team-mates to prove they ar... http://bit.ly/1dyV4bC     
    
    
    The Obamacare website mess underscores the first rule of good management http://onforb.es/1dY5ZOH  #Forbes @bamfodinho @westman86    
    
    
    Wow! 52 days more to An #EPIC Christmas. Shoppin' spree is imminent.... Yaaaaaay!!! Brace Yourselves my friends.... http://fb.me/2bFCjVwxJ     
    
    
    Christmas Countdown 2013 - Find out how many days until Christmas 2013 http://www.xmasclock.com/     
    
    
    Self-appointed Technical Tactician/ Director of Mandis Football Team. 3 weeks to go... Play against a formidable Community Team. #TeamMandis    
    
    
    RT"@MirrorFootball:Bonus Kenny Dalglish: Is Arsenal vs Liverpool a battle of title contenders? Just look at the table" #EPIC #KING @LFC    
    
    
    Missing Home Already... Awwww!! Stay Calm cuz my long awaited Annual leave is looming... Yaaaaaaaay!!! #Excited pic.twitter.com/2PttaO0C4K    
    
    
    AGREED!! "@MutomboDaPoet: Clear RT @kinnareads: @Kwabena GBC is to be disregarded, utterly useless. BBC is to be hated. @MutomboDaPoet"    
    
    
    Steven Gerrard Captains the Red Army 'Anfield Warriors' tonite. Let no team forget how menacing we've become as a... http://fb.me/2LZdJRI5S     
    
    
    EPIC COMBO!! @LFCFansCorner TRIO! @OptaJoe Suarez And Sturridge = #SAS   Suarez + COUtinho + SturridgE = SCOUSE  @luis16suarez @D_Sturridge    
    
    
    @westman86 sure bruv!! Its been awhile since i went. Work stuff u noe. Home is where the Heart is they say. #HomeSweetHome    
    
    
    AGREED! RT"@GreatestQuotes: "The most delightful surprise in life is to suddenly recognise your own worth." - Maxwell Maltz" #Onehundred    
    
    
    Greater Days Ahead guys... Brace Yourselves and Believe!!! #StayCalm #Faith #Believe #ENJOY #TIMBA #OneHundred #SALUTE    
    
    
    I Bet!! "@DietmarHamann: Fancy LFC to get a result today.Not sure whether Arsenal got the defensive weapons to stop SAS" @LFC    
    
    
    "@ParisHilton: Hey Moscow, see you all today at The June Shopping Mall in Mytischi. Can't wait to meet you all! See… http://instagram.com/p/gNF8KvK     
    
    
    Totally Deserved!! "@empireofthekop: Suarez named PFA player of the month for October http://liverpoolfc.com/news/latest-ne …" @luis16suarez #SALUTE    
    
    
    "@thisisanfield: Lots of excellent writing from our columnists ahead of today’s game at the Emirates: http://thisisanfield.com/tag/arsenal  #LFC #AF    
    
    
    GROSS! "@iTweetFacts: Gambrinous is a word that describes someone who becomes full from drinking beer." #Hehe    
    
    
    When Liverpool drew 2 : 2 with Newcastle, Chelsea fans be like... Typical Li'pool herh. Today Newcastle scored... http://fb.me/13qEMHpeN     
    
    
    The Coast is Clear for Liverpool to rise to the Top spot of the #BPL Table... All we need is an emphatic Win... http://fb.me/181HEjPPh     
    
    
    Luis Suarez has pipped the likes Wayne Rooney and Mesut Özil to be named as the PFA Fans' Player of the month of... http://fb.me/6ikiOagpC     
    
    
    STAY CALM LIVERPOOL!!! We got this.    
    
    
    DAMN! @iamlord_zico sure! We can't loose this game.    
    
    
    @splizidie I agree!    
    
    
    Sure! @splizidie Arsenal out-played i must say.    
    
    
    Arsenal 2 : 0 Liverpool ...  Arsrenal Play very well and won convincingly. Good nite guys!!! #NotGood    
    
    
    @iamlord_zico Well Done Gunners!!! #TOP #SALUTE    
    
    
    Football  #RIDDLE
I'm currently the top goal scorer in #CL with #7
I'm currently the top goal scorer in  #Laliga... http://fb.me/6wZqwU2cy     
    
    
    Top  Google   users    educated at Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology KNUST [1 - 11], total of 11 found    
    
    
    @Timbahood can't be friends with everyone... my only leverage is to choose them carefully. #HardTruth #PowerOfChoice #AGREED @IamLord_Zico    
    
    
    "The man who does more than he is paid for will soon be paid for more than he does." - Napoleon Hill  #Diligence is Key here  #Noted    
    
    
    Asamoah Gyan: I'm Rooting For Eaglets | NAIJA Lately - Read Nigeria Newspapers Online http://www.naijalately.com/news/asamoah-gyan-im-rooting-for-eaglets#.UnZEhaZP47s.twitter …    
    
    
    Romney: Obama 'dishonest' about Obamacare http://news.yahoo.com/romney-meet-the-press-140953473.html?soc_src=mediacontentstory … via @YahooNews    
    
    
    http://fb.me/6yFtUzUvR     
    
    
    