A firefly just got caught in my hair and struggled to get out. Maybe it's a sign that I need a trim...    
    
    
    My local Capital One bank is packed today. Are they giving away money or something?    
    
    
    @jonmarkgo LOL I get the urge to do that whenever I see the Seinfeld episode.    
    
    
    I miss that one week in Spring where it was in the 40s. #HeatWave #IWantWinerBack    
    
    
    From One Direction to The Doors - my neighbor's BBQ DJ is casting a wide musical net.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov What time does the UFC fight start? I can't find a clear answer on Google.    
    
    
    I imagine DMX is pretty popular to play at UFC matches.    
    
    
    @PeteLabozetta Do you have a good stream for the fight?    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov He won! I think?    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Woohoo!!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Getting mad retweets!    
    
    
    Looks like I need to make some changes to my annual social media report #Hofstra #UFC    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Folks on the Hofstra FB think the match was fixed. Unreal...    
    
    
    @Jsheehan83 Craziness on Twitter!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Mine    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Montrose (8), Sublime (7) & Third Eye Blind (7) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    @ReneAlexMolina :-( how long was your fast food fast?    
    
    
    Fireworks on July 7th is unacceptable.    
    
    
    Only 3% of Americans list "blues" as their favorite style of music. #BarRescue    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley I feel weird without my morning coffee. It's a sign I'm an adult now :( lol    
    
    
    Today would be a great day for the Hofstra @ChipotleTweets to offer delivery. #hot #humid    
    
    
    @bberg1010 Email? I get people I emailed once in 2009 that show up on my suggestions.    
    
    
    @bberg1010 Weird! Maybe you two were on the same email blast. Lol don't laugh, that was my only connection to one of my suggested people.    
    
    
    I hope this HR Derby gets Wright back into 1st half 2006 form, when he was a HR monster! #ASG #Mets    
    
    
    I miss 2006. #Mets    
    
    
    Community managers, Facebook released their new insights dashboard! It's huge improvement and gives you clearer data. Check it out!    
    
    
    @DannyBarbaccia Real white collar crime or the TV series? (which is great!) @TimDeKay    
    
    
    Sounds familiar...RT @mashable: Google+ Update Makes It Easier to See What Your Friends Like http://on.mash.to/172bYvp     
    
    
    Seeing the new follower notice on Instagram only to find that it's spam #letdown    
    
    
    I like @UpWorthy but I can't stand the constant popups. If I like what I'm seeing, I'll share it on my own.    
    
    
    @AntDeRosa "If you're not feeling it, don't write it" - NiemanLab article on the story behind Upworthy's success. http://www.niemanlab.org/2013/06/if-youre-not-feeling-it-dont-write-it-upworthys-social-success-depends-on-gut-checking-regular-people/ …    
    
    
    @AntDeRosa Basically they take regular people and have them "gut-check" content to see if it moves them. Agree w/ u about annoying popups.    
    
    
    When did Justin Bieber and Bill Clinton start beefing with each other? I have some catching up to do...    
    
    
    You can now embed public Instagram photos & videos through the web, mobile coming soon. http://www.theverge.com/2013/7/10/4510544/instagram-enables-photo-and-video-embedding …    
    
    
    Olivia Bertalan had 97 followers before her testimony, now 200 & climbing. #ZimmermanTrial @OliviaGrace18    
    
    
    Bring back the "I'm On A Boat" badge, @foursquare. Even Michael Jordan came out of retirement! @dens    
    
    
    Empty since 2009..RT @darrenrovell: Shot of seats at the top of the 1st at Yankee Stadium tonight pic.twitter.com/MWyZm1jBBG (H/T @DufourJW)    
    
    
    @_rachclark Did she announce any intentions for a higher office? @elizabethforma    
    
    
    @StxV There is a record label for you - @secretlycndian    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz Weather's been like that for past two weeks (on and off showers)    
    
    
    Can the humidity please go away? #Brutal    
    
    
    Sigh :( http://instagram.com/p/bpDTqNnZAq/     
    
    
    Ok my entire timeline is talking about #Sharknado...I have to check this out. #ViralMarketingOMG    
    
    
    And  the #Sharknado talk is across industry lines...journalists, sports guys, wise guys,...and now a #highered guy..    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov YES!!!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Sadly I am...    
    
    
    SharkNATO would've ended the Cold War in 1947. #SharkNado    
    
    
    More people will watch #SharkNado than the MLB All Star Game. #FinalVote    
    
    
    Twitter has jumped the shark tonight #SharkNado    
    
    
    @Nagler busy day in the office today? #SharkNado    
    
    
    @Nagler Awesome, sounds like fun!    
    
    
    Sick burn by @SanJoseSharks to @espn pic.twitter.com/tu4u4xbBeZ    
    
    
    @cdorso I am very intrigued at your Twitter chat.    
    
    
    Which song is more epic for karaoke: Jukebox Hero or Wanted Dead Or Alive?    
    
    
    Live on the air until 9:00 AM! Tune in http://www.wusb.fm  #wusb #longisland http://instagram.com/p/btDa7jnZGG/     
    
    
    90% Of Customers Will Recommend Brands After Social Media Interactions http://www.businessinsider.com/90-of-customers-will-recommend-brands-after-social-media-interactions-2013-7 …    
    
    
    Randomly listening to Dark Side of the Moon in its entirety.    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz Congrats on your new position at TIME, Alex!    
    
    
    Ted (the movie, not the talks) is on HBO Go!    
    
    
    I am genuinely looking forward to tonight's season premiere of #NewsRoom!    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Bob Marley & The Wailers (14), Third Eye Blind (12) & Foghat (12) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    Come on Cablevision, don't start crapping out on me during #Newsroom!    
    
    
    That theme song always gives me chills #NewsRoom    
    
    
    Friday! Friday! Gotta get down on Friday! #NewsRoom    
    
    
    @JuliaSkrobak When are you and @caitlynhutchis coming back? I miss ya'll!    
    
    
    @_SueCaulfield Our side of campus was hit twice too! Luckily, I just lost email drafts.    
    
    
    @GeorgiaRuocco Welcome to Twitter, Aunt Georgia!    
    
    
    Why couldn't the Knicks sign Charles Jenkins? It would've made my day a lot more interesting...    
    
    
    David Wright #HRDerby    
    
    
    Someone throw a Bud Light at Pitbull #HRDerby    
    
    
    @JoeandEvan One needs a lot of Bud Light to get into Pitbull    
    
    
    @Nagler Yeah - #HRDerby ruined him in 2006. I'm nervous!    
    
    
    I haven't seen Citi Field this full since...ever. #HRDerby    
    
    
    Luis Castillo RT @StephenGorchov: Who taught these kids in the outfield how to catch?  #BRUTAL #HRDerby    
    
    
    I hope the Apple gets some action when David Wright's up. #Mets #HRDerby    
    
    
    Cesepedes is finding seats I did not know existed at Citi Field! #HRDerby    
    
    
    @BHarper3407 Did your father teach the cutter to Mariano Rivera? #HRDerby    
    
    
    @cdorso I think Luis Castillo taught these kids how to catch fly balls.    
    
    
    Piazza going hard with the hair gel. I can't get my hair that stiff no matter how much gel I use.    
    
    
    Berman with a Ronkonkoma reference! Suffolk county getting a natl shout out! #HRDerby #longisland    
    
    
    @StxV right?! Totally unexpected!    
    
    
    Bold! Especially from a journalist! RT @AdamReports: I LIKE THE NEWSROOM. Unafraid and unashamed to admit it. cc @kansasalps @OkieCaitlin    
    
    
    Go SeaEagles! RT @sbusports: BREAKING: Fox Sports reports @MichaelBamiro will sign with the Philadelphia Eagles.    
    
    
    The Blue Jays must feel awkward right now #asg    
    
    
    "THAT'S FOR MIKE PIAZZA"    
    
    
    Beltran and Wright in the same lineup. Reminds me of the good ole days...    
    
    
    Harvey apologized. You can all calm down now, Yankees fans.    
    
    
    Beltran disrupts a no-hit bid at Citi Field..good thing he didn't do that on June 1, 2012!    
    
    
    Keith Olbermann Returns to ESPN http://www.nytimes.com/2013/07/17/sports/after-16-year-absence-olbermann-is-said-to-be-returning-to-espn-to-host-show.html?_r=0 …    
    
    
    The Kremlin are buying typewriters to avoid leaks http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-23282308 …    
    
    
    Here's what Manhattan would look like inside the Grand Canyon http://guspetro.com/merge/     
    
    
    Is it just me or is LinkedIn blowing up everyone's inbox this morning?    
    
    
    @digg In the next Reader update, will there be an unread count next to each subscription?    
    
    
    @digg How did I miss that one? Lol, thanks for the assistance!    
    
    
    @GeorgiaRuocco it is a scorcher..almost a 100 degrees on some parts of the Island.    
    
    
    It is Buster Pointdexter hot today!    
    
    
    @goofy_stance #Howto wake up like a gangsta (DMX Approved wake up routine)  https://vine.co/v/h7z1YYiULtb     
    
    
    @nicktestaNY He's going up against Fox Sports 1 so I'm sure we'll see some backhanded jabs in the mix, if you know what I'm saying ;)    
    
    
    Why Is Netflix Secretly Cropping Movies?: http://wp.me/p2Xrlp-1Hen     
    
    
    @DonQuixie Sounds like trouble... ;P    
    
    
    @StxV This is the most ridiculous article I've seen in the last two weeks, at least.    
    
    
    Dear Google, if Chrome is indeed the "future of browsing", a 1990s artifact like Shockwave shouldn't make it crash!    
    
    
    The Simpsons and Family Guy are doing a crossover episode. Eh, at this point, why not? http://insidetv.ew.com/2013/07/18/simpsons-family-guy-crossover-episode/ …    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley yes. And when people ask about it, tell them you're an international man of mystery.    
    
    
    @dness88 its got soul    
    
    
    @Jsheehan83 @nydailynews I have to look this one up.    
    
    
    @StxV can you see yourself working with Tom Mele and help him with his radio ads?    
    
    
    “@HofstraU: Before @El_PresiDante was in movies like The Water Boy and Grandma's Boy, he played lax at Hofstra! pic.twitter.com/HogQTH0Hs0”    
    
    
    @Jsheehan83 Oh I believe it, just want to see it for myself. That's some headline! http://ephemeralnewyork.files.wordpress.com/2009/11/fordtocityheadline.jpg …    
    
    
    It is downright oppressive outside. Please rain! #HeatWave    
    
    
    @cdorso is it raining by Stony Brook yet? It's all oppressive sun in Hempstead...    
    
    
    Can the Nas concert start now? #Mets    
    
    
    Catching up on season 2 of Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee. Great stuff, @JerrySeinfeld!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Yikes! Don't tell me you've had no A/C this week.    
    
    
    Crazy lightning in Nassau County.    
    
    
    Spice Girls metal cover https://vine.co/v/hKzuPHuiYQ7     
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Pink Floyd (21), Best Coast (15) & The Rolling Stones (13) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    Glad the Heat Dome has been lifted but still a bit muggy out there.    
    
    
    @thest0rysofar all that's missing is the Instagram shot lol    
    
    
    @dobrock The end of youth gets closer and closer.    
    
    
    Get out of your comfort zone by ordering pineapple pizza.    
    
    
    NEWSROOM! Here we go!    
    
    
    Don't accept random friend requests on foursquare.  #newsroom    
    
    
    @jonmarkgo you might get cornered at laundromat and confronted about your YouTube video that ruined said stranger's life    
    
    
    @jonmarkgo watch tonight's newsroom :)    
    
    
    Any one else's follower count tumbling today? I hope it's Twitter cleaning out spam accounts...    
    
    
    Please be an Alexander. Please be an Alexander. Please be an Alexander.    
    
    
    @Nagler It's my pick ;)    
    
    
    My foot falls asleep way too easily.    
    
    
    Photographer captures terrible beauty of filthy canal. http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/06/08/gowanus-canal-pollution-william-miller-photos_n_3397220.html … #Gowanus    
    
    
    At first glance, I read #LindoWing as #LionKing.    
    
    
    I would love to see a "Where Are They Now" with the kids from the original Kidz Bop album.    
    
    
    Am I the only person under 30 who thought of Van Halen when they heard about Amanda Bynes being 5150'd?    
    
    
    I feel awful for Ike Davis    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov the boo's are getting louder and louder.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Yeah, he's trying to do anything to get out of his season long rut.    
    
    
    LOL RT @Jsheehan83: Anthony Weiner and Ryan Braun to open a sports restaurant together and call it, "Bat and Balls" !    
    
    
    American media, will they be patriotic and stay with Obama speech or cut to the Royal Baby naming? CNN still on Obama.    
    
    
    Making Seinfeld jokes on the work Twitter account.    
    
    
    Classy reaction from the Citi Field crowd after gruesome ankle injury to Tim Hudson.    
    
    
    Love seeing lefty on lefty action. Go Murphy! 6-2 Mets bot. 8    
    
    
    @DonQuixie there's always that one :-(. Hope the Mets keep this rally going!    
    
    
    Loving the chilly weather this morning!    
    
    
    @goofy_stance awesome! have a safe flight    
    
    
    Blasting Copacabana throughout the office.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov You missed a good time!    
    
    
    Run support for Wheeler, hooray! Mets up 4-1 bot. 3    
    
    
    Coffee drinking tied to lower risk of suicide http://goo.gl/6OtEgk     
    
    
    New Yorkers are using their treat receipts for hot latte's today @Starbucks    
    
    
    @datgreekguy foreign policy bocce. I can dig it!    
    
    
    The Science Behind How We Learn New Skills http://lifehacker.com/the-science-behind-how-we-learn-new-skills-908488422 …    
    
    
    When I can't sleep I watch news 12 traffic and weather on repeat.    
    
    
    @maiadowling are you ok?    
    
    
    @maiadowling Ouch...hope you get well soon!    
    
    
    Save some runs for tonight's game. #Mets    
    
    
    @daydraa Happy birthday Dayna! Have fun in Ocean City!    
    
    
    Redemption time, Ike Davis! #GiveHarveyALead    
    
    
    Ugh...well..#Natitude is still lame.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov The campaign itself is cool. the name is questionable.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @HofstraPride #HofNation    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @HofstraPride #PrideOrDie    
    
    
    Getting ready to go on air @wusbradio - tune in! 7:00 - 9:00 AM http://www.wusb.fm     
    
    
    @Trot17 Thanks Carol :-). Any requests?    
    
    
    @Trot17 Done!    
    
    
    Rocking the #vinyl turntables in the @wusbradio studios! pic.twitter.com/8fLqInFXC8    
    
    
    DMX was arrested. In other news, the sun rose in the East this morning.    
    
    
    NASCAR would be watchable if they threw banana peels and turtle shells.    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Ratt (14), Van Halen (13) & Third Eye Blind (13) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Not bad, I like it! It links Hofstra to a phoenix, which is pretty cool. Though it implies we've been dead or dormant    
    
    
    "If a #1 pop song of today came out 30 yrs ago w same sales figures, it wouldn't make Billboard's Top 100." - @ThisIsSethsBlog    
    
    
    @Penenberg Re your @PandoDaily digital music fidelity post, what is your streaming music service of choice?    
    
    
    Some friends' Instagram accounts have been infected with a weird fruit virus. Any one else experiencing this?    
    
    
    I wish tweeting burned calories...    
    
    
    According to Gary Cohen, @Jay_HorwitzPR is getting a bobble head because of his massive Twitter presence. #Mets    
    
    
    @Penenberg Spotify user here, haven't tried MOG but heard good things. Thx for reply & great post, will look into mobile DACs.    
    
    
    How to boost sales for your book: go on Fox News and hope the anchor absurdly challenges your credentials.    
    
    
    Bob @Lefsetz has been M.I.A. for two weeks. I hope he's alright...    
    
    
    I didn't realize so many people love @Sbarro    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Are you excited for the return of Sbarro?    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov One more thing, Moes or Chipotle?    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Yeah, you get more from Moes but the quality isn't all there, especially w/ the burrito.    
    
    
    I am afraid to turn on the #Mets game.    
    
    
    @dobrock What did you get? @TacoBell    
    
    
    Past, Present, and Future walked into a bar... 

It was tense.    
    
    
    Cool! MT @SportsCenter Pro Bowl will no longer have AFC vs. NFC format. Teams will be chosen with fantasy-like draft. (via @AdamSchefter)    
    
    
    @dness88 still..taking my time to perfect the beat but I still got love for the tweets, it's the DRE.    
    
    
    Facebook is working on a new feature called On This Day, like timehop for your newsfeed http://on.mash.to/16aCp11     
    
    
    Score some runs for Matt Harvey, please. #Mets    
    
    
    Lackmann gets a lot of flack but they make GREAT cookies!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Yes, their fruit is pretty good, especially the pineapple!    
    
    
    @DonQuixie Where are you moving to?    
    
    
    Is there a remedy to soothing a burn on the roof of your mouth?    
    
    
    I can't wait for the premier of Alex Rodriguez's Yankeeography on @YESNetwork    
    
    
    Pumped for Mets - Royals tonight.    
    
    
    I wish the #LIRR had outlets...    
    
    
    @Trot17 not on a double decker :(    
    
    
    @Trot17 found one! It was behind seat next to the door to the next car! Hidden treasure for sure lol    
    
    
    Twitter should create a Youtube - like interface for VINE. It would make discovering cool VINES so much easier.    
    
    
    @PeteLabozetta did you wake her up?    
    
    
    I Was Made For Lovin' You is the most popular KISS song on Spotify. Interesting choice...    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley Right? It would be like YouTube pre-2008, before all the brands / mainstreamers came in.    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Galaxie 500 (10), Hüsker Dü (6) & Daft Punk (5) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    If Orange is the new Black, then is Black the new Orange?    
    
    
    Not a fan of the new @MiamiDolphins logo. #MIAvsDAL    
    
    
    I can't wait for the Hofstra episode in next seasons #NewsRoom. Will McAvoy will go live from the Unispan!    
    
    
    @donewman It was a joke but it could become a reality next season ;-)    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Are you familiar with Hofstra's Jeopardy controversy?    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov I just caught up with the story, unreal! I'll tell you the Hofstra one next time I see you.    
    
    
    A-rod: playing 3rd, batting 4th and pleading the 5th!    
    
    
    Really @RealMichaelKay...one at-bat and the Yankees are exonerated in all this?    
    
    
    What is wrong with my computer? #vinetechsupport https://vine.co/v/hbI9pZAZdWV     
    
    
    I can't shake the Top Gun soundtrack from my head. #DangerZone #TakeMyBreathAway    
    
    
    Folks on @Klout, check your FB integration. Klout disconnected both my personal and brand pages without notice.    
    
    
    My house is infested with moths. I need to call Godzilla!    
    
    
    This is what Wi-Fi would look like if you could see it http://sobadsogood.com/2013/08/05/so-this-is-what-wi-fi-actually-looks-like/ …    
    
    
    Is that a blue moon out there? Harvey gets run support!    
    
    
    Twitter is the Paul Revere of modern revolutions #TwitterRevolution    
    
    
    @kaelynjean He won't do a show unless the venue supplies him with at least 80, according to @uberfact.    
    
    
    I automatically say "thank you" after I sneeze, even if no one says "bless you." #EntitledMillennial    
    
    
    Stout...Stout..Let it all out...#TearsForFearsBeer    
    
    
    They should have cell phone chargers in waiting rooms instead of magazines.    
    
    
    Check out this delicious calzone made by my bro @goofy_stance pic.twitter.com/9Yl7zAevlq    
    
    
    Tea from the @Keurig machine. Not bad!    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz Thanks for the reminder!    
    
    
    On the air #wusb #stonybrook #collegeradio https://vine.co/v/hhwa7mK9QPj     
    
    
    @Trot17 coming up after the Dave Bromberg tune!    
    
    
    @StxV  We need dynamic MAC addresses that change during each connection, like IP addresses do with Cable.    
    
    
    River of Dreams turns 20 today. #BillyJoel    
    
    
    When did Long Island become filled with country music fans? #KennyChesney    
    
    
    It's disgusting how many news outlets use spam Twitter accounts to spread a story.    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Miles Davis (13), John Coltrane (12) & Billy Joel (11) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    30 years ago! RT @wusbradio: Ticket stub for U2 show in 1983 at @stonybrooku! pic.twitter.com/gJzTOrfsoK    
    
    
    Aaron Sorkin should write a TV series about working in a University as an administrator.    
    
    
    I have Meat Loaf stuck in my head thanks to that M&M commercial. #IWouldDoAnythingForLove    
    
    
    I'm 13 and None of My Friends Use Facebook http://mashable.com/2013/08/11/teens-facebook/ …  ..should us #highered mkt'ing folks be worried?    
    
    
    "This is the hyperloop to, Penn Station. The next stop is, Hillside Support Facility (Employees Only)" #LIRR    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz The Hyper Jitney    
    
    
    Let him who hath understanding reckon the number of the beast, for it is a human number pic.twitter.com/Kwtd0YoQ86    
    
    
    How does LIU have such a big advertising budget?! They're everywhere...    
    
    
    Students forced to retake their #Regents after their original tests FELL OUT OF A TRUCK. http://bit.ly/1a2zvAU     
    
    
    @dobrock Ah so that's why traffic was light from 41-50.    
    
    
    Microscopic Life In Single Drop Of Pond Water http://youtu.be/0YAfpGlNLmc     
    
    
    10 years ago today! #nyc #blackout pic.twitter.com/p9mtQ7Mk8Y    
    
    
    Behind the Screens of Twitter's Funniest Parody Accounts http://mashable.com/2013/08/14/parody-twitter-accounts/ …    
    
    
    Tebow leads the Patriots to a Super Bowl win in Met Life Stadium. #JetsFanNightmare    
    
    
    Is anyone else creeped out by the guy in the Advantage Hyundai commercial?    
    
    
    @cesca_nnella Chipotle > Moe's.    
    
    
    @goofy_stance Your Twitter cover photo is awesome!    
    
    
    Do it! RT @SanskarWagley: Listening to Limelight by Rush, resisting the urge to sing out loud    
    
    
    We get it. You run.    
    
    
    @kschreebz so far so good! #clocks #12k @Wheelerpro45    
    
    
    Why is Obama's bus tour not stopping at Hofstra or Stony Brook to talk about college education?    
    
    
    Ok granted, Hofstra has hosted Obama before, but if he's visiting SUNYs upstate, he should show LI some love at @stonybrooku    
    
    
    I think Obama's SUNY snub at @stonybrooku should be taken up by the @StonyBrookDems.    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz @stonybrooku @StonyBrookDems Obama speaking at Binghamton & Buffalo over The Brook. http://auburnpub.com/blogs/eye_on_ny/president-obama-s-upstate-new-york-bus-tour-to-stop/article_3392986a-04fd-11e3-b11c-0019bb2963f4.html …    
    
    
    @cat_attack Binghamton and Buffalo!    
    
    
    Hey @vineapp - can we have the option to turn off revines in the next update? That would be GREAT!    
    
    
    Pro tip - don't include "Summer of 69" in your Woodstock tribute set list. #facepalm    
    
    
    Dub side of the moon.    
    
    
    There needs to be a study that ends all coffee studies. If coffee were running for office, it'd be the biggest flip-flopper.    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Dave Brubeck (15), Sublime (13) & U2 (9) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    If A-Rod homers off Dempster, he should do the Macarena while rounding the bases.    
    
    
        
    
    
    This Yankees - Red Sox game is incomplete without @RealMichaelKay screaming at the end of it.    
    
    
    I'm shocked that Sugar Ray still has a big and young fanbase.    
    
    
    @chrisgebhard stay tuned to the Hofstra FB for a big Fall Fest announcement not being tweeted about    
    
    
    @AngelooC @chrisgebhard and by "not tweeting about" I am referring to the general chatter.    
    
    
    Tom Haverford is coming to Hofstra University http://hofstrastudentlife.blogspot.com/2013/08/hofstra-fall-festival-comedian-announced.html?spref=fb …    
    
    
    @cdorso More to come soon :-)    
    
    
    @RachAClark Are the Stony Brook Dems going to take up the Obama snubbing of SBU?    
    
    
    I was hoping Mike Pelfrey would start for the Twins today. #Mets.    
    
    
    FACT: There are too many preseason NFL games. Just give me the real thing!    
    
    
    When you were 12 in 2000, did you know who New Kids On The Block were? Didn't think so. #NSYNC @BuzzFeed    
    
    
    @cdorso 61. They've always known what a Seawolf is.    
    
    
    Tonight's #fullmoon taken through a telescope by @goofy_stance pic.twitter.com/LgdhUFNgtm    
    
    
    “You've had your debate. There’s no need to write any more.” http://pressthink.org/2013/08/conspiracy-to-commit-journalism/ …    
    
    
    @kschreebz Wheeler again! #clocks    
    
    
    If a horror movie took place at Hofstra, it would be this. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q7U2aVUAqPI …    
    
    
    I wish I could download food.    
    
    
    I sound awesome when I sing to the steering wheel. When I sing to a microphone? Not so much!    
    
    
    @datgreekguy email ;)    
    
    
    @maiadowling well done.    
    
    
    Was there a time when RTs were endorsements?    
    
    
    @iancahir #irony.    
    
    
    Matt Harvey and R.A. Dickey have the same amount of wins (9).    
    
    
    @Nagler it was raining hardcore out on the Island. Brace yourselves..    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley Hofstra? I am a little biased though lol.    
    
    
    I'm responsible for the latter RT @HofstraU: Hofstra ranks #1 in College Early Birds and #3 in Most Coffee Drinkers http://www.sacbee.com/2013/08/21/5668948/urban-college-students-are-early.html …    
    
    
    @tehlizz I miss you too! How has your summer been?    
    
    
    @tehlizz Same - just way too quick! I blinked and it's nearly September :(.    
    
    
    @ScottMooreMedia @AdamReports Go back as grad students!    
    
    
    The Dice-K signing reminds me of Mo Vaughn, a little. #Mets    
    
    
    And worst idea ever: eating lunch heavy in garlic when you have afternoon meetings.    
    
    
    All the good stuff happens at your school after you graduate.    
    
    
    @cdorso Yeah, it's great to see! SBU has come a long way since my freshman year..when it was #1 in Least Happiest Students.    
    
    
    Old school! RT @wusbradio: The infamous @stonybrooku "Bridge to Nowhere" being demolished in the summer of 2002. pic.twitter.com/b80daMtefT    
    
    
    @deeannaboo822 happy birthday!!!    
    
    
    Ben Affleck can be Bruce Wayne but when he is wearing the #Batman suit, I want to hear Kevin Conroy!    
    
    
    @kschreebz Aaron Sorkin needs to write a show about the UR department.    
    
    
    Your favorite 90s tunes, acapella. https://soundcloud.com/isolatedvocals     
    
    
    @cdorso That's weird. It's not letting you make a new album?    
    
    
    If everyone cared about *insert world problem here* instead of Ben Affleck being Batman, we would end said world problem.    
    
    
    D'Arnaud uses Van Halen's Panama as his at bat music. Awesome!    
    
    
    Dice-K and the Mets opening for @3eb pic.twitter.com/IOVprvt02A    
    
    
    My section is starting the Wave and it's only the 3rd inning. Embarrassing #Mets    
    
    
    @kschreebz 511! Haha you're one over...I'm in the 3rd last row    
    
    
    Finally - my pretzel wasn't stale!!! #Mets #CitiField    
    
    
    Heads up @Jay_HorwitzPR, my mom is calling Fred, angry that ya'll ran out of bobble heads.    
    
    
    #InstaMets? More like #SelfieMets    
    
    
    Field seats are empty but fans can't move down for @3eb? What a joke, @mets. @CitiFieldEvents    
    
    
    No sound check from @3eb leads to a terrible sound for Never Give You Up. Come on @mets @CitiFieldEvents @Citi_Field_NY  get it together    
    
    
    Matt Harvey should get on stage with @3eb and sing Jumper.  How epic would that be? @MattHarvey33    
    
    
    "This one is going out to the @mets fans in the upper deck!" and then @3eb begins Jumper!    
    
    
    @kschreebz @3eb  jumper is the story of being a @Mets fan ;)    
    
    
    That new song was worse than Dice-K was tonight! #mets    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov HAHA the opening was brutal but they got better. Still mad they didn't let fans move down.    
    
    
    Just saw two deer at @stonybrooku by main entrance!! Wasn't quick enough to get a pic :(    
    
    
    @Trot17 @stonybrooku Yes! Ah my last update didn't go through. On air till 9..any requests?    
    
    
    Nothing says Saturday morning like a bacon, egg and cheese sandwich on an everything bagel.    
    
    
    Wow! @mets called my house today and talked to my mom about the bobble head situation. Great job @Jay_HorwitzPR! pic.twitter.com/VVnnwVhjRB    
    
    
    GENO BABY.    
    
    
    Carl Banks is the worst broadcaster ever.    
    
    
    I can't believe Geno is still in. Jets brass is overriding Rex, who you know wants Sanchez.    
    
    
    @StxV yeah it's awful. I think the broadcast is technically NBC New York so no traditional NBC Sunday Night fanfare.    
    
    
    MTV is to music as KFC is to chicken. #VMAs    
    
    
    MTV hosting a music awards show is like the NRA presenting the Nobel Peace Prize.    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Third Eye Blind (71), Nirvana (27) & John Coltrane (13) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    To all my @stonybrooku peeps, good luck on your 1st day of classes!    
    
    
    I read the news today, oh boy.
About a pitcher who made the grade. And though the news was rather sad. Well, I just had to laugh.    
    
    
    But seriously, the Matt Harvey news is downright devastating. Even the most jaded #Mets fans are feeling the pain today.    
    
    
    @kschreebz You should play It's the End of the World As We Know It.    
    
    
    @kschreebz Woo, you rock! I'm tuned in at the office.    
    
    
    @Tmartorano_BLG Ban-Ki Moon ;)    
    
    
    It's going to be a long September RT @AdamRubinESPN: Source: John Buck and Marlon Byrd to #Pirates. #mets    
    
    
    This iconic '90 album turns 22 years old today! pic.twitter.com/p9TPPbOgwW    
    
    
    @Melissa_Kue Congratulations!    
    
    
    @StxV I would fit right in with my black @RADickey43 t-shirt.    
    
    
    MLK receives an honorary degree from #Hofstra in 1965, two years after #DreamDay pic.twitter.com/RPE20gwr2U    
    
    
    @RachAClark PSL10    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov PSL10 alert    
    
    
    @AdamReports PSL10    
    
    
    @AdamReports say it next time you go to Starbucks.    
    
    
    @RachAClark say it next time you go to Starbucks.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov don't let anyone say it at Starbucks.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov If someone says PSL10 to a Starbucks barista, they start serving Pumpkin Spice Lattes. :-o    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov I'm not sure...maybe it's the drink's 10th anniversary?    
    
    
    @adamallabout just do it    
    
    
    @adamallabout don't you miss the taste of autumn?    
    
    
    @adamallabout yes.    
    
    
    @adamallabout someone instagrammed a pic of it and tweeted hofstra.    
    
    
    Even Google has given up on the Mets pic.twitter.com/InDkNtc7ZA    
    
    
    Way to go Instagram, you stop working when I need you most. Camera keeps crashing.    
    
    
    Vineing it up today RT @HofstraU: #Hofstra17 SHOUTING their Hofstra Pride!  ZachLFeldman https://vine.co/v/hi2zMXLmV55     
    
    
    Parents of freshman: your kids don't want you taking pictures of them on line for their first Student Center meal.    
    
    
    If you're DJ'ing at any "Welcome Week" university event, you MUST play Parents Just Don't Understand. #FreshPrince #HigherEd    
    
    
    @FOGHAT Thank you so much! Long live rock and roll!    
    
    
    The past is the present.    
    
    
    Office #selfie http://instagram.com/p/dpUMM5nZBY/     
    
    
    @_SueCaulfield slappin da bass mon    
    
    
    Deer in #WestHampton! http://instagram.com/p/dsoXbrnZDA/     
    
    
    Jerry Dantana #newsroom MT @USATODAY Kerry says new evidence Syria used sarin gas http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/09/01/kerry-syria-sarin-evidence/2752837/ …    
    
    
    And the heavens have opened up in Suffolk County.    
    
    
    A mosquito flew into my #bluepoint beer. http://instagram.com/p/dupoZdnZBf/     
    
    
    Packed campgrounds for Bradstock pic.twitter.com/8kpzK75mAK    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Stevie Wonder (21), Radiohead (20) & Bob Marley & The Wailers (18) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    "Excuse me waiter, I'd like to return my food. It only received 6 likes on Instagram."    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz Mario Tennis for me.    
    
    
    In the two years I've been here, it has rained on the 1st day of classes. #Hofstra    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley WSOU?    
    
    
    Is it requirement to scream when you record a @vineapp?    
    
    
    Ocean Parkway has saved my commute from being a total nightmare. #backtoschool #september    
    
    
    You Can Now Search for Any Tweet in History http://on.mash.to/1798Yy9     
    
    
    Springsteen version of Blinded by the Light just came on Spotify. Much different vibe than Manfred Mann.    
    
    
    Tonight's weather is perfect for hoodies.    
    
    
    @cdorso New DEC system?    
    
    
    Former #Mets pitching match-ups: Wheeler vs. Kazmir (Mets @ Indians) and Dickey vs. Pelfrey (TOR @ MIN)    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz Sea salt...I see what you did there!    
    
    
    @TonyFlacko The hard part is finding a pasta that captures the individual.    
    
    
    You meet a proctologist at a party, don't walk away. Plant yourself there!    
    
    
    If there is one '80s album you need to listen to today, make it Romeo Void's "It's A Condition" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bof0zdX0MyU&list=ALBTKoXRg38BB1SdecWnbnQwqj6jKmHehD …    
    
    
    My #WUSB playlist from this morning. #collegeradio #stonybrook http://wusb.fm/node/20842     
    
    
    Imagine if Stony Brook booked Mike Miller instead of Mac Miller. Hoo boy..    
    
    
    The stands are still standing but I am keeping a close eye on Twitter tonight.    
    
    
    @Jsheehan83 I got my tweet thumb ready...    
    
    
    I know the Jets are expected to be awful but I'm still excited for the start of the season! J-E-T-S!!! JETS JETS JETS    
    
    
    Oh shoot, @kevinburkhardt is calling the Jets game on FOX. Good stuff!    
    
    
    The Bucs are making the Jets look like an elite football team!    
    
    
    Smh #nyjets    
    
    
    There you go!!!! Geno's 1st NFL TD...ok..some hope has been instilled in me.    
    
    
    Whoever has Buffalo in their knockout pool should play LOTTO tonight!    
    
    
    Folk yeah!!!!! This is comical...but I'll take it!!! #nyjets    
    
    
    Geno > Eli.    
    
    
    Giants fans....now you feel our pain. #Jets    
    
    
    @LenSkoros Len, there is plenty of room on the Jets bandwagon. Don't despair!    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz Don't despair, Alex. There's plenty of room on the Jets bandwagon!    
    
    
    @Rcvryguy There is plenty of room on the Jets bandwagon, John!    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Billy Joel (27), Bruce Springsteen (21) & Catholic Spray (7) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    @Nagler @cdorso I heard it was directed at Greek life presidents from upd. I'll see if I can dig up the tweet.    
    
    
    @RachAClark late rt but I am still all WTF SORKIN    
    
    
    @cdorso @Nagler @RachAClark  don't sweat it, you're doing a great job. Only so much we can do with limited info.    
    
    
    Is there a secret code to unlock the Gingerbread Latte yet? @Starbucks    
    
    
    I picked the Eagles tonight. #JustSayin cc @StephenGorchov    
    
    
    @goofy_stance "Aware of Weather Patterns"    
    
    
    22 years ago today: Nirvana releases Smells Like Teen Spirit as a single. (1991) http://www.history.com/this-day-in-history/nirvanas-quotsmells-like-teen-spiritquot-is-released-as-a-single …    
    
    
    Google Plus just crashed Chrome. Even Google's own browser despises Google Plus...    
    
    
    Now would be a great time for Facebook to announce a privacy policy change.    
    
    
    Anthony Weiner should recite the lyrics to Closing Time and call it a concession speech.    
    
    
    Who needs meaningful baseball in September when you can have Spongebob show up instead? #Mets pic.twitter.com/TKw1vS9O33    
    
    
    Did we ever figure out who started the fire? #BillyJoel    
    
    
    I am feeling optimistic tonight. Go #Jets!    
    
    
    Get ready for auto-play video ads in the Facebook newsfeed. #ugh http://mashable.com/2013/09/12/facebook-autoplay-video-ads …    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov I think so. @hootsuite is down for me as well.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Must be the forces of Friday the 13th at work...    
    
    
    Ok now @Tweetdeck is acting up. It has to be a Friday the 13th thing.    
    
    
    @HootSuite_Help Looks like I'm back in action. I'm using Chrome.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Hootsuite is back for me. @chrisgebhard    
    
    
    To thine own selfie be true.    
    
    
    Apparently the Toyota Scion is not pronounced "scone"    
    
    
    @cesca_nnella ask @gpc17, he might know lol    
    
    
    The theme song to Cheers is randomly stuck in my head. "Sometimes you want to go..."    
    
    
    @StxV You're in Alaska?! I went in 2001 on a cruise. Ketchikan was fun, did some canoeing followed by clam chowder.    
    
    
    I want to go back to Alaska.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Cosmos?    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Billy Joel (14), 2Pac (11) & R.E.M. (11) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Your "empty office" tweet last night reminded me of this http://youtu.be/LIAZWb9_si4?t=12s …    
    
    
    What's going on with the Eagles? Wake up!!!    
    
    
    @_SueCaulfield ice is back with a brand new invention?    
    
    
    San Diego Chargers are your 2013 Super Bowl champions! #EaglesHomeOpener    
    
    
    Eli makes his presence known. #nygvsden    
    
    
    So the #Jets are the best football team in New York right now :-)    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Did Mariano Rivera ever make an appearance at Hofstra for anything?    
    
    
    @kschreebz Have you ever had moon cake?    
    
    
    @kschreebz a Chinese cake eaten during China's Mid-Autumn Day, which is Thursday. Might get one for the office :)    
    
    
    @LenSkoros @StephenGorchov That sounds awesome! Please tell me the fun didn't stop once them Pringles popped!!    
    
    
    Will  @SNFonNBC play Nirvana every time the @Seahawks score? I can dig that!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov  Did you lose power on the north side of campus?    
    
    
    Hot @Starbucks on a cold New York morning is fine by me.    
    
    
    No outlets?! grr MT @Newsday #LIRR previews new train cars due in 2017 http://www.newsday.com/long-island/lirr-previews-new-train-cars-due-in-2017-1.6085375 …    
    
    
    Live from New York … Hofstra Alum Makes SNL Cast http://bit.ly/153gpEf     
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz @politico Good thing there aren't term limits for Super Bowls amirite?    
    
    
    @StxV Are they talking about this in the @snytv booth? I just tuned in  (doubt it but ya never know)    
    
    
    Jerry Seinfeld in the @SNYtv booth is the best #Mets moment since the Subway Series.    
    
    
    “Liking” something on Facebook is protected by the First Amendment http://on.wsj.com/1f6pHq1     
    
    
    No one is in the office. Time to blast Led Zeppelin's Immigrant Song.    
    
    
    @chrisgebhard You were right. Nappolini's buffalo pizza is amazing! Totally changed my opinion of the topping.    
    
    
    Why didn't anybody tell me it was Auto Reply Friday?    
    
    
    @DSSimon Thank you so much for the #FF !    
    
    
    Twizzlers and coffee surprisingly go great together!    
    
    
    On @wusbradio until 9 am! Tune in: http://www.wusb.fm  - I'll have Albert Bouchard of BOC on at 8:30!    
    
    
    @Trot17 @wusbradio coming up!    
    
    
    You spent your summers at Jones or Robert Moses & you’re still not sure of the purpose of that pencil-looking building, #LongIsland    
    
    
    ATTENTION STONY BROOK STUDENTS: CAN YOU KICK?! PLEASE REPORT TO LAVALLE STADIUM MONDAY    
    
    
    Technical difficulties on SNY makes me feel better about WUSB.    
    
    
    @Rcvryguy I went to a protest and a football game broke out.    
    
    
    @Nagler @StxV @MGHeinz I'd be down for Sunday. #piazzaday    
    
    
    iOS 7 reminds me of the Wii. The interfaces are very similar.    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: The Police (19), Van Halen (12) & Oasis (11) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    I'm not crazy. I may look weird, but I'm just like you... I'm just a regular guy..    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Sorry, meant to ask about the cake on this account :-).    
    
    
    Any recs for Twitter analytics dashboards? Looking for alternative to Topsy Pro; something simpler, less $ #highered    
    
    
    @_SueCaulfield Thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    @HUSpecColl who is standing next to RFK?    
    
    
    @_SueCaulfield Nope, just an intense wave of silence :( haha.    
    
    
    @AR1EL_A I hope you get to meet and greet Sugar Ray    
    
    
    @AR1EL_A lol it's your office that's running the show :p    
    
    
    @cdorso @clconzen Just ask Beck. Losing helped him peak at 10 on the Hot 100 in 1994!    
    
    
    Eating moon cake in Hofstra Hall! pic.twitter.com/JhlM6kIH4s    
    
    
    Classic rock radio needs to chill out with  the Foo Fighters. Stop treating them like Led Zeppelin!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Looks like I have to up my Squirrel game this year!    
    
    
    Find yourself disappointed after clicking an enticingly juicy Upworthy headline? Follow @UpworthySpoiler. Problem solved!    
    
    
    Rock on, I wanna be President! RT @KISSopolis: Gene Simmons Will Sing The U.S. National Anthem In London This Sunday http://bit.ly/191fquE ”    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley @MTV Solution: Use Youtube.    
    
    
    In the 90s we had East vs. West..now we have @kanyewest vs. @jimmykimmel #wheresthebeef    
    
    
    I could watch the ending to Game 7 of the '94 Stanley Cup finals a trillion times & it would never get old. @NYRangers    
    
    
    @jaygeemsg Torts def. changed, much more open and affable. Good interview!    
    
    
    Happy 15th birthday @Google! One more year until you can get your permit in NY. #selfdrivingcarsstillneedlicense?    
    
    
    Best @nytimes correction ever. #nintendo pic.twitter.com/txqEF6LOjx    
    
    
    @AR1EL_A When It's Over is my personal Sugar Ray favorite :)    
    
    
    @Nagler Killer tofu!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @NeuLionIPTV @WRHUSports Can I listen to it in the background or does the app need to stay open?    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @NeuLionIPTV @WRHUSports Excellent! The WRHU app needs to stay open which is why I was concerned.    
    
    
    @KarlaSchuster @Sears LOL this is amazing! Well done.    
    
    
    @sms1998 Lol @KarlaSchuster just tweeted me this too. So good!    
    
    
    @RealTimers New York > California    
    
    
    .@lastfm Any plans for a timeline feature? It would be fun to see how tastes change over the years.    
    
    
    @RachAClark yeah Jon Milhiser.    
    
    
    When is Kel Mitchell joining #SNL to reunite with Kenan? Can we get a Kenan and Kel reunion?    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Billy Joel (17), Ann Licater (11) & CHVRCHES (11) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    In honor of last @MetsWFAN game, I am voluntarily listening rather than watching.    
    
    
    I miss Sanchez. #Jets    
    
    
    Football was not kind to the NYC area this wknd...Seawolves, Giants and Jets all lose.    
    
    
    Breaking Sad.    
    
    
    ROCK ON! RT @wusbradio: 40 years ago tonight, Bruce Springsteen rocked @stonybrooku! pic.twitter.com/JsLrOADcnp    
    
    
    Fox News is covering the #shutdown like it's New Year's Eve!    
    
    
    Government Shutdown Rockin' Eve with Ryan Seacrest    
    
    
    Car fire on LIE ext 53-51W    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @KarlaSchuster  Mike Francesa, 1776 edition. LML funny!  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ptPBCSsPJR4 …    
    
    
    @dness88 I was about to tell you Andrew O'Geen is on LinkedIn but you're already connected LOL.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov The yellow tie was a great choice, it catches the eye while scrolling through Twitter.    
    
    
    Washington can get shut down the government but they can't stop the Blackhawks.    
    
    
    Google Accused of Wiretapping in Gmail Scans http://nyti.ms/15JXDSI     
    
    
    @KrissyRubbles Kosher pickles for me.    
    
    
    @kschreebz mind if I share this on Hofstra Facebook?    
    
    
    Feeding time for the #Hofstra cats! https://vine.co/v/hg2dTqVznbl     
    
    
    I can't stop whistling Minnie the Moocher #cabcalloway #bluesbrothers    
    
    
    @sosoglos Woohoo! You guys are on Spotify now!    
    
    
    Scenes from an Italian Restaurant    
    
    
    @ScottMooreMedia what's the islanders score? :p    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley how did the LSAT go?    
    
    
    What was the point of the DJ in Limp Bizkit?    
    
    
    @Lv5LaserLotus Pop culture historians are still figuring the one out :)    
    
    
    NJ Transit makes me miss the LIRR    
    
    
    These are giant headphones. pic.twitter.com/P6CEsAiIjl    
    
    
    I'm ready for some football. (@ MetLife Stadium - @mlstadium w/ @nagler @adamallabout) http://4sq.com/16MPumG     
    
    
    How is that not a safety? #giants    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Canibus (11), José González (8) & John Williams (7) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    How do #Giants & #Jets season tix holders put up with the #brutal commute to Met Life stadium? Took me 3 hrs to get home via train    
    
    
    My last tweet was meant for Long Island #Giants & #Jets fans..but the sentiment remains.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Did you watch SNL last night? There was a Hof cameo...    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov  intramural field was used as a backdrop in one of the skits. pic.twitter.com/lP96SE1ekL    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Nevermind its an old one.    
    
    
    I'm finding more interesting and relevant content in Facebook's trending topics than Twitter's so far.    
    
    
    @Sid_Madden Great meeting you, Sidney! Glad I was able to help you out.    
    
    
    Breaking Away: Top Public Universities Push for ‘Autonomy’ From States http://www.propublica.org/article/breaking-away-top-public-universities-push-for-autonomy-from-states …    
    
    
    @RachAClark You don't need to be governor, per se. All you need is a lot of money! He plays private parties :).    
    
    
    Never a dull moment.  #NYJvsATL    
    
    
    @BCusterTV @SNYtv broooo    
    
    
    ESPN app keeps flashing #Seawolves final score after every Jets scoring play. pic.twitter.com/H6IUEYhaVo    
    
    
    YEAH!!!!! TOUCHDOWN!!! Geno > Eli. #WentThere #NYJvsATL    
    
    
    I am going to be insufferable tomorrow if the Jets pull this one out. #MNF #NYJvsATL    
    
    
    I feel like Howard Dean during the scream: first we take Atlanta, then Pittsburgh! And then NEW ENGLAND and NEW ORLEANS - AWYAHHHHH #JETS    
    
    
    @StxV how's the crowd?    
    
    
    I can't wait until the Rangers play Vancouver  #BradRichards #NYR    
    
    
    I tweeted too soon -_- #NYR    
    
    
    Can't believe the Rangers gave up 9 goals...@HLundqvist30, what happened? Is it the new pads?    
    
    
    The Grotto is an ice box right now.    
    
    
    The British Horror Story is much better than the American one. #AmericanHorrorStory    
    
    
    Go Dodgers! #NLCS    
    
    
    .@paparoach You're fine.    
    
    
    @cdorso WUSB is streaming it today if you can't find the raw feed. http://www.wusb.fm     
    
    
    Tweet about Jan Session registration...nothing. Tweet about cats...all the retweets!    
    
    
    @kschreebz FYI, your half-cupcake has caused an uproar in The Grotto lol    
    
    
    There has to be a college or university out there that licenses the Jurassic Park theme for their tours. It would be epic!    
    
    
    @kschreebz yum!    
    
    
    Giants fans, if this is any consolation, I picked against them for the 1st time this season. So...#AngeloJinx    
    
    
    Alain Vigneault, the Mike D'Antoni of hockey? #NYR    
    
    
        
    
    
    America likes Nickelback more than Congress http://consequenceofsound.net/2013/10/america-likes-nickelback-more-than-congress/ …    
    
    
    Why is everyone suddenly discovering the vineyards out east? #LongIsland    
    
    
    Average White Band is so underrated.    
    
    
    Excited to hear objective commentary from Bill Cowher in the booth for Jets - Steelers.    
    
    
    Too many missed tackles!! #Jets    
    
    
    Oh the pain. #Jets    
    
    
    I hope all my Canadian followers are enjoying their Thanksgiving.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov This is pretty cool!    
    
    
    What happened? I was looking at the 2014 Mets schedule.  #ALCS    
    
    
    I still root for the Red Sox to spite Yankees fans.    
    
    
    @bearslothbearsl #2004eva    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: John Coltrane (9), Ratt (8) & John Williams (6) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
        
    
    
    I wish my commute could be like Columbus Day every day. There was no traffic!!    
    
    
    Does the Binder and Binder lawyer wear his hat in court? If not, the commercials are false advertising!    
    
    
    Slice of pie in its fitted Tupperware. #pies #90s http://instagram.com/p/ffRdN6nZDJ/     
    
    
    @AdamReports @sbusports @TheRealMaysonet WELCOME ABOARD THE JETS BANDWAGON ADAM    
    
    
    I'm seeing Billy Joel in Miami, 4 years from now!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Nope, just pages for now.    
    
    
    Say what now? RT @JoeLhota4Mayor: FACT: @deBlasioNYC is the Tim Tebow of NYC politics”    
    
    
    @CQBalthazar @HofstraU We got it covered, thanks Claudia. :)    
    
    
    @Nagler congratulations on the new gig !    
    
    
    @kschreebz You should scream at them "FREE BIRD!"    
    
    
    @RachAClark Is this an org first? I don't remember seeing Dems hoodies in my day.    
    
    
    The King Has Returned! #NYR @HLundqvist30    
    
    
    Photobombing @BretBaier at last year's #hofdebate. #tbt pic.twitter.com/FJIN3jNgkw    
    
    
    GIF: Mike Francesa spills his diet coke. http://twitpic.com/dhv41f  @StephenGorchov @KarlaSchuster    
    
    
    I'm obsessed with @Shazam    
    
    
    It's hard to give things away for free and then ask for money later.    
    
    
    Conductor of @LIRR announced a proposal was made on train (Ronk westbound). No word on if s/he said yes.    
    
    
    @PeteLabozetta @LIRR agreed lol. Maybe they met on train though and doing the whole "new beginning" scenario.    
    
    
    Some dude had his sword out in Penn Station. Cops had to talk to him lol.    
    
    
    @ScottMooreMedia lol literal    
    
    
    They really need a train between 1:23 and 2:53 am....#lirr    
    
    
    NFL Sunday: When I wear my Mets shirt, the Jets win. When I wear my Jets shirt, the Jets lose. I'm putting on my Mets shirt!    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley Uh oh, did u take the corvette out on a little spin and get caught speeding 90mph with a 12 year old runaway? #freshprince    
    
    
    @SpotifyPlatform Will there be offline integration with Djay in the near future? @Algoriddim    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Billy Joel (24), Eagles (11) & Bruce Springsteen (7) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    Kerley is having a MONSTROUS game today! #NYJ    
    
    
    I LOVE IT! JETS WIN! If the big banks can be bailed out, so can the Jets!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ericajmoss Fantastic photo!    
    
    
    @Algoriddim Ah, I see this is a popular request. :)    
    
    
    @dobrock You can sync your  @Spotify playlists offline on your phone over wifi/3G, so no data/service needed for listening :)    
    
    
    Out of office replies. #admissionprobs    
    
    
    The John Spano 30 for 30 is very good so far.  #isles    
    
    
    Mike Milbury needs his own 30 for 30. #isles    
    
    
    Coliseum deli sighting! #30for30    
    
    
    Don't get it perfect, get it right.    
    
    
    Only the Mets.... pic.twitter.com/hf3cuMJqeT    
    
    
    Buzzfeed without the GIFs http://buzzfeedminusgifs.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    @RachAClark @billclinton @Tom_Suozzi garden city hotel?    
    
    
    Boston sports are having a tough week with refs and umps. #WorldSeries    
    
    
    Looks like the Red Sox cleaned up their beards a bit. They're tamer.    
    
    
    COLD    
    
    
    I beat the Elite 4 with one Metapod. #pokemon    
    
    
    Wow tonight was first World Series loss for Red Sox since Game 7 of 86 WS against the Mets! pic.twitter.com/9IAL8kASf5    
    
    
    30% of Americans Get Their News on Facebook http://mashable.com/2013/10/24/1-in-3-americans-get-news-on-facebook/ …    
    
    
    27 years ago today, it got through Buckner. http://atmlb.com/HluaIr  #WorldSeries #Mets    
    
    
    Today is perfect for endlessly listening to Led Zeppelin's Ramble On. #leavesarefallingallaround    
    
    
    Let's go Rangers! #BeatDetroit    
    
    
    If #Seawolves want to succeed in CAA, they need to master the Statue of Liberty and the Flea Flicker. Otherwise they're doomed!    
    
    
    @kschreebz mad lackmann cookies in student center and cultural center theater, FYI    
    
    
    @kschreebz are you still in Herbert?    
    
    
    So is Lou Reed dead or alive? I'm hearing conflicted reports. Is Rolling Stone only mainstream media with story?    
    
    
    Enough with the bit strips.    
    
    
    Home opener. LETS GO RANGERS!!    
    
    
    @chrisgebhard @NeilSchloth App called "Repost"    
    
    
    Is Brad Richards playing tonight? #NYR    
    
    
    Brutal. Just brutal. #NYR    
    
    
    Is anyone else having trouble closing ads from iPhone apps? The 'x' icon is slow to react!    
    
    
    If a holiday is recognized by Google, that's as good as the federal government, right? #catday    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/Nl8aY1bvs4    
    
    
    @cdorso It's meta.    
    
    
    Woo! RANGERS WIN! #nyr pic.twitter.com/Sz4snQxEFH    
    
    
    The 20% text rule for boosting Facebook posts #smmproblems    
    
    
    @Jsheehan83 I see someone rode the Blue Beetle this morning!    
    
    
    Most exciting part about tonight's @nyknicks opener? The return of Walt Clyde Frazier on @MSGNetworks!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Congratulations!    
    
    
    Sabremetrics lol #Redsox #SOXTOBER    
    
    
    Congratulations Boston! Someday @Mets fans, October will be ours. Someday...    
    
    
        
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Queen (10), The Doobie Brothers (6) & Derek and the Dominos (6) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    @StephenGorchov I stopped by the trailer this morning looking for you. #HofstraHalloween    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov This is what you would've seen. pic.twitter.com/mQBs6TOnVe    
    
    
    I am rooting against Adam Jones. #CINvsMIA    
    
    
    The #LIRR custodians are going to be very busy tonight. #Halloween    
    
    
    Perfect time for this song! #gnr pic.twitter.com/uk0QdlHUKY    
    
    
    "Forget about the curve ball, Ricky. Give'em the heater!"    
    
    
    On my way to the @wusbradio studios. Tune in from 7-9 am, http://www.wusb.fm     
    
    
    Fascinating..."Why Attractive Candidates Win http://nyti.ms/1hAfjrS "    
    
    
    #NYCmarathon  ♫ I Ran (So Far Away) – A Flock Of Seagulls http://spoti.fi/VNTYQS  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    A THROW IN THE WILDCAT!!! #rare #NYJ    
    
    
    Run Geno Run!! Touchdown! Who Dat!    
    
    
    You're not allowed to hit Drew Brees. Good to know. #NYJvsNO    
    
    
    Come on, hold on to this one! #NYJvsNO    
    
    
    Wow, the Jets just can't close this one out. #NYJvsNO    
    
    
    The Jets D was rock solid today! What a win! #NYJvsNO    
    
    
    @Nagler I'm glad I was proven wrong :)    
    
    
    Stadium DJs should replace Hells Bells with Number of the Beast, it would freshen things up!    
    
    
    @StxV Is there a Fox outlet on any media that has remarkable credibility?    
    
    
    What channel is the YouTube Music Awards on? #YTMA #trolling    
    
    
    I think the Eagles were inspired by the @Sixers.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @MLB @Yankees @CAASports That year's championship stings me the most.    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: The Who (31), Guns N' Roses (14) & Queen (10) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    Can you spot the #Hofstra squirrel? Repost by @dana_gibbs94. http://instagram.com/p/gTICF0S7Qt/     
    
    
    I was kind of hoping the Mets would join the Islanders on WRHU radio Hofstra.    
    
    
    My hair is long enough now that I need to tie it back when eating a burrito.    
    
    
    @thest0rysofar I heard Iceland is really beautiful, the name is deceiving :).    
    
    
    MICHAEL. DEL. ZOTTO.    
    
    
    I still had no power on Election Day last year. My generator died right as they announced Ohio for Obama.    
    
    
    Bring back the red robin 7 train cars. @BilldeBlasio    
    
    
    A New Full House is Coming Starring DJ and Stephanie Tanner http://www.tvovermind.com/full-house/a-new-full-house-is-coming-starring-dj-and-stephanie-tanner-223330 …    
    
    
    @RachAClark "ameliorated" - great word!    
    
    
    @RachAClark Tonight's LI results are anathema    
    
    
    GAS TV is still running political ads!    
    
    
    Whoaaaa oh oh! Two goals in aim ute and five seconds! Let's go Rangers!    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz I'm just as shocked!    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz That's our captain!    
    
    
    BOYLE?! Lol I love it ! # nyr 3-0!!!    
    
    
    Realistically colorized historical photos make the past seem incredibly real #history http://twentytwowords.com/2013/11/06/realistically-colorized-historical-photos-make-the-past-seem-incredibly-real-36-pictures/ …    
    
    
    Congratulations Twitter.  #ring    
    
    
    I need to keep a spare pair of socks in my office. #wetsocks    
    
    
    So..many...rainbow...photos!    
    
    
        
    
    
    This is the first time I'm seeing @3eb where the Mets aren't the opening act. #3ebontheroad pic.twitter.com/IyvJn75FYl    
    
    
    Good things come to those who wait! #cliches RT @SanskarWagley Why do the best things in life get postponed? Wahhhh    
    
    
    Being sick on a Friday night should be illegal.    
    
    
    Bare feet, cold floor. #SundayMorning    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: John Coltrane (26), Weezer (16) & U2 (15) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    Knicks and Giants playing at the same time this afternoon. What are NY fans going to do?    
    
    
    @AR1EL_A @Amtrak Did you do Acela? I loved it when I did NY -> DC.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Craving some goji berries right now.    
    
    
    @AR1EL_A @Amtrak LIRR could score major points if they get WIFI and outlets.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov I'm trying a new Instagram rally technique for likes. The "double tap"    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Thx! IG technique, usually used by celeb tribute accounts. I haven't seen a brand/Uni use it yet.    
    
    
    @PeteLabozetta The saxophone needs to make a comeback in theme music.    
    
    
    @StxV What KoRN song was on WRCN? Freak on a Leash? Blind?    
    
    
    11:11 on 11/11 AHHHH    
    
    
    @KrissyRubbles Check the WUSB homepage when you get a moment.    
    
    
    Freedom rises above all! #America MT @BreakingNews World Trade Center in NY ruled tallest building in US, beating Chicago's Willis Tower    
    
    
    Twitter Announces Custom Timelines http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/12/twitter-to-let-you-create-custom-timelines-for-hashtags-or-topics-from-tweetdeck-developers-too/ … ..basically Twitter's version of Storify.    
    
    
    @_SueCaulfield Yes, they are. I am looking fwd to new timelines. Makes curating tweets SO much easier. :)    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov I'm on it!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Some of these tweets are infuriating!    
    
    
    Down 5....    
    
    
    @kschreebz Shoot, I tweeted too soon :(    
    
    
    @kschreebz Ugh..I need to step away from Twitter. Almost got into it with a sassy Louisville fan on the work account.    
    
    
    New York > Kentucky.    
    
    
    Good day for soup and a sandwich from Hofstra's @AuBonPain    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kschreebz whatchu talkin about    
    
    
    Listening to 1963's top @billboard hits, tons of great surf rock tracks! 
http://www.bobborst.com/popculture/top-100-songs-of-the-year/?year=1963 …    
    
    
    Economic segregation is seeping into every pore of our society. http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/12/opinion/bruni-the-extra-legroom-society.html?ref=frankbruni&_r=0 …    
    
    
    The @StallerCenter steps, back when it was all concrete (1980). #stonybrook pic.twitter.com/utDrVfwmsM    
    
    
    Randomly have the Degrassi theme song stuck in my head. #iknowicanmakeitthrough    
    
    
    @NeilSchloth Happy birthday Neil...21...enjoy it!    
    
    
    @BTW892 460 on optimum. The channel is called "sign off"    
    
    
    Am I the only one that watches the musicians during the opening monologue? #snl    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Van Halen (7), The Rolling Stones (6) & Toto (6) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    Sunday morning rain is the best rain.    
    
    
    Geno Smith is to the #Jets what Oliver Perez was to the #Mets. #Enigma    
    
    
    I watched the entire Jets game. Clearly I'm a masochist. #JetsvsBills    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov It has an extremely good chance of making it!    
    
    
    I bet @Upworthy has a " Chief Headline Officer" (CHO) in its C-Suite.    
    
    
    @deannaboo822 *slowly raises hand* - idk it's too thick with milk.    
    
    
    Yum...@UncleJerrys' pretzels are the best! As a pretzel connoisseur, I highly recommend them!    
    
    
    Jets would be a game out of 1st place if they skipped @DaveandBusters and showed up against @buffalobills #mnf    
    
    
    @AR1EL_A welcome to my life    
    
    
    @KrissyRubbles funk masta flexha    
    
    
    Bill Belichick and John Tortorella need to host a press conference together.    
    
    
    @dness88 Congratulations! pic.twitter.com/s7pVHCtzsY    
    
    
    It makes so much sense it sounds absurd.    
    
    
    @StxV @MGHeinz @Nagler something fishy is going on, that's for sure!    
    
    
    Oh snap. #CatchingFire #vip http://instagram.com/p/g9Q1uDHZMW/     
    
    
    @MGHeinz @StxV @Nagler My theory - Pres. Stanley convinced Jim Calhoun to take job. It fits him perfectly given all the uconn around him.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Grabbed a bag of chips and realized it was "Sea Salt and Vinegar" after popping the first chip in my mouth. Taste buds are in shock!    
    
    
    The best broadcast team in baseball remains intact! 
"Darling is staying with @snytv" http://metsblog.com/metsblog/ron-darling-is-staying-with-sny/ …    
    
    
    @StxV @infinity_shred Similar to the difference between soundtracks on an NES and SNES?    
    
    
    @Elle_Murray "Get Lucky" also works for finals :)    
    
    
    I love the latest Twitter iOS update! My favorite part about it is the ability to sort by ALL TWEETS in search.  #socialmedia    
    
    
    Eating nuts can reduce a person's risk of dying from cancer or heart disease. http://www.foxnews.com/health/2013/11/21/study-says-nut-eaters-have-lower-cancer-heart-disease-risk/ …    
    
    
    @Trot17 The jury is still out on that one!    
    
    
    I'm all about dipping chips into a @ChipotleTweets burrito bowl. #LunchTime    
    
    
    While most media outlets are running the JFK memorial, @wusbradio is airing JFK conspiracy theories. http://www.wusb.fm     
    
    
    Good to be back @stonybrooku for #EmpireClash but it's chilly.    
    
    
    @WolfieSeawolf with the kids! pic.twitter.com/qtzTmztME4    
    
    
    Local music marathon! #LongIsland (@ WUSB 90.1 FM - @wusbradio) http://4sq.com/1edXkEF     
    
    
    You CANNOT say these words on the radio! #wusb #localmusicmarathon pic.twitter.com/RVTIIOmVzI    
    
    
    @RachAClark Poor Lenny Kravitz    
    
    
    @theanimalarrg Congratulations on your wedding, Doug! From your friends at WUSB :)    
    
    
    Is he halfway there? "Jon Bon Jovi interested in purchasing the Buffalo Bills http://cbsprt.co/19TfI1l  via @cbssports"    
    
    
    Don't worry fellow #Jets fans, 79 days until pitchers & catchers report! Oh wait, most of us are #Mets fans, too..    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @Newsday Is it really that good?    
    
    
    Sunglasses are like life's Instagram filter.    
    
    
    Are they playing with a football or a hot potato? #HoldOnToTheBall @SNFonNBC    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Billy Joel (8), The Doors (4) & The Rolling Stones (4) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    The only Christmas song I can listen to right now is "Christmas in Hollis"by Run DMC.    
    
    
    It's Christmas time in Hollis Queens, mom's cooking chicken and collard greens!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @dness88 You've been runnin' up that hill!    
    
    
    @cdorso I first read that as "Master of Puppets" :)    
    
    
    Hunger Games: Catching Cold. If you thought Jennifer Lawrence was impressive with a bow, wait until you see her work a tissue!    
    
    
    Five Towns College Put on Probation http://deerpark-northbabylon.patch.com/groups/schools/p/five-towns-college-put-on-probation-deerpark-northbabylon …    
    
    
    @kschreebz from the office of admission :) pic.twitter.com/Srj5DXkFov    
    
    
    I liked Drake better on Degrassi.    
    
    
    @KrissyRubbles I speak truth    
    
    
    @KrissyRubbles Whatever happened to Spinner?    
    
    
    @jayflour @KrissyRubbles Everything changed when he got shot.    
    
    
    Sweet someone just put on Mambo No. 5 on the jukebox!    
    
    
    @SanskarWagley I wonder if you could get that at a Starbucks in Amsterdam.    
    
    
    The worst #BlackFriday experience you will ever witness. 
http://youtu.be/RTRXnuoK1ss     
    
    
    @RobbieRackem Were you live from the studio this morning?    
    
    
    The music from 80s horror films freaks me out. It's cheesily scary!    
    
    
    Getting tons of email this morning from retailers extending their Black Friday deals into Sat. morning....when will it end?!    
    
    
    All of the #NYR players that were in Torts' doghouse are making him pay today! Love it!    
    
    
    GO GET BRONSON ARROYO! #METS    
    
    
    Sometimes I let the sound of my own wheels drive me crazy.    
    
    
    That moment when you leave Iranian airspace #Argo    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: The Rolling Stones (17), Kiss (13) & The Doors (11) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    That had to be the most incompetent half of professional football I've ever seen. #Jets #Dolphins    
    
    
    Geno Smith couldn't hit water jumping out of a boat. Put Simms in. Please! #Jets    
    
    
    How did this team beat the Saints? #jetsnation    
    
    
    I'm shutting off the Jets and turning on the Seawolves.    
    
    
    I bet @ChampsRadioLI wishes they were broadcasting the #Seawolves game today.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov The Knicks are clearly motivated from your viral tweet.    
    
    
    With tonight's @nyknicks loss, @StephenGorchov 's tweet remains accurate. https://twitter.com/StephenGorchov/status/407215323251630081 …    
    
    
    Don't despair, Knicks fans! We're still 3 games out of 1st in the Atlantic!    
    
    
    You will be able to send and receive private messages on Instagram next month. 
http://mashable.com/2013/12/01/instagram-new-messaging-feature/ …    
    
    
    My coworkers are going to be shocked when they see me today.    
    
    
    Sam Champion Leaves ABC News to Join The Weather Channel http://abcnews.go.com/blogs/headlines/2013/12/sam-champion-leaves-abc-news-to-join-the-weather-channel/#.Upyz5-Ey3Z4.twitter … via @abc    
    
    
    @thest0rysofar You can't let the sound of your own wheels drive you crazy. I learned that from The Eagles. :)    
    
    
    I wonder if Talbot is the new #1 goalie against Western Conf. opponents, given Lundqvist's play against them #NYR    
    
    
    “@CloydRivers: United States of College Football. Merica. pic.twitter.com/Mx8pl9t5Y6” New York should be a Seawolf! @stonybrooku    
    
    
    So weird not having long hair any more.    
    
    
    @Trot17 Yes, that's why I updated my profile picture :).    
    
    
    @ArielLAdrian You can do it, Ariel!    
    
    
    @ArielLAdrian Good luck, it's very competitive this year!    
    
    
    How could the Mets non tender @redturn2? Especially after his GUTSY. performance in the 2013 Mets Holiday Card!!! #MetsTwitter    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz Funny, I was grumbling about that this morning during my commute!    
    
    
    The @NYRangers and Billy Joel are both MSG franchises, and both have not had a championship or hit-song in 20 years!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Must be tough for you knowing that Billy Joel is now an MSG team.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Soon - I hear they're going to air Hofstra Wrestling on MSG and boot the Knicks to MSG+2.    
    
    
    @MGHeinz Scenes from a Chinese Restaurant.    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Yankees get Ellsbury while the Mets are still sticker-shocked by moderately priced free agents!    
    
    
    Long live the King! RT @ESPNNewYork Henrik Lundqvist of New York Rangers signed to seven-year extension http://dlvr.it/4RhbLw     
    
    
    Frank Zappa died 20 years ago today. But his spirit lives through his music, which is alive and well.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @KarlaSchuster what did you do?!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @hootsuite Check your settings, there should be a time zone option. It's the gear icon on main sidebar.    
    
    
    My shirt was inside-out and my fly has been open all morning. Not the best start to my day...    
    
    
    @Trot17 thanks :)    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz Your toilet , too.    
    
    
    The tweets are alive with the #SoundofMusic    
    
    
    Carrie Underwood needs an acting double. #SoundofMusic    
    
    
    Someone needs to invent a device that dries your socks while they're still on your feet. #wetsocks    
    
    
        
    
    
    THEY DID SOMETHING! WOO! @Mets    
    
    
    If the United States wins the World Cup, the rest of the world has to call it Soccer.    
    
    
    @kschreebz @StephenGorchov He's flying to Dallas!    
    
    
    @defiantlydutch @StephenGorchov @kschreebz @Mike_Sulls @Cody_Normand It's currently 27 degrees in Dallas with a chance of snow all weekend.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov Mike Woodson to his team before tonight's game: "Hofstra wrestling has more home wins here than us. We HAVE to win!"    
    
    
    On my way to @TheGarden to see Stony Brook play La Salle! There are a lot of #Seawolves fans on the Ronkonkoma line.    
    
    
    Stony Brook vs. La Salle (@ Madison Square Garden - @thegarden w/ 8 others) https://foursquare.com/angelooc/checkin/52a340c2498e2417435b00da?s=iw5ghtz1xBOY1l4fVwASrWIv43c&ref=tw …    
    
    
    Replace @FordhamRams with @HofstraPride for next year's MSG Holiday Festival. @TheGarden    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @KarlaSchuster was he sent to the rafters?    
    
    
    Is there ever a time when there ISN'T traffic on the Van Wyck Expressway?!    
    
    
    @dness88 They're mad too...just lost against Devils in OT. Watch out!    
    
    
    @Rcvryguy @gusjohnson his screaming gets him the big bucks !    
    
    
    @kschreebz was it pepperoni at least?    
    
    
    How can you have Will Ferrell on and not do Celebrity Jeopardy?! #SNL    
    
    
    @WUSBSportsRadio :)...How about the new Garden? It is AMAZING!    
    
    
    @StxV Did Spacehog end their set with In the Meantime?    
    
    
    Making a '90s playlist on Spotify, any recommendations would be appreciated.    
    
    
    Whoever paid to attend today's #Knicks game better get their money back. What a disgrace!    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: The Doors (5), Kiss (5) & Lana Del Rey (5) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    Let it snow!    
    
    
    @imseanavery We need you back! #NYR    
    
    
    Snowing hard in Nassau    
    
    
    Welcome to December! #hofstra #snow https://vine.co/v/hQFw7HE7xwI     
    
    
        
    
    
    @Sid_Madden Great job, Sidney! (and my hair was pretty wild that day too lol)    
    
    
    FB Page publishers: If you're having trouble posting through desktop, try mobile. It's working for me.    
    
    
    Word. RT @AlexJamesFitz: 97, 98, 2003, 2007, 2013 #FiveWordTechHorrors”    
    
    
    French Cafe Charges Rude Customers More Than Double http://eater.cc/1coqHS7  via @Eater    
    
    
    Any chance Instagram gets a "regram" option? Or will that end Instagram as we know it?    
    
    
    @MetalChickSofia For real?!    
    
    
    @MetalChickSofia Wow! Just signed in and saw albums I through IV. This is great news...I wonder if the Beatles follow suit?    
    
    
    Instagram direct is not a Snapchat killer. The photos don't disappear...    
    
    
    @MetalChickSofia True! AC/DC and Tool are still holding out, too. But the addition of Led Zeppelin is HUGE!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov "Pride and Paradise"    
    
    
    Led Zeppelin fans: Houses of the Holy and Physical Graffiti are now on @Spotify, along w/ I - IV.    
    
    
    @AnnikHSpencer Thanks for the follow :)    
    
    
    It's starting to snow in Stony Brook !    
    
    
    On the radioooo! Tune in: http://www.wusb.fm , and yes it's already snowing here in Stony Brook!    
    
    
    Great morning for John Carpenter's "The Fog" as the snow begins to descend on Long Island.    
    
    
    @StxV Yup, mixing up the new with the classic while trying to give snow updates lol. Thanks for tuning in!    
    
    
    Good day for a Curb Your Enthusiasm marathon.    
    
    
    Highly anticipating Rich Mom's Top 10 Records of 2013 list.    
    
    
    @cat_attack deadass?    
    
    
    @cat_attack Now imagine him pulling this off on St. Patricks Day...deadly! lol    
    
    
        
    
    
    I was going to change my pick from Patriots to Dolphins but left that and changed Seattle to Giants, thinking they'd cover. UGH!!!    
    
    
    Never thought I'd hear "Sonic Reducer" in a commercial. @Sonos    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Led Zeppelin (10), Daft Punk (3) & Nine Days (2) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    Is this paid programming or 60 Minutes?    
    
    
    THIS! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0x2E1cyTVBA … 
RT @AlexJamesFitz: Where is Marek Malik when you need him?    
    
    
    The smell of sharpies always brings me back to elementary school.    
    
    
    @RachAClark Only Long Islanders are allowed to complain about high property taxes!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @StephenGorchov #1! :-p    
    
    
    @PeteLabozetta Sunday Night ruined Monday Night.    
    
    
    @kschreebz  there's cake tomorrow?    
    
    
    @kschreebz I'm all about the Hofstra Hall pretzels!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Orange is to Black as Stafford is to Romo. #BALvsDET    
    
    
    This @ESPNMondayNight football season has had a lot of games down to the wire!    
    
    
    @danbonebright thanks :) and thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    There should be an app for my @Keurig machine. #coffee    
    
    
    If "Plan A" didn't work, there are 25 more letters in the alphabet.    
    
    
    Things I miss from 2003: Nextel push-to-talk. BEEP BEEP    
    
    
    Hofstra students #flashmob the library singing "The Lion Sleeps Tonight" during finals week. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kx7qvD3BBe8 …    
    
    
    Hey @BorowitzReport, would you work with NBC to do a spin-off series on "The Guys Who Were Up To No Good" in Will Smith's neighborhood?    
    
    
    @kschreebz @RaquelCona Is this why you two were late to the party?!    
    
    
    @NeilSchloth Did you happen to get a sunset picture today?    
    
    
    @NeilSchloth You rock!!!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov How do you hate cats considering where we work?!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov @KarlaSchuster your criticism was dead on    
    
    
    I wasn't the biggest John Oliver fan but I will miss him. #DailyShow    
    
    
    Cheering loudly for grads with no families present at @goofy_stance's commencement. Congrats bro! @FarmingdaleSC    
    
    
    Tough commencement crowd. No courtesy clapping for every graduate. Some names are met with total silence.    
    
    
    Today feels more like the first day of summer. Nature has it backwards today!    
    
    
    If you change for the haters you'll disappoint the lovers.    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov What's The Phanatic Say http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ONCYHSgxhVs …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just saw Anchorman 2: The marketing was much better than the movie!    
    
    
    I muted JT and put on Ozzy Osbourne. #SNL    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Billy Joel (11), The Beatles Tribute Band (10) & Kiss (8) #tweeklyfm http://bit.ly/aRzr5F     
    
    
    I want to see Rex Ryan host SNL. Make this happen, please. @nbcsnl @SNLUpdate @SNL_Mexico    
    
    
    @tehlizz nice corset!    
    
    
    I hope @MikeFrancesaNY is the SNL host during Super Bowl weekend. It would only make sense! @nbcsnl    
    
    
    Visit the New York City Spots Where Famous Album Cover Photos Were Taken http://ultimateclassicrock.com/new-york-city-album-cover-locations/ …    
    
    
    Don't infringe on my rights to celebrate new holidays! #Festivus    
    
    
    Twitter has turned the Airing of Grievances into an everyday tradition. #festivus #seinfeld    
    
    
    Since seeing Anchorman 2, I have Thunder Island and Ride like the Wind stuck in my head. #yachtrock    
    
    
    If you're wearing a blue polo with dark pants inside @BestBuy, don't get mad if people think you work there!    
    
    
    FINALLY! #nyr    
    
    
    Long Islanders: Here are photos from the @SmithHavenMall from the summer of 1990. http://www.retronaut.com/2011/03/shopping-malls-usa/ …    
    
    
    This is going to make a great episode of HBO 24/7. I hope they got all this! #NYR    
    
    
        
    
    
    7 fishes! #christmaseve #dinner http://instagram.com/p/iVBbNZnZPq/     
    
    
    @Nagler #joytothenagler    
    
    
    @Nagler you're welcome    
    
    
    @Nagler I forgot the smiley at the end of that last tweet! Lol merry Christmas!    
    
    
    FYI - it's COLD outside!    
    
    
    @sms1998 someone had to tweet it :). Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    Looks like I was on the naughty list! #christmaspresent pic.twitter.com/z7fVUUHjdR    
    
    
    Not even a Miracle on 34 St. could save the Knicks today. -_-    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hooray! Now that the holiday season is over, we will no longer hear the Hoodie Footie Pajamagram radio commercials!    
    
    
    Guns N' Roses with the original lineup.  #2014ConcertWish @Slash @axlrose    
    
    
    Here Are All The Movies Expiring On Netflix As Of January 1st  http://gothamist.com/2013/12/27/here_are_all_the_movies_expiring_on.php …    
    
    
    I love that the Verizon Center organist plays the Law and Order theme when the #Caps get a power play.    
    
    
    @StxV @NYRangers I wish I could rt that!    
    
    
    I feel for the community managers of the @nyknicks social media team. These are tough times for them...    
    
    
    I don't like Louisville fans. #Hofstra    
    
    
    @AR1EL_A @AMCTheatres You can order food at the movies now?    
    
    
    @tehlizz sounds like you're at commiskys?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AR1EL_A Amazing!    
    
    
    @StephenGorchov 118 RTs..this has to be a @HofstraPride record!    
    
    
    @RachAClark you'll always have your memories and Facebook newsfeed updates :)    
    
    
    “@BuzzFeedSports: The horror … RT @justRVB: This is not a Rams game. It's WAS vs. NYG at MetLife pic.twitter.com/akaYH1JYE0” // wow!    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz that's called a  "stopper" on Long Island.    
    
    
    @AlexJamesFitz mandator thing for drive through Starbucks orders :)    
    
    
    This is the best thing ever. Snoop Dogg doing Gin and Juice, Hancock style! #KCHonors    
    
    
        
    
    
    Don't yell at your University's Twitter account if your grades aren't up. That's on your professor!    
    
    
    Brainlike Computers, Learning From Experience http://nyti.ms/Kcdt3Z     
    
    
    I was about to go to bed but then Joe Cocker's With A Little Help From My Friends came on. So now I need to listen to that! #wonderyears    
    
    
    The Wonder Years, they don't make great shows like that any more.    
    
    
    FLURRIES IN NESCONSET NY#LongIsland    
    
    
    Worst night to be a bartender, especially if you're working an open bar! You have my sympathies...    
    
    
        
    
    
    @EmilieEYonan Don't forget hockey!    
    
    
    Long Islanders w/ 516 and 631 area codes were not affected in Snapchat breach.  http://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/1u53oh/off_snapchat_got_hacked_all_username_and_phone/ …    
    
    
    The red and blue uniforms reminds me of Blades of Steel. #WinterClassic pic.twitter.com/IkKlzrYbAL    
    
    
    I'm predicting the final score to be 8-6, Red Wings. #WinterClassic    
    
    
    Starting the new year with some fine cuisine! #ocotopus pic.twitter.com/yy1ZZTjDru    
    
    
        
    
    
    KNICKS TAPE!    
    
    
    Watching Kenan and Kel on Teen Nick. Holy nostalgia!    
    
    
    Kenan saves the President Clinton's life after pushing him out of the way from a castle of orange soda cans!    
    
    
    