Het is maar een naar ding: barbecueverbodsbord #vondelpark http://at5.nl/s/hj8 #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Kora's Place http://4sq.com/oB1u17    
    
    
    Google crashes when googling "123456..123456" http://www.google.com/?q=123456..123456 … http://twitpic.com/6eirn6  (via @goncalcalvo). #fb    
    
    
    #clef2011 has started!    
    
    
    @mdr introduces the first keynote speaker, Elaine Toms #clef2011    
    
    
    Lunch! #clef2011    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer jah! Running smoothly.. so far  (knocks on wood) :-)    
    
    
    W00t! There's no way back now :). Hoe interpreteert een zoekmachine een zoekvraag? - Universiteit van Amsterdam http://www.uva.nl/actueel/agenda.cfm/074D127C-5CB6-4433-A4DCE6B805C7AC77?sms_ss=twitter&at_xt=4cfe967aabc0b5ac,0 … #fb    
    
    
    Impressed with @HyperDock for the Mac. From window previews to snapping, very useful. This should be included in Mac OS by default IMO    
    
    
    70% vd Marketing managers noemen "explosie aan data en opkomst van Social Media" als grootste uitdagingen. Kom maar op! http://bit.ly/nIhsF4     
    
    
    Dr. Weerkamp? http://yfrog.com/mf2gzij     
    
    
    I want it. Now. http://www.google.com/nexus/  @googlenexus #fb    
    
    
    Nice read: Interview with Google's director of research on their search algorithms http://www.stonetemple.com/search-algorithms-with-google-director-of-research-peter-norvig/ …    
    
    
    My WSDM paper "Adding Semantics to Microblogs" has been accepted! See http://bit.ly/q6Mo6m     
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer goed man! Well done :-)    
    
    
    @samanos nice, congrats!    
    
    
    Geestig: kom er net pas achter dat mijn proefschrift een jaar geleden vermeld werd in de Automatisering Gids, zie http://www.automatiseringgids.nl/nieuws/2010/47/promovendus-maakt-zoekmachines-slimmer … #fb    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog Nice! Care to send me a preprint? I'm curious :-)    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog yes, I'm curious ;-)    
    
    
    @gerdiend: Hora est! http://yfrog.com/gzi01pj #fb    
    
    
    Two ECIR papers accepted! A Framework for Unsupervised Spam Detection in Social Networking Sites: http://bit.ly/mZ5Kl9  ...    
    
    
    ... and Adaptive Temporal Query Modeling (poster), http://bit.ly/qpRYp2 .    
    
    
    @dvdgrs PhD @ UvA? http://ilps.science.uva.nl/news/four-phd-positions …    
    
    
    @dvdgrs Denk dat met name een van de Semantic Search plekken interessant voor je zijn... Laat maar weten als je vragen hebt!    
    
    
    Android 2.2, nice http://is.gd/chYTe    
    
    
    @leesmeemetdejee ik zeg, #albatros    
    
    
    Vakantiegeld, nice :-)    
    
    
    I'm at Bar Brandstof‎ (Marnixstraat 341, Amsterdam) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/70OB5W    
    
    
    #Apache #OpenNLP v 1.5.2 is out! Some new features, improvements and bug fixes. http://incubator.apache.org/opennlp/download.cgi … #nlproc #java    
    
    
    I'm at Healthclub Jordaan (1e rozendwarsstraat 10, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/cLAl0H    
    
    
    I'm at Noordwest (Noordermarkt 41, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/51TN4g    
    
    
    Preprint of my WSDM paper, 'Adding Semantics to Microblog Posts' available now: http://bit.ly/q6Mo6m . Resources will follow soon.    
    
    
    @SamsungMobileNL oppakken lukt niet! #nexushunt    
    
    
    I'm at Caffe Milo (Linnaeusstraat 71, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/bt6hIN    
    
    
    Friday 23 december 2012, Inbox: 0. Time for holidays :-)    
    
    
    @damiano10 Fijne kerstdagen! :)    
    
    
    @damiano10 ¡dos cervezas!    
    
    
    @Judithtiduj nog zo een: 
http://www.nytimes.com/2010/05/30/magazine/30Mayor-t.html    
    
    
    Promotion date is set! 10 Dec 2010, 10:00 AM    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos ja, maar 14:00 23-12-2010 is natuurlijk niet zo mooi als 10:00 10-12-2010 :-)    
    
    
    My Information Processing & Management paper is finally available! See http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.ipm.2009.09.005.    
    
    
    Wat zal de invloed zijn van het twitter debat vanavond op de VK Twitter monitor? #rtldebat http://bit.ly/b6Suv0    
    
    
    Hadoop 1.0.0 has arrived! #in http://hadoop.apache.org/common/releases.html#News …    
    
    
    Dataset (tweets + manual Wikipedia annotations) for my WSDM '12 paper "Adding Semantics to Microblog Posts" released. http://bit.ly/A7yJoZ     
    
    
    I'm at Louter Café Restaurant (De Clercqstraat 82, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/8zxbsJ    
    
    
    iPhone 4 makes me want to trade in my Nexus One. Almost. http://bit.ly/9z33Nn    
    
    
    Get early access to DataSift's Twitter archive http://datasift.com/historic?ref=ceh … via @DataSift    
    
    
    A comparison of five semantic linking algorithms on tweets http://bit.ly/zRrKvX     
    
    
    Stephen Wolfram is accelerating the birth of the data web, by promoting a .data Top-Level Internet Domain. http://blog.stephenwolfram.com/2012/01/a-data-top-level-internet-domain/ …    
    
    
    @nathanmarz Trying to order your book, but "The coupon code you have entered has expired." :(    
    
    
    LOL "NS adviseert niet met de trein te reizen." Da's net zoiets als AH die mensen afraadt boodschappen te doen :-). http://bit.ly/g7IIZo #fb    
    
    
    @nathanmarz Cheers!    
    
    
    ECIR preprints are available now. One on adaptive query modeling, the other on unsupervised spam detection. http://bit.ly/ygndzG  #fb    
    
    
    LREC 2012 Workshop on Language Engineering for Online Reputation Management http://bit.ly/wGh6Le     
    
    
    @suzan zou ie ook why questions doen? :)

The Watson Trivia Challenge: Play against I.B.M.’s question-answering supercomputer. - http://cot    
    
    
    @pogil Did you chateau des charm them? :) Congrats!    
    
    
    Jas verwisseld! Wie heeft mijn zwarte jas met handschoenen meegenomen uit de pancakes? Ik heb de jouwe... please RT #blup    
    
    
    @amazingamazone @ParisVanDerValk Dat zou super chill zijn. Is het een zwarte wollen, half lang?    
    
    
    @ParisVanDerValk Jammer! En ja, de mijne ook :-(. Infobalie heeft 'm niet, misschien morgen.. #blup    
    
    
    #Bungalup was top, maar mijn jas is nog steeds kwijt. Heb een @centerparcs telnr gekregen maar dat is "niet in gebruik" WTF @Valtifest #blup    
    
    
    Net klaar met mijn praatje voor de @KLPD Internet Masterclass. Was leuk, kreeg goede vragen. Nu snel terug naar A dam om college te geven...    
    
    
    RIP Whitney Houston...    
    
    
    New blog post: Zoekmachines van de toekomst http://bit.ly/zrRS1U     
    
    
    LOL. The fellowship of the vuvuzela / http://youtu.be/7B2LPxggvqY    
    
    
    Forget Siri; Upcoming Android app 'Utter!' takes speech-to-text to a whole new level. http://bit.ly/yxZy3B  #fb    
    
    
    LREC 2012 Workshop on Language Engineering for Online Reputation Management http://bit.ly/wGh6Le     
    
    
    LOL For all the geeks among us: Java 4-Ever Trailer / http://youtu.be/A1zySeNpW20    
    
    
    @dvdgrs dat is geen precision-recall graph :)    
    
    
    @dvdgrs dit zijn precision-recall grafieken: http://nlp.stanford.edu/IR-book/html/htmledition/evaluation-of-ranked-retrieval-results-1.html …    
    
    
    Ski = amazing! #onemoreday #fb pic.twitter.com/AKrq3TF5    
    
    
    Naaimachine ging draaien, tub tub tub en dan draait ie en dan zit ie er gewoon in!!? 

http://youtu.be/aPlVNmuHVms    
    
    
    Stack Exchange Q&A site proposal: Information Retrieval and Search Engines http://bit.ly/GOsocM  #fb    
    
    
    @Marijejans Inderdaad, bijkletsen met een biertje is hoog nodig ;-). Tot vanavond!    
    
    
    Het Nederlands elftal wordt ondanks de verloren finale toch gehuldigd met rondvaart. http://bit.ly/aJWtPA    
    
    
    Structured Data: "Wikimedia Proposes Wikidata Project" http://wp.me/p1mjr5-3Ls  via @infodocket    
    
    
    In 2010, Google developed self-driving cars. Now these can navigate a fast food drive-through. This is human progress. http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2012/03/28/googles-driverless-cars-can-now-fetch-food/ …    
    
    
    A Corpus for Entity Profiling in Microblog Posts http://bit.ly/GYx6Ir  #fb    
    
    
    I'll be giving a talk on Large-scale Data Processing for Information Retrieval at the Dutch Hadoop User Group meetup! http://meetu.ps/84W9q     
    
    
    @krisztianbalog nice, congrats!    
    
    
    I'm at Pompstation (Zeeburgerdijk 52, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/6W3flG    
    
    
    @wmijn da's heeeel lang geleden ;). Alles prima, al helpt het weer ook :). Hoe is het met jou?    
    
    
    @wmijn eerst proefschrift afmaken, dan vakantie :). Maar eerst congres in Geneve. Jij bijna op weg naar la france zie ik?    
    
    
    I'm at Schiphol gate C12. http://4sq.com/9Tdggg    
    
    
    It was a fun #nlhug meeting! Thanks @eevrt. My slides are online: Large-scale Data Processing for IR - http://www.slideshare.net/edgar.meij/largescale-data-processing-for-information-retrieval-nlhug … #in    
    
    
    @eevrt Doing what? :)    
    
    
    @eevrt cool! I'll have a look at the job later this week...    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer wij hebben dr wel een? Tis geen opwerper, maar snel is ie wel:)    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Ja hoor, zit in een handig tassie. Tot morgen!    
    
    
    I'll be giving a talk on semantic search in the context of e-discovery at the "Symposium Ontdek E-Discovery" next week. http://www.hva.nl/e-discovery     
    
    
    Use SVR to predict readability level for summarization http://bit.ly/bi1VjL #sigir2010    
    
    
    Term position and proximity evidence helps pseudo relevance feedback on web collections http://bit.ly/9ST2pA #sigir2010    
    
    
    LOL: RT @LoesjeNL **BREIN denkt nog dat je inbraken kunt voorkomen . .  door schroevendraaiers te verbieden** http://www.mobypicture.com/user/loesjeNL/view/12554021 … #loesje    
    
    
    @visualisingdata where/what do you need?    
    
    
    @wmijn goeie vakantie!    
    
    
    Revised journal of web semantics paper submitted! #eindelijkweekend #fb    
    
    
    Hmm, wit bier... (@ Noorderlicht) http://4sq.com/6fgIJI    
    
    
    @visualisingdata Ah. My faculty isn't in the center of AMS, so I can't really help, sorry. Perhaps a hotel or something similar?    
    
    
    If you've got a few free moments :-) "Ten of the greatest: Maths puzzles" http://bit.ly/c9PgVA #fb    
    
    
    A new kind of time travel gets around the paradoxes that have plagued other time machines. http://bit.ly/cj2NBg #fb    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Haha, ja, had 'm al gezien ;)    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Tuurlijk schat! Dansje leggen op het Amstelveld was het plan toch?    
    
    
    LOL RT @AT5 Op de Geldersekade heeft parkeerbeheer het zekere voor het onzekere genomen bij deze auto. http://at5.nl/s/bNm    
    
    
    @damiano10 beer?    
    
    
    Yahoo! Japan to adopt Google's search engine http://bit.ly/aqgxm0 #fb    
    
    
    Our SIGIR poster "Identifying Entity Aspects in Microblog Posts" (w/ Damiano Spina et al.) has been accepted! http://bit.ly/JFPhDf  #in    
    
    
    Today is System Administrator Appreciation Day. See http://xkcd.com/705/ and http://www.SysAdminDay.com/ #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Struik (Rozengracht 160, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/6vzN3Q    
    
    
    Recent PhD comics are right on point :) http://bit.ly/91PcsJ #fb    
    
    
    Nice, accessible post on IR/document ranking in general and at eBay in particular http://wp.me/prDub-9B  via @hughewilliams    
    
    
    Yep, we're getting there... Google's Knowledge Graph: searching for things instead of words http://insidesearch.blogspot.com/2012/05/introducing-knowledge-graph-things-not.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I'll be giving a talk on semantic linking for Twitter at the CognAC Artificial Intelligence symposium next Tue (May 22) http://bit.ly/LVkUYZ     
    
    
    A visual diary documenting a transatlantic flight. Yep, very recognizable... http://nyti.ms/9dQj0F #fb    
    
    
    The Ultimate Google I/O 2012 Preview http://www.androidpolice.com/2012/05/29/the-ultimate-google-io-2012-preview/ … via @AndroidPolice    
    
    
    Nice! Our project is featuring in a Spanish magazine :). RT @JulioGonzalo1 Nuestro proyecto Limosine en El Pais Semanal
http://www.slideshare.net/LLORENTEYCUENCA/twitter-una-mina-sociolgica-13101693 …    
    
    
    @JulioGonzalo1 I stand corrected ;-)    
    
    
    LOL The illustrated guide to a Ph.D. http://bit.ly/a683CR #fb    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Have fun!    
    
    
    ROFL, PhD comics hits the nail on the head again: http://www.phdcomics.com/comics.php?f=1354 #fb    
    
    
    Visualizing user interests changing over time, based on Twitter search queries: http://engineering.twitter.com/2012/06/studying-rapidly-evolving-user.html ….    
    
    
    Bad day for LinkedIn: 6.5 million hashed passwords reportedly leaked – change yours now http://tnw.to/1EhVs     
    
    
    Waarom maakt de westerkerk geen geluid meer? Zowel de klokken als het carillon doen het niet meer... @AT5 #durftevragen    
    
    
    Google's Hybrid Approach to Research | July 2012 | Communications of the ACM: http://bit.ly/KYiTuj     
    
    
    @Dropbox website and webservice down.. #fail    
    
    
    5 Ways Semantic Search Will Disrupt Business - Forbes http://onforb.es/LE0xhI     
    
    
    De Anne Frankboom is zojuist omgewaaid. http://at5.nl/s/ccK #fb    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos het was GAY-NIAAL!! hoe was jou O&N?    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos hangt van je client af...    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos twitterclient.. telefoon? Web?    
    
    
    Nice: The first ever Digital Camera (Kodak, 1975) - http://nyti.ms/czD34h #fb    
    
    
    Nice patterns: Church or Beer? Americans on Twitter (via @samanos) http://www.floatingsheep.org/2012/07/church-or-beer-americans-on-twitter.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Leap second troubles and how to fix them...   http://www.cloudera.com/blog/2012/07/watching-the-clock-clouderas-response-to-leap-second-troubles/ … via @cloudera    
    
    
    I'm not a mobile app UI designer, but if I were, I'd use http://www.fluidui.com/ . A very nice, live UI mock up designer made in HTML5.    
    
    
    PhD thesis has been sent to the committee! Kan wel janken #fb    
    
    
    I've decided to put some of the Hadoop code I developed for the TREC KBA task online, see http://bit.ly/OepyE1     
    
    
    @eevrt And this was only a single month worth of data ;).    
    
    
    @eevrt Step one: 239k mappers for 5 months of data. Let's see how that goes.    
    
    
    .@eevrt Running the #TREC #KBA toy example system on all data (381m docs in 353k mappers/thrift files), 1.2T ("cleansed-only") in ~1 hour :)    
    
    
    @eevrt This *is* the full batch :). Or do you mean the non-cleaned version?    
    
    
    Some Fresh Twitter Stats (as of July 2012, Dataset Included) http://post.ly/8ZK0v     
    
    
    LOL Man arrested at Large Hadron Collider claims he's from the future http://bit.ly/cirldW #fb    
    
    
    "We are pleased to inform you that your paper has been accepted..." http://researchinprogress.tumblr.com/post/33884075941/we-are-pleased-to-inform-you-that-your-paper-has-been …    
    
    
    How Ebay uses big data to improve recommendations (and more) http://www.zdnet.com/au/how-ebay-uses-big-data-to-make-you-buy-more-7000006498/ …    
    
    
    Scaling up Dynamic Time Warping, i.e., "Mining Time-series with Trillions of Points" http://practicalquant.blogspot.com/2012/10/mining-time-series-with-trillions-of.html …    
    
    
    OpenGeist, a RESTful API for accessing page view counts information of Wikipedia articles: http://www.opengeist.org/  and http://edgar.meij.pro/opengeist-insight-stream-page-views-wikipedia/ …    
    
    
    Ellen is introducing the TREC KBA track: filter a (big!) stream of documents, based on relevance to an entity http://ow.ly/f5Niw  #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC2013: 2 new tracks (Federated search and Temporal summarization), 1 new collection (ClueWeb12), and 1 rename: Real-time search #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC KBA overview starting.. #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC KBA 2013 possible directions: incorporate events, pharmaceutical compounds, and/or combine with the TAC KBP track #trec2012    
    
    
    Data-driven voter analytics and predictions: the big data crunchers who helped Obama win http://ti.me/Uj7o9o  via @TIMEPolitics    
    
    
    Ellen presenting an overview of the TREC Medical track.. The track won't be continuing due to data/privacy considerations #trec2012    
    
    
    @mounialalmas "balance between eﬀectiveness (gains across queries) and robustness (minimizing possibility of signiﬁcant failure)" #trec2012    
    
    
    Track sessions starting. First up: Medical and Web (in parallel). #trec2012    
    
    
    @bevan_koopman Indeed. Getting a proper medical records dataset is not a trivial task though..    
    
    
    Atigeo find that using (the text of) report-level ICD-9 codes help in retrieving medical records #trec2012    
    
    
    DCU obtain best performance using only BM25 on TREC Medical '11 and '12 test collections. (Unweighted) query expansion hurts. #trec2012    
    
    
    @leifos Indeed, BM25 pwnage. Too bad there aren't more TREC approaches/tracks using it as a default baseline.    
    
    
    UDel / @zhudq uses mixture of relevance models for TREC-Med. Seems reminiscent of external expansion (@fdiaz_msr SIGIR '06) #trec2012    
    
    
    @bencarterette @zhudq There you go :). Interesting twist including MeSH in the collections though. Did that make a (significant) difference?    
    
    
    UTD find sign. improvements using (heuristic) assertions for adhoc reranking. Sounds a bit like hedging (Medlock & Briscoe ACL'07) #trec2012    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries best for theirs :). I think UDel did quite well overall, but can't recall the exact ranking of participating systems.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries Did you participate in TREC-Medical also?    
    
    
    .@ssn There's little info on the TREC 2013 Temporal Summarization track online; here's a photo of the poster #trec2012 http://ow.ly/i/16Hzl     
    
    
    TREC 2013 Planning sessions starting... #trec2012    
    
    
    Two candidate goals for TREC KBA 2013: (i) improve sensitivity, (ii) explore temporality. #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC-KBA '13 also considering detecting (first mentions of) "adverse reactions" to pharmaceutical compounds. TREC-KBA-Medical? #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC 2013 Temporal Summarization, Real-time, and KBA tracks will probably use (a subset of) the same document collection #trec2012    
    
    
    New shared document collection *probably* TREC-KBA '12 with some additions (Twitter & FB from Spinn3r) and exclusions (bit.ly) #trec2012    
    
    
    @JeffD talking about bidirectional entity linking, combining KBA and KBP - good stuff #trec2012 pic.twitter.com/eL3luHbP    
    
    
    TREC 2013 summary http://bit.ly/UdNSoE  #trec2012    
    
    
    Lots of alignments between tracks. ClueWeb12 for cont.sugg., crowds., and web. KBA for realtime, kba, and  (possibly) realtime #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC Temporal Summarization 2013 is now online: http://www.trec-ts.org/  (website) and https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups#!forum/temporalsummarization2013 … (Google group) #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC Web 2013: New collection and new coordinators (MS). Also: diversity replaced by risk-sensitive task, safely reranking results #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC Web 2013 Risk-sensitive task: increase effectiveness over all (or most) queries. Determine when/how to change/improve results #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC Web 2013 Risk-sensitive task: combine difficulty prediction/classification with reranking (e.g., pseudo-relevance feedback) #trec2012    
    
    
    LOL! Industry vs. Academia http://tmblr.co/Zuxy3uX2KKYl  via @ResearchInP    
    
    
    Scaling Deep Learning @ Google.. SMT, ASR, and Image classification: all pretty cool stuff.  http://techtalks.tv/talks/57639/     
    
    
    LOL :). Someone in the audience points out a practical application for my research http://tmblr.co/Zuxy3uXJoDe0  via @ResearchInP    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries Re: Countries ranked by ease... With NL having the highest score for the category "Closing a Business." Go figure :)    
    
    
    Best plan for generating startup ideas: "Live in the future, then build what's missing." http://paulgraham.com/startupideas.html …    
    
    
    Battling against the state of the art.. http://researchinprogress.tumblr.com/post/36417281882/battling-against-the-state-of-the-art …    
    
    
    Getting ready for the defense of the soon-to-be-dr @simoncarter http://yfrog.com/esft2kcj     
    
    
    And now @samanos is getting ready/nervous http://yfrog.com/ocfo3eej     
    
    
    Interesting and very applicable: "Practical machine learning tricks from the KDD 2011 best industry paper" #ml http://blog.david-andrzejewski.com/machine-learning/practical-machine-learning-tricks-from-the-kdd-2011-best-industry-paper/ …    
    
    
    "More than 200M individual profiles based on what we browse and buy online." Who do online advertisers think we are? http://nyti.ms/X8z0yP     
    
    
    @UPC Geen internet, geen telefoon. Reset helpt niet. #UPC klantenservice via mobiel ook geen gehoor... What gives?    
    
    
    LOL! Go to Google maps, bring up directions from Japan to China and look at instruction number 43. #fb RT @TheFagCasanova    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer @YInspiration @ellenemonds Geestig... Wij noemen dat "Just in Time Teaching" op de universiteit :). http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Just_in_Time_Teaching …    
    
    
    Steun @Chrisbelloni z'n nieuwe film over de Turkse boot op de gay pride! Crowdfunding campagne @ http://www.cinecrowd.nl/de-turkse-boot     
    
    
    Ik stond in de NRC afgelopen zaterdag! Hier een scan en een tekst versie van het artikel “Een bril die alles weet.” http://bit.ly/Xx8dXD     
    
    
    @sies22 Thanks!    
    
    
    .@ian_soboroff We're currently at 68.89M. And counting. :)    
    
    
    Friday afternoon && inbox 0. Perfect time to head for @samanos in Berlin together w/ Wouter and @simonccarter    
    
    
    Our paper "Feeding the Second Screen..." (w/ @dodijk and @mdr) has been accepted as full paper at OAIR 2013. http://edgar.meij.pro/feeding-screen-semantic-linking-based-subtitles …    
    
    
    @aaranged thanks for your interest! Will do..    
    
    
    @JanHilverda Morgenochtend 8:30 Starbucks op de Ramblas? ;)    
    
    
    @JanHilverda Geen idee, maar dat leek me wel een schappelijke tijd ;-). 20:30 maar doen dan?    
    
    
    @JanHilverda Inderdaad. Laten we dat maar doen dan :).    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Yep, thanks!    
    
    
    Our paper "Using Temporal Bursts for Query Modeling" (with @mariahendrike and @mdr) has been accepted for IRJ! http://edgar.meij.pro/temporal-bursts-query-modeling/?utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos mooie dag om op de bank te zitten dus. Voor een sportliefhebber :)    
    
    
    #sigir2013 full paper notifications are coming in. Score: one paper in and one out, not bad..    
    
    
    CLEF RepLab 2013 Call for Participation and guidelines are now online, see http://limosine-project.eu/events/replab2013 …    
    
    
    @giusepperizzo @damiano10 @www2013rio Apparently the deadline has been extended? I hate rushing for no reason :(.    
    
    
    Our tutorial "Entity Linking and Retrieval" (with @krisztianbalog and @dodijk) has been accepted for #SIGIR2013!    
    
    
    @www2013rio Heh, according to this, Yahoo! Research now has a lab in The Netherlands? I'm actually in Barcelona, ES.. http://www2013.org/2013/04/15/13th-tutorial-11-entity-linking-and-retrieval/ …    
    
    
    @www2013rio thanks!    
    
    
    @abdoelali You mean like https://wavii.com/ ?    
    
    
    @abdoelali I don't know, in that case probably not. So make it yourself! Procrastination++ ;-)    
    
    
    @abdoelali Hehe, exactly ;-).    
    
    
    @larsmans_nl WAT? :-) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kXEgk1Hdze0 …    
    
    
    Slides, code and biblio for our #WWW2013 "Entity Linking and Retrieval" tutorial are now online: http://ejmeij.github.io/entity-linking-and-retrieval-tutorial/ …    
    
    
    Krisztian (@krisztianbalog) talking about entity retrieval #WWW2013 pic.twitter.com/YLLx8LvTfB    
    
    
    Me talking about entity linking :-) #WWW2013 http://flic.kr/p/eiWYEb     
    
    
    @dvdgrs @dodijk @TomKenter Net gepitched, nog anderhalf uur wachten op de uitslag ;-) pic.twitter.com/VLCp0csj1c    
    
    
    @dvdgrs @dodijk @TomKenter Any ideas how to share an iPad amongst four people?    
    
    
    @dvdgrs @dodijk @TomKenter Ladies and gentlemen.. We got him.    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog Excellent decision ;-)    
    
    
    Nice! Our Semantic TED demo won the #WoLE2013 "Doing Good by Linking Entities" Challenge! #WWW2013 http://wole2013.eurecom.fr/challenge     
    
    
    @dvdgrs Cheerful screenshot :-)    
    
    
    This paper describes our (winning!) approach to the "Doing Good by Linking Entities" Challenge @ #WoLE2013 #WWW2013 http://edgar.meij.pro/multilingual-semantic-linking-video-streams-making-ideas-worth-sharing-accessible/?utm_source=bit.ly&utm_medium=linked&utm_campaign=twitter …    
    
    
    Is it me, or are some of the PDF files on the #WWW2013 USB stick corrupted? I've tried two sticks, both with the same result...    
    
    
    Third time lucky, @YashMosh's USB disk does work :-). #WWW2013    
    
    
    @evelinamorim No, just some of them – really weird. Anyway, I have them now, all is good.    
    
    
    @mzurko Just some of them – really weird. Anyway, I have them now, all is good :-). Thanks!    
    
    
    @McHildebrand Yes, but we want to keep it under wraps for the time being. If you send me an email, I'll reply with the URL..    
    
    
    Hey, that's me! #WWW2013 http://flic.kr/p/ejxxY5     
    
    
    Semantic e-mails, pretty cool: Gmail now supports JSON-LD and Microdata to markup information in email. https://developers.google.com/gmail/schemas/embedding-schemas-in-emails …    
    
    
    @nc2y Yep, for me only the third USB stick worked. You can find the same contents online though: http://www2013.org/papers/     
    
    
    @NS_online wow, zonetaxi #fail. 20 minuten staan wachten, geen taxi. Gebeld, "komt eraan," en toen "rit onbekend." Toen maar de bus gepakt.    
    
    
    Tried to get #Uber car in A'dam but 20 mins wait was too long. Received: "added €10 in your account to make up for the inconvenience" Nice.    
    
    
    Some very interesting titles/abstracts to bid on for #CIKM2013. Seemingly interesting though, let's wait for the actual papers first :-).    
    
    
    Entity linking for the masses/webdevs: Google's (wrapper induction based) Data Highlighter now supports 6 more types http://searchengineland.com/googles-data-highlighter-supports-6-new-data-types-160320 …    
    
    
    Duolingo Android app is here; excellent online language learning, now made mobile. Oh, and it's fun too! http://www.androidpolice.com/2013/05/29/duolingo-releases-android-app-brings-free-language-learning-on-the-go/ …    
    
    
    Creative: Flickr adding a link to job postings for engineers/designers in the source code of redesigned main page. http://on.mash.to/13fFqf3     
    
    
    Google (@egabrilovich) releases automatic Freebase annotations for TREC MQ and Web Track queries: http://bit.ly/ZxpB69  - via @ipeirotis    
    
    
    @djoerd @suzan on which query logs do you base this observation?    
    
    
    @KLM Trying to book/check in an exit row seat (29B) for KL2288 on 23 Jun, but keep getting "Your seat selection failed" error. What gives?    
    
    
    @KLM Done.    
    
    
    RDF Search Engine Glimmer Released by Yahoo. See http://bit.ly/12ehki5  and http://glimmer.research.yahoo.com/     
    
    
    Very compact language detection with code extracted from Google Chromium (via @dvdgrs):  http://blog.mikemccandless.com/2011/10/language-detection-with-googles-compact.html … and https://code.google.com/p/chromium-compact-language-detector/ …    
    
    
    All the world are belong to us, the Dutch. Hypothetically. http://what-if.xkcd.com/53/  (via @arjenpdevries)    
    
    
    Work–life balance of scientists: working during weekends has been increasing since 2005 (based on JASIST submissions) http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/asi.22888/abstract …    
    
    
    Interesting, Google does poems :-) http://www.googlepoetics.com/     
    
    
    @mounialalmas nice, well done!    
    
    
    Using Twitter Cards for SEO: hadn't realised this was so easy...  http://searchengineland.com/use-twitter-cards-for-branding-local-seo-166388?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=feed-main …    
    
    
    Introducing new travel-related Yahoo! image search results from Getty images http://yahoosearch.tumblr.com/post/55191648187/introducing-beautiful-new-travel-related-yahoo-image …    
    
    
    This may be the best scientific paper abstract ever written: http://io9.com/this-may-be-the-best-scientific-paper-abstract-ever-wri-729221070 …    
    
    
    Google: 88% of traffic generated by mobile search ads is not replaced by traffic from mobile organic search http://googleresearch.blogspot.com/2013/07/new-research-from-google-shows-that-88.html …    
    
    
    The verb "unfriend" actually dates back to 1659 :-) – "Five words that are older than you think" http://blog.oxforddictionaries.com/2013/06/5-words-that-are-older-than-you-think/ …    
    
    
    Gorgeous new Google Maps UI now open to everyone, although you do need to opt-in: http://www.google.com/maps/about/explore/ … http://searchengineland.com/new-google-maps-now-open-to-all-no-invite-needed-167002 …    
    
    
    WhatsApp “Bigger Than Twitter”: over 200M monthly users, 8B inbound and 12B outbound messages daily  http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/16/whatsapp-bigger-than-twitter-with-over-200m-monthly-active-users-8b-inbound-and-12b-outbound-messages-daily/ …    
    
    
    Bing's new Autosuggest expands to take on instant search with a knowledge graph in one go http://sewat.ch/12BuPtP     
    
    
    Nice intro to Semantic Search basics: http://searchengineland.com/leveraging-search-algorithms-in-a-semantic-search-world-166815 …    
    
    
    LOL: NSA says it can’t search its own emails http://www.propublica.org/article/nsa-says-it-cant-search-own-emails … (via @suzan)    
    
    
    Someone finally tested the prisoner's dilemma on actual prisoners — and the results were not what you would expect... http://www.businessinsider.com/prisoners-dilemma-in-real-life-2013-7 …    
    
    
    Yahoo, Alibaba and why Mayer can keep buying whatever she wants: "Go crazy, Mayer" :)
 http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/r_lQq_bRyZM/ …    
    
    
    Interesting: Chromecast: Chrome in the living room. Might pick up one in the US in August. Now I just need a tv :) http://pocket.co/sPhIn     
    
    
    Turn phones into universal translators: allowing to speak in one language, the other person hears a different one http://www.thetimes.co.uk/tto/technology/article3825506.ece …    
    
    
    Chromecast vs. AirPlay: how do they compare? http://vrge.co/18AlA1L     
    
    
    All the slides for our #SIGIR2013 entity linking and retrieval tutorial are at http://bit.ly/ELR-slides     
    
    
    And all references in our #SIGIR2013 entity linking and retrieval tutorial are in a Mendeley group: http://bit.ly/ELR-bib .    
    
    
    Btw, we are planning on keeping our entity linking and retrieval bibliography updated, to serve as a dedicated, shared resource #SIGIR2013    
    
    
    Hahaha, @leifos stepping up to explain language modeling for IR in our tutorial. On his socks :) #SIGIR2013 pic.twitter.com/9M56dzAhYq    
    
    
    And @krisztianbalog continues #SIGIR2013 pic.twitter.com/uGHdfyYQiD    
    
    
    Updated Slides, Code, and Bibliography for our Entity Linking and Retrieval tutorial @ #SIGIR2013 available now at http://bit.ly/13guNvb     
    
    
    Estefania and Ric at the @YahooLabs booth, ready for action :) #SIGIR2013 pic.twitter.com/HRIsbDBhBm    
    
    
    Our IR journal paper "Using temporal bursts for query modeling" (w/ @mdr and @mariahendrike) is now available: http://bit.ly/Xy9DlH     
    
    
    @paulmwatson it's downstairs, where the coffee breaks are...    
    
    
    @fkschmidt Sure, here's a pic, but it's not the best one.. pic.twitter.com/BriTTdRadJ    
    
    
    RT Ricardo Baeza-Yates at #sigir2013it #SIGIR2013 pic.twitter.com/hnIaGADzJN (cc @fkschmidt @YahooLabs), via @JimiShan    
    
    
    @fkschmidt @fabreetseo last one: https://twitter.com/fabreetseo/status/362492966855651328 … :-)    
    
    
    Cool idea: Tile uses bluetooth tags and a network of app installs to find lost items. Grabs $2.6M via Selfstarter http://techcrunch.com/2013/07/24/tile-grabs-2-6m-via-selfstarter-for-its-lost-property-finding-bluetooth-tags-plus-app/ …    
    
    
    Personalized query understanding for IR at LinkedIn: nice set of slides by @dtunkelang http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130731111846-50510-find-and-be-found-information-retrieval-at-linkedin …    
    
    
    Proud to be one of them! Yahoo’s Marissa Mayer rebuilding research with 50 PhD hires in 2013 http://bloom.bg/15yxNTq     
    
    
    Indeed – “Search is far from over,” Marissa Mayer says. “It’s physics in the 1600s or biology in the 1800s.” http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-08-01/can-marissa-mayer-save-yahoo …    
    
    
    Finally: locate, ring, and wipe a misplaced android, all built into the OS (well, into Google Play). http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2013/08/dude-wheres-my-phone-simple-steps-to.html …    
    
    
    Hadoop cluster for under $200, with three Raspberry Pi's: tiny Big Data. http://blog.ittoby.com/2013/08/starting-small-set-up-hadoop-compute.html …    
    
    
    Intimacy at scale: on any given day, more than 40 percent of Americans – 128 million people – visit Facebook http://nyti.ms/169pca8     
    
    
    The science behind the space station featured in Elysium, using Wolfram|Alpha http://shar.es/ySnAn     
    
    
    Why can’t my computer understand me? – Interesting, though I'd argue there's more to AI than just anaphora resolution http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/elements/2013/08/why-cant-my-computer-understand-me.html …    
    
    
    LOL! An easter egg inside Google Maps: Step inside the Tardis from "Dr. Who" by clicking the arrows on the ground. https://maps.google.co.uk/maps?hl=en&ll=51.492159,-0.19092&spn=0.005291,0.013937&sll=51.492140,-0.193028&layer=c&cid=12502927659667388442&panoid=c9UMhWP_MWm9U0L48xEjYw&cbp=13,291.8,,0,18.86&gl=US&t=m&cbll=51.492132,-0.192862&z=17 …    
    
    
    Interesting post on Facebook's news feed ranking algorithm (i.e., EdgeRank's successor) http://marketingland.com/edgerank-is-dead-facebooks-news-feed-algorithm-now-has-close-to-100k-weight-factors-55908 …    
    
    
    Compared to this, we're being way too easy on our interns... http://blog.sfgate.com/hottopics/2013/08/21/interns-death-puts-banking-culture-under-microscope/ …    
    
    
    Very cool 3D visualization of London’s metro trains. Uses real-time data! http://brunoimbrizi.com/experiments/#/07 …    
    
    
    A mathematician, physicist, economist, engineer, and computer scientist split a check... http://bit.ly/13IhHZM     
    
    
    Prisoners serving long sentences have never been online. This is what they think it’s like. http://www.buzzfeed.com/justinesharrock/the-internet-explained-by-prisoners-who-have-never-seen-it …    
    
    
    Google is calling the next version of its mobile operating system Android KitKat – yes, from the chocolate bars http://bbc.in/15AUoLW     
    
    
    Your resume as a Linux man page – nice twist, albeit geeky :) http://resume.majorhayden.com/     
    
    
    @simonccarter Yeah, indeed.. Can you also select specific columns?    
    
    
    @simonccarter LOL :)    
    
    
    How many ping pong balls could fit in a Boeing 747? @Wolfram_Alpha will tell you http://shar.es/iletk     
    
    
    Dogs are perfectly happy to socialize with robots  http://www.popsci.com/science/article/2013-09/key-making-robots-more-socially-adept-puppies …    
    
    
    Yesterday's RepLab workshop at #CLEF2013 was a big success! I've uploaded all slide decks if you want to know more: http://www.limosine-project.eu/events/replab2013#RepLab_2013_Workshop_Programme_at_CLEF_2013 …    
    
    
    Yahoo offers [...] the opportunity to be creative, and the resources to fulfill the vision http://mashable.com/2013/09/25/yahoo-nyc-mobile-office/ …    
    
    
    "The Google scholar experiment: How to index false papers and manipulate bibliometric indicators" http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/asi.23056/abstract …    
    
    
    Web search volume as a predictor of academic fame – http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/asi.23016/abstract …    
    
    
    The final version of our tutorial on Entity Linking and Retrieval (w/ @dodijk and @krisztianbalog) has been accepted at @WSDM2014! >>    
    
    
    This time, the focus of our tutorial will lie on Semantic Search and other practical applications of Entity Linking and Retrieval. <<    
    
    
    We have opened up our applications for next year's internships at Yahoo Labs Barcelona! See http://comunicacio.barcelonamedia.org/yahoo/ . Deadline: 13 Jan 2013    
    
    
    @roiblanco si, claro    
    
    
    Nice: Royal Dutch Airline gives passengers a personalized surprise http://thenextweb.com/socialmedia/2010/11/12/royal-dutch-airline-gives-passengers-a-surprise/ … via @tnwsocialmedia #fb    
    
    
    @ReaderMeter There was a power outage I believe. @mariahendrike do you know more?    
    
    
    @ReaderMeter @mariahendrike told me that she'll try to bring it back up as soon as possible..    
    
    
    @airfrance got transferred just now to AF0083 for today. Available seats are horrible. Is there a seat plus available? Thanks.    
    
    
    @airfrance No, not yet. Is the flight full? I don't mind paying for an upgrade.    
    
    
    @mariahendrike Hola, any news on http://opengeist.org ?    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer tuurlijk mag dat! Plastic tas eromheen en klaar.    
    
    
    Testdriving #Firefox 4, get it here: http://bit.ly/hMiyLY. Official release later today... #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Health Club Jordaan (Eerste Rozendwarsstraat 10, Amsterdam) http://4sq.com/kEUBwS    
    
    
    I'm at Vorstelijk Complex (Prinses beatrixlaan 2, Utrecht) http://4sq.com/ihDVqX    
    
    
    I'm at Café Thuys (De Clercqstraat 129, Amsterdam) http://4sq.com/mgKdZg    
    
    
    @suzan @DaphneNL dagbladbezorger!    
    
    
    Twitter Acquires TweetDeck Software http://blog.twitter.com/2011/05/all-decked-out.html … via @twitter    
    
    
    Bbq! (@ Vondelpark w/ 20 others) http://4sq.com/kExPtD    
    
    
    LOL MI6 brings down Al Qaeda website full of bomb making instructions with cupcake recipes http://bit.ly/iyANqR #fb    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer he da's cool.! En lijkt erg op wat wij doen.. staan de resultaten ergens?    
    
    
    @Chrisbelloni Afpakken? Dat mag ie helemaal niet. Je koopt "gewoon" een kaartje voor deze reis en je mag je retourtje houden. @NS_online #NS    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer die nrc next analyse van gister...    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer top! Enjoy vlieland    
    
    
    Still about 2 days left to submit your research papers and compressed contributions to #dir2011 http://ilps.science.uva.nl/dir2011 #fb    
    
    
    @yompie Nespresso is toch één grote flashrommel?    
    
    
    @IRtalk he dank je wel heh :-)    
    
    
    Excellent vlog-style introduction to quantum computing! Kudos to @michael_nielsen for taking the time to educate us. See http://bit.ly/kiPxCs     
    
    
    Do you have an interestibg demo to show? #dir2011 now accepts demo submissions! Check the website:  http://ilps.science.uva.nl/dir2011 #fb    
    
    
    @IRtalk waiting for the commitee to come back...    
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/n2m6r0j Dr. Bouke :-) #fb    
    
    
    LOL RT @AT5 Handig obstakel voor blinden: Wie plaatst er nu zo z'n steigers? #wieisernublind http://at5.nl/s/gIf #fb    
    
    
    Both the HTML and Flash edition of my PhD thesis are online now! Check http://phdthes.is/ #fb    
    
    
    Warempel, de zon breekt door!    
    
    
    Downloading new #java7. See http://dhruba.name/2011/06/04/jdk7-project-coin-primer/ … for an exampled list of changes, mainly from Project Coin.    
    
    
    Today is the 12th Annual System Administrator Appreciation Day :) http://www.SysAdminDay.com/index2011.html  #fb    
    
    
    Het is maar een naar ding: barbecueverbodsbord #vondelpark http://at5.nl/s/hj8 #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Kora's Place http://4sq.com/oB1u17    
    
    
    Google crashes when googling "123456..123456" http://www.google.com/?q=123456..123456 … http://twitpic.com/6eirn6  (via @goncalcalvo). #fb    
    
    
    #clef2011 has started!    
    
    
    @mdr introduces the first keynote speaker, Elaine Toms #clef2011    
    
    
    Lunch! #clef2011    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer jah! Running smoothly.. so far  (knocks on wood) :-)    
    
    
    W00t! There's no way back now :). Hoe interpreteert een zoekmachine een zoekvraag? - Universiteit van Amsterdam http://www.uva.nl/actueel/agenda.cfm/074D127C-5CB6-4433-A4DCE6B805C7AC77?sms_ss=twitter&at_xt=4cfe967aabc0b5ac,0 … #fb    
    
    
    Impressed with @HyperDock for the Mac. From window previews to snapping, very useful. This should be included in Mac OS by default IMO    
    
    
    70% vd Marketing managers noemen "explosie aan data en opkomst van Social Media" als grootste uitdagingen. Kom maar op! http://bit.ly/nIhsF4     
    
    
    Dr. Weerkamp? http://yfrog.com/mf2gzij     
    
    
    I want it. Now. http://www.google.com/nexus/  @googlenexus #fb    
    
    
    Nice read: Interview with Google's director of research on their search algorithms http://www.stonetemple.com/search-algorithms-with-google-director-of-research-peter-norvig/ …    
    
    
    My WSDM paper "Adding Semantics to Microblogs" has been accepted! See http://bit.ly/q6Mo6m     
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer goed man! Well done :-)    
    
    
    @samanos nice, congrats!    
    
    
    Geestig: kom er net pas achter dat mijn proefschrift een jaar geleden vermeld werd in de Automatisering Gids, zie http://www.automatiseringgids.nl/nieuws/2010/47/promovendus-maakt-zoekmachines-slimmer … #fb    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog Nice! Care to send me a preprint? I'm curious :-)    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog yes, I'm curious ;-)    
    
    
    @gerdiend: Hora est! http://yfrog.com/gzi01pj #fb    
    
    
    Two ECIR papers accepted! A Framework for Unsupervised Spam Detection in Social Networking Sites: http://bit.ly/mZ5Kl9  ...    
    
    
    ... and Adaptive Temporal Query Modeling (poster), http://bit.ly/qpRYp2 .    
    
    
    @dvdgrs PhD @ UvA? http://ilps.science.uva.nl/news/four-phd-positions …    
    
    
    @dvdgrs Denk dat met name een van de Semantic Search plekken interessant voor je zijn... Laat maar weten als je vragen hebt!    
    
    
    Android 2.2, nice http://is.gd/chYTe    
    
    
    @leesmeemetdejee ik zeg, #albatros    
    
    
    Vakantiegeld, nice :-)    
    
    
    I'm at Bar Brandstof‎ (Marnixstraat 341, Amsterdam) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/70OB5W    
    
    
    #Apache #OpenNLP v 1.5.2 is out! Some new features, improvements and bug fixes. http://incubator.apache.org/opennlp/download.cgi … #nlproc #java    
    
    
    I'm at Healthclub Jordaan (1e rozendwarsstraat 10, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/cLAl0H    
    
    
    I'm at Noordwest (Noordermarkt 41, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/51TN4g    
    
    
    Preprint of my WSDM paper, 'Adding Semantics to Microblog Posts' available now: http://bit.ly/q6Mo6m . Resources will follow soon.    
    
    
    @SamsungMobileNL oppakken lukt niet! #nexushunt    
    
    
    I'm at Caffe Milo (Linnaeusstraat 71, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/bt6hIN    
    
    
    Friday 23 december 2012, Inbox: 0. Time for holidays :-)    
    
    
    @damiano10 Fijne kerstdagen! :)    
    
    
    @damiano10 ¡dos cervezas!    
    
    
    @Judithtiduj nog zo een: 
http://www.nytimes.com/2010/05/30/magazine/30Mayor-t.html    
    
    
    Promotion date is set! 10 Dec 2010, 10:00 AM    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos ja, maar 14:00 23-12-2010 is natuurlijk niet zo mooi als 10:00 10-12-2010 :-)    
    
    
    My Information Processing & Management paper is finally available! See http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.ipm.2009.09.005.    
    
    
    Wat zal de invloed zijn van het twitter debat vanavond op de VK Twitter monitor? #rtldebat http://bit.ly/b6Suv0    
    
    
    Hadoop 1.0.0 has arrived! #in http://hadoop.apache.org/common/releases.html#News …    
    
    
    Dataset (tweets + manual Wikipedia annotations) for my WSDM '12 paper "Adding Semantics to Microblog Posts" released. http://bit.ly/A7yJoZ     
    
    
    I'm at Louter Café Restaurant (De Clercqstraat 82, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/8zxbsJ    
    
    
    iPhone 4 makes me want to trade in my Nexus One. Almost. http://bit.ly/9z33Nn    
    
    
    Get early access to DataSift's Twitter archive http://datasift.com/historic?ref=ceh … via @DataSift    
    
    
    A comparison of five semantic linking algorithms on tweets http://bit.ly/zRrKvX     
    
    
    Stephen Wolfram is accelerating the birth of the data web, by promoting a .data Top-Level Internet Domain. http://blog.stephenwolfram.com/2012/01/a-data-top-level-internet-domain/ …    
    
    
    @nathanmarz Trying to order your book, but "The coupon code you have entered has expired." :(    
    
    
    LOL "NS adviseert niet met de trein te reizen." Da's net zoiets als AH die mensen afraadt boodschappen te doen :-). http://bit.ly/g7IIZo #fb    
    
    
    @nathanmarz Cheers!    
    
    
    ECIR preprints are available now. One on adaptive query modeling, the other on unsupervised spam detection. http://bit.ly/ygndzG  #fb    
    
    
    LREC 2012 Workshop on Language Engineering for Online Reputation Management http://bit.ly/wGh6Le     
    
    
    @suzan zou ie ook why questions doen? :)

The Watson Trivia Challenge: Play against I.B.M.’s question-answering supercomputer. - http://cot    
    
    
    @pogil Did you chateau des charm them? :) Congrats!    
    
    
    Jas verwisseld! Wie heeft mijn zwarte jas met handschoenen meegenomen uit de pancakes? Ik heb de jouwe... please RT #blup    
    
    
    @amazingamazone @ParisVanDerValk Dat zou super chill zijn. Is het een zwarte wollen, half lang?    
    
    
    @ParisVanDerValk Jammer! En ja, de mijne ook :-(. Infobalie heeft 'm niet, misschien morgen.. #blup    
    
    
    #Bungalup was top, maar mijn jas is nog steeds kwijt. Heb een @centerparcs telnr gekregen maar dat is "niet in gebruik" WTF @Valtifest #blup    
    
    
    Net klaar met mijn praatje voor de @KLPD Internet Masterclass. Was leuk, kreeg goede vragen. Nu snel terug naar A dam om college te geven...    
    
    
    RIP Whitney Houston...    
    
    
    New blog post: Zoekmachines van de toekomst http://bit.ly/zrRS1U     
    
    
    LOL. The fellowship of the vuvuzela / http://youtu.be/7B2LPxggvqY    
    
    
    Forget Siri; Upcoming Android app 'Utter!' takes speech-to-text to a whole new level. http://bit.ly/yxZy3B  #fb    
    
    
    LREC 2012 Workshop on Language Engineering for Online Reputation Management http://bit.ly/wGh6Le     
    
    
    LOL For all the geeks among us: Java 4-Ever Trailer / http://youtu.be/A1zySeNpW20    
    
    
    @dvdgrs dat is geen precision-recall graph :)    
    
    
    @dvdgrs dit zijn precision-recall grafieken: http://nlp.stanford.edu/IR-book/html/htmledition/evaluation-of-ranked-retrieval-results-1.html …    
    
    
    Ski = amazing! #onemoreday #fb pic.twitter.com/AKrq3TF5    
    
    
    Naaimachine ging draaien, tub tub tub en dan draait ie en dan zit ie er gewoon in!!? 

http://youtu.be/aPlVNmuHVms    
    
    
    Stack Exchange Q&A site proposal: Information Retrieval and Search Engines http://bit.ly/GOsocM  #fb    
    
    
    @Marijejans Inderdaad, bijkletsen met een biertje is hoog nodig ;-). Tot vanavond!    
    
    
    Het Nederlands elftal wordt ondanks de verloren finale toch gehuldigd met rondvaart. http://bit.ly/aJWtPA    
    
    
    Structured Data: "Wikimedia Proposes Wikidata Project" http://wp.me/p1mjr5-3Ls  via @infodocket    
    
    
    In 2010, Google developed self-driving cars. Now these can navigate a fast food drive-through. This is human progress. http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2012/03/28/googles-driverless-cars-can-now-fetch-food/ …    
    
    
    A Corpus for Entity Profiling in Microblog Posts http://bit.ly/GYx6Ir  #fb    
    
    
    I'll be giving a talk on Large-scale Data Processing for Information Retrieval at the Dutch Hadoop User Group meetup! http://meetu.ps/84W9q     
    
    
    @krisztianbalog nice, congrats!    
    
    
    I'm at Pompstation (Zeeburgerdijk 52, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/6W3flG    
    
    
    @wmijn da's heeeel lang geleden ;). Alles prima, al helpt het weer ook :). Hoe is het met jou?    
    
    
    @wmijn eerst proefschrift afmaken, dan vakantie :). Maar eerst congres in Geneve. Jij bijna op weg naar la france zie ik?    
    
    
    I'm at Schiphol gate C12. http://4sq.com/9Tdggg    
    
    
    It was a fun #nlhug meeting! Thanks @eevrt. My slides are online: Large-scale Data Processing for IR - http://www.slideshare.net/edgar.meij/largescale-data-processing-for-information-retrieval-nlhug … #in    
    
    
    @eevrt Doing what? :)    
    
    
    @eevrt cool! I'll have a look at the job later this week...    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer wij hebben dr wel een? Tis geen opwerper, maar snel is ie wel:)    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Ja hoor, zit in een handig tassie. Tot morgen!    
    
    
    I'll be giving a talk on semantic search in the context of e-discovery at the "Symposium Ontdek E-Discovery" next week. http://www.hva.nl/e-discovery     
    
    
    Use SVR to predict readability level for summarization http://bit.ly/bi1VjL #sigir2010    
    
    
    Term position and proximity evidence helps pseudo relevance feedback on web collections http://bit.ly/9ST2pA #sigir2010    
    
    
    LOL: RT @LoesjeNL **BREIN denkt nog dat je inbraken kunt voorkomen . .  door schroevendraaiers te verbieden** http://www.mobypicture.com/user/loesjeNL/view/12554021 … #loesje    
    
    
    @visualisingdata where/what do you need?    
    
    
    @wmijn goeie vakantie!    
    
    
    Revised journal of web semantics paper submitted! #eindelijkweekend #fb    
    
    
    Hmm, wit bier... (@ Noorderlicht) http://4sq.com/6fgIJI    
    
    
    @visualisingdata Ah. My faculty isn't in the center of AMS, so I can't really help, sorry. Perhaps a hotel or something similar?    
    
    
    If you've got a few free moments :-) "Ten of the greatest: Maths puzzles" http://bit.ly/c9PgVA #fb    
    
    
    A new kind of time travel gets around the paradoxes that have plagued other time machines. http://bit.ly/cj2NBg #fb    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Haha, ja, had 'm al gezien ;)    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Tuurlijk schat! Dansje leggen op het Amstelveld was het plan toch?    
    
    
    LOL RT @AT5 Op de Geldersekade heeft parkeerbeheer het zekere voor het onzekere genomen bij deze auto. http://at5.nl/s/bNm    
    
    
    @damiano10 beer?    
    
    
    Yahoo! Japan to adopt Google's search engine http://bit.ly/aqgxm0 #fb    
    
    
    Our SIGIR poster "Identifying Entity Aspects in Microblog Posts" (w/ Damiano Spina et al.) has been accepted! http://bit.ly/JFPhDf  #in    
    
    
    Today is System Administrator Appreciation Day. See http://xkcd.com/705/ and http://www.SysAdminDay.com/ #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Struik (Rozengracht 160, Amsterdam). http://4sq.com/6vzN3Q    
    
    
    Recent PhD comics are right on point :) http://bit.ly/91PcsJ #fb    
    
    
    Nice, accessible post on IR/document ranking in general and at eBay in particular http://wp.me/prDub-9B  via @hughewilliams    
    
    
    Yep, we're getting there... Google's Knowledge Graph: searching for things instead of words http://insidesearch.blogspot.com/2012/05/introducing-knowledge-graph-things-not.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I'll be giving a talk on semantic linking for Twitter at the CognAC Artificial Intelligence symposium next Tue (May 22) http://bit.ly/LVkUYZ     
    
    
    A visual diary documenting a transatlantic flight. Yep, very recognizable... http://nyti.ms/9dQj0F #fb    
    
    
    The Ultimate Google I/O 2012 Preview http://www.androidpolice.com/2012/05/29/the-ultimate-google-io-2012-preview/ … via @AndroidPolice    
    
    
    Nice! Our project is featuring in a Spanish magazine :). RT @JulioGonzalo1 Nuestro proyecto Limosine en El Pais Semanal
http://www.slideshare.net/LLORENTEYCUENCA/twitter-una-mina-sociolgica-13101693 …    
    
    
    @JulioGonzalo1 I stand corrected ;-)    
    
    
    LOL The illustrated guide to a Ph.D. http://bit.ly/a683CR #fb    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Have fun!    
    
    
    ROFL, PhD comics hits the nail on the head again: http://www.phdcomics.com/comics.php?f=1354 #fb    
    
    
    Visualizing user interests changing over time, based on Twitter search queries: http://engineering.twitter.com/2012/06/studying-rapidly-evolving-user.html ….    
    
    
    Bad day for LinkedIn: 6.5 million hashed passwords reportedly leaked – change yours now http://tnw.to/1EhVs     
    
    
    Waarom maakt de westerkerk geen geluid meer? Zowel de klokken als het carillon doen het niet meer... @AT5 #durftevragen    
    
    
    Google's Hybrid Approach to Research | July 2012 | Communications of the ACM: http://bit.ly/KYiTuj     
    
    
    @Dropbox website and webservice down.. #fail    
    
    
    5 Ways Semantic Search Will Disrupt Business - Forbes http://onforb.es/LE0xhI     
    
    
    De Anne Frankboom is zojuist omgewaaid. http://at5.nl/s/ccK #fb    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos het was GAY-NIAAL!! hoe was jou O&N?    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos hangt van je client af...    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos twitterclient.. telefoon? Web?    
    
    
    Nice: The first ever Digital Camera (Kodak, 1975) - http://nyti.ms/czD34h #fb    
    
    
    Nice patterns: Church or Beer? Americans on Twitter (via @samanos) http://www.floatingsheep.org/2012/07/church-or-beer-americans-on-twitter.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Leap second troubles and how to fix them...   http://www.cloudera.com/blog/2012/07/watching-the-clock-clouderas-response-to-leap-second-troubles/ … via @cloudera    
    
    
    I'm not a mobile app UI designer, but if I were, I'd use http://www.fluidui.com/ . A very nice, live UI mock up designer made in HTML5.    
    
    
    PhD thesis has been sent to the committee! Kan wel janken #fb    
    
    
    I've decided to put some of the Hadoop code I developed for the TREC KBA task online, see http://bit.ly/OepyE1     
    
    
    @eevrt And this was only a single month worth of data ;).    
    
    
    @eevrt Step one: 239k mappers for 5 months of data. Let's see how that goes.    
    
    
    .@eevrt Running the #TREC #KBA toy example system on all data (381m docs in 353k mappers/thrift files), 1.2T ("cleansed-only") in ~1 hour :)    
    
    
    @eevrt This *is* the full batch :). Or do you mean the non-cleaned version?    
    
    
    Some Fresh Twitter Stats (as of July 2012, Dataset Included) http://post.ly/8ZK0v     
    
    
    LOL Man arrested at Large Hadron Collider claims he's from the future http://bit.ly/cirldW #fb    
    
    
    "We are pleased to inform you that your paper has been accepted..." http://researchinprogress.tumblr.com/post/33884075941/we-are-pleased-to-inform-you-that-your-paper-has-been …    
    
    
    How Ebay uses big data to improve recommendations (and more) http://www.zdnet.com/au/how-ebay-uses-big-data-to-make-you-buy-more-7000006498/ …    
    
    
    Scaling up Dynamic Time Warping, i.e., "Mining Time-series with Trillions of Points" http://practicalquant.blogspot.com/2012/10/mining-time-series-with-trillions-of.html …    
    
    
    OpenGeist, a RESTful API for accessing page view counts information of Wikipedia articles: http://www.opengeist.org/  and http://edgar.meij.pro/opengeist-insight-stream-page-views-wikipedia/ …    
    
    
    Ellen is introducing the TREC KBA track: filter a (big!) stream of documents, based on relevance to an entity http://ow.ly/f5Niw  #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC2013: 2 new tracks (Federated search and Temporal summarization), 1 new collection (ClueWeb12), and 1 rename: Real-time search #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC KBA overview starting.. #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC KBA 2013 possible directions: incorporate events, pharmaceutical compounds, and/or combine with the TAC KBP track #trec2012    
    
    
    Data-driven voter analytics and predictions: the big data crunchers who helped Obama win http://ti.me/Uj7o9o  via @TIMEPolitics    
    
    
    Ellen presenting an overview of the TREC Medical track.. The track won't be continuing due to data/privacy considerations #trec2012    
    
    
    @mounialalmas "balance between eﬀectiveness (gains across queries) and robustness (minimizing possibility of signiﬁcant failure)" #trec2012    
    
    
    Track sessions starting. First up: Medical and Web (in parallel). #trec2012    
    
    
    @bevan_koopman Indeed. Getting a proper medical records dataset is not a trivial task though..    
    
    
    Atigeo find that using (the text of) report-level ICD-9 codes help in retrieving medical records #trec2012    
    
    
    DCU obtain best performance using only BM25 on TREC Medical '11 and '12 test collections. (Unweighted) query expansion hurts. #trec2012    
    
    
    @leifos Indeed, BM25 pwnage. Too bad there aren't more TREC approaches/tracks using it as a default baseline.    
    
    
    UDel / @zhudq uses mixture of relevance models for TREC-Med. Seems reminiscent of external expansion (@fdiaz_msr SIGIR '06) #trec2012    
    
    
    @bencarterette @zhudq There you go :). Interesting twist including MeSH in the collections though. Did that make a (significant) difference?    
    
    
    UTD find sign. improvements using (heuristic) assertions for adhoc reranking. Sounds a bit like hedging (Medlock & Briscoe ACL'07) #trec2012    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries best for theirs :). I think UDel did quite well overall, but can't recall the exact ranking of participating systems.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries Did you participate in TREC-Medical also?    
    
    
    .@ssn There's little info on the TREC 2013 Temporal Summarization track online; here's a photo of the poster #trec2012 http://ow.ly/i/16Hzl     
    
    
    TREC 2013 Planning sessions starting... #trec2012    
    
    
    Two candidate goals for TREC KBA 2013: (i) improve sensitivity, (ii) explore temporality. #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC-KBA '13 also considering detecting (first mentions of) "adverse reactions" to pharmaceutical compounds. TREC-KBA-Medical? #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC 2013 Temporal Summarization, Real-time, and KBA tracks will probably use (a subset of) the same document collection #trec2012    
    
    
    New shared document collection *probably* TREC-KBA '12 with some additions (Twitter & FB from Spinn3r) and exclusions (bit.ly) #trec2012    
    
    
    @JeffD talking about bidirectional entity linking, combining KBA and KBP - good stuff #trec2012 pic.twitter.com/eL3luHbP    
    
    
    TREC 2013 summary http://bit.ly/UdNSoE  #trec2012    
    
    
    Lots of alignments between tracks. ClueWeb12 for cont.sugg., crowds., and web. KBA for realtime, kba, and  (possibly) realtime #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC Temporal Summarization 2013 is now online: http://www.trec-ts.org/  (website) and https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups#!forum/temporalsummarization2013 … (Google group) #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC Web 2013: New collection and new coordinators (MS). Also: diversity replaced by risk-sensitive task, safely reranking results #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC Web 2013 Risk-sensitive task: increase effectiveness over all (or most) queries. Determine when/how to change/improve results #trec2012    
    
    
    TREC Web 2013 Risk-sensitive task: combine difficulty prediction/classification with reranking (e.g., pseudo-relevance feedback) #trec2012    
    
    
    LOL! Industry vs. Academia http://tmblr.co/Zuxy3uX2KKYl  via @ResearchInP    
    
    
    Scaling Deep Learning @ Google.. SMT, ASR, and Image classification: all pretty cool stuff.  http://techtalks.tv/talks/57639/     
    
    
    LOL :). Someone in the audience points out a practical application for my research http://tmblr.co/Zuxy3uXJoDe0  via @ResearchInP    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries Re: Countries ranked by ease... With NL having the highest score for the category "Closing a Business." Go figure :)    
    
    
    Best plan for generating startup ideas: "Live in the future, then build what's missing." http://paulgraham.com/startupideas.html …    
    
    
    Battling against the state of the art.. http://researchinprogress.tumblr.com/post/36417281882/battling-against-the-state-of-the-art …    
    
    
    Getting ready for the defense of the soon-to-be-dr @simoncarter http://yfrog.com/esft2kcj     
    
    
    And now @samanos is getting ready/nervous http://yfrog.com/ocfo3eej     
    
    
    Interesting and very applicable: "Practical machine learning tricks from the KDD 2011 best industry paper" #ml http://blog.david-andrzejewski.com/machine-learning/practical-machine-learning-tricks-from-the-kdd-2011-best-industry-paper/ …    
    
    
    "More than 200M individual profiles based on what we browse and buy online." Who do online advertisers think we are? http://nyti.ms/X8z0yP     
    
    
    @UPC Geen internet, geen telefoon. Reset helpt niet. #UPC klantenservice via mobiel ook geen gehoor... What gives?    
    
    
    LOL! Go to Google maps, bring up directions from Japan to China and look at instruction number 43. #fb RT @TheFagCasanova    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer @YInspiration @ellenemonds Geestig... Wij noemen dat "Just in Time Teaching" op de universiteit :). http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Just_in_Time_Teaching …    
    
    
    Steun @Chrisbelloni z'n nieuwe film over de Turkse boot op de gay pride! Crowdfunding campagne @ http://www.cinecrowd.nl/de-turkse-boot     
    
    
    Ik stond in de NRC afgelopen zaterdag! Hier een scan en een tekst versie van het artikel “Een bril die alles weet.” http://bit.ly/Xx8dXD     
    
    
    @sies22 Thanks!    
    
    
    .@ian_soboroff We're currently at 68.89M. And counting. :)    
    
    
    Friday afternoon && inbox 0. Perfect time to head for @samanos in Berlin together w/ Wouter and @simonccarter    
    
    
    Our paper "Feeding the Second Screen..." (w/ @dodijk and @mdr) has been accepted as full paper at OAIR 2013. http://edgar.meij.pro/feeding-screen-semantic-linking-based-subtitles …    
    
    
    @aaranged thanks for your interest! Will do..    
    
    
    @JanHilverda Morgenochtend 8:30 Starbucks op de Ramblas? ;)    
    
    
    @JanHilverda Geen idee, maar dat leek me wel een schappelijke tijd ;-). 20:30 maar doen dan?    
    
    
    @JanHilverda Inderdaad. Laten we dat maar doen dan :).    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer Yep, thanks!    
    
    
    Our paper "Using Temporal Bursts for Query Modeling" (with @mariahendrike and @mdr) has been accepted for IRJ! http://edgar.meij.pro/temporal-bursts-query-modeling/?utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    @frankhulsbos mooie dag om op de bank te zitten dus. Voor een sportliefhebber :)    
    
    
    #sigir2013 full paper notifications are coming in. Score: one paper in and one out, not bad..    
    
    
    CLEF RepLab 2013 Call for Participation and guidelines are now online, see http://limosine-project.eu/events/replab2013 …    
    
    
    @giusepperizzo @damiano10 @www2013rio Apparently the deadline has been extended? I hate rushing for no reason :(.    
    
    
    Our tutorial "Entity Linking and Retrieval" (with @krisztianbalog and @dodijk) has been accepted for #SIGIR2013!    
    
    
    @www2013rio Heh, according to this, Yahoo! Research now has a lab in The Netherlands? I'm actually in Barcelona, ES.. http://www2013.org/2013/04/15/13th-tutorial-11-entity-linking-and-retrieval/ …    
    
    
    @www2013rio thanks!    
    
    
    @abdoelali You mean like https://wavii.com/ ?    
    
    
    @abdoelali I don't know, in that case probably not. So make it yourself! Procrastination++ ;-)    
    
    
    @abdoelali Hehe, exactly ;-).    
    
    
    @larsmans_nl WAT? :-) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kXEgk1Hdze0 …    
    
    
    Slides, code and biblio for our #WWW2013 "Entity Linking and Retrieval" tutorial are now online: http://ejmeij.github.io/entity-linking-and-retrieval-tutorial/ …    
    
    
    Krisztian (@krisztianbalog) talking about entity retrieval #WWW2013 pic.twitter.com/YLLx8LvTfB    
    
    
    Me talking about entity linking :-) #WWW2013 http://flic.kr/p/eiWYEb     
    
    
    @dvdgrs @dodijk @TomKenter Net gepitched, nog anderhalf uur wachten op de uitslag ;-) pic.twitter.com/VLCp0csj1c    
    
    
    @dvdgrs @dodijk @TomKenter Any ideas how to share an iPad amongst four people?    
    
    
    @dvdgrs @dodijk @TomKenter Ladies and gentlemen.. We got him.    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog Excellent decision ;-)    
    
    
    Nice! Our Semantic TED demo won the #WoLE2013 "Doing Good by Linking Entities" Challenge! #WWW2013 http://wole2013.eurecom.fr/challenge     
    
    
    @dvdgrs Cheerful screenshot :-)    
    
    
    This paper describes our (winning!) approach to the "Doing Good by Linking Entities" Challenge @ #WoLE2013 #WWW2013 http://edgar.meij.pro/multilingual-semantic-linking-video-streams-making-ideas-worth-sharing-accessible/?utm_source=bit.ly&utm_medium=linked&utm_campaign=twitter …    
    
    
    Is it me, or are some of the PDF files on the #WWW2013 USB stick corrupted? I've tried two sticks, both with the same result...    
    
    
    Third time lucky, @YashMosh's USB disk does work :-). #WWW2013    
    
    
    @evelinamorim No, just some of them – really weird. Anyway, I have them now, all is good.    
    
    
    @mzurko Just some of them – really weird. Anyway, I have them now, all is good :-). Thanks!    
    
    
    @McHildebrand Yes, but we want to keep it under wraps for the time being. If you send me an email, I'll reply with the URL..    
    
    
    Hey, that's me! #WWW2013 http://flic.kr/p/ejxxY5     
    
    
    Semantic e-mails, pretty cool: Gmail now supports JSON-LD and Microdata to markup information in email. https://developers.google.com/gmail/schemas/embedding-schemas-in-emails …    
    
    
    @nc2y Yep, for me only the third USB stick worked. You can find the same contents online though: http://www2013.org/papers/     
    
    
    @NS_online wow, zonetaxi #fail. 20 minuten staan wachten, geen taxi. Gebeld, "komt eraan," en toen "rit onbekend." Toen maar de bus gepakt.    
    
    
    Tried to get #Uber car in A'dam but 20 mins wait was too long. Received: "added €10 in your account to make up for the inconvenience" Nice.    
    
    
    Some very interesting titles/abstracts to bid on for #CIKM2013. Seemingly interesting though, let's wait for the actual papers first :-).    
    
    
    Entity linking for the masses/webdevs: Google's (wrapper induction based) Data Highlighter now supports 6 more types http://searchengineland.com/googles-data-highlighter-supports-6-new-data-types-160320 …    
    
    
    Duolingo Android app is here; excellent online language learning, now made mobile. Oh, and it's fun too! http://www.androidpolice.com/2013/05/29/duolingo-releases-android-app-brings-free-language-learning-on-the-go/ …    
    
    
    Creative: Flickr adding a link to job postings for engineers/designers in the source code of redesigned main page. http://on.mash.to/13fFqf3     
    
    
    Google (@egabrilovich) releases automatic Freebase annotations for TREC MQ and Web Track queries: http://bit.ly/ZxpB69  - via @ipeirotis    
    
    
    @djoerd @suzan on which query logs do you base this observation?    
    
    
    @KLM Trying to book/check in an exit row seat (29B) for KL2288 on 23 Jun, but keep getting "Your seat selection failed" error. What gives?    
    
    
    @KLM Done.    
    
    
    RDF Search Engine Glimmer Released by Yahoo. See http://bit.ly/12ehki5  and http://glimmer.research.yahoo.com/     
    
    
    Very compact language detection with code extracted from Google Chromium (via @dvdgrs):  http://blog.mikemccandless.com/2011/10/language-detection-with-googles-compact.html … and https://code.google.com/p/chromium-compact-language-detector/ …    
    
    
    All the world are belong to us, the Dutch. Hypothetically. http://what-if.xkcd.com/53/  (via @arjenpdevries)    
    
    
    Work–life balance of scientists: working during weekends has been increasing since 2005 (based on JASIST submissions) http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/asi.22888/abstract …    
    
    
    Interesting, Google does poems :-) http://www.googlepoetics.com/     
    
    
    @mounialalmas nice, well done!    
    
    
    Using Twitter Cards for SEO: hadn't realised this was so easy...  http://searchengineland.com/use-twitter-cards-for-branding-local-seo-166388?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=feed-main …    
    
    
    Introducing new travel-related Yahoo! image search results from Getty images http://yahoosearch.tumblr.com/post/55191648187/introducing-beautiful-new-travel-related-yahoo-image …    
    
    
    This may be the best scientific paper abstract ever written: http://io9.com/this-may-be-the-best-scientific-paper-abstract-ever-wri-729221070 …    
    
    
    Google: 88% of traffic generated by mobile search ads is not replaced by traffic from mobile organic search http://googleresearch.blogspot.com/2013/07/new-research-from-google-shows-that-88.html …    
    
    
    The verb "unfriend" actually dates back to 1659 :-) – "Five words that are older than you think" http://blog.oxforddictionaries.com/2013/06/5-words-that-are-older-than-you-think/ …    
    
    
    Gorgeous new Google Maps UI now open to everyone, although you do need to opt-in: http://www.google.com/maps/about/explore/ … http://searchengineland.com/new-google-maps-now-open-to-all-no-invite-needed-167002 …    
    
    
    WhatsApp “Bigger Than Twitter”: over 200M monthly users, 8B inbound and 12B outbound messages daily  http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/16/whatsapp-bigger-than-twitter-with-over-200m-monthly-active-users-8b-inbound-and-12b-outbound-messages-daily/ …    
    
    
    Bing's new Autosuggest expands to take on instant search with a knowledge graph in one go http://sewat.ch/12BuPtP     
    
    
    Nice intro to Semantic Search basics: http://searchengineland.com/leveraging-search-algorithms-in-a-semantic-search-world-166815 …    
    
    
    LOL: NSA says it can’t search its own emails http://www.propublica.org/article/nsa-says-it-cant-search-own-emails … (via @suzan)    
    
    
    Someone finally tested the prisoner's dilemma on actual prisoners — and the results were not what you would expect... http://www.businessinsider.com/prisoners-dilemma-in-real-life-2013-7 …    
    
    
    Yahoo, Alibaba and why Mayer can keep buying whatever she wants: "Go crazy, Mayer" :)
 http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/r_lQq_bRyZM/ …    
    
    
    Interesting: Chromecast: Chrome in the living room. Might pick up one in the US in August. Now I just need a tv :) http://pocket.co/sPhIn     
    
    
    Turn phones into universal translators: allowing to speak in one language, the other person hears a different one http://www.thetimes.co.uk/tto/technology/article3825506.ece …    
    
    
    Chromecast vs. AirPlay: how do they compare? http://vrge.co/18AlA1L     
    
    
    All the slides for our #SIGIR2013 entity linking and retrieval tutorial are at http://bit.ly/ELR-slides     
    
    
    And all references in our #SIGIR2013 entity linking and retrieval tutorial are in a Mendeley group: http://bit.ly/ELR-bib .    
    
    
    Btw, we are planning on keeping our entity linking and retrieval bibliography updated, to serve as a dedicated, shared resource #SIGIR2013    
    
    
    Hahaha, @leifos stepping up to explain language modeling for IR in our tutorial. On his socks :) #SIGIR2013 pic.twitter.com/9M56dzAhYq    
    
    
    And @krisztianbalog continues #SIGIR2013 pic.twitter.com/uGHdfyYQiD    
    
    
    Updated Slides, Code, and Bibliography for our Entity Linking and Retrieval tutorial @ #SIGIR2013 available now at http://bit.ly/13guNvb     
    
    
    Estefania and Ric at the @YahooLabs booth, ready for action :) #SIGIR2013 pic.twitter.com/HRIsbDBhBm    
    
    
    Our IR journal paper "Using temporal bursts for query modeling" (w/ @mdr and @mariahendrike) is now available: http://bit.ly/Xy9DlH     
    
    
    @paulmwatson it's downstairs, where the coffee breaks are...    
    
    
    @fkschmidt Sure, here's a pic, but it's not the best one.. pic.twitter.com/BriTTdRadJ    
    
    
    RT Ricardo Baeza-Yates at #sigir2013it #SIGIR2013 pic.twitter.com/hnIaGADzJN (cc @fkschmidt @YahooLabs), via @JimiShan    
    
    
    @fkschmidt @fabreetseo last one: https://twitter.com/fabreetseo/status/362492966855651328 … :-)    
    
    
    Cool idea: Tile uses bluetooth tags and a network of app installs to find lost items. Grabs $2.6M via Selfstarter http://techcrunch.com/2013/07/24/tile-grabs-2-6m-via-selfstarter-for-its-lost-property-finding-bluetooth-tags-plus-app/ …    
    
    
    Personalized query understanding for IR at LinkedIn: nice set of slides by @dtunkelang http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130731111846-50510-find-and-be-found-information-retrieval-at-linkedin …    
    
    
    Proud to be one of them! Yahoo’s Marissa Mayer rebuilding research with 50 PhD hires in 2013 http://bloom.bg/15yxNTq     
    
    
    Indeed – “Search is far from over,” Marissa Mayer says. “It’s physics in the 1600s or biology in the 1800s.” http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-08-01/can-marissa-mayer-save-yahoo …    
    
    
    Finally: locate, ring, and wipe a misplaced android, all built into the OS (well, into Google Play). http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2013/08/dude-wheres-my-phone-simple-steps-to.html …    
    
    
    Hadoop cluster for under $200, with three Raspberry Pi's: tiny Big Data. http://blog.ittoby.com/2013/08/starting-small-set-up-hadoop-compute.html …    
    
    
    Intimacy at scale: on any given day, more than 40 percent of Americans – 128 million people – visit Facebook http://nyti.ms/169pca8     
    
    
    The science behind the space station featured in Elysium, using Wolfram|Alpha http://shar.es/ySnAn     
    
    
    Why can’t my computer understand me? – Interesting, though I'd argue there's more to AI than just anaphora resolution http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/elements/2013/08/why-cant-my-computer-understand-me.html …    
    
    
    LOL! An easter egg inside Google Maps: Step inside the Tardis from "Dr. Who" by clicking the arrows on the ground. https://maps.google.co.uk/maps?hl=en&ll=51.492159,-0.19092&spn=0.005291,0.013937&sll=51.492140,-0.193028&layer=c&cid=12502927659667388442&panoid=c9UMhWP_MWm9U0L48xEjYw&cbp=13,291.8,,0,18.86&gl=US&t=m&cbll=51.492132,-0.192862&z=17 …    
    
    
    Interesting post on Facebook's news feed ranking algorithm (i.e., EdgeRank's successor) http://marketingland.com/edgerank-is-dead-facebooks-news-feed-algorithm-now-has-close-to-100k-weight-factors-55908 …    
    
    
    Compared to this, we're being way too easy on our interns... http://blog.sfgate.com/hottopics/2013/08/21/interns-death-puts-banking-culture-under-microscope/ …    
    
    
    Very cool 3D visualization of London’s metro trains. Uses real-time data! http://brunoimbrizi.com/experiments/#/07 …    
    
    
    A mathematician, physicist, economist, engineer, and computer scientist split a check... http://bit.ly/13IhHZM     
    
    
    Prisoners serving long sentences have never been online. This is what they think it’s like. http://www.buzzfeed.com/justinesharrock/the-internet-explained-by-prisoners-who-have-never-seen-it …    
    
    
    Google is calling the next version of its mobile operating system Android KitKat – yes, from the chocolate bars http://bbc.in/15AUoLW     
    
    
    Your resume as a Linux man page – nice twist, albeit geeky :) http://resume.majorhayden.com/     
    
    
    @simonccarter Yeah, indeed.. Can you also select specific columns?    
    
    
    @simonccarter LOL :)    
    
    
    How many ping pong balls could fit in a Boeing 747? @Wolfram_Alpha will tell you http://shar.es/iletk     
    
    
    Dogs are perfectly happy to socialize with robots  http://www.popsci.com/science/article/2013-09/key-making-robots-more-socially-adept-puppies …    
    
    
    Yesterday's RepLab workshop at #CLEF2013 was a big success! I've uploaded all slide decks if you want to know more: http://www.limosine-project.eu/events/replab2013#RepLab_2013_Workshop_Programme_at_CLEF_2013 …    
    
    
    Yahoo offers [...] the opportunity to be creative, and the resources to fulfill the vision http://mashable.com/2013/09/25/yahoo-nyc-mobile-office/ …    
    
    
    "The Google scholar experiment: How to index false papers and manipulate bibliometric indicators" http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/asi.23056/abstract …    
    
    
    Web search volume as a predictor of academic fame – http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/asi.23016/abstract …    
    
    
    The final version of our tutorial on Entity Linking and Retrieval (w/ @dodijk and @krisztianbalog) has been accepted at @WSDM2014! >>    
    
    
    This time, the focus of our tutorial will lie on Semantic Search and other practical applications of Entity Linking and Retrieval. <<    
    
    
    We have opened up our applications for next year's internships at Yahoo Labs Barcelona! See http://comunicacio.barcelonamedia.org/yahoo/ . Deadline: 13 Jan 2013    
    
    
    @roiblanco si, claro    
    
    
    Nice: Royal Dutch Airline gives passengers a personalized surprise http://thenextweb.com/socialmedia/2010/11/12/royal-dutch-airline-gives-passengers-a-surprise/ … via @tnwsocialmedia #fb    
    
    
    @ReaderMeter There was a power outage I believe. @mariahendrike do you know more?    
    
    
    @ReaderMeter @mariahendrike told me that she'll try to bring it back up as soon as possible..    
    
    
    @airfrance got transferred just now to AF0083 for today. Available seats are horrible. Is there a seat plus available? Thanks.    
    
    
    @airfrance No, not yet. Is the flight full? I don't mind paying for an upgrade.    
    
    
    @mariahendrike Hola, any news on http://opengeist.org ?    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer tuurlijk mag dat! Plastic tas eromheen en klaar.    
    
    
    Testdriving #Firefox 4, get it here: http://bit.ly/hMiyLY. Official release later today... #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Health Club Jordaan (Eerste Rozendwarsstraat 10, Amsterdam) http://4sq.com/kEUBwS    
    
    
    I'm at Vorstelijk Complex (Prinses beatrixlaan 2, Utrecht) http://4sq.com/ihDVqX    
    
    
    I'm at Café Thuys (De Clercqstraat 129, Amsterdam) http://4sq.com/mgKdZg    
    
    
    @suzan @DaphneNL dagbladbezorger!    
    
    
    Twitter Acquires TweetDeck Software http://blog.twitter.com/2011/05/all-decked-out.html … via @twitter    
    
    
    Bbq! (@ Vondelpark w/ 20 others) http://4sq.com/kExPtD    
    
    
    LOL MI6 brings down Al Qaeda website full of bomb making instructions with cupcake recipes http://bit.ly/iyANqR #fb    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer he da's cool.! En lijkt erg op wat wij doen.. staan de resultaten ergens?    
    
    
    @Chrisbelloni Afpakken? Dat mag ie helemaal niet. Je koopt "gewoon" een kaartje voor deze reis en je mag je retourtje houden. @NS_online #NS    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer die nrc next analyse van gister...    
    
    
    @paulienkreutzer top! Enjoy vlieland    
    
    
    Still about 2 days left to submit your research papers and compressed contributions to #dir2011 http://ilps.science.uva.nl/dir2011 #fb    
    
    
    @yompie Nespresso is toch één grote flashrommel?    
    
    
    @IRtalk he dank je wel heh :-)    
    
    
    Excellent vlog-style introduction to quantum computing! Kudos to @michael_nielsen for taking the time to educate us. See http://bit.ly/kiPxCs     
    
    
    Do you have an interestibg demo to show? #dir2011 now accepts demo submissions! Check the website:  http://ilps.science.uva.nl/dir2011 #fb    
    
    
    @IRtalk waiting for the commitee to come back...    
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/n2m6r0j Dr. Bouke :-) #fb    
    
    
    LOL RT @AT5 Handig obstakel voor blinden: Wie plaatst er nu zo z'n steigers? #wieisernublind http://at5.nl/s/gIf #fb    
    
    
    Both the HTML and Flash edition of my PhD thesis are online now! Check http://phdthes.is/ #fb    
    
    
    Warempel, de zon breekt door!    
    
    
    Downloading new #java7. See http://dhruba.name/2011/06/04/jdk7-project-coin-primer/ … for an exampled list of changes, mainly from Project Coin.    
    
    
    Today is the 12th Annual System Administrator Appreciation Day :) http://www.SysAdminDay.com/index2011.html  #fb    
    
    
    