@lisiepeasie Folks at http://SGPad.com . Pretty happy with their service so far    
    
    
    Wow, I actually overheard someone start a sentence with ‘We Chinese have a saying…’. Who says that in real life?!    
    
    
    We Chinese have a saying, don’t say ‘We Chinese have a saying’ where someone can overhear and make fun of you on Twitter    
    
    
    Hilarious forum letter about my wife's school: "[My son] had refused to complete his exam and began dancing instead." http://www.straitstimes.com/premium/forum-letters/story/school-caring-teachers-20121123 …    
    
    
    (She was just telling me about that incident. They let him retake the exam on A3 paper, which apparently helped him concentrate.)    
    
    
    @minal_9 I had no idea! (About the baby, and the point raised in the post.) Congrats! (About the baby.)    
    
    
    @SGNextRide @honcheng Four stars? That’s a damn shame. Telling my friends to go give it five. Great work!    
    
    
    Have a pocket of free time tonight. Sitex or Sigur Ros concert?    
    
    
    @andycroll So the key is don’t fail miserably *and* sue your clients? Sweet!    
    
    
    @mengwong Not entirely the same, though? I don’t believe ranking here is as closely tied to test scores.    
    
    
    Great Jets impression there by UCLA. #gostanford    
    
    
    @vickiho Just listened to ep 6 of @StaringScreens. Shouldn’t need to switch Xbox accounts to use Netflix—just have the app installed, right?    
    
    
    @vickiho @StaringScreens I recall this working for me: sign out of SG account, sign in to US, install Netflix, sign in to SG account (VPN).    
    
    
    @vickiho @StaringScreens But I’ve since obtained two other Netflix-capable boxes to use, so my info may be outdated    
    
    
    SAF advertising, 2012-2020:

• Every Soldier A Leader
• Every Soldier Listens To Orders
• Every Soldier Showing Up Would Be Nice But Ah Well    
    
    
    @sangsara @vickiho @StaringScreens Actually went and tried it (switch account, install, switch back). Still works! It’s under Apps.    
    
    
    @sangsara @vickiho @StaringScreens But yeah, the music and video tabs are gone.    
    
    
    @iamclovin Thanks for the invite btw! No web projects for now, but will give it a try when we do. Cheers :)    
    
    
    Bought an Xbox game and left it in the car for 2 days so far. Entertainment value from finding out everyday if disc has melted: check    
    
    
    Got an iPad mini, and the iPad 3 has been relegated to service as Gigantic 3G Tethering Modem With 10 Hours Battery Life.    
    
    
    @pyrmont Just a little. Can’t help but imagine how great this’d be with retina.    
    
    
    @andycroll Yeah, it’s a gift. I’d have picked up a LTE one given a choice. Can’t believe yours still isn’t here!    
    
    
    Configured a $3,900 iMac and staring at the screen. I probably need a 3TB fusion drive for, er, work, right?    
    
    
    @sangsara I’m mildly worried about not being able to back that monster up. But it’s less than $200 over the cost of a 1TB!    
    
    
    @pyrmont Downsides?    
    
    
    @pyrmont Oh that’s the Mac Pro. I’m eyeing the new iMac    
    
    
    @pyrmont Yup, the highest end one in Sing$, with 16GB RAM, i7 upgrade, and 3TB Fusion Drive. Not sure about the first and third bits though.    
    
    
    @pyrmont Hm, good point! Crucial does ship pretty quickly.    
    
    
    @sangsara There’s always CrashPlan, I guess. How’s that upload going?    
    
    
    Last college football tweet of the year until Jan 1 for the Rose Bowl. All right now! #gostanford    
    
    
    @jussi Thank you kind sir!    
    
    
    Why didn’t any of my American friends spend this much effort learning Singlish? Hmph. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fiYXiixlV0A …    
    
    
    @jussi No, no, I insist    
    
    
    @jussi Thank you for thanking me!    
    
    
    @jussi Thank No, thank YOU for being thankful!    
    
    
    @jussi ARE YOU DRUBNK SIR    
    
    
    @jussi I suppose we can agree on that.    
    
    
    @jussi Noooooooo    
    
    
    Finding myself in the strange position of agreeing with Gawker over NYT on Popova. "It's like Buzzfeed, but boring." http://gawker.com/5964868/the-new-york-times-has-a-really-kooky-boner-for-curation-wizard-maria-popova …    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie She’s not too bad, but the NYT piece really was quite fawning    
    
    
    @nfarina Not sure I get what you mean—like Google Instant?    
    
    
    @nfarina Odd, that’s never happened to me. (Maybe because lookups are slower here.) And it goes away with the extension disabled?    
    
    
    @thedak Ahh my trophy puked    
    
    
    Ordered iMac over the phone. Rep was mildly distraught that I maxed out the CPU and video card but left it at 8GB RAM.    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie It’s only 3-4 weeks from arriving at your door if you order now!    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Oh, maybe that’s the 21 inch one?    
    
    
    @zachphillips Ugh at 3-4 weeks shipping though. I’ll be going on vacation for a week, shipping RAM from the US, and it’ll still not be here.    
    
    
    @wynlim Seconding the Slicy recommendations. You can work at 1x and auto 2x, or the other way round.    
    
    
    Managed to take the wrong train twice already in Taipei. I blame iOS 6 Maps    
    
    
    Refusing to acknowledge I overate. (Rushes downstairs, buys random food off streetcarts next to hotel, gobbles another coffee)    
    
    
    Finding Apple Maps close to useless in Taipei. Probably due to complicated road names, traditional Chinese, and non-pinyin romanisations    
    
    
    @pyrmont To be fair, I can't find anything with Google Maps, either    
    
    
    This is way more fried chicken than the human mind was designed to comprehend    
    
    
    I can't fit this much fried chicken in my mouth at one time, can I    
    
    
    YES WE CAN    
    
    
    @jussi No, thank YOU    
    
    
    @zachphillips Latest estimate is next year. Next year! Harrumph.    
    
    
    Every time I visit a Singaporean tech blog, I end up writing one of these: http://yjsoon.com/2012/12/more-singapore-tech-blog-writing …    
    
    
    @zachphillips @Twitterrific Not loving the limited gap-catch-up either, being in another time zone.    
    
    
    @zachphillips @Twitterrific Wasn’t able to when I tried this morning — ends up filling it in backwards, losing my position.    
    
    
    @justin But but think of all the mouthes you're not feeding    
    
    
    @inky @Instapaper Fixed naming of variable from 'i' to more descriptive 'count'    
    
    
    @sangsara Potential obstacle: Can't open that link in T'rrific and Tweetbot because they assume all http://yfrog.com  links are pictures.    
    
    
    And thus ends my annual attempt at using @Twitterrific. Maybe next year they’ll get gap detection right (he also said, last year).    
    
    
    @sangsara @Twitterrific Tiny tap target for that, and fails after a few taps. Not great for catching up overnight from our time zone…    
    
    
    @sangsara @Twitterrific ‘Fails’ as in it starts loading backwards and losing the old tweets after a few taps.    
    
    
    @sangsara Usually when I tap, it loads above the marker. After about 4 taps though, it loads below, removing the old tweets    
    
    
    Reading my iPad mini from across the room. SO RETINA    
    
    
    @jarrold Yeah I wouldn't have gotten it (was a gift). Love it and use it all the time, but can't help thinking how great it'd be with Retina    
    
    
    @sangsara @andycroll @jarrold Or use it as a flashlight    
    
    
    @nickheer What! What will I do with this ‘Instagram’ app then    
    
    
    @zachphillips Felt a little overdone though. Lost a couple of sympathy points five page scrolls in    
    
    
    Suffering from overpriced cheesecake withdrawal symptoms    
    
    
    ‘That’ll be good, but don’t get your socks up’ – the distracted wife    
    
    
    "I haven't had cheesecake in a week!"
"When the hell did cheesecake become a staple food for you?!"    
    
    
    ‘It’s in a… remote location?’
‘We have a…. remote chance of finding it?’

‘You’ve run out of puns and still haven’t found the damn remote?!’    
    
    
    After 8 days of getting lost in the rain, I get  Google Maps and perfect weather on my last day here in Taipei. Bah.    
    
    
    What's wrong with chopped liver anyway    
    
    
    You’d think that Super Hexagon would be easier on an iPad than an iPhone. You’d also have forgotten about your cat wanting in on the fun.    
    
    
    Scrolled through 6 hours’ worth of angry and/or shell-shocked tweets before the poop jokes started appearing again.    
    
    
    Probably linking to this piece for @TheRoundDown. http://onion.com/VFXppF     
    
    
    Ohhh man the Monty Python sequence nearly killed me http://goo.gl/fe2R0  #GetGlue #fringe    
    
    
    The dangers of auto-cropping thumbnails pic.twitter.com/pv1nVvt7    
    
    
    @thedak Great link. Thanks!    
    
    
    Crap, got caught stealing the chips http://instagr.am/p/TStszBgPyW/     
    
    
    @vickiho Get a VPN account (he typed, from the couch he hasn’t left all weekend because he’s been watching Netflix)    
    
    
    @cimota Has anyone stepped in with an inappropriate Life of Pi quip yet? Because, y'know, always glad to be of service.    
    
    
    @honcheng Hey dude, do you foresee any difficulties if I were to try adopting Paperfold for 0 folds? i.e. just flip around to a side menu    
    
    
        
    
    
    @honcheng Ah, cool. We need not quite a flip but more a ‘flattening’, but can work from here I think :) Thanks a lot!    
    
    
    @honcheng @DillionTan Understood. Thank you kind sirs!    
    
    
    @andycroll Goodbye benign British overlord    
    
    
    Ooh, Google Maps managed to pronounce Yio Chu Kang Road. Apple and Garmin both give up and say ‘Y. I. O.’ instead.    
    
    
    @pyrmont During voice navigation    
    
    
    @ExtraTan Doubt it    
    
    
    "The tenor of the times is that anyone can design a course, anyone can teach." No truer words. http://cestlaz.github.com/2012/12/17/layers-of-a-lesson.html …    
    
    
    Just finished season 1 of American Horror Story in 3 days. That was… bizarre.    
    
    
    @nfarina Yeah, that was a jaw-dropping reveal. Think I need a break before starting season 2 though…    
    
    
    @skinnylatte Started off as decent horror, then became less scary as it went bonkers towards the end of the season. Quite enjoyed it.    
    
    
    @RagingTBolt I read him to get annoyed over the weird em-dash usage    
    
    
    SingTel seems to have enabled LTE access at my block... in the elevator?    
    
    
    An Unexpected Journey Top Hits Compilation    
    
    
    @thedak Is the Jot Touch the Bluetooth one? How is it?    
    
    
    Guess who just found out that the icon at row 4, column 3 on an iPad remains stationary when rotating, and then spent 5min rotating his iPad    
    
    
    Lol who gives a crap *dunks entire thing in wasabi* @ Itacho Sushi http://instagr.am/p/Tf7OOogPz4/     
    
    
    SingTel rushed out an update to their iPhone app before the holiday submission shutdown for THIS?! pic.twitter.com/B99mvLEA    
    
    
    Starhub ad proclaims they'll help people disconnect from their devices, spend more time with family. What, by crapping out our connections?    
    
    
    The Hobbit, with great characters such as Bilbo Baggins, Gollum, Galadriel and Golden Village Auntie. pic.twitter.com/p2c8Ex8E    
    
    
    @Youssef90 Haven’t seen any issues yet    
    
    
    @Youssef90 That's what I said :)    
    
    
    Who ate my Mass Effect 2 disc 2?!? (I haven't played it in over a year, and now it's missing, and I blame the cats)    
    
    
    @jeffsiow B A, not A B :p    
    
    
    @davechua YES WTF    
    
    
    @tsewei I couldn't get past "Turtle Eggs" without breaking down    
    
    
    The Soon household's Great Calendar Sync Failure of 2012 (August - November) claims another social event as its victim. I blame you, Google    
    
    
    Amazing Spider-WTF 700    
    
    
    @sangsara Now I know how all those old codgers felt about the clone saga back in the day    
    
    
    iMac shipped! Might make it before next year.    
    
    
    @suyuen Yup. Which ibanking? DBS has a "bill payment" option—one for their own cards, and one for other banks'.    
    
    
    @jaryl Same! Shanghai?    
    
    
    "Anyone good at cutting pie?"
(Everyone stares at our doctor friend)
"I don't cut patients into eight equal pieces!"    
    
    
    @nfarina Looks terrible after half a year of abuse, though.    
    
    
    Tried changing the comforter cover. Discovered it has six corners. What mathematical anomaly is this thing    
    
    
    @b_catenin But it was square when I startedddd    
    
    
    The iMac is here! So long, 9GB swap files while running Photoshop and Xcode! (For another couple of years, anyway.)    
    
    
    Still reeling from the news about PAP owning AIM. So the yellow jumpsuits are just old PAP uniforms? Does this mean LKY is MODOK?    
    
    
    @andycroll I end up not playing my games for so long I sometimes re-buy them thinking "ooh, I'd love to play that"    
    
    
    @andycroll Yeah, I'm happy to keep paying for those. And Steam does help keep track of what I've bought. It's the console games that kill me    
    
    
    Oh crap I fell asleep and missed something people were all excited about    
    
    
    @dsng Really enjoying the recommendations. Thanks!    
    
    
    Had no idea what to do with the 24" monitor, plonked it next to the iMac, and got instant neck ache from trying to look at this much screen    
    
    
    Woke up early to catch the Rose Bowl and hopefully not neglect to drive the wife to work #gostanford    
    
    
    Well, that was… efficient #gostanford    
    
    
    All right now!    
    
    
    @taratan If by "use" you mean "constantly realise I left them in the car when others give me their cards", yes yes yes    
    
    
    @ngchinleng @singaporebrides Congrats! Love that it looks great even on an iPhone.    
    
    
    DAMN IT CATS STOP SQUATTING ON MY F (and cmd-n?!) KEY AT NIGHT pic.twitter.com/mrqgdzp7    
    
    
    Downloaded ST's new "Happening" app. Non-retina icons, misaligned rounded corners, Lobster, outdated events. 

What's happening: deletion    
    
    
    @dsng The font. It's the new Comic Sans. (I should talk, I use it on one of my logos.)    
    
    
    @dsng It's well made, but quickly became overused. Check out the creator's other free fonts too: http://www.impallari.com/     
    
    
    I take back what I said about an efficient first touchdown in the Rose Bowl    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Noooooo why the Cinema Display? You can get at least 2 Korean 27" IPS monitors for that price http://www.codinghorror.com/blog/2012/07/the-ips-lcd-revolution.html …    
    
    
    The new desktop setup. So many pixels it hurts. (Including the 7.85" distraction machine.) pic.twitter.com/2UhjCXym    
    
    
    @cheeaun Yeah the gaming mouse is for gaming and Photoshop. Not to mention the Magic Trackpad in the keyboard drawer :p    
    
    
    @cheeaun Yah, used to it lor. Even have to use normal scrolling on one mouse and inverted on the Magic Mouse...    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Still can amend order and buy from gmarket?    
    
    
    Nooooo I accidentally pressed the "..." gap loading button 5 times on @twitterrific and now my iPhone has exploded    
    
    
    @RagingTBolt I do. Let me know if you still need it    
    
    
    Discovered more sources of UK Cadbury here in Singapore and now I've eaten two meals' worth of Twirls.    
    
    
    @Samantha The Value-$ and ABC neighborhood stores tend to have them (but running out lately). Small number of Cold Storages stock them too    
    
    
    @Samantha Latest find though: Liang Court Meidi-Ya. You're back in the country?    
    
    
    X-O Manowar Crab Bee Hoon    
    
    
    @Samantha Shucks. Have a good trip back!    
    
    
    @thedak You can’t post a link to a Starcon2 remake and expect me to be able to do anything else for a few weeks :p    
    
    
    @thedak I'd have thought you'd be more of a (the)daktaktakpak guy. Oh wait they only showed up in the non-canon sequel    
    
    
    @joycesohn The inventor of the Happy Meal was called Chicken McNugget?!    
    
    
    @chuyeow Both female cats right? Quite poor thing, takes longer to recover than males…    
    
    
    @sangsara Better than the M50s? How comfy are they?    
    
    
    Thanks for ruining my Google search history, cats pic.twitter.com/D4offx3G    
    
    
    @sangsara Cool. Yeah the M50s felt pretty tight when I put them on, perhaps because we have giant heads. How much is it?    
    
    
    The PAP candidate just needs a bit more forehead and some green paint to look exactly like Hulk villain The Leader    
    
    
    @sangsara Hmm. Don’t think I can justify one of those just yet, then… if I flew more maybe, love noise-cancellers on flights.    
    
    
    I MEAN SERIOUSLY GUYS

GAMMA-IRRADIATED MAD SCIENTIST ALERT pic.twitter.com/A55uOrKW    
    
    
    related: i ♥ content-aware transforms    
    
    
    @RagingTBolt There’s a Send To Kindle app for Mac that achieves what you want, I think.    
    
    
    The cat just went into a killing frenzy over this lizard he saw sneak out from under his water dish. So cute!    
    
    
    I’m the most annoying teacher ever pic.twitter.com/j4hJXz6t    
    
    
    @tsewei As long as they leave each other alive in the morning I’m happy!    
    
    
    @jeslin_mx What for?!    
    
    
    @jeslin_mx Oh right, you’re in JC now. We’re conducting the Monday morning INVENT programme, if you’re interested    
    
    
    @jeslin_mx It’s during the “protected time” on Monday mornings before lessons start, I thought. Friday is just a briefing.    
    
    
    Something about this unassembled ikea cupboard looks off http://instagr.am/p/UgfELNAP4I/     
    
    
    Just saw Silver Linings Playbook. Best movie I’ve seen ALL YEAR. (I’m like this every January, sorry everyone)    
    
    
    Best tweet I’ve written ALL YEAR    
    
    
    @vickiho Around December 26, my level of optimism skyrockets at the thought of the ‘see you next year’ jokes I can annoy everyone with    
    
    
    @thedak @vickiho Didn’t know you were performing today! Happened to be dragged along to the fair. Sounding good!    
    
    
    Tried to ask, in Chinese voice entry, if my grandpa needed to go to the hospital, but forgot to switch the keyboard. pic.twitter.com/qpuQuWdB    
    
    
    (He's ok right now, small scare from a marrow condition. Just glad the iPhone managed to inject some levity here)    
    
    
    @thedak Thanks dude :)    
    
    
    @chuyeow Don’t worry about it, just a scare    
    
    
    Oh boy one step closer to Harbaughggedon    
    
    
    Teaching Python to a class with this book: http://interactivepython.org/courselib/static/thinkcspy/index.html … Pretty well structured. Recommended.    
    
    
    Also, been a while since I taught intro programming. Fun!    
    
    
    Found some poster designs I did in college. One of them was in Comic Sans. I need a place to hide my head    
    
    
    @davechua I hope they get to play FIFA a lot, because that’s pretty much all I did in my dorm    
    
    
    @sangsara @taratan This one seems to work on my SingTel Fibre connection    
    
    
    Woohoo! My mildly-discounted 30-pin Lightning adapter has shipped! Now to refresh the shipping page obsessively, like I did for my iMac!    
    
    
    @honcheng Better watch out, I bet this “Hon Cheng Muh” fellow who made it will come after you    
    
    
    Oh good I can finally go back to that part of Sengkang again    
    
    
    You Only… Laxative Once?    
    
    
    #firstpost on Vine: the cat. What else? http://vine.co/v/bJMW6b5BJj3     
    
    
    Apple just sent out a couple of cards I ordered from their Cards app in 2011. This is going to be interesting.    
    
    
    @honcheng And here I was thinking my friends didn’t appreciate my cards    
    
    
    @sangsara I don’t recall getting any replies from the folks I sent to, so maybe not!    
    
    
    @andycroll I send my students with programming experience to the Stanford iTunes U course.    
    
    
    @andycroll (And ask them to not worry too much about the lectures, but not skip the assignments.)    
    
    
    How is this PIN entry improving security? By giving people looking over my shoulder more time to copy down my PIN? pic.twitter.com/ss4mYcBD    
    
    
    @marcedwards It’s been 50-50 for me; sometimes, you just need to re-enter your password to reauthorize and it’ll work.    
    
    
    @honcheng Workers’ Party SGBuses users??? (Sorry)    
    
    
    Every so often, I think: let’s use Compass spriting! It’ll save me time! Then I spend an hour looking up how the syntax works.    
    
    
    Confuse-a-cat http://vine.co/v/b1zhx5pBVqq     
    
    
    Newfound exercise in futility: taking Vine videos of the cat    
    
    
    Just read this Facebook comment on an ST post on missing cats: "They might have been eatened?"

WTF, education system    
    
    
    @joe_hill Congrats! Love the series, and really looking forward to the ending.    
    
    
    @_abi_ I don’t know how long you’ve been away, but this isn’t China! Yet. Anyway, I was more annoyed by the grammar :)    
    
    
    Yay, I got Facebook Graph Search! I’ve found graphs for e^x, x^2, and the rate of change of how this joke becomes less funny over time.    
    
    
    @vickiho Congrats on finishing Chapter 1 of The Hunger Games!    
    
    
    @vickiho Oh you mean the job    
    
    
    @taratan I’ve used it for over 2 years now. Perfect for Inbox Zero addicts.    
    
    
    Feeling special today as one of the 250,000. Thanks, Twitter!    
    
    
    @thedak @lisiepeasie @sangsara Just saw Lisa’s comment—did you actually get a password reset request from not-Twitter?    
    
    
    Toy attack http://vine.co/v/b1gDxJwjKXA     
    
    
    Dancing cat http://vine.co/v/b1tIqlEnpmU     
    
    
    @chuyeow Got to train them from young to sit like that :p    
    
    
    “Go Piggers” getting more results than usual during the Super Bowl. Well done, Oatmeal    
    
    
    @ohryan The CDATA bit? Fixed it on the github version a while back, but forgot to send to the WordPress directory, oops :/ Thanks though!    
    
    
    @ohryan And the echo, too. If you see anything else, let me know or put up a pull request? Thanks! https://github.com/yjsoon/df-style-linked-list_wordpress-plugin/blob/master/linked_list.php#L77 …    
    
    
    @ohryan Sadly, I’ve been useless at remembering to update the WP plugin version. Now to check if this will break any of my favourite blogs…    
    
    
    Just discovered I have email receipts for every movie I watched in the last year. Now to fill up my @Letterboxd account with stupid reviews.    
    
    
    Bak kwa and pineapple tarts and shrimp rolls for breakfast I LOVE CHINESE NEW YEAR    
    
    
    MY ARTERIES DO NOT    
    
    
    Went to my backup folder to find something, forgot it symlinked back into my home folder, spent half an hour yelling "HOW IS THIS HAPPENING"    
    
    
    You encounter a wild DIET PLAN

You use PINEAPPLE TARTS

IT’S SUPER EFFECTIVE!    
    
    
    Silly me    
    
    
    Fireworks man fireworks http://vine.co/v/bn2T1mzIj6r     
    
    
    I can't count to 12 http://vine.co/v/bn2FET7hBIH     
    
    
    Hit 2.5 million points in Temple Run 2 during Reunion Dinner. The heights of human achievement, attainable only during large family dinners.    
    
    
    Grumpy cat dresses up for the new year http://vine.co/v/bvzVwMqTrMd     
    
    
    Woohoo I have @mailbox! Somebody send me an email so I can archive it and never reply!    
    
    
    Ahhhhh! It’s the worst enemy of every bored iPhone user at family gatherings… the dreaded 2G connection!!    
    
    
    @sangsara Pretty sure researchers didn’t put in algorithms for cancelling lion dance sounds    
    
    
    @sangsara Looks decent. I remember when it was all web based. Will try reading my humble bundle ebooks on it    
    
    
    I quit counting calories for Chinese New Year because I can't count beyond 8,000    
    
    
    @janseurinck Not sure what you’ve tried and haven’t. Email me? This handle at gmail.    
    
    
    A tale of a jar of pineapple tarts http://vine.co/v/bvL6zw5Xu1L     
    
    
    Maybe reading my entire Twitter feed after waking up at 3am wasn't such a great idea, he thought 2 hours later, unable to return to sleep    
    
    
    Finally got around to watching Objectified, and recognised a couple of the IDEO designers in there from college. Bizarro    
    
    
    That’s a lot of hacked Yahoo email accounts guys    
    
    
    @dsng Agreed, Downcast is great. Earned a spot on my dock.    
    
    
    @ngchinleng Your birthday today? Happy one dude! Haven’t seen you in ages, catch up sometime :)    
    
    
    Persona? Is that like a female persono?    
    
    
    Misread the @mailbox inbox zero message (“You’re all done”) as “You’re all alone.” I guess that’s true, too…?    
    
    
    @garrettmurray Seriously?! I had no idea. Now I'm sitting in a corner sobbing uncontrollably. Look what you've done, @mailbox    
    
    
    @garrettmurray That’s a mild relief, thanks for explaining.    
    
    
    ‘This is where we post about new features on Posterous Spaces.’ Today’s new feature: a shutdown! Trololol http://blog.posterous.com/thanks-from-posterous …    
    
    
    git pish
gi tpush
git pushh
gi

My terminal window just told me I need a break    
    
    
    Oh good, an image processing assignment. Time to use my cat pictures all over this thing    
    
    
    @davechua That’s a great idea. We’re setting up a mini-hardware lab in the school too, and they already have a 3D printer...    
    
    
    ‘OCBC Titanium gives you up to 2.5 miles here & overseas when you spend S$1.5K/month.’

Dude I can get 2.5 miles while taxiing on the runway    
    
    
    @wynlim (Re: Sketch) It’s great! I used it for drawing, now exploring interface design with it. Some resources: https://plus.google.com/u/0/communities/105292892811319179094 …    
    
    
    @mrbrown In other countries, reasons have usually been protectionism and anti-laundering    
    
    
    Here’s a super effective weight loss tip! How to lose 2kg in 5 minutes: give me your laptop    
    
    
    That was pretty terrible, even by my standards    
    
    
    @pyrmont Well give me two then    
    
    
    @StaringScreens Your followers might be interested to know abt the Bioshock Infinite pre-order deals everywhere (Steam, Greenman, Amazon)?    
    
    
    @StaringScreens Oh and Amazon's digital download sale http://www.amazon.com/gp/feature.html/?ie=UTF8&docId=1000716161 …    
    
    
    @StaringScreens (US-billing address only for Amazon)    
    
    
    @nfarina Just did the same, because I love how Chrome tries to squeeze 50 open tabs into one window.    
    
    
    Oh nice, HSBC reversed my credit card annual fee twice. Free $200! Next year, I’ll try calling them up thrice to waive the fee.    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk I dutifully reported it on their dinky customer service messaging system. (Not about to hold on the phone to return them money!)    
    
    
    Gabe at Penny Arcade reviews the Surface Pro as a drawing tablet: like a small Cintiq that plays games. Intriguing! http://pocket.co/s6QAN     
    
    
    ‘FACE-PLAM’, declared this angry and hilarious internet comment I just read    
    
    
    @RagingTBolt You can get a lot of those emoji built-in on the Chinese keyboard too. pic.twitter.com/8VM1qwJkAB    
    
    
    Looking at the pedagogy, I guess I see why the site is called Learn Python The Hard Way.    
    
    
    (Looking for example problems for my students before their test next week. Ended up making my own)    
    
    
    Formal teacher training means you get to use ‘pedagogy’ to win any education-related argument. Example:    
    
    
    ‘<Online learning site> is great!’
‘No it’s not because pedagogy!’
<END>    
    
    
    Gave up on Mailbox.app after 2 weeks. Main reason: I became unreasonably angry every time deferred mails returned to my inbox.    
    
    
    @zachphillips None of the email apps do a great job of searching through archived mail, I’ve found. I use Cloudmagic for that.    
    
    
    @zachphillips Cloudmagic? It lets you search across all your accounts (mail, calendar, etc)… as long as you trust it with that much access!    
    
    
    @ohryan Sorry, wrong Ryan :/    
    
    
    Wow, @mrgan’s “Brogrammer’s Story” is puns made high art. Strongly recommended. http://mrgan.tumblr.com/post/44556199571/brogrammers-story …    
    
    
    @juvejazzman I nearly died somewhere around B=NB    
    
    
    @thedak Re your Wacom tweet from yesterday — I believe they left out “for $3,000” after the ellipsis.    
    
    
    Man where did people get their cat gif fix before the internet 

Were there like cat gif print magazines    
    
    
    Corn! Actual corn! Mildly ashamed of having played a farming game for more than 89 days. pic.twitter.com/9zC7jOf5Zr    
    
    
    Just tested our new website in IE6. It’s horrific! I love it!    
    
    
    We hacked up GuestDay, an on-site guest registration system, 4(!) yrs ago… and we’re still at it. Announcing a new http://guestday.com  :)    
    
    
    Uh, please report typos, thanks    
    
    
    @pyrmont Thanks! Got to do something about the giant fading gallery though :)    
    
    
    An amusing and depressing summary of Bill Gates’ talk at #sxswedu by @audreywatters pic.twitter.com/GQRBcs45FC    
    
    
    “You are already login. Click here to surf.”

Except I’m not “already login”. Wirelessless at SG :-/    
    
    
    This may be the best Chrome extension ever: replaces occurrences of 'the cloud' in webpages with 'my butt'. https://github.com/panicsteve/cloud-to-butt …    
    
    
    But but but… it’s not April 1 guys 
http://googlereader.blogspot.com/2013/03/powering-down-google-reader.html …    
    
    
    Looking up my feedafever server name, login, and password. Grrrrrrr    
    
    
    Hey tech columnists quit filling up my Google Reader with articles and tributes to Google Reader    
    
    
    "The One Biggest Issues for Southeast Asia's Startup Ecosystem" is either the cleverest or worst headline ever. http://www.techinasia.com/not-good-enough-entrepreneurs-is-the-problem-in-southeast-asia/ …    
    
    
    They've changed it, but you can see it in the browser window title. Note the URL slug, too: not-good-enough-entrepreneurs-is-the-problem :-/    
    
    
    @RagingTBolt ‘8 cores! 13 MP camera!’ Specs seem to have impressed.    
    
    
    @andycroll What is this ‘reasonable discourse’ thing you are attempting?! I do not comprehend    
    
    
    @sangsara My nose, as ever, suffers the crushing disappointment of not being optimized for    
    
    
    @chuyeow Are those last two Instagram photos thematically related    
    
    
    This mall has some gov-setup booth on keeping marriage alive. Calling the wife to come by to start a violent argument in front of them    
    
    
    Agh! Parallel import chain Valu$ used to bring in UK Cadbury for cheap… but the latest batch is imitation horsemeat-like crap from Malaysia.    
    
    
    First Google Reader, now my Cadbury supplier. WHYYYYYY    
    
    
    Observation 1: The laksa I just had looks a lot like this cat puke I’m cleaning up.

Observation 2: I’m glad I ate early.    
    
    
    iOS developers — anyone seen this weird behaviour before? One-pixel shift in bar button item. Grateful for any help! http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15478970/uibarbuttonitem-shifting-downwards-after-a-uinavigationcontroller-push …    
    
    
    @jarrold BarButtons don’t inherit from UIView so no frame property, but good point, let me see if I can look around there…    
    
    
    Last night’s iOS problem was due to nav bar not liking 31px-tall buttons, which in turn was due to not-pixel-snapped edges (1/5 pixel off!)    
    
    
    I don’t think I read that much faster with @ReadQuickApp, but using it at 600 words/min does give a ridiculous rush http://readquickapp.com/     
    
    
    @andycroll Congrats, and, er, welcome back to our timezone?    
    
    
    "It might be good, or even better than Evernote. But I still won't use Keep. Why? Google Reader." http://prsm.tc/JiqtW0     
    
    
    @prismatic On the iPhone app, is there a way to highlight text from an article to tweet? Also, any way to combine accounts? Thanks.    
    
    
    @thedak Dead nest > live nest, right    
    
    
    @radiomaru 2cm    
    
    
    @thedak Oh unrelated*, emailed @vickiho about lunch on Sat with you & @lisiepeasie… on? Our treat for referring a client.

* really hope so    
    
    
    @thedak @lisiepeasie @vickiho Yeah next week would be better, we have something on late afternoon. Have fun recording!    
    
    
    Go to fridge, find no chocolate, eat a banana 

I’ve eaten six bananas this way today I think I need help    
    
    
    The announcer just said “UNLV has trouble against the Cal zone” and now I can’t stop imagining a basketball team fighting a calzone    
    
    
    @dsng Wow.    
    
    
    @sausheong Don’t be disheartened dude, there’s a silent majority who loves that you’re sharing what you do.    
    
    
    Cat puked on my work chair, I couldn’t get the smell out, so my pants now smell like cat puke and I finally get the concept of oversharing.    
    
    
    The Maniacal Rage Podcast by @garrettmurray is back! This makes me so happy. I fondly remember that 8-note segue. http://maniacalragepodcast.net/episodes/33     
    
    
    Picked up a Bioshock Infinite and XCOM pre-order bundle just before pre-orders end. I guess I’m done for the work week…    
    
    
    @adriantan18 @FunkeeMonk @mugunthkumar @wilfredphua My Twitter history says grey + white    
    
    
    @inkedmn git pull --rebase?    
    
    
    The Cave is on offer on Steam, so I finally bought it. Look, that "I caved" pun isn't going to write itself, ok?    
    
    
    @thedak Seriously    
    
    
    @thedak @junshenc I haven't had this much fun killing racists in ages!    
    
    
    @sangsara @thedak It’s a long weekend, man    
    
    
    @thedak @sangsara Yeah uhh it sucks. Umm not dark and dank enough for a Bioshock.    
    
    
    @thedak @Joel_Koh @junshenc This game has something to do with the sky?! SPOILER ALERT    
    
    
    @Joel_Koh @thedak @junshenc I have definitely had cheeses that would qualify for that line    
    
    
    Flipboard magazines + Google Reader going away means I might just kill my blog. My magazine is at http://flip.it/aK6mA .    
    
    
    @andycroll What if I *like* the panicky feeling of scrambling to find alternatives to something being shut down    
    
    
    Whiteboard insight from the students http://instagram.com/p/XZUbVHAP13/     
    
    
    @sangsara @thedak Hey, I'm (likely) going to SF too. (School 10 year reunion.) I've survived United to SFO many times, at my size...    
    
    
    @sangsara @thedak Freakishly large Asian high five! October for me.    
    
    
    Bom-bo-bom-bo-bom. https://vine.co/v/bjjngiiH6uX     
    
    
    Just replied to SingTel's "Your Store & Share account has been upgraded!" email with "Lol don't be stupid". I hope they reply!    
    
    
    @audreywatters To some extent, teachers are testing and iterating their lessons (I know I am). But those are cheap, small-scale tests    
    
    
    @audreywatters (Aaand I just read your next tweet.)    
    
    
    @ejames_c @andycroll But isn't that why I signed up for ImpulseFlyer's mailing list?    
    
    
    @andycroll You leave that Cadbury manufacturing plant alone now!    
    
    
    My carrier's promotional SMS is so long, they couldn't afford to fit it in a single message. pic.twitter.com/NZQWZe9aPV    
    
    
    @thedak Not that bad lah. What's going on in Pitt?    
    
    
    @jdalrymple I keep expecting you to storm out from behind this sign. pic.twitter.com/Y3O3LDch8M    
    
    
    @thedak Awesome. Umm don't blame me if you lose a limb or two k    
    
    
    Who cares about the Japanese specialty imports, Meidi-Ya has the widest variety of UK Cadbury in the country pic.twitter.com/c7dzURFRsy    
    
    
    @thedak Survived long haul UA flight! Achievement unlocked    
    
    
    It's really happening, as Scoopertino predicted last year. Tim Cook doubling down on the apology strategy: http://scoopertino.com/tim-cook-goes-on-apology-binge/ …    
    
    
    @sausheong What a troll. Sorry dude.    
    
    
    Why isn't my Instagram filling up with photos of people's fish dinners captioned "Finding Dory? Done!"? So disappointed, internet.    
    
    
    @wynlim Just read about the acquisition. Congrats! Happy for you all    
    
    
    Translated, I believe that meant "Close LucasArts? Has Disney thought about the consequences?"    
    
    
    @jarrold Ooh, looks good!    
    
    
    @RagingTBolt SO GREAT    
    
    
    The most bittersweet eulogy for Ebert, by the inimitable @TheOnion: http://flip.it/Gmx9P     
    
    
    @jarrold Awesome. You're not the only one on it, are you?    
    
    
    @lucian Does it work well? Happy with my nonsensical multi-router VPN setup, but might recommend Teleport to friends.    
    
    
    @thedak Hey, you updated your profile. So you've confirmed? Congrats!    
    
    
    I haven't gotten the Game of Thrones theme song out of my head for the last four days I need help    
    
    
    @davechua I'll just hear the tune in my head going puzzle-puzzlepuzzle-puzzlepuzzle-puzzlepuzz    
    
    
    @thedak Now no need return ticket! You're safe!!    
    
    
    @thedak Wow that's 48 hours of UA flights away    
    
    
    @pyrmont I believe the internet vernacular for this is "smh". Which is appropriate for the site!    
    
    
    @pyrmont They still rank higher than "shake my head" in a google search for smh, so there's that    
    
    
    @jarrold Will let you know if we hear of anyone worthy :)    
    
    
    Begging Snack Lady (my mother) for food https://vine.co/v/bTMaevJVTh7     
    
    
    @davechua @sangsara Man, you guys are piling on the pressure to finish that thing    
    
    
    "Zombie saves cat" is pretty much the perfect story for the internets. http://flip.it/BOEDp     
    
    
    @Horse_ebooks No WONDER my pain and suffering hasn't worked before    
    
    
    Finally finished all five episodes of the The Walking Dead game, and only because the wife kept pestering me to play it so she could watch.    
    
    
    @msvindicta Hmm I don't recall! I think just look in the opposite direction?    
    
    
    @RobSandbach Hm, I didn't get that feeling. Overall, I liked them all better than the TV series (too long-winded) and the comics (numb).    
    
    
    She hasn't been quite as taken in by Bioshock Infinite, but that could be because I keep yelling "moneymoneymoney" nonstop when I play.    
    
    
    @thedak Yeah, and she likes the series. Could be a gateway drug into more involved adventure games though.    
    
    
    @thedak Mm, been meaning to try that!    
    
    
    So I'm working with old friend (and actual artist) @eektertainment on a new Chicken comic. See http://chickochoco.com  & follow @chickochoco!    
    
    
    @eektertainment It wasn't me    
    
    
    Google apparently has time to randomly unshare documents I was working on, but not to maintain Reader. Hmph.

(I'll never stop complaining)    
    
    
    Re-shameless-self-promotion for the morning: please check out my new comic at http://chickochoco.com , and follow @chickochoco for updates    
    
    
    @eektertainment @chickochoco Shaddup worst collaborator ever    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk No need, we'll wait. Thanks for the update!    
    
    
    Comixology's Saga ban was a great move — we all jumped to blame Apple, and now more people know about their commission-free web store.    
    
    
    Finally finished Bioshock Infinite. Now to catch up with all the spoilery articles I saved for later...    
    
    
    @eektertainment Pay?!    
    
    
    @eektertainment Dammit I shouldn't have moved    
    
    
    Realised that Bioshock Infinite's big reveal is a lot like <TV series which I can't mention or I'll end up spoiling either>.    
    
    
    This is my new favourite thing: http://sportballsreplacedwithcats.tumblr.com/ 

Via @TheRoundDown, arriving in your inbox in a couple of hours if you subscribe now.    
    
    
    @JavenKing Email me? This handle at gmail.    
    
    
    @wynlim There's something about lindy hop that just appeals to nerds. I remember a lot of fellow CS students in the intro lindy class…    
    
    
    Perils of naming: I didn't open the BBQ invite from dev shop Neo because I thought it was advertising from local catering company Neo Group.    
    
    
    @eektertainment I saw them at Fort Canning a couple of months ago… rained exactly at the last song    
    
    
    @iamclovin @nitrousio Congrats! I was just thinking about using it in class... Any chance we can arrange accounts for that? :)    
    
    
    @ajhit406 @iamclovin Will do. Thanks!    
    
    
    Couldn't even stay up to midnight to announce yesterday's new @chickochoco comic. Anyway, it's at http://chickochoco.com/comic/003-aplusplusplus-would-kidnap-agai …    
    
    
    @keyist @ajhit406 @raingrove @iamclovin You guys know one another? (Not referring to the Nitrous folks knowing themselves, of course)    
    
    
    Well that was a thoroughly entertaining hour-and-half spent in traffic, he didn't think to himself    
    
    
    @coolinsights Driving, unfortunately. Finally made it though — 7km in 1.5 hours! Could have walked faster.    
    
    
    @iamclovin @keyist @ajhit406 @raingrove Super cool. Catch up when we're all in the same place :)    
    
    
    @eektertainment @chickochoco Quit it! Worst co-creator ever    
    
    
    @eektertainment @chickochoco How'd you know I was poopin    
    
    
    @eektertainment @chickochoco I'm not digging through that crap for a script    
    
    
    @eektertainment @chickochoco Eh the only people who follow us both is our comic. And maybe Tim Goh. Poor dude    
    
    
    There's... a Facebook login in the Twitter music app pic.twitter.com/yFHjJAOA92    
    
    
    @jussi Is Being Human by them? Not half bad, last I saw.    
    
    
    @jussi Ooh, new to me. That's going in this week's issue    
    
    
    FIGHT https://vine.co/v/bUXYlxdaZJD     
    
    
    @jussi Oops we ran out of space. Blame the bombs...    
    
    
    Battlin' cats make for decent enough Sunday entertainment I guess    
    
    
    Love how LastPass's default shared password accept reply is "Thank you for sharing this with me!". For effect, I like adding a few more !'s.    
    
    
    “We just didn’t invite him over after that. How many people just pick up your cat and go upstairs?” http://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2013/04/19/bombing-suspect-attended-umass-dartmouth-prompting-school-closure-college-friend-shocked-charge-boston-marathon-bomber/8gbczia4qBiWMAP0SQhViO/story.html …    
    
    
    Anyone know teachers with iPhones? We have a new app coming out for teachers, and we’d like to try and give away copies to folks you like.    
    
    
    Stay away from my fuzzy animal, says the fuzzy animal http://instagram.com/p/Ybvz2wgP7r/     
    
    
    @jussi They're all at Blk 71 nowadays, apparently.    
    
    
    Woke up at 5am and couldn't get back to sleep, so I caught up on @readmatter articles. Well worth the subscription fee.    
    
    
    @jussi Former industrial building in Ayer Rajah turned tech startup haven.    
    
    
    @sangsara that's the second time you've found a misspelling    
    
    
    Agh misspelled the URL. It's http://chickochoco.com , DYAC, etc. (thx @sangsara @thedak)    
    
    
    Shameless self-promotion riding on current local events: Check out my new and extremely unseditious comic! http://chickochoco.com     
    
    
    Excited to announce our new app for teachers is out: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/teachers-pet-to-do-lists-context/id637562954?ls=1&mt=8 … Tell your teacher friends, or better yet, gift it to them :)    
    
    
    (I hastily cobbled together the website at http://getteacherspet.com , and it's not mobile-ready yet, oops)    
    
    
    So with three launches in the last 2 months — http://guestday.com , http://chickochoco.com  & http://getteacherspet.com  —    
    
    
    ...I may occasionally become that annoying self-promoting ass for a while. Sorry!

(Also, more soon.)    
    
    
    @eektertainment Dammit    
    
    
    @StaringScreens Sorry is it because I download you guys thrice a day

No lah don't be silly congrats!!!    
    
    
    We have a new comic up for the weekend: It's got 7 freaking panels AND Hitler as a stalk of celery. http://chickochoco.com/comic/006the-asses-of-evil …    
    
    
    @eektertainment What do you mean you can't come up with new variations on the same joke twice a week    
    
    
    @vickiho Just got mine today too! (Re-got... Tried and failed to revive my faulty first-gen one last week)    
    
    
    @lucian I had the first one and it was comfortable, so I figured why not. (Would've considered the fuelband if it were here.)    
    
    
    @vickiho I totally had one before it was cool. (Not to mention functional.)    
    
    
    Woke up to find the cats did a re-staging of their digested-food stop-motion feature, Wallace and Vomit    
    
    
    Why thanks Chrome, I didn't have quite enough Tumblr bookmarklets, how could you tell pic.twitter.com/OOOXadT2pr    
    
    
    Been a big fan of Jason Collins since college. His honest and funny coming out essay: http://m.si.com/2854664/an-nba-player-comes-out/ …    
    
    
    @jdalrymple Thanks very much for the mention!    
    
    
    @thedak @vickiho Congrats on the EP launch! PayPal wouldn't let me buy on mobile for some reason though    
    
    
    @sangsara That's what they call your "tribe". Or "support group".    
    
    
    New Chicken vs. Chocolate comic is up! It's about... eh... box cutters? http://chickochoco.com/comic/007-cereal-boxcutter/ …    
    
    
    @eektertainment You lie! There's no such thing as a concerned random person on the internet    
    
    
    @sangsara Me me. Uh once I reinstall it.    
    
    
    @sangsara Have you been using Google Now a lot on iOS? How does it fit into one's life other than for searching?    
    
    
    Wife encourages me to play the new Tomb Raider so she can watch, but expressly forbids any killing of rabbits. Humph    
    
    
    @sangsara If he doesn't shower, maybe he has bigger problems than failing electronics    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie I'm ashamed to say I think it was "Amadeus"    
    
    
    @illyrica @lisiepeasie FALCO 4EVA    
    
    
    @sangsara @tricksandcider Wish I were there, but still sneezing like a madman. So... probably good I'm not there ruining it for everyone.    
    
    
    @sangsara I believe the proper result of that setup is "get well, Soon"    
    
    
    New comic and new character on @chickochoco! We may not have put much thought into this character design. http://chickochoco.com/comic/008arguing-semangtics/ …    
    
    
    Man I hate when products are made from stinking http://instagram.com/p/Y4ym2CgP28/     
    
    
    @eektertainment Up up down down don't wipe    
    
    
    @bradleychambers Thank you kind sir!    
    
    
    @jussi I like it and I know I could replace Photoshop with it for most of my needs but raaargh hate change etc. Now using it for mockups.    
    
    
    @jussi Also, can't re-appropriate parts of old designs locked in PSDs so I often end up in Photoshop, muttering "maybe next time" to myself.    
    
    
    Hmmmm pic.twitter.com/PpgUlH2UkB    
    
    
    All I need now is sleepwear and a definite article and I can say I ate the bananas in pyjamas    
    
    
    "This Ad Has a Secret Anti-Abuse Message That Only Kids Can See But We Revealed It To Everyone Whoops Ha Ha"    
    
    
    Really unnecessarily excited by adjustable round rect corners    
    
    
    Altavista Glass
Excite Glass
Lycos Glass    
    
    
    @MSchechter Sorry I've been useless at getting back to you about the plugin. Just replied to your email, let me know if you still need help!    
    
    
    Apparently SMSing the Infocomm Dev Authority about broken Wireless@SG hotspots means they will call and email you forever until it's fixed    
    
    
    Just bought Singaporean artist Drewscape's Eisner-nominated graphic novel. Now to read it while singing Majulah Singapura    
    
    
    @sangsara Physical, wife happened to want to go to Cat Socrates at Bras Basah. Turns out that was one of his early distributors!    
    
    
    @b_catenin Gotta love those government service level promises    
    
    
    New comic up today at http://chickochoco.com , which I now live in fear of mistyping    
    
    
    @ajhit406 yeah, it's not a bad problem to have (here, I mean)    
    
    
    Love how doctors walk around with their stethoscopes at lunchtime. Gonna look into hanging a laptop running Xcode & Photoshop around my neck    
    
    
    Vampires Who Snore When Sleeping On Their Backs    
    
    
    @mrbrown That's why it's Into Darkness, so everyone can see his lens flare    
    
    
    Nooooo I've run out of things to read while lying down and refusing to acknowledge my awakeness    
    
    
    @MSchechter Did it work?    
    
    
    @MSchechter Cool. Let me know if you need any more tips :)    
    
    
    @namedotcom Umm, I _just_ reset my password manually from the webpage this morning… and you went and reset it again?!    
    
    
    @namedotcom No, I got a second "please reset " email, and when I logged in, was told to reset again. Just don't do it again please!    
    
    
    Why isn't saying API Interfaces a thing    
    
    
    Working on Features Nobody Asked For for our next IC Photo app update. Can't wait to write the release notes    
    
    
    @jdalrymple Congrats Jim! Glad to see the magazine finally out there :)    
    
    
    @jdalrymple I'm having problems restoring subscription on a second device. Am I the only one? Let me know who to send details to if need...    
    
    
    Ooooh we found an easter egg in our own app. So exciting!!! Because it's an easter egg and uh not a bug.    
    
    
    @ExtraTan Wow, I no longer feel like I have a surname that's easily made fun of. "That's gross loh!"    
    
    
    What do you mean you don't also spend most of your time on Twitter looking up replies to horse_ebooks    
    
    
    I've been told that in disagreements, one should always strive to be the bigger person. I tried and now my BMI is 30 :(    
    
    
    @eektertainment Nom Nom Nominal    
    
    
    @pyrmont The appropriate thing to do would be to reply with 
*･゜ﾟ･*:.｡..｡.:*･'(*ﾟ▽ﾟ*)'･*:.｡. .｡.:*･゜ﾟ･*

(From the iOS Chinese keyboard)    
    
    
    @pyrmont Those silly Asians!    
    
    
    A surprisingly uncynical view of the GaTech/Udacity/AT&T Master's & the usual sadly-never-gonna-happen ed tech ideas http://flip.it/UJ7Bk     
    
    
    Cats will be confused about breakfast time when I wake at 4.30 to pick my visiting cousin up from airport. I should get them wristwatches    
    
    
    @joycesohn You're still using your UP?    
    
    
    @joycesohn Cool! I started using mine again recently. Let me try and find you to add :)    
    
    
    @eektertainment Weird metal like gallium?    
    
    
    @eektertainment Buy us a 3D printer and print Chicken & Chocolate merch k    
    
    
    @ajhit406 @iamclovin Trying to do a class using nitrous now, and forgot to get invites for the students. Any chance you have codes ready? :P    
    
    
    @iamclovin @ajhit406 8 please :) Thanks!    
    
    
    @iamclovin I suspect you might be chatting with a couple of them -__-    
    
    
    @iamclovin Ah ok, got the conflicting message to email you. Ignore that :)    
    
    
    @iamclovin Thanks a bunch!    
    
    
    @iamclovin And thanks for humoring the students :P    
    
    
    @keyist Shhhh    
    
    
    Thx @iamclovin for getting our students onto @nitrousio for intro Rails class & for humouring idiot student who begged for invite on webchat    
    
    
    Wow, that was fast — 3 days approval for our IC Photo update! Here are the ridiculous release notes: pic.twitter.com/0QHU1El1es    
    
    
    @thedak Yeah I've misspelled it three out of four times I didn't copy and paste... :p    
    
    
    @thedak Seriously considering it actually. We'll see :)    
    
    
    @eektertainment That's the car with the singing animals?    
    
    
    @eektertainment Why didn't you steal it    
    
    
    @eektertainment What am I paying you for dammit    
    
    
    @eektertainment Printer printer? Printer printer 3D canon printering printer    
    
    
    @b_catenin Only for head-shaped bicycles    
    
    
    @eektertainment IT WORKEDDDD    
    
    
    @eektertainment I guess I did have 6 printers in that last tweet    
    
    
    @eektertainment What if we make a bot to just say printer a lot    
    
    
    @eektertainment Botswana bet    
    
    
    @b_catenin And happy birthday!    
    
    
    SUPER EXCITED https://vine.co/v/b9eqPVEwj7m     
    
    
    ATTACK https://vine.co/v/b9eMelrlUhX     
    
    
    @chuyeow Some battery-operated Japanese toy we bought from Pet Lovers Centre    
    
    
    @zachphillips I tried it last week and couldn't lift my arms for a day. I haven't dared attempt it since    
    
    
    @zachphillips I also recall I was panting so hard my cats were becoming afraid of me. What is this sorcery    
    
    
    @vickiho What then we won't see the inevitable Fall is Falling    
    
    
    Confusing a cat    
    
    
    @eektertainment Wow thanks, I didn't know the damn thing auto-tweeted for me    
    
    
    @eektertainment Mang I hate dose bots    
    
    
    @eektertainment Ooh tempting    
    
    
    @eektertainment Maybe you needed 3D    
    
    
    Twitter 2-factor authentication: not cat-proof, as demonstrated by Twitter co-founder. pic.twitter.com/qbd8zcE0Go    
    
    
    Did the government just call for tenders on… agile software development? Great buzzword-searching there, bureaucrats! http://www.todayonline.com/singapore/govt-call-s12b-worth-it-tenders …    
    
    
    Hello I propose a $2M project to deliver "agile software development" for you    
    
    
    @pyrmont Sorry, which? Didn't see a replied-to link..    
    
    
    @pyrmont Ah yes. You're not the first person to send that to me :)    
    
    
    What in the world have they done to the Chrome URL font    
    
    
    I fell asleep last night and forgot to draw my part for the @chickochoco comic so Chicken is more feathery this time: http://chickochoco.com/comic/014-shenanigans/ …    
    
    
    @thedak Lovely stuff! Don't stop    
    
    
    Candy store employee giving me dirty looks for checking Cadbury chocolate & making disgusted sounds when I find out they're from Australia    
    
    
        
    
    
    Annual reservist training for a week from tomorrow. Maybe now I'll make a tiny dent in my read-later queue.    
    
    
    @pyrmont I wouldn't be so annoyed if it weren't the de facto type we get here...    
    
    
    Things to do at reservist: bust my data cap watching Arrested Development    
    
    
    @eektertainment omg quicksilver is Jamie Lannister    
    
    
    Time passes awfully slowly in here    
    
    
    More like Ah Men To Lao Uncles    
    
    
    @eektertainment I escaped! For a couple hours    
    
    
    Whoever at DairyFarm Group decided to put UK Cadbury at random in their supermarkets has made grocery shopping into an adventure game for me    
    
    
    @thedak @lisiepeasie @vickiho @sangsara > eating ice cream in reservist    
    
    
    @thedak @lisiepeasie @vickiho @sangsara I swear there is nothing to do but eat. I walked around the office for 30 minutes though.    
    
    
    @vickiho Oh dear/ew. Get well soon!    
    
    
    Reservist, otherwise known as getting dumb & fat week    
    
    
    @sangsara Too dumb to use when wearing green solly    
    
    
    UK Cadbury, Toffee Popcorn flavour?! Now these importers are just  trying to see if I'll really buy anything    
    
    
    I just went and compared our comic to Watchmen (pretty unfavorably, but still) http://chickochoco.com     
    
    
    Am I the only one who keeps x-ing out friends' updates and yelling at Facebook "STOP IT I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT PERSON STOP TRYING"    
    
    
    Two accounts for the LOLs: @GooglePoetics and @RedWeddingTears (Game of Thrones). Both spoilerific, the latter perhaps more so.    
    
    
    Dispatch, a great-looking new email iPhone app by local devs @honcheng and @jjlin: http://www.dispatchapp.net/     
    
    
    Not sure how to feel about the ULTRA-FRANTIC DEMO VIDEO, which made me dizzy and/or want to watch again    
    
    
    @eektertainment HmmmMMMmmmMMmmm    
    
    
    Instructing cats on how to take care of my pregnant wife for next few days, because my family forbade her to attend my grandfather's wake.    
    
    
    That last tweet was carefully designed to maximise confused responses, e.g. "Congrats/Condolences/Cats?!" Don't disappoint me, Twitters    
    
    
    (Anyway, I'm ok, glad he didn't suffer for too long, but watching out for my mum who's understandably a wreck.)    
    
    
    Dammit cat I gave you one job pic.twitter.com/RzIaWB6HKl    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie @thedak Thanks you two! Appreciate the thoughts :) Now wondering how to avoid 500 steps a day for next few days…    
    
    
    @pyrmont Thanks! :)    
    
    
    Should have volunteered for tomorrow night's shift at the wake because WWDC. Ah well this will help adjust my body clock    
    
    
    Apparently my job scope for the wake is to chase away cats. I'm so very well-trained at this    
    
    
    @eektertainment Backpack?! Are you crazy

I parked my car right here for that    
    
    
    Local man who died of dengue lived in AMK Ave 3, which is where I'm staying overnight for a wake. Went to buy a couple of mosquito coils…    
    
    
    @eektertainment Reported for spelling    
    
    
    iMac's drive went nuts, I formatted it, then found out Time Machine backup is dead. Anyway, can't wait for new Apple product announcements!!    
    
    
    @jarrold Haven't decided yet... trying to fix my backups, will see how long that takes :P    
    
    
    @jarrold Fwah! Mine was a Fusion Drive related issue—wouldn't boot after updating to 10.8.4, Disk Utility couldn't recognise the drive    
    
    
    @thedak Also had to send car in for repair. Lovely few days eh    
    
    
    Got my backups back! I no longer need to feel mildly conflicted about whether to buy the latest to-be-announced Apple products I don't need!    
    
    
    @thedak Yup have crashplan but somehow don't feel like restoring from it because it'd be so slow... which makes me wonder why I pay for it    
    
    
    Sums up iOS 7 for me:

“@waxpancake: Jony Ive redesigns the dollar. http://waxy.org/random/images/weblog/ios7_dollar-20130610-125125.png …”    
    
    
    Any word on new Xcode? I wonder what the default elements look like now in Interface Builder    
    
    
    @eektertainment Who are you and how did you get on my Twotters    
    
    
    @eektertainment I actually meant to say Twitters but autocorrect is funnier than me    
    
    
    @nickheer You installed? Any major app incompatibilities?    
    
    
    @nickheer Always worried about my third-party apps when updating. Guess I'll give it a shot later in the cycle.    
    
    
    @zachphillips "Personal Hotspot (Internet Tethering) will not work if this seed of the iOS SDK 7.0 is installed."    
    
    
    @gssq You should wear a "young girl" t-shirt    
    
    
    Reading the iOS 7 UI design guidelines, and there's a lot of emphasis on Auto Layout and Dynamic Type. Another screen size coming soon?    
    
    
    The wake's over, whew. I can finally start fretting about those iOS 7 icons!!!!1

But first, draw some Chicken, then sleep    
    
    
    @zachphillips Got that from the release notes, but colleague reports it doesn't seem to be gone. Worth asking around, I guess.    
    
    
    After an hour of testing, isolates which of two third-party RAM sticks was causing kernel panics

Puts it together with the working one

ARG    
    
    
    @eektertainment Good point, remedying that    
    
    
    Awesome folks kept @TheRoundDown and @chickochoco going strong while I was out of action: thanks @sangsara & @eektertainment respectively!    
    
    
    By “going strong” I mean “still had consistently terrible jokes”, which is the best metric for everything    
    
    
    A 27" tablet-PC hybrid that ships with air hockey pucks! I think I want one. http://flip.it/DECnV     
    
    
    @eektertainment Why are you so excited about a West Coast division of the Blackberry company    
    
    
    Oh and new comic: http://chickochoco.com/comic/020-searching-aim-lessly …    
    
    
    Wife's comment during Man of Steel: "Oh, cool! He found some hair gel with the costume in his ship!"    
    
    
    That, and the RSS feeds. RSS feeds!    
    
    
    @davechua I really enjoyed it! Started off slow and picked up the pace, like the zombies.    
    
    
    iOS 7 totally stole design cues such as heavy background blurring and colorful circles from… the NDP 2013 website? http://ndp.org.sg/     
    
    
    @chuyeow My Time Capsule doesn’t have _that_ great range. New one could, though, and the price isn’t too bad for what it does.    
    
    
    @zachphillips Good to know! Going ahead to install on my main device, because I really need to get used to this to redesign our apps.    
    
    
    @zachphillips There're a bunch of location and data toggles you can turn off to conserve some battery, perhaps those might help..    
    
    
    @zachphillips General - Background App Refresh; Privacy - Location - System Services are the ones I've been advised on    
    
    
    Reddit love for the comic would be very much appreciated: http://www.reddit.com/r/webcomics/comments/1gljc9/a_webcomic_review_of_man_of_steel_as_discussed_by/ …

(Also, new comic, sorry for the spam, thanks)    
    
    
    Heyz, the air is haze-ardous, don’t be haze-ty to go out, even if you cr-haze-ily crave a haze-lnut latte omg what am I saying I’m sorry    
    
    
    Locke & Key movie! Best comic I've read in years. Too much story for one movie, though.  http://on.mtv.com/17nXUjW     
    
    
    Someone left a review that says "this app presents information in an elegant manor". Major skeuomorphism, man    
    
    
    The Atlantic's In Focus takes on the Singapore Haze, because lol at the irony of blurry photos "in focus" http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2013/06/singapore-haze/100538/ …    
    
    
    NPR Sports, a parody of NBA Finals commentary. Why is NPR Sports not an actual thing?! http://youtu.be/nZhEGxI09-Y     
    
    
    North West? That the best silly name you can burden your son with, Kanye?  (Currently considering "Kah Ming Soon" for mine)    
    
    
    Dear Samsung, I Really do want to deny this Email, because I clicked the ‘yes’ button just now https://www.dropbox.com/s/376qql2takaobso/Screenshot%202013-06-27%2001.15.43.PNG …    
    
    
    @nickheer I think it means “you cannot unsubscribe lol”, because I clicked OK and nothing happened    
    
    
    We’ve been posting new comics regularly at http://chickochoco.com . Please subscribe in your Google Reader! Thanks!!! 

Wait what    
    
    
    @eektertainment I been got    
    
    
    Oh good my replacement RAM is here. No more living on only 16GB like a savage    
    
    
    @eektertainment Ooh I love Krispy Kreme    
    
    
    @thedak I know rite    
    
    
    Saw a mention of @Uber_TPE and wondered briefly why they set up a hyper-local service that only served the Tampines Expressway    
    
    
    @thedak Nah pretty happy with my iMac for now. It really was getting cranky on less RAM though    
    
    
    @eektertainment Sugar is sugar mang    
    
    
    @eektertainment Barmang sings Def Leppard karaoke, goes "Pour some sugar on me", gets eaten, the end    
    
    
    According to Google Translate, one of Sun Tzu's tenets from the Art of War is... "Kill the mutant" pic.twitter.com/PpmbBUHqso    
    
    
    We spent 2.5 years training the cat to sit on our laps so we could make YouTube videos of of him "dancing": http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f3ZgBbiRHbI …    
    
    
    Over at @chickochoco, we made a comic lamenting the death of Google Reader: http://chickochoco.com/comic/025-reader-i-arrdly-even-knew-er …    
    
    
    @eektertainment Like, literally collide    
    
    
    @thedak @StaringScreens I hope you’re happy with our “Mattricks of Leadership” one in this week’s @TheRoundDown.    
    
    
    SingTel apparently has servers in “Alto Palo” pic.twitter.com/GyvSKfPVkI    
    
    
    @eektertainment She has servers in a tall tree? Well sheeyit    
    
    
    @eektertainment Oh so you know all about ass bots, including the random ones    
    
    
    @eektertainment I like big bots and I cannot lie    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie So tempted to try    
    
    
    @pyrmont @feedly Vehemently agree. There are other options too but they're all weird.    
    
    
    @vickiho @lisiepeasie Lol. I was just wondering last night whether UP would fit as a cat collar… (won’t try, they’re cranky about collars)    
    
    
    I always appreciate comics about chickens http://camodad.com/archives/246     
    
    
    Thanks for the mailbox spam, guys! I always wondered where to find a realty mager and a principle director. pic.twitter.com/rl5u1mQUtK    
    
    
    @eektertainment SAWBS    
    
    
    @iamclovin Ooh! Congrats :)    
    
    
    “You Surf, We Serve”: Man, our tax portal’s motto is just dripping with contempt for us web-surfing slackers pic.twitter.com/2SzZy1ZetO    
    
    
    @eektertainment Shaddup art school    
    
    
    @eektertainment Mang you’re not very eektertaining    
    
    
    @chuyeow Sonic has to drive safe also or he’ll lose his rings mah    
    
    
    "A movie like Sharknado[…] should be judged on how well it fulfils the standards of a movie with the title Sharknado" http://entertainment.time.com/2013/07/12/perfect-storm-the-genius-of-sharknado/ …    
    
    
    EEK's still busy watching Pacific Rim, so I got to turn @chickochoco back into a stupidchicken comic for one episode: http://chickochoco.com/comic/028-chicken-vs/ …    
    
    
    Side benefit of the wifi weighing scale: cat sits on it pretty regularly, readings show up on app, get to laugh at it for being fat    
    
    
    @eektertainment Yes don't you    
    
    
    @eektertainment Pants what are pants    
    
    
    Stacked cats http://instagram.com/p/byKeIvAPwC/     
    
    
    @thedak @lisiepeasie Yay!! Many many congrats!!!    
    
    
    @vickiho @thedak @lisiepeasie Wasn’t the engagement announcement an hour ago? Well that escalated quickly    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie @sangsara @thedak I'm confused, was it a wedding or engagement? Or both? Double congrats if so!    
    
    
    Help I've fallen down and can't get up oh look tweets to read lying down nevermind then    
    
    
    Wolverine: The Musical. I lost it around when Multiple Man showed up http://youtu.be/xy8FjcmDgck     
    
    
    Yeah this rain is so much better than the haze <walks around looking like someone dumped a bucket of water on him>    
    
    
    "Remind me tomorrow at 10am that I parked on the second floor" is the full extent of my Siri usage nowadays    
    
    
    While I was out the cats apparently fought over the Chinese language assessment books. Well done cats    
    
    
    I saw this Pitchfork Bat For Lashes “article”, and suddenly felt like throwing money at Pocket/Instapaper/Readability http://pitchfork.com/features/cover-story/reader/bat-for-lashes/ …    
    
    
    @theloop @jdalrymple I'd just bought an 8-inch Acer tablet when you posted that! The Android one, for work. It's.... not horrific, I guess.    
    
    
    Installation art cat http://instagram.com/p/b7qvb7AP93/     
    
    
    @StaringScreens Re: Joel's barely-audible comment in latest episode -- Infinite Crisis! Not Marvel!

Sorry, breathing normally now    
    
    
    @StaringScreens Brb adding "accused by gaming podcast of being a nerd" to my LinkedIn now    
    
    
    Weird, iPhone completely bricked itself — blank screen, no response to charging cable. (Can't reset it because power button broken.) Fun!    
    
    
    Stumbled across this MS page on how to use Windows 8. Actually useful, but the videos demo the _same_ thing 3+ times? http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-8/tutorial …    
    
    
    Oh UOB you and your imaginary "Secure Zone" pic.twitter.com/tehioh64Xu    
    
    
    @eektertainment Quit picking on different things than what I'm making fun of dammit    
    
    
    @eektertainment Like that time with the tax portal

Now I'm angry or something    
    
    
    @eektertainment Hate-faving is the best faving    
    
    
    - Wait till kiwi fruit ripens
- Cut in half
- Carefully scoop out fruit portion
- Drop it on floor
- Tweet about it, sobbing uncontrollably    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk Thanks so much man! Tomorrow I'll be running around the whole day though then have a wedding dinner to attend though..    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk I can come pick up from yr place on Sun or after? Or meet to buy you lunch sometime? Sorry for all the trouble, and thanks lots    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk @mugunthkumar Oh hm perhaps! What time?    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk I'll be passing by around 10 and 3. Will either time be ok?    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk I'll SMS you before I head over then. Much appreciated!    
    
    
    Nooooo its an its/it's error right in the middle of a comic I was enjoying    
    
    
    GV has new faulty JavaScript to enable their submit button, so I couldn't book my movie. Solution: DELETE ATTRIBUTE pic.twitter.com/Q8Mkin81vv    
    
    
    Nevermind the movie, that mid-credits sequence! #wolverinemovie #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/16pVoV2     
    
    
    Post-The Wolverine conversation with The Wiferine:

Her: What was Jean Grey's power?
Me: She was a telepath. 
Her: She was a curry puff?!    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Happy birthday!    
    
    
    @m0t0chan Woo congrats!    
    
    
    Really like the responsive design at the Trask Industries site. Mutant-killing-sentinel-makers sure know their HTML5! http://www.trask-industries.com/     
    
    
    Sometimes I over-react to spammers. Thank! pic.twitter.com/cLveRr7fMg    
    
    
    @eektertainment Those arent my number thank!    
    
    
    @eektertainment Here pic.twitter.com/TLOwgxxJoi    
    
    
    My double all-nighters seem to have confused the cats into sleeping all day.    
    
    
    After 3 days with a total of 10 hours of sleep, finally done delivering this Android course. Time to sleep till Saturday goodnight guyz    
    
    
    @downcastapp Getting error initializing sync on all 4 iCloud sync settings on iPhone. This was after I updated desktop app. Any way to fix?    
    
    
    @downcastapp I'll try that when I get back to my desktop. Thanks!    
    
    
    Places to buy UK Cadbury in Singapore: (some) Cold Storages, Valu$, Meidi-Ya, and... Venus Beauty  neighborhood cosmetic shop in Toa Payoh?!    
    
    
    Filing under "future parenting tips" http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/smbc-comics/PvLb/~3/7xuByEf2yBE/index.php …    
    
    
    @eektertainment me me I got more reasons will I win a prize    
    
    
    Came across http://www.reddit.com/r/petloss , now sobbing uncontrollably. Will now attempt to hug cat and get scratched and end up crying some more    
    
    
    @eektertainment aw mang now i'm the idiot    
    
    
    @bradleychambers I ended up with Downcast too; no idea Pocketcasts was on iOS! (Also, I think you meant irrelevant not irreverent somewhere)    
    
    
    Somehow, I had to look into cross-browser CSS issues (specifically, background-position-x) on Firefox for… my comic. http://chickochoco.com/comic/037/     
    
    
    @honcheng Much subtler than mine who just SCREAMS IN MY FACE for everything    
    
    
    Great deal on EA titles at current Humble Bundle. And EA is sending on all their proceeds to charity! http://www.humblebundle.com     
    
    
    Throat is going. Damn you throat I needed a vacation first    
    
    
    @eektertainment While eating durian yeah    
    
    
    @downcastapp Reset iCloud syncing once before for this, worked for a while, but today I got "error initializing sync" again. Any way to fix?    
    
    
    @downcastapp Do you mean disable all of iCloud Documents & Data, not just Downcast?    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Sorry to hear that. I picked up the flu myself last night and I'm so confused about the time of day now from all the sleeping    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Waiting for the persistent cough to go away. Get well soon too!    
    
    
    I still can't feel my throoaaaat

Why am I yellinggggg this    
    
    
    @eektertainment You mean @chickochoco? Sawbs    
    
    
    @eektertainment "It makes you're sick"    
    
    
    Cat engrossed in National Day Rally http://instagram.com/p/dKCLtFgP9U/     
    
    
    Oh man that was boring http://instagram.com/p/dKDUUhgP-0/     
    
    
    WORST NOSE EVAR ★☆☆☆☆    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Out of warranty from frequent misuse    
    
    
    Dangerous, but so satisfying:

cd Dropbox
find . -name *conflicted\ copy* -delete

(Don't try at home kids etc.)    
    
    
    Running three Android emulators on my 2+ year old MacBook Air like a boss. An old, sluggish boss who's about to die of a heart attack.    
    
    
    @thedak Quick!!! Go hang out with the undergrads like a creepy grad student!!!    
    
    
    @davechua Looking forward to it!    
    
    
    Whoa, my Amazon GlobalSaver order arrived in 2 working days from the US (ordered Thursday). Who needs Prime, man    
    
    
    My reply to a "NIE trained school teacher" spammer: pic.twitter.com/4Y1EM6DtQy    
    
    
    @sangsara But but but if you hold up your iPhone to take a selfie with that case on, it'd be like a SEE-THROUGH PHONE    
    
    
    Is there a lozenge eating competition out there I can apply for and win    
    
    
    @honcheng Yeah, or use it with someone familiar with the terminology/workflow    
    
    
    Mindef introduces… Really Unresponsive Web Design. pic.twitter.com/fcTHpL0tnr    
    
    
    What other sugary goods can I ingest alarming amounts of now that I'm off that stupid diet    
    
    
    @nickheer That's just disturbing    
    
    
    @eektertainment What no ick    
    
    
    @eektertainment You can't just end every sentence with "my ass" and expect to sound cool mang    
    
    
    What! Nobody told me it was All Rechargeable Batteries Simultaneously Run Out Day    
    
    
    Great Zen Pencils piece today http://zenpencils.com/comic/128-bill-watterson-a-cartoonists-advice …    
    
    
    I need a keyboard shortcut for “search Google for git push new branch”    
    
    
    I read an internet comment by accident and it angrily declared that the author "has been shown to be a lair" and now I can't stop giggling    
    
    
    A new comic… barely. http://chickochoco.com/comic/sick-day-part-2-rks-returns/ …    
    
    
    @eektertainment Sheeyit    
    
    
    Hell yes @rocksontan is back and on form http://rockson.blogspot.com/2013/08/rockson-love-serina-swee.html …    
    
    
    @eektertainment Don't make me send you another chicken-killer video wait or did you send that to me    
    
    
    @b_catenin Eh you clicked on phishing link ah    
    
    
    @mrbrown But what if people ignore them and sit down and use your children to wipe their nose    
    
    
    @sangsara That good! I might get mine fixed up soon then.    
    
    
    Time for my daily round of "I don't want to see this" clicks on Facebook why am I even using that site    
    
    
    @eektertainment http://twitter.com/feffrey/status/374137633560989696 …    
    
    
    Awesome. Congrats Viki crew! “@karaswisher: Exclusive: Japan’s Rakuten Acquires Viki Video Site for $200 Million http://dthin.gs/19b1cnz ”    
    
    
        
    
    
    @eektertainment Sawry mang!!!    
    
    
    @pyrmont Nice one    
    
    
    @andycroll Great post. (Word 5: its, not it's :)    
    
    
    25 Integers To Use In Your Next SEO-Friendly Blog Post Title    
    
    
    @andycroll Sorry to be That Guy On The Internet :p    
    
    
    I actually REALLY want a Kit Kat now after watching their Jony Ive spoof video http://youtu.be/OKOrkLxOBoY     
    
    
    @eektertainment No.    
    
    
    @eektertainment I know let's have a character who argues on the internet    
    
    
    Yay for the new Google Drive iOS icon! Boo for Google's steadfastness in adding chins to all their icons.    
    
    
    Time to go find a questionable online video source to watch Stanford football games the rest of the year from here    
    
    
    @JennyAnnChou No legal ways, even if I wanted to pay. So I have to use... less than reputable sources.    
    
    
    Saw a Nutella cupcake recipe and: mentally multiplied  Nutella serving by 20, wondered why I'd bother with flour, realised why I don't bake    
    
    
    No no no Alfred I meant to open Xcode not XCOM ah well no choice but to goof off for a couple of hours then    
    
    
    Where's the nearest toilet, my motion coprocessor is activating    
    
    
    Right side of iPhone registering phantom touches. Have so far sent a tweet, an email, some SMSes. Thanks, right-side send button placement!    
    
    
    @nickheer Error report: "With its myriad features, it’s we often forget", somewhere around word.... 62,000? :)    
    
    
    Gold 5S's on SingTel ran out in 2 minutes (my wife wanted one). They did good on the load balancing this year though!    
    
    
    @tsewei Nope, failed at the gold. Reserved a black instead, will see if she wants to wait.    
    
    
    @chuyeow You mean the not-crashing site for once? The cause for hope was when the URL they gave started with "cdn."...    
    
    
    Got damaged iPhone 5 replaced at telco for faulty power button. Yay, resale value!, I thought, then dropped & chipped it in the same corners    
    
    
    @tsewei Re the NTU comment — that's exactly what the wife said!    
    
    
    Wait, Google launched a calico cat where?!    
    
    
    Watched next to normal. Recommended except for the pervasive smell of sock. (This might or might not have been a feature.)    
    
    
    My mother just sent me a pleased-sounding message to tell me she had upgraded to iOS 7 without my help    
    
    
    @eektertainment Speak like a pirate mang    
    
    
    Getting ready with thematic snacks for The World's End pic.twitter.com/HmG3TGgBgQ    
    
    
    20-0! Maybe I should have woken up earlier for the game. #gostanford    
    
    
    Not sure if football game or physical comedy #gostanford    
    
    
    I imagine this game with the Benny Hill theme playing in the background #gostanford    
    
    
    @eektertainment Sawbs    
    
    
    Oh also the comic is baaaaaack http://chickochoco.com     
    
    
    @lisiepeasie We're very proud of that one    
    
    
    Got my 5s real quick at the SingTel launch event at Marina Bay Sands... But now I have to wait 3 hours in traffic to exit the F1 area.    
    
    
    New phone is all set up! ...Now I have no idea what to do with it other than repeatedly lock and unlock it with Touch ID.    
    
    
    @pyrmont Grey 32GB. My telco was out of white and golds but still had leftover greys for walk-ins.    
    
    
    I miss sliding to unlock already    
    
    
    Never mind the Touch ID  hack, the real question is how did anyone manage to get his cat's paw still for a whole minute to train the sensor    
    
    
    525,600 minutes! 
How do you measure a year? 
Seasons of iPhone upgraaaaaades    
    
    
    @johncarneyau When he saved a search for his name on Twitter?    
    
    
    Noooooooo don't go away horse http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/elements/2013/09/horse-ebooks-and-pronunciation-book-revealed.html …    
    
    
    Not going to deny that proximity to late night prata was a factor in home purchase decision (@ Thohirah Restaurant) http://4sq.com/19AIHHu     
    
    
    @nickheer Nice. Congrats! Now to tell everyone I knew you pre-DF link.    
    
    
    @mrbrown Re iOS 7 calendar — tapping search to get list view not permanent enough?    
    
    
    @nickheer Re Clear: backlash was because iPhone-only users saw no difference after paying again. iPad-only might've gone over better.    
    
    
    @nickheer Yeah I didn't rebuy, but it seems enough people did to leave a ton of nasty reviews. Maybe they expected some iOS 7 niceties?    
    
    
    Denial, anger, bargaining, SNACKS    
    
    
    @eektertainment Did you watch that same episode for three hours    
    
    
    Reading up on EasyJet fiasco http://boingboing.net/2013/09/25/easyjet-tells-law-professor-he.html#more-257929 …, childishly amused to see the rep sign off as "CB" on replies: pic.twitter.com/MXMwrt45ZS    
    
    
    @tjathurman It's a local thing, I'm afraid — CB is short for a particularly overused Hokkien curse word involving female anatomy.    
    
    
    @tjathurman As do football headlines like today's "Richards says Pellegrini doesn't see him as a CB".    
    
    
    Hey I need some tissue WAIT A MINUTE WHAT IS THIS DAMN YOU HUMANS http://instagram.com/p/eunthlAP-L/     
    
    
    I love it when one of my programming class students is designated as "Anonymous Nyan Cat" on a shared Google Doc pic.twitter.com/6f52MLZmqN    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Not sure I'd lump @thedak in with "the sweetest girls" but what do I know    
    
    
    @eektertainment Oh cool I always wanted to grow a cynicism tree thanks    
    
    
    Cat went for skin biopsy and I'm heartbroken seeing her giant stitches and how am I going to be a parent to a human when I get like this now    
    
    
    Found an alternative to the e-collar though: ridiculous shirts we used to buy for the cats. http://instagram.com/p/e4sVnGgP_p/     
    
    
    Read Breaking Bad finale reviews that proclaimed "for every action there's an equal and opposite reaction" that's not chemistry you asses    
    
    
    @Joel_Koh Deleted unnecessarily that-guy-on-the-internet tweet. Pardon me!    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Wow, I honestly had no idea    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie As in I had no idea those existed, because that's what the wife must have been doing!    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie In any case I approve and must now take a listen    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie That was... the cats. Yeah    
    
    
    This iPad is the best half-kilogram 3G modem ever    
    
    
    @ExtraTan Ya. Stupid reduced 4G limits hmp    
    
    
    "Hey I forgot, are we meeting at Bishan or Novena at 2.30?"
"Busan"
"OK"

Thanks autocorrect, now I have to get to Korea in half an hour    
    
    
    “@derozard: Apple hires cable TV technology exec for “something big" http://feedly.com/k/18qC9NN ”

Woohoo 27" iPad    
    
    
    "What am I to you, chopped liver? Yes? Aww, thanks!" - kway chap hawker    
    
    
    It's Children's Day here, which is kind of like Hungry Ghosts Festival but instead of ghosts we have hungry children everywhere    
    
    
    @eektertainment All bots    
    
    
    @eektertainment Sob printer nobody printer loves printer me printer printer    
    
    
    @eektertainment I'm not your bot bitch    
    
    
    @eektertainment Yes, in episode 300    
    
    
    Baby fair duties: queueing, paying, not letting feet get rolled over by strollers (@ Singapore Expo w/ @joeyweini) http://4sq.com/1hrnML8     
    
    
    "Please do not throw any articles into urinal"

*Puts away newspaper clipping, feels despondent*    
    
    
        
    
    
    @sangsara Is that what's going on in the app? Worked ok in iTunes though when I tried last month.    
    
    
    Mother-in-law sets table for dinner; me: "Oh crap! Gold 5S's are in stock!"; wife and I rush out of house. Sorry, mama.    
    
    
    @zachphillips Yup, just got the elusive thing in my hands. It's the wife's, though. Quite happy with my grey one    
    
    
    $1mm = one dollar millimetres    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Get Amazon Prime, stock up on stuff in your basket, look forward to hitting "Buy" before you leave. Instant readiness    
    
    
    Wife, with third trimester insomnia, has taken to texting me what I babble in my sleep. Tonight was WA YAI YAI YAI “in a gruff voice”.    
    
    
    @pyrmont Thanks!    
    
    
    @eektertainment Naw mang    
    
    
    Vet called with lump biopsy results. Benign! Yay!! http://instagram.com/p/fcQHMRAP35/     
    
    
    Much needed relief, too... Found three new lumps last night on her, and was prepared for the worst.    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Maybe because she knows we don't have to activate the emergency spoil-her-rotten-before-the-end plan just yet.    
    
    
    So I downloaded GIF Finder and I searched for cat and I haven't been able to use my phone for anything else since pic.twitter.com/lyiW28IEIA    
    
    
    Is there a Launch Center Pro shortcut to directly add an entry to MyFitnessPal for 2 tablespoons of Nutella as a meal? Because uh no reason    
    
    
    @brainopera Excellent truncation in your tweet: "For the third dish, this kid..."    
    
    
    Oh, how nice! <Local MP>'s Photoshop-cutout face wishes me Happy <Next Chronological Festival> in a timely manner, as usual!    
    
    
    If you've ever tried any kind of vector-based design, watch this dude draw iOS 7 in Word. Slack-jawed amazement. http://youtu.be/RZp7BvQJnU8     
    
    
    Procrastination: a story in an Asana screenshot pic.twitter.com/mvNP8T1vTm    
    
    
    @sangsara Put up Pokemon training as a skill and I'll endorse you    
    
    
    @sangsara Likewise!    
    
    
    The Black Knight??! Damn it Schiller! *turns off stream, goes to sleep*    
    
    
    Oh sweet, a motion sensor on the new Mac Pro. Shake to undo!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Seen in Mail, Preferences, Accounts: what in the pic.twitter.com/RpR9rar5sx    
    
    
    Use Gmail on OS X Mavericks Mail.app? Archive emails by deleting? DON’T. Use ctrl-cmd-a or archive button instead. http://tidbits.com/article/14219     
    
    
    From article: Mail.app now automatically maps your Gmail’s Trash folder to your own, so your deleted mails will be gone in 30 days.    
    
    
    Love the text on this $2 iPhone case the wife bought off Taobao pic.twitter.com/UGmjvXo1lJ    
    
    
    $2.99 to be told I’m still in Johor Bahru?! One star    
    
    
    @sangsara Yeah I appreciate the effort that goes into each update, but the “I pay for things” drum has been beaten way too loudly for me    
    
    
    Hmm. There’s really no reason @getglue needs to use 15MB of cellular data for me to check in to *one* movie…    
    
    
    It was a great movie, though. Totally worth the 15MB check-in. Also, disabling GetGlue’s cellular data access.    
    
    
    @eektertainment Dude lookit @trigramosaurus    
    
    
    Help I can’t stop watching the Days of Future Past trailer help http://youtu.be/pK2zYHWDZKo     
    
    
    This @keyboardmaestro shortcut letting me hit delete to archive made Mail.app usable for me again: http://cl.ly/SAud     
    
    
    Enjoying my Apples in a peace of mind! pic.twitter.com/Ztderh9ka4    
    
    
    @andycroll Sweet! The good scary link at the bottom goes to web root listing though    
    
    
        
    
    
    @sangsara So I take it you’ve bought two already    
    
    
    Oh good 5 attempted downloads and 6GB later I finally managed to update Infinity Blade 3    
    
    
    Why yes @tweetbot obviously the intuitive iOS 7-like way to follow someone is to tap on the “does not follow you” button    
    
    
    @chuyeow Congrats! Still based here?    
    
    
    @bradleychambers Did that since last version, I think.    
    
    
    Cancelled $5-a-month caller ID now that my number 1 source of missed calls (mum) is on FaceTime Audio. Technology!    
    
    
    If you’re planning to watch Thor: Now You’re Thinking With Portals, remember to stay for both post-credits sequences.    
    
    
    @ftrain There was a recent NYT blog entry about such phrases: http://sinosphere.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/10/27/better-than-a-tweet-using-four-characters-young-chinese-create-internet-idioms-with-a-new-world-of-meaning/?_r=2& … — linguistically lovely, total pain for students.    
    
    
    @StaringScreens Why was the Halloween episode not called “Scaring and Screams”? I want my money back    
    
    
    @Jawbone Finally taking you up on support offer — my UP seems to be dead, flashes 3x red sun & not tracking steps […]    
    
    
    @Jawbone […] even after charging for hours. Anything I can do?    
    
    
    @gssq "Success" as in "high alcohol tolerance"    
    
    
    @chuyeow Sweet. Sending to my parents, who've been paying SingTel every month for "push notifications"...    
    
    
    @vickiho Read your entry about S.U.R.E. and I believe you did your readers a disservice by not mentioning the hilarious “Sure Lok Hom”    
    
    
    Singaporean friends: shop a lot on Amazon? Always trying to find items that ship here free? We built something to help, @ me to help test    
    
    
    Woohoo, a Gmail update for Mail.app!
<upgrades>
<hits reply on mail>
<iMac freezes for 45 seconds>
…    
    
    
    Watching the Stanford-Oregon game. I believe the term for that pass interference call was “si bei heng”    
    
    
    So excites! Sports!    
    
    
    This! Game! #gostanford    
    
    
    Talk about white-knuckle games. Whatever the case, YESSS #gostanford    
    
    
    @shiyankoh Difficulty… breathing    
    
    
    Things I have to consciously stop myself from doing: yelling “WHERE MA CHOCOLATE STARS AT” when I enter a supermarket. (Aside: so delicious)    
    
    
    I just ate all my chocolate stars and now I’m drunk on chocolate    
    
    
    Wife went off shopping because she didn’t want to wait for me to buy chocolate stars. Now I can’t find her so I should buy more?    
    
    
    @readmill Is there any way to un-abandon a book? I can't seem to find it in the iOS app or on the web.    
    
    
    The Walking Dead airs this time of the week to make us all feel great about going back to work.    
    
    
    @Readmill Thanks! That sounds like a lot more trouble than it should be, though :)    
    
    
    @Readmill Appreciate it :) Thanks!    
    
    
    @cheeaun Yah see if you ever get Anonymous Nyan Cat    
    
    
    Unmanned Arial Vehicles. THE HORROR    
    
    
    @thedak Hate snow so much. So cold. I expect it’s worse for you now that you’re at -5% body fat    
    
    
    I was so looking forward to having some pets and other food for lunch but ah well http://instagram.com/p/gpTymggP2w/     
    
    
    Installing Mavericks on my 2007 MBP, feeling pretty great about it. Even better, the install’s taken over 2 hours, extending the feeling.    
    
    
    @sidoneill I actually haven’t even reached that! It’s been taking about 5 real-world minutes for every progress-bar minute so far.    
    
    
    @sidoneill Going to bed, will see if it’s still done in the morning. If my cats don’t trip over the power cable in the meantime…    
    
    
    @sidoneill Also, saw your tweet about the UP. Still using it? Just got my replacement after mine broke very unsurprisingly.    
    
    
    @sidoneill Looks like they’re keeping v2 around for the same price. Get it replaced first, then sell?    
    
    
    “WHAT”

“NO”

“EW”

“WHY EAT THAT”

“THAT IS NOT GOOD”

http://nonomella.tumblr.com/post/66672487041/i-made-this-powerpoint-for-this-weeks-lesson …    
    
    
    And my personal favourite, “You will be fat”    
    
    
    When someone tells you you’re rubbing them the wrong way, try rubbing them again and again until you do it the right way #lifeprotip    
    
    
    What in the world are these fuzzy tab bar icons in new iBooks pic.twitter.com/rNhLJL244A    
    
    
    1 and 5s http://instagram.com/p/gvNjc4AP84/     
    
    
    How to improve your Facebook news feed: liberal use of the “Hide All From User” button. Wait, if I hide everyone, why am I even hmmmmmm.    
    
    
    Wait what a "WANTED" sign for... citizen patrol? Have you guys thought through this mixed messaging http://instagram.com/p/gxfkGNgP1z/     
    
    
    Searching all of Canon’s international sites to get latest TWAIN drivers for new scanner because some sites have newer versions. WHYYY    
    
    
    Seen on Amazon: “open a bowser” pic.twitter.com/dThOPWi8Mf    
    
    
    @DavidMLombardi I’m convinced this was David Shaw’s way of making us feel better about the Utah loss. Worked for me!    
    
    
    Holy crap, AMC adapting Preacher for TV! Still my favourite comic series of all time. http://comicsalliance.com/preacher-adaptation-amc-garth-ennis-steve-dillon-vertigo/ …    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk Yah, a bit hopeful since it’s AMC.    
    
    
    @FunkeeMonk So true. This could potentially offend both liberals (homophobic language and themes) and conservatives (sacrilege). Can’t wait!    
    
    
    Tough work, changing education. (I’ve never actually completed any of the MOOC courses I took.) http://www.fastcompany.com/3021473/udacity-sebastian-thrun-uphill-climb …    
    
    
    Watched Almost Human, and nearly yelled “JD!!!” when they introduced John & Dorian to each other. I miss Scrubs.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Have you figured it out? I’d usually search for the where the post header goes first…    
    
    
    New hobby: complaining at SMS telemarketers. Got to use up that 800 monthly quota. pic.twitter.com/FODb0ngf3E    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ @jssrea That’s great :)    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Look for google in the code you included? You should be putting in the linked-list link instead.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ Look for “single-title-home”? The <a> tag’s href might be currently hardcoded to google.    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ That’s strange. And you’re certain you didn’t set your linked_list_url custom field to be google?    
    
    
    @m_kasshif Afraid not! Google for it?    
    
    
    "Check out our new iOS 7 look and feel", says PayPal pic.twitter.com/8tKa5If4Ld    
    
    
    @AndyNico_ That’s strange. Email me with login details, if you’d like me to go in and take a look? This handle at gmail.    
    
    
    Telling my cat Hunger Game puns while she eats. She’s probably amused, right    
    
    
    iPhone 5s TouchID fails the chocolate-on-fingers test. 0 stars out of 5, unable to use in most common daily situations    
    
    
    Weird Twitter… in Singlish    
    
    
    This Week’s @TheRoundDown Is Something Special. You’ll Regret It Forever If You Don’t Sign Up In The Next Hour: http://therounddown.com     
    
    
    Just saw an assessment book called “English Mock”. Deep.    
    
    
    @sangsara Nope, ack. Thanks for the note    
    
    
    @eektertainment Oh man such a great song    
    
    
    Got handed the Pac-12 North. Beating Cal. Great day. #gostanford    
    
    
    Got a phishing email with subject line “CAN I TRUST YOU” and now I’m confused. Have I been the email scammer all along?!    
    
    
    CAN you trust me, email phishing scammer? I… I don’t know. I’m sorry. I’m so sorry.    
    
    
    @nickheer Given my fat fingers, probably not!    
    
    
    @Joel_Koh @vickiho That’s what my Nutella sandwiches look like, except for when I skip the bread. Which is always. Umm nevermind    
    
    
    My favourite feature of my new retina iPad mini: having another Lightning cable.    
    
    
    Omg two new PBF comics it really is Christmas http://pbfcomics.com/261/     
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Seriously doubt I’m going to have more free time for moar comix though    
    
    
    Wtf who threw away an (unreleased here) Xbox One box downstairs JEALOUS RAGE pic.twitter.com/dU2tlWvuGm    
    
    
    I wouldn't want to stay here too long for fear of mosquitoes, because it's a... denki hotspot (@ Best Denki) http://4sq.com/1fIxKvu     
    
    
    I can’t believe I tweeted a foursquare checkin just for that pun    
    
    
    @skinnylatte Much appreciated :)    
    
    
    Launching in time(ish) for Black Friday: http://125andup.sg , a site to help find Amazon items that ship free to Singapore. Buy buy buy!    
    
    
    Here’s a nice bargain on 125andup: the ASUS RT-N66U for US$129 (about S$170), compared to S$209 at Sitex http://125andup.sg/products/9463     
    
    
    @ExtraTan Yeah that’s cheaper on Amazon too (US$180 vs. S$300 here), but doesn’t ship at all.    
    
    
    @ExtraTan Ah I recall something like that which tempted me once :)    
    
    
    I now have a retina iPad mini, an iPad Air, and a new son. Impressive haul for a week!    
    
    
    Will totally start posting pictures of the first two soon. Not sure what to do with the third.    
    
    
    @notabilia Thank you!    
    
    
    @zachphillips Thanks very much sir!    
    
    
    @pyrmont Thanks thanks :)    
    
    
    @andycroll Thanks very much kind sir!    
    
    
    What happens when your parents and spouse teach the Chinese language: you end up with a name for your kid you can't read. (It's 孙启睿.)    
    
    
    "AVOID CHILDREN
TOUCH THE PLUG"

Pretty drastic man pic.twitter.com/FA5VQRN2EH    
    
    
    My conversation with one "Lowest Interest Alex". The Do-Not-Call Registry can't come fast enough. pic.twitter.com/lB9TW9pHR8    
    
    
    Oh good, WhatsApp got an iOS 7 update! 

...and "Chats" is still the 4th tab. Clarity! Deference! Deleting.    
    
    
    This SMS marketer is on iMessage, so he gets to enjoy animated GIF responses. pic.twitter.com/lVZXYSA6JS    
    
    
    Managed to get 3 hours of sleep, newborn's fed and snoozing, team leading in Pac-12 title game by 3 touchdowns. A good Sunday. #gostanford    
    
    
    Pac-12 again! What a special season. #gostanford 

(Baby woke up exactly as the game ended, too. Great timing, little dude)    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Apart from the sleep deprivation and poo explosions, he's been super fun! Also, we've given up trying to match his socks.    
    
    
    @sangsara Oh that's probably Joey who shares my account. I pretty much listen to the same 5 albums on repeat..    
    
    
    I really need to end this parenthetical statement in a frowny face but if I do it’ll look like :() and that shit looks terrifying    
    
    
    @nickheer Nor read many comics — they didn't credit Brian K Vaughan for Saga.    
    
    
    Good job little dude http://instagram.com/p/h5Pi1vpJxu/     
    
    
    Unbelievable. Prolonged doge exposure has made me into a comic sans fan. I feel... such free    
    
    
    @zachphillips much sorry    
    
    
    Middle of night:
"I'm tired, can you feed him formula?"
"OK! Hey kid, x equals to -b + or - square root of b^2 - 4ac over 2a"    
    
    
    Apple just convinced me to tweet about my purchase of a Magsafe to Magsafe 2 converter. SOCIAAAL MEDIAAAA  http://www.apple.com/s/AB2h9y6     
    
    
    (Thing is, I ordered that and a Retina MacBook Pro, but they defaulted to the $13 item in the tweet intent…) pic.twitter.com/KCZouiZD0K    
    
    
    @Joel_Koh Sweet, did I also increase my Kloun score    
    
    
    My father bought me nearly a kilo of UK Cadburys — they were half off because they expire in 2+ weeks. CHALLENGE ACCEPTED    
    
    
    @tsewei Yes I saw that a couple of days ago! And didn't buy before it went up by 200%. much regret    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @garrettmurray Yeah but you know her heart will go on    
    
    
    Person in front of me in this queue is either having a Duck Rice Christmas Party or planning to eat 20 packs on his own    
    
    
    Duuuuuuck
Riiiiiiiice
Xmaaaaaas
Paaaaaaaaarty

Yeah that could work    
    
    
    ★☆☆☆☆ Not that many "what"s in this app! False advertising.    
    
    
    Brought the cats home, and they're terrified of this tiny month-old infant. They're such scaredy-... oh right ok    
    
    
        
    
    
    @eektertainment I got your card! Thanks for the 360-day early Xmas greeting    
    
    
    @andycroll Now playing that fun game, "Does stroller fit next to this dining table?". You guys play at a whole other difficulty level though    
    
    
    @bradleychambers You can endorse them back for the skill of Endorsing.    
    
    
    Holy shit Andrew Luck    
    
    
    @shaunkoh Indeed :) I'm a bit tied down (and sleepy) at home being a new dad for the time being though. Will you be around after CNY?    
    
    
    @ewat Hi Eric! I don't think we've met, but I hope you and PJ are doing well :) (Unless I'm thinking of another set of Balin-Watkinses…)    
    
    
    Humming the Sherlock theme every time I peel open the baby's diapers. WHAT COULD IT BE THIS TIME    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie Folks at http://SGPad.com . Pretty happy with their service so far    
    
    
    Wow, I actually overheard someone start a sentence with ‘We Chinese have a saying…’. Who says that in real life?!    
    
    
    We Chinese have a saying, don’t say ‘We Chinese have a saying’ where someone can overhear and make fun of you on Twitter    
    
    
    Hilarious forum letter about my wife's school: "[My son] had refused to complete his exam and began dancing instead." http://www.straitstimes.com/premium/forum-letters/story/school-caring-teachers-20121123 …    
    
    
    (She was just telling me about that incident. They let him retake the exam on A3 paper, which apparently helped him concentrate.)    
    
    
    @minal_9 I had no idea! (About the baby, and the point raised in the post.) Congrats! (About the baby.)    
    
    
    @SGNextRide @honcheng Four stars? That’s a damn shame. Telling my friends to go give it five. Great work!    
    
    
    Have a pocket of free time tonight. Sitex or Sigur Ros concert?    
    
    
    @andycroll So the key is don’t fail miserably *and* sue your clients? Sweet!    
    
    
    @mengwong Not entirely the same, though? I don’t believe ranking here is as closely tied to test scores.    
    
    
    Great Jets impression there by UCLA. #gostanford    
    
    
    @vickiho Just listened to ep 6 of @StaringScreens. Shouldn’t need to switch Xbox accounts to use Netflix—just have the app installed, right?    
    
    
    @vickiho @StaringScreens I recall this working for me: sign out of SG account, sign in to US, install Netflix, sign in to SG account (VPN).    
    
    
    @vickiho @StaringScreens But I’ve since obtained two other Netflix-capable boxes to use, so my info may be outdated    
    
    
    SAF advertising, 2012-2020:

• Every Soldier A Leader
• Every Soldier Listens To Orders
• Every Soldier Showing Up Would Be Nice But Ah Well    
    
    
    @sangsara @vickiho @StaringScreens Actually went and tried it (switch account, install, switch back). Still works! It’s under Apps.    
    
    
    @sangsara @vickiho @StaringScreens But yeah, the music and video tabs are gone.    
    
    
    @iamclovin Thanks for the invite btw! No web projects for now, but will give it a try when we do. Cheers :)    
    
    
    Bought an Xbox game and left it in the car for 2 days so far. Entertainment value from finding out everyday if disc has melted: check    
    
    
    Got an iPad mini, and the iPad 3 has been relegated to service as Gigantic 3G Tethering Modem With 10 Hours Battery Life.    
    
    
    @pyrmont Just a little. Can’t help but imagine how great this’d be with retina.    
    
    
    @andycroll Yeah, it’s a gift. I’d have picked up a LTE one given a choice. Can’t believe yours still isn’t here!    
    
    
    Configured a $3,900 iMac and staring at the screen. I probably need a 3TB fusion drive for, er, work, right?    
    
    
    @sangsara I’m mildly worried about not being able to back that monster up. But it’s less than $200 over the cost of a 1TB!    
    
    
    @pyrmont Downsides?    
    
    
    @pyrmont Oh that’s the Mac Pro. I’m eyeing the new iMac    
    
    
    @pyrmont Yup, the highest end one in Sing$, with 16GB RAM, i7 upgrade, and 3TB Fusion Drive. Not sure about the first and third bits though.    
    
    
    @pyrmont Hm, good point! Crucial does ship pretty quickly.    
    
    
    @sangsara There’s always CrashPlan, I guess. How’s that upload going?    
    
    
    Last college football tweet of the year until Jan 1 for the Rose Bowl. All right now! #gostanford    
    
    
    @jussi Thank you kind sir!    
    
    
    Why didn’t any of my American friends spend this much effort learning Singlish? Hmph. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fiYXiixlV0A …    
    
    
    @jussi No, no, I insist    
    
    
    @jussi Thank you for thanking me!    
    
    
    @jussi Thank No, thank YOU for being thankful!    
    
    
    @jussi ARE YOU DRUBNK SIR    
    
    
    @jussi I suppose we can agree on that.    
    
    
    @jussi Noooooooo    
    
    
    Finding myself in the strange position of agreeing with Gawker over NYT on Popova. "It's like Buzzfeed, but boring." http://gawker.com/5964868/the-new-york-times-has-a-really-kooky-boner-for-curation-wizard-maria-popova …    
    
    
    @lisiepeasie She’s not too bad, but the NYT piece really was quite fawning    
    
    
    @nfarina Not sure I get what you mean—like Google Instant?    
    
    
    @nfarina Odd, that’s never happened to me. (Maybe because lookups are slower here.) And it goes away with the extension disabled?    
    
    
    @thedak Ahh my trophy puked    
    
    
    Ordered iMac over the phone. Rep was mildly distraught that I maxed out the CPU and video card but left it at 8GB RAM.    
    
    
    