Alan Turing: Inquest's suicide verdict 'not supportable' http://prsm.tc/lFeffi     
    
    
    How we die (in one chart) http://prsm.tc/Hwmurn     
    
    
    @ChristopheViau Nice!    
    
    
    @mbauhardt @maschahcsam Unix is the OS of the future since 40 years. :)    
    
    
    @Datameer infographic wallboard showing Datameer 2.0 download locations "real time" pic.twitter.com/BsuMiUQu    
    
    
    @wck @datameer Great surprise! Suprise us more often. :)    
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MJCHeEQV454&feature=relmfu …    
    
    
    @davefauth let us know if we can help with anything… BTW, thanks for the write up...    
    
    
    Just analyzed my emails w/ @Datameer - now I know who is bugging me the most ;)   http://bit.ly/LpX4SY  #hadoop pic.twitter.com/1vnUxAWR    
    
    
    @serby #ruby and #regex? How many handbreaks can you build into a hadoop job? :-) Anything that runs in the same jvm will run in 10min.    
    
    
    @wattsteve Uhh - who is missing? :) We happy to add them. cc: @rqtaylor    
    
    
    @flo still down? wow.    
    
    
    @flo haha - well if you have hundreds of thousands of instances ten tousand is just 10 percent. :)    
    
    
    Funny, we (@Datameer) had to reboot all our servers as well, #LeapSecondProblem in #debian.    
    
    
    We really should rethink NTP if we want to take Linux based devices on time travels in the future. :) #LeapSecondProblem    
    
    
    Nice, @datameer had much more reach than last week. #socialmedia #analytics http://www.datameer.com/gallery/84?t=undefined …    
    
    
    OS X, single application mode. I love it. http://zackshapiro.com/post/26300586593/single-application-mode-my-favorite-hidden-feature-of …    
    
    
    @KathrinPauly @steffenbuechner @wbenica @sfroehlich008 You guys are funny with your mugs.    
    
    
    @HauteSaone Try to use the twitter wizard to get some twitter data e.g.  @BarackObama and than analyze and visualize his tweets and retweets    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/Gk7LKDQC    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/SaZZJzA7    
    
    
    I would love to change the world but they won't give me the source code.    
    
    
    I just analyzed my twitter stream with @Datameer to learn more about my followers: http://www.datameer.com/gallery/115?t=2  #BigData #SocialMedia    
    
    
    @joprichard Yes, Github, Sourceforge, Google Code - nothing. Even data.un didn't had it. :)    
    
    
    @murphdec thanks making us aware. So you mean our website or within the product?    
    
    
    Believe in your dreams. pic.twitter.com/p0e7TAAR    
    
    
    Analytics a $51B business by 2016 thanks to big data http://prsm.tc/cIsrDO     
    
    
    Troll sues Facebook, Amazon and others for using Hadoop http://gigaom.com/2012/07/13/troll-sues-facebook-amazon-and-others-for-using-hadoop/ …    
    
    
    @cwensel @cascading nice - build with gradle?!    
    
    
    Find out where the most UFO sighting in US are. #dataanalytics #tutorial #hadoop http://www.datameer.com/documentation/display/DAS20/UFO+Sightings …    
    
    
    @mhawksey @datameer Should be possible. Make sure you have the right delimiter sign. Make sure you choose texts are in quotes.    
    
    
    @mhawksey I noticed your dataset has a few carriage return in the tweets. This will be corrcupted record since it is not valid csv.    
    
    
    @graemethickins try @datameer and you are a #datascientist in no time, as long you know how to use a spreadsheet. :)    
    
    
    .@mhawksey I downloaded the file and I'm able to import it with 2.0.1. What version do you use. I'm not using http though.    
    
    
    @mhawksey Let me try this too… give me a minute...    
    
    
    @mhawksey The problem might be https the forced redirectto https. :( Sorry. Any way you can make the data available with http?    
    
    
    @mhawksey yep I personal pushed it as critical into 2.0.3 (~4 weeks from now). cc @ejrosas can we give @mhawksey a custom plugin up front?    
    
    
    AWESOME, RT @davefauth: a post http://bit.ly/OVSOfX  on using @datameer to analyze MN campaign contributions http://bit.ly/OdjcV6     
    
    
    A Sequential I/O Reading List http://codedependents.com/2012/07/08/a-sequential-io-reading-list/ …. Thanks for sharing Kelly!    
    
    
    Do you need to parachute in a data analytics solution? No Problem! Checkout @Datameer in a Pelican case. pic.twitter.com/t5YxplYV    
    
    
    @techmilind sounds like you have the most complete Hadoop shirt collection. :)    
    
    
    @rachelmetz 2k sounds like a good price in sf. :) blame the rich kids that work at successful tech startups. :) btw, parking will be extra.    
    
    
    At least now I know the ip of the airbus 340 I'm flying to Europe with. Scary thought what would be possible. DDOS pic.twitter.com/4fyH0Iow    
    
    
    @mikeolson Yep vey nice, almost like a big data happy meal in small, medium or large. :)    
    
    
    Shut Up and Play the Hits - http://itun.es/i6jW6ws  #iTunes #LCDSoundSystem    
    
    
    Don't bother with Big Data – listen to customers instead http://prsm.tc/88lPnE     
    
    
    Say no! 8 Ways to Keep Your Brain Innovative http://www.inc.com/geil-browning/personal-productivity-keep-your-brain-innovative-eight-ways.html …    
    
    
    Citi is hiring a @Datameer big data analyst: http://jobs.citi.com/warren/technology/jobid2632473-hadoop-engineer-jobs?apstr=%26src%3DJB-14023 … Get Certified Now: http://www.datameer.com/support/certification/certification_program.html …    
    
    
    Think before you debug! http://www.informit.com/articles/article.aspx?p=1941206 …    
    
    
    Last weekend beach camping, this weekend downhill mountain biking. 
I <3 CA pic.twitter.com/PTSaXGiS    
    
    
    How Big Is Facebook’s Data? 2.5 Billion Pieces Of Content and 500+ Terabytes Ingested Every Day http://prsm.tc/7p4r69  via @prismatic    
    
    
    When Freemium Fails http://prsm.tc/BXzum0     
    
    
    Why Innovative People Fail http://prsm.tc/P2CYiR     
    
    
    Meet Your Company's New Chief Customer Officer http://prsm.tc/REIZag     
    
    
    What Successful People Do With The First Hour Of Their Work Day http://prsm.tc/XBAmXx     
    
    
    Lessons GrubHub's CEO Learned Using Freemium http://prsm.tc/NBWU4y     
    
    
    @bradfordcross @prismatic Congrats on the iphone app launch. I'm looking forward to use it.    
    
    
    4 Questions to Ask Before Starting a Big Data Initiative http://prsm.tc/CAeiau     
    
    
    @susanpuccinelli Happy work == happy private life. Frustrating work == frustrating private life?    
    
    
    Manage Creativity in Your Company by Dedicating Time http://prsm.tc/TnNWw6     
    
    
    114 Entrepreneurs On 1 Train For 8 Hours Pitching Ideas http://prsm.tc/qG1euH     
    
    
    Five Ways San Francisco Improves During Burning Man http://prsm.tc/TQ3RZe     
    
    
    Understanding Customers in the Solution Economy http://prsm.tc/PXBD4W  #startup    
    
    
    Should Start-Up Founders Make Six Digits? http://prsm.tc/FalhfO  #startup    
    
    
    O'Reilly Media: Staying ahead of the curve with big data http://prsm.tc/jYMExH  #bigdata    
    
    
    Screw design and get data, says Ben Huh of I Can Has Cheezburger http://prsm.tc/W52wEx  #startup    
    
    
    @ChristopheViau I couldn't agree more! :)    
    
    
    @TravisDe @rqtaylor @cmeily @lesleyyoungster @datameer Rich, screw 1,2,3 I just buy you a ticket. Proving your friends are at @datameer :)    
    
    
    The next billion-dollar enterprise tech companies http://prsm.tc/NOQpaD  #startup #hadoop    
    
    
    Defining Big Data for the Public CIO http://prsm.tc/kpNiMW  #bigdata    
    
    
    Wow, Apple awarded over $1bn in Samsung patent infringement trial http://prsm.tc/i9XE1u     
    
    
    Un, un, unbelievable amazing http://www.break.com/index/breathtaking-human-flight-is-also-frightening-2362231 …    
    
    
    Mountain biking in the Sierra foot hills. cc: @JonOslowski pic.twitter.com/NDPZ2kr8    
    
    
    Neil Armstrong: One Small Step http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HCt1BwWE2gA …    
    
    
    We Stopped Dreaming: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CbIZU8cQWXc … #NASA    
    
    
    Stanford biologist and computer scientist discover the 'anternet' http://prsm.tc/3Aj46H  #tech    
    
    
    Big data: all you need to know http://prsm.tc/K46x4j  #bigdata    
    
    
    Examining the True Cost of Big Data http://prsm.tc/jv6jNi  #bigdata    
    
    
    Hadoop, Business Analytics and Beyond http://prsm.tc/fDw3Br  #bigdata    
    
    
    How to Enter New Markets in 3 Steps http://prsm.tc/NtJzWM  #startup    
    
    
    6 Steps to Successfully Grow Your Small Business from Richard Branson http://prsm.tc/UUwCSW  #startup    
    
    
    The Rise Of Visual Social Media http://prsm.tc/qNucWW     
    
    
    Big Data Be Damned, The Web Still Needs a Human Touch http://prsm.tc/9cHLfE  #bigdata    
    
    
    Don't drink the startup Kool-Aid – find a problem and try to solve it http://prsm.tc/eeB0tb  #startup    
    
    
    I.B.M. Mainframe? Really?  http://prsm.tc/IdxvfW     
    
    
    Freemium Business Models: How Not to Go Broke http://prsm.tc/p5rIpe  #startup    
    
    
    New York, New York. pic.twitter.com/ta02I8As    
    
    
    @tacohiddink Great info graphic!    
    
    
    Hadoop: The Definitive Guide, 3rd Edition http://prsm.tc/ZvU65h  #hadoop    
    
    
    MongoDB 2.2 Released http://prsm.tc/4eEJoX  #nosql    
    
    
    Employee Recognition: 5 Steps to Make Yours One of the Best Companies to Work for http://prsm.tc/xyixC6  #startup    
    
    
    5 Tips on Fast Growth from a 5-Time Inc. 5000 Company http://prsm.tc/Pcdkf2  #Startup Culture    
    
    
    Four Things to Get Right When Starting a Company - Bruce Gibney and Ken Howery http://prsm.tc/aNwVRF  #startup    
    
    
    Effective CEOs Spend Their Time http://prsm.tc/ntWKjr  #startup    
    
    
    Big Data Makes Better Business Decisions http://prsm.tc/Z97E8u  #bigdata    
    
    
    Do You Need a Data Dictator? http://prsm.tc/GxfTeN  #data    
    
    
    Using Market Research Just for Marketing Is a Missed Opportunity http://prsm.tc/6pwhrE  #startup    
    
    
    Big Brother on a budget: How Internet surveillance got so cheap http://prsm.tc/wucOMO  #bigdata    
    
    
    Facebook Updates Graph API To Make Data More Accessible To Developers http://prsm.tc/EM8Po4  #data    
    
    
    I Further Predict the Death of Your Web Framework
http://mailinator.blogspot.com/2012/08/i-further-predict-death-of-your-web.html …    
    
    
    What numbers and a new book tell us about the Y Combinator way http://prsm.tc/kvsHlV  #startup    
    
    
    Learn More By Asking Fewer Questions http://prsm.tc/AwM0pB     
    
    
    The Dangerous Seduction of the Lifetime Value (LTV) Formula http://prsm.tc/sM9t1n  #startup, #businessmodel    
    
    
    @ScottLeatherman @SAPStartups @Datameer It would be my pick too. :)    
    
    
    How fun, "Shooting The Tube" :) 
http://youtu.be/W0Hzl_KCX2k     
    
    
    .. and the people's choice awards go to: @datameer #BigData #SAP #Hanna pic.twitter.com/ZP6YTxrd    
    
    
    Intro To Hadoop http://prsm.tc/s62V9Z  #bigdata    
    
    
    Introducing the ISTC for Big Data Blog http://prsm.tc/VD2yi0  #bigdata #intel    
    
    
    Think Your Private Data Is Secure? Scientists Can Hack Your Brain http://prsm.tc/beY8ka     
    
    
    Bye, bye NYC.    
    
    
    The top ten TED and TEDx startup talks http://prsm.tc/DI2R4N  #startup    
    
    
    Spectacular Curiosity Panorama Puts You on Mars http://prsm.tc/tSsOzl     
    
    
    Customer to me: "Next time you can take our latest super car for a spin on the race track." Great that everybody needs big data today. :)    
    
    
    Why big data means big things for the future of marketing http://prsm.tc/USykah  #bigdata    
    
    
    @garyteagarden Yes, I used @Datameer before. :) How can I help?    
    
    
    The value of data http://prsm.tc/6MHfiY  #data    
    
    
    Daily chart: The Devil's in the deterrent http://prsm.tc/cs6JYI     
    
    
    Big Data Working Group formed aims to solve real world problems http://prsm.tc/VVP6mE  #bigdata    
    
    
    Awesome video animation put together by @Datameer's design team. Learn more about Financial Compliance: http://vimeo.com/48607207     
    
    
    Looking for a technical co-founder? Be hacker in 10 sec: http://hackertyper.net/ 
#startup    
    
    
    @bethebutterfly Thx.    
    
    
    More Tweets across the web http://prsm.tc/6NLi5W     
    
    
    Use Big Data to Predict Your Customers' Behaviors http://prsm.tc/LnpG5Q     
    
    
    5 Tips and Tools to Create a Company Culture When You Run a Virtual Business http://prsm.tc/KZufbn  #startup    
    
    
    Big Data is Creating A Digital Nervous System http://prsm.tc/5q56NX  #bigdata    
    
    
    @garyteagarden try the low cost personal edition. There is a learning curve but it is the most flexible and powerful analytics product.IMHO    
    
    
    @garyteagarden however it always depends on the use case. Try our videos and webinars to get a kick start.    
    
    
    “In the Studio,” LinkedIn’s Pete Skomoroch Discusses The Voltron Of Data Science http://prsm.tc/B3hsR1  #data    
    
    
    Y Combinator Founder Paul Graham Issues New Warning to Start-ups http://prsm.tc/VUvr4u  #startup    
    
    
    Keep Your Best Employees: 5 Steps http://prsm.tc/01qrJM  #startup    
    
    
    . @Datameer at Forbes: http://www.forbes.com/sites/davefeinleib/2012/09/07/the-big-data-science-behind-todays-most-popular-content/ …    
    
    
    Put together some thoughts on bursting this Big Data bubble. First posted on ZDNet; republished on our blog: http://bit.ly/P5dynJ  #hadoop    
    
    
    Jack Dorsey: A Founder Is Not A Job, It’s A Role http://prsm.tc/zMDXdy  #startup    
    
    
    How Bad Leadership Spurs Entrepreneurship http://prsm.tc/CsxaY0  #startup    
    
    
    16 free fall Stanford classes that will help you build your business http://prsm.tc/Xx80qa  #startup    
    
    
    … it compiling… #nerdjokes pic.twitter.com/AY4mMcpz    
    
    
    What do you think about our new @Datameer website? http://www.datameer.com/hbr/index.html     
    
    
    Big Data's Management Revolution  - Erik Brynjolfsson and Andrew McAfee http://prsm.tc/J46vzW  #bigdata    
    
    
    Box CEO Aaron Levie: Startups Have An “Unfair Advantage” In The Enterprise Market http://prsm.tc/BQHYZA  #startup    
    
    
    The GPU "Sweet Spot" for Big Data http://prsm.tc/cDo1JS  #bigdata    
    
    
    Welcome to HBR's Big Data Insight Center http://prsm.tc/z3AbDH  #data    
    
    
    @eric_kavanagh A free mind, agility and time to market are invaluable advantages. Since sales changed from push to pull it easier than ever    
    
    
    @eric_kavanagh IMHO most startups have execusion issues. Staying humble is hard  with VC money, time to market relative without competition.    
    
    
    @eric_kavanagh Every entrepreneur should try to build at least one company out of his own credit card.    
    
    
    @eric_kavanagh sure, sign me up. :)    
    
    
    Jim Collins: 7 of the 10 most critical ceo decisions should be people decisions. #KPCEOSUMMIT    
    
    
    Sequoia's Jim Goetz On Enterprise Startups http://prsm.tc/OcjKeF  #startup    
    
    
    What Executives Don't Understand About Big Data http://prsm.tc/dYHj0C  #bigdata    
    
    
    Who's Really Using Big Data - Paul Barth and Randy Bean http://prsm.tc/dWP0ys  #bigdata    
    
    
    100 Books Every Entrepreneur Should Read @sujanpatel http://prsm.tc/dO1L4S  #startup    
    
    
    The amazing map that shows all of the world's recorded hurricanes in a single image http://prsm.tc/Zb4Nut  #infographic    
    
    
    15 Ways To Keep Startup Employees Happy http://prsm.tc/KJNZgy  #startup    
    
    
        
    
    
    .@dsdownunder Sorry about this. This should be fixed now. Thanks for pointing it out.    
    
    
    Big Data's Human Component http://prsm.tc/sjRr5v  #bigdata    
    
    
    Analyzing our Bamboo Performance http://prsm.tc/BD2izK  #hadoop    
    
    
    Amazon Developing Its Own Mapping Service http://prsm.tc/yDbKVg     
    
    
    Prismatic takes on Twitter in the race to build a better serendipity engine http://prsm.tc/IZVFLA     
    
    
    Distributed Algorithms in NoSQL Databases http://prsm.tc/oljPGc  #bigdata    
    
    
    @ChristopheViau … and our ♥ is with you! :)    
    
    
    Gnip Offers Twitter's Complete Archive for Analysis http://prsm.tc/kgi6cA  #social #data    
    
    
    If 'Big Data' Simply Meant Lots of Data, We Would Call It 'Lots of Data' http://prsm.tc/oDakzk  #bigdata    
    
    
    7 new types of jobs created by Big Data http://prsm.tc/DENiWg     
    
    
    8 Reasons Startups With Good Ideas Fail http://prsm.tc/UEekwc     
    
    
    @TravisDe Awesome! Thank you so much! :)    
    
    
    Three Questions to Ask Your Advanced-Analytics Team http://prsm.tc/6UAZty     
    
    
    Think Stats: Probability and Statistics for Programmers http://prsm.tc/rnXyKW  #data    
    
    
    The Deadly Cost Of Ignoring Big Data: $71.2 Million Per Year http://prsm.tc/loHSAR  #bigdata    
    
    
    Google's Dremel Makes Big Data Look Small http://prsm.tc/a9lXXb  #bigdata    
    
    
    Visualizing the news, literally http://prsm.tc/4PVBqZ  #data    
    
    
    Your digital Mirror. http://prsm.tc/OHnqyt     
    
    
    Trulia's IPO Blows Past Expectations http://prsm.tc/vzILJ0     
    
    
    Amazing! The most concerning is that can profile a person just by this kind of data so well.
http://mirror.nationalmediamuseum.org.uk/?UserId=6dcb5fc4-f27f-4626-8d68-459cdce88d0a …    
    
    
    The Most Astounding Fact. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9D05ej8u-gU …    
    
    
    @techmilind ... And how long did it took for you to learn awk? :)    
    
    
    Metrics Are Easy; Insight Is Hard http://prsm.tc/1yqkH3  #data    
    
    
    Why Big Companies Can't Innovate http://prsm.tc/o98Vd4     
    
    
    Balancing team passion and product-market fit http://prsm.tc/YM77ex  #startup    
    
    
    Why I got Fired from Facebook (a $100 Million dollar lesson) http://prsm.tc/d4n0md  #startup    
    
    
    Become A Leader Others Want To Follow http://prsm.tc/Q6mYGp  #leadership    
    
    
    K-means, Classifiers, Logistic Regression, Evaluation http://prsm.tc/lp8qge     
    
    
    Why Everyone (Not Just Geeks) Should Care About Big Data | Wired Enterprise | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2012/09/human-face-of-big-data/ …    
    
    
    I just learned in a #Hadoop class that hive and pig are not all java some of it is actually into bite code. :) #fail    
    
    
    @mrflip still in the hyatt?    
    
    
    Worldwide, the digital warehouses use about 30 billion watts of electricity. http://www.siliconvalley.com/news/ci_21609749/power-pollution-and-internet …
#hadoop #green    
    
    
    Meet the New Boss: Big Data http://online.wsj.com/article_email/SB10000872396390443890304578006252019616768-lMyQjAxMTAyMDIwMDAyODA3Wj.html?mod=wsj_valetleft_email …    
    
    
    Shocker! Oracle clouds will run all-Oracle-all-the-time http://prsm.tc/MLZBqn     
    
    
    Machine Learning Demos http://prsm.tc/xjk8mq     
    
    
    How to Be Happier at Work: 10 Tips http://prsm.tc/mAnMCK     
    
    
    Richard Branson’s Six Secrets to Productivity http://prsm.tc/fusOqF     
    
    
    What an Astronaut's Camera Sees at Night http://flpbd.it/jis8Q     
    
    
    Test You Startup Ideas With This Free Validation Board http://prsm.tc/CYHwIf     
    
    
    Big Data's Biggest Obstacles http://prsm.tc/KqV9Mg     
    
    
    The Evolution of Big Data as a Research and Scientific Topic: Overview of the Literature http://prsm.tc/kzJGNi     
    
    
    Nick Woodman: How I Bootstrapped GoPro http://prsm.tc/63VIgQ     
    
    
    Steve Jobs Speech in 1983 Reveals Apple Working on iPad for 27 Years http://prsm.tc/QGa1TR     
    
    
    3 Employees You Need To Fire. Now http://prsm.tc/b5GuJE     
    
    
    How to Develop a Culture of Innovation http://prsm.tc/FL6teS  #startup    
    
    
    15 Billion Page Views a Month and Harder to Scale than Twitter http://prsm.tc/2op9yQ     
    
    
    Prismatic blog - Prismatic Blog - Prismatic's "Graph" at Strange Loop http://blog.getprismatic.com/blog/2012/10/1/prismatics-graph-at-strange-loop.html …    
    
    
    John Maeda: How art, technology and design inform creative leaders #TED
http://www.ted.com/talks/john_maeda_how_art_technology_and_design_inform_creative_leaders.html …    
    
    
    Goldman Sachs: Biggest opportunities are in data, efficiency http://prsm.tc/pPpkGV     
    
    
    Big Data To Drive $232 Billion In IT Spending Through 2016 http://prsm.tc/Mq7W27     
    
    
    Even Stranger than Expected: a Systematic Look at EC2 I/O http://prsm.tc/0wDJJB     
    
    
    @bigdata thanks Ben!    
    
    
    Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery! See yourself. cc @alexwilliams pic.twitter.com/xoqPShxl    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/O8ngTz5Q    
    
    
    Hadoop Creator Outlines the Future of Big Data Platform http://prsm.tc/XoSJ3Z     
    
    
    Richard Branson on the Entrepreneurs He Admires http://prsm.tc/Xd7foW     
    
    
    Getting into Y Combinator as a single non-technical founder http://prsm.tc/buJjMK     
    
    
    UA Study Examines How News Spreads on Twitter http://uanews.org/story/ua-study-examines-how-news-spreads-twitter …    
    
    
    @reillyusa Thank you. :) Let us know if we can help or demo you anything...    
    
    
    Why Sears Is Going All-In On Hadoop http://prsm.tc/W1S8fq     
    
    
    Leaving to #Wday Rising conference to Las Vegas tonight.    
    
    
    Workday drops the Other Shoe(s): BigData Analytics, Recruiting, and Extensible Objects http://www.bersin.com/blog/post/2012/11/Workday-drops-the-Other-Shoe(s)--BigData-Analytics2c-Recruiting2c-and-Extensible-Objects.aspx …    
    
    
    @taylb536 @Datameer Yes. Basically we "compile" into MR and than optimize the job run highly. Download a job trace and visualize the pipe...    
    
    
    @taylb536 @Datameer … just uncompress the zip file and open the .dot files in a tool like OmniGraffle and you will see something like this..    
    
    
    @merv @TonyBaer Thanks! It's the first vertical big data solution. #crossing_the_chasm    
    
    
    @merv @TonyBaer Also it is the first of it's kind big data partnership, since all others are handshake partnerships or reseller agreements    
    
    
    Big data center opening in Cambridge http://prsm.tc/7cIUN4     
    
    
    @wbenica Sure thing.    
    
    
    beautiful weather infographic user interface for iPhone http://partlycloudy-app.com/     
    
    
    @Prismatic When clicking the login via twitter button many times quick enough the iPhone app crashes for me.    
    
    
    Enterprises Spend Big On 'Big Data' http://prsm.tc/8U78Cg     
    
    
    @MaineC If big data is an IT project most likely it will fail. If it is a business project it most likely will be very successful.    
    
    
    @obrienjw Refreshing accurate understanding of Hadoop and big data at #TDWI    
    
    
    Is Big Data Right for Your Business? President Obama Thinks So. http://prsm.tc/rNCYiC     
    
    
    @herberts .... or just use a simple spreadsheet and get the job done in a few minutes. :)    
    
    
    @herberts actually yes and yes. The magic of inversion of control. :) http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inversion_of_control …    
    
    
    @herberts right. One can only wonder why #Hadoop / related project did not used that. We would be so much ahead today.    
    
    
    @herberts IOC has nothing todo with the container! You don't even needs a container. A simple java class can assemble your object graph.    
    
    
    Hack any skype account in 6 easy steps. (They fixed it yesterday) http://pixus-ru.blogspot.ru/2012/11/hack-any-skype-account-in-6-easy-steps.html …    
    
    
    Urgh, but wow. “@mlalebasak: Urine-powered generator unveiled at international exhibition http://lnkd.in/kgtR7d ”    
    
    
    @marksmithvr thank you!    
    
    
    2012 KPCB Internet Trends Year-End Update http://prsm.tc/yRxomI     
    
    
    5 Signs You're Sucking as an Entrepreneur http://prsm.tc/7osZvX     
    
    
    @merv Thx. :)    
    
    
    Apache Ambari: Hadoop Operations, Innovation, and Enterprise Readiness http://prsm.tc/0Y7hs8     
    
    
    Twitter's Giving You Your Data Back, Enables Archiving http://prsm.tc/UURuJp     
    
    
    Oracle upgrades Big Data Appliance with Xeon E5s http://prsm.tc/2VLoy1     
    
    
    Big Data's Surprising Uses: From Lady Gaga To CIA http://prsm.tc/ESFOBm     
    
    
    Revenue is the new black http://prsm.tc/PgccFY     
    
    
    @emh :) yep.    
    
    
    Big Dollars from Big Data http://prsm.tc/l4gco8     
    
    
    My prediction for 2013 - goodbye Hadoop, hello Big Data: http://bit.ly/TzCF4r     
    
    
    .@InfoMgmtExec :) agree - its the same  thing.    
    
    
    Your Twitter archive http://prsm.tc/2wyeFi     
    
    
    Foundation: Tony Hsieh On Building A Great Company Culture http://prsm.tc/FRY3Km  #startup    
    
    
    Why big data means big business for online retailers http://prsm.tc/6cgN4q  #bigdata    
    
    
    Kleiner Partners' View of the Future of Tech http://prsm.tc/admCro     
    
    
    @mmurph thanks for sharing. :)    
    
    
    A Former Facebook Executive Warns About The Problem That Could Kill The Company http://prsm.tc/g2tSv1  #startup    
    
    
    The Hierarchy Of Business Needs http://prsm.tc/5cCDpY     
    
    
    Big data word of the year? #npr
http://www.npr.org/2012/12/20/167702665/geoff-nunbergs-word-of-the-year-big-data?sc=tw&cc=share … cc: @merv    
    
    
    The Hierarchy Of Business Needs http://prsm.tc/VY4ABO     
    
    
    Beyond Hadoop http://prsm.tc/u2TXg3     
    
    
    Datameer 2.1.1 released. New and Noteworthy
http://www.datameer.com/documentation/current/2.1.1+New+and+Noteworthy …    
    
    
    Can Big Data  Solve America's Gun Problem?
http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/12/how-big-data-can-solve-americas-gun-problem/266633/ …    
    
    
    Datameer 2012 Video -Wow, I work with fun and amazing colleagues: https://vimeo.com/55546001     
    
    
    Wow we resolved 6,756 jira tickets this year. A lot of very cool new features to come in 2013…. @datameer #bigdata    
    
    
    @wattsteve Thanks for the kind words! You know it's a team sport and we all are very fortune to work together with so driven and smart folks    
    
    
    Which Best Practice Is Ruining Your Business?http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2012/12/which_best_practice_is_ruining.html …    
    
    
    Acoustically experience the Nasdaq and apple trading. #data https://docs.google.com/presentation/pub?id=17FngGmMTcOcQFMvPNgV3QZTIwXTwkVB8OMa52mhQsSg&start=false&loop=false&delayms=3000#slide=id.p …    
    
    
    Netflix shows off its Hadoop architecture http://prsm.tc/XN25IJ     
    
    
    Hortonworks adds Ambari control freak to Hadoopery http://prsm.tc/AaEAav     
    
    
    The CTOvision Disruptive IT List: Firms we believe all enterprise technologists should be tracking http://prsm.tc/oduNnN     
    
    
    Why is Map Reduce faster? -- A practical example of data joins http://prsm.tc/ojE5xt     
    
    
    A Visual History of Nobel Prizes http://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2012/11/29/giorgia-lupi-noble-prizes-visualization/ …    
    
    
    How the Most Productive Bosses Spend Their Day http://prsm.tc/FyYNPA     
    
    
    Marketers Upping the Ante on Big Data in 2013 http://prsm.tc/nfx9xf     
    
    
    Redesigning Google: how Larry Page engineered a beautiful revolution http://prsm.tc/pHuICt     
    
    
    Big medical data http://prsm.tc/fFZc8S     
    
    
    Congrats team! @datameer one of the World's Top 10 Most Innovative Companies in Big Data http://prsm.tc/tucZFD  via @prismatic    
    
    
    The Best Entrepreneurs Are Older, Have Less Ego http://prsm.tc/Dezna5     
    
    
    How http://Ancestry.com  uses @Datameer, @Mapr, @10gen MongoDB via @Forbes http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomcoughlin/2013/02/11/the-ascent-of-storage-preserving-family-history/ …    
    
    
    Big Data: Why it's not always that big nor even that clever http://prsm.tc/xTNJJv     
    
    
    Turning Data Into Profit http://prsm.tc/QYWkIN     
    
    
        
    
    
    On a serious note, a product CEO is 10% vision and 90% QA - means push a vision  all the way through is a lot of work.    
    
    
    Social media experts, turned mobile, turned bigdata experts predict SQL is what  #Hadoop needs. Though, intentionally we made it NO-SQL!    
    
    
    Pushback against 'Big Data' begins http://prsm.tc/5TxYZT     
    
    
    A futuristic gesture: PointGrab aims to bring remote motion control to iOS devices http://prsm.tc/hEn3CQ     
    
    
    Data Mining Systems Improve Cost and Quality of Healthcare http://prsm.tc/mTdMs6     
    
    
    Fast clustering algorithms for massive datasets http://prsm.tc/qaUpkb     
    
    
    Put analytics at centre of business or perish: Gartner http://prsm.tc/wNzFgX     
    
    
    Visa stacks its database for big data analysis http://prsm.tc/x76gmj     
    
    
    #GartnerBI and Big Data: Fear, Loathing, and Business Breakthroughs http://prsm.tc/iAotRt     
    
    
    Awesome, as more #Hadoop distros as better, since eventually each Hadoop will run a @Datameer. @intel, we welcome you to the big data market    
    
    
    Big Data brings intelligence-based security, RSA chief says http://prsm.tc/58XyUL     
    
    
    DataDirect Networks brings out Hadoop appliance for enterprises http://prsm.tc/SEwMBp     
    
    
    Forget Big Data, Think Mid Data | OdinText Blog http://prsm.tc/jfexRU     
    
    
    10 interesting digital marketing stats we've seen this week http://prsm.tc/aIj2uG     
    
    
    IBM CEO Predicts Three Ways Technology Will Transform The Future Of Business http://prsm.tc/OmyvIa     
    
    
    The big data world is operating at 1 percent http://prsm.tc/xUQHSz     
    
    
    ‘Big Data’ Generates Big Returns: Q&A With VC Roger Ehrenberg http://prsm.tc/9tWGiW     
    
    
    Proprietary Hadoop Is A Losing Strategy http://prsm.tc/Slik57     
    
    
        
    
    
    Big Data Is Enabling Marketers to Do More With Less http://prsm.tc/dLpWXu     
    
    
    Hadoop as a Data Hub. A Sears Case Study. Join the webinar with Phil Shelley, CTO of Sears. http://info.datameer.com/Hadoop-as-a-Data-Hub-Sears.html …    
    
    
    Join me tomorrow at Bloomberg Big Data conference. From hype to value http://www.bloomberglink.com/event/big-data/     
    
    
    Discussing from hype to value at #bloomberg's big data conference #bbdata #hadoop pic.twitter.com/y21DmUCzU0    
    
    
    .@datameer at #Bloomberg #bigData from Hype to Value http://www.bloomberg.com/video/altman-groschupf-mahony-strawn-big-data-value-YIifIV~KRcCmDxtZqd891A.html …    
    
    
    Top Ten Mistakes of Entrepreneurs (Guy Kawasaki)
http://www.slideshare.net/GKawasaki/top-ten-mistakes-of-entrepreneurs?utm_source=slideshow&utm_medium=ssemail&utm_campaign=weekly_digest …    
    
    
    . @Toffleresque, yes we have quite a few health care customers but I can't give you names. What's your use case?    
    
    
    Reminder #InMemory != #BigData. Keep it real kids.    
    
    
    .@TonyBaer No. #BigData is like a freight train. If you need the speed of a sports car don't expect you can bring a lot of luggage.    
    
    
    Walmart Makes Big Data Part of Its DNA http://prsm.tc/OiIrrt     
    
    
    Visa identifies $2b in annual fraud with "Hadoop based analytics" cc @datameer.
http://blogs.wsj.com/cio/2013/03/11/visa-says-big-data-identifies-billions-of-dollars-in-fraud/ …
http://www.datameer.com/     
    
    
    @dberkholz calling you right now…    
    
    
    The world is ready for the consumer-grade enterprise http://prsm.tc/wmHL4l     
    
    
    The City of Chicago wants you to fork its data on GitHub http://prsm.tc/JizYHU     
    
    
    Great talk by Gus Hunt. #bigdata at #gov
http://gigaom.com/2013/03/20/even-the-cia-is-struggling-to-deal-with-the-volume-of-real-time-social-data/ …    
    
    
    Living in the future is great.  http://prsm.tc/P2RTFW  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Focus, focus, focus.  http://prsm.tc/tn353R     
    
    
    Big Data Right Now: Five Trendy Open Source Technologies http://prsm.tc/ENqP78     
    
    
    Message To The Future - Neil DeGrasse Tyson http://www.break.com/index/message-to-the-future-neil-degrasse-tyson-2427338 …    
    
    
    .@techmilind I couldn't disagree more! My macbook SSD has 750GB for 3k, you spend 50k+ for a 200GB in memory cluster. -> Tiny data.    
    
    
    .@techmilind even worst in memory clusters are slower due to network latency, where my SSD has full Disk to CPU IO.    
    
    
    Does Big Data Spell the End of Business Intelligence As We Know It? http://prsm.tc/XiO2d4     
    
    
    My colleague @mattschumpert just send me a document and attached a picture with his current view. #inflightWIFI pic.twitter.com/huCpz8wiPc    
    
    
    Oracle’s is in Big Trouble : Big Data is to Blame http://prsm.tc/16RblZ     
    
    
    Doctors turn to big data for help with cancer care http://prsm.tc/elFALt     
    
    
    "You own it to your children to take as far as you can." Right on! @carterac #startup @thestartupkids http://thestartupkids.com     
    
    
    Top 11 Reasons Startups Succeed http://prsm.tc/iiPFqJ     
    
    
    Horizon, 2013-2014, The Age of Big Data http://prsm.tc/1ggtJT     
    
    
    How Vizify Gives Recruiters Context for Your Digital Identity http://prsm.tc/bBj0SX     
    
    
    The new analytic stack is all about management, transparency and users http://prsm.tc/Ivf84X     
    
    
    Amazon buys Goodreads: We’re all just data now http://prsm.tc/HMM0jX     
    
    
    The Skills Most Entrepreneurs Lack http://prsm.tc/axhW6s     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: A Data Scientist's Real Job: Storytelling http://s.hbr.org/14oR5Mf     
    
    
    .@dvellante thank you!    
    
    
    Data For All! How New Tools Democratize Visualization http://prsm.tc/DuiZF8     
    
    
    Peter Thiel's 3 Rules for Starting a Business http://prsm.tc/0ks2PQ     
    
    
    NASA-backed fusion engine could cut Mars trip down to 30 days http://prsm.tc/sQDG7P     
    
    
    The Best Data Minning Tools You Can Use for Free in Your Company http://prsm.tc/ZycdNr     
    
    
    Google Turns to Big Data to Unmask Human Traffickers http://prsm.tc/YPleQk     
    
    
    Gartner: CIOs and CMOs must 'turn sparks into flame" http://prsm.tc/J0Woz6     
    
    
    The Modern Data Nerd Isn't As Nerdy As You Think http://prsm.tc/GXbX9P     
    
    
    Big data and society - interview with Kenneth Cukier, The Economist http://prsm.tc/xZpffI     
    
    
    @theMasterLink Just got a Roubaix E. SL4 Disc. When back breaking the plastic that runs the break cable on the bottom of the bike moves? :(    
    
    
    IDC: Big data alone will drive billions in storage sales http://prsm.tc/4PaXKY     
    
    
    thearn/webcam-pulse-detector · GitHub http://prsm.tc/N7FFhl     
    
    
    Ex-Googler releases big update to Disconnect, a data-blocking tool http://prsm.tc/TFizTz     
    
    
    Big data could uncover clue on marathon: Column http://prsm.tc/Zdo1aQ     
    
    
    Cognitive Overhead, Or Why Your Product Isn’t As Simple As You Think http://prsm.tc/LbsP9e     
    
    
    The Big Data Landscape Revisited http://prsm.tc/cN0iNZ     
    
    
    Why Getting Comfortable With Discomfort is Crucial to Success http://prsm.tc/ax4zCh     
    
    
    Big money in Big Data: SGI debuts petabyte-juggling archiving tool http://prsm.tc/FcHlz4     
    
    
    Hello! We have great mpp db's. Making #Hadoop look like one is the biggest marketing non sense in big data ever. It's sequential IO!    
    
    
    Apache Mahout http://prsm.tc/YSA41o     
    
    
    MacBook Pro Is 'Best Performing' Windows Laptop, Report Claims http://prsm.tc/0bs0QW     
    
    
    How big data will save your life http://prsm.tc/U8iZSG     
    
    
    Without Analytics, Big Data is Just Noise http://prsm.tc/tRctFm     
    
    
    Wikipedia is now drawing facts from the Wikidata repository, and so can you http://prsm.tc/sNRgVX     
    
    
    Big Data Gets Bigger: Now Google Trends Can Predict The Market http://prsm.tc/zTBIvz     
    
    
    How Big Data Will Mean the End to Job Interviews http://prsm.tc/QQbB70     
    
    
    @tlipcon LOL :)    
    
    
    How Twitter Stores 250 Million Tweets a Day Using MySQL http://prsm.tc/0cDOi1     
    
    
    3 Steps To Incorporate Big Data Into Your Small Business http://prsm.tc/1tWt9i     
    
    
    The Rising Costs Of Misunderstanding Big Data http://prsm.tc/VPxGXF     
    
    
    Hadoop: Expect enhanced performance soon http://prsm.tc/u7Y35e     
    
    
    Healthcare's Big Problem With Little Data http://prsm.tc/WnhJMQ     
    
    
    Data-Driven Band 'CSV Soundsystem' Makes Music From Spreadsheets http://prsm.tc/IQYbYL     
    
    
    SAPVoice: Big Data Is Hollywood's New Rising Star http://prsm.tc/qIngwX     
    
    
    More data usually beats better algorithms http://prsm.tc/P41xZg     
    
    
    “Entrepreneurs should become experts at learning from mistakes” Laurence Weinzimmer, co-author, The Wisdom of Failure http://prsm.tc/1i6ikj     
    
    
    3 Ways Big Data has Changed Retail Analytics Forever http://prsm.tc/F5ypAx     
    
    
    Deleting Photoshop or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Keynote http://prsm.tc/wwzh8J     
    
    
    @allthingshadoop But than you limited to what ever you can load in memory. 
Also you divide the men by number of active users.    
    
    
    When a defense contractor gets hacked repeatedly, you know cybersecurity is a problem http://gigaom.com/2013/05/02/when-a-defense-contractor-gets-hacked-repeatedly-you-know-cybersecurity-is-a-problem/ … via @gigaom    
    
    
    @allthingshadoop You build an app, uploaded it and define how much you want to charge for it. That's it. Json parser comes with the product.    
    
    
    Halley's Comet Meteor Shower Peaks Sunday: Watch Online http://prsm.tc/B226vp     
    
    
    Little Data Makes Big Data More Powerful http://prsm.tc/gsrCgi     
    
    
    CIOs like big data, just not in the cloud http://prsm.tc/hyGBIL     
    
    
    For "Big Data" to make a difference, we should also listen to its doubters. http://prsm.tc/LWEWSr     
    
    
    5,000,000 free datasets at the tip of your fingers! http://prsm.tc/aRdvrB     
    
    
    What is Personal Data and How Much Personal Data Exists? http://prsm.tc/OlmmAZ     
    
    
    John Doerr's Plan To Reclaim The Venture Capital Throne http://prsm.tc/yAKCVM     
    
    
    Come join us for the big data future panel discussion at #Interop with @brunoaziza    
    
    
    I don't think people yet get what impact 3d printing in the world will have. 
http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=WT3772yhr0o# …!    
    
    
    How Nest and Opower quietly morphed into competitors http://prsm.tc/3pBVoD     
    
    
    Teradata gets into the in-memory biz to take on SAP’s HANA http://prsm.tc/pAp8uj     
    
    
    Why don’t we just Hadoopify it? Datameer at InterOp Las Vegas http://prsm.tc/WxmJz4     
    
    
    Real-Time Venture Capital Investing: Chi-Hua Chien's Data-Based Approach http://prsm.tc/LRhqwh     
    
    
    Becoming a change agent - data-driven marketing http://prsm.tc/4nbd9k     
    
    
    Hortonworks Sandbox http://prsm.tc/N6iihk     
    
    
    Obama Administration Releases Historic Open Data Rules to Enhance Government Efficiency and Fuel Economic Growth http://prsm.tc/JSKfr3     
    
    
    @McKinsey @dfmarin @mchui consider it solved with @Datameer.    
    
    
    Hadoop Adoption Accelerates, But Not For Data Analytics http://prsm.tc/Inr8ll     
    
    
    Bill Gates: I Wish I Had Steve Jobs' Sense of Design http://prsm.tc/z8dlDd     
    
    
    Chris Hadfield, Space Oddity
http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=KaOC9danxNo …    
    
    
    @netzkobold thx.    
    
    
    Can Big Data Cure Your Churn Rate? http://prsm.tc/2X6XXb     
    
    
    Larry Page Lays Out His Vision For The Future Of Google And Technology http://prsm.tc/YUxWTm     
    
    
    Is It Wrong to Use Data From the World's First 'Nice' Botnet? http://prsm.tc/vDiyGS     
    
    
    The Art of Data Visualization
http://de.engadget.com/2013/05/16/video-the-art-of-data-visualization/ …    
    
    
    "Look after truth and goodness and beauty will look after her self"
Edward Tufte #inforgraphics    
    
    
    Nine Lessons for Innovators from a Nobel Prize-Winning Psychologist http://prsm.tc/y26ps8     
    
    
    Entrepreneurial Advice from SaaS Pioneer and Salesforce CEO Marc Benioff http://prsm.tc/VTK8ke     
    
    
    Why use a database instead of just saving your data to disk? http://prsm.tc/wUtiGI     
    
    
    Yahoo! and AOL Back On Top! Time To Party Like It's 1999! http://prsm.tc/JfCaKs     
    
    
    The IPO market is back—for enterprise tech http://prsm.tc/z5zjMe     
    
    
    NASA and Google Plan to Tackle Big Data with Quantum Computing http://prsm.tc/zRSDUq     
    
    
    .@marissamayer Respect! Awesome job bring Y! back to the 21 century.    
    
    
    Excited to see @Datameer's new NYC office tonight.    
    
    
    SVB Startup Outlook Report: "Twenty-two percent of startups have one or more women on their founding team." We need more woman in startups!    
    
    
    SVB Startup Outlook Report: "Forty-six percent of startups have one or more foreign born persons on their founding team." #startup    
    
    
    @TonyBaer We have an super strong NYC development office since early 2010. We just upgraded the office to a nice one in SoHo.    
    
    
    Machine learning climbs atop Hadoop http://prsm.tc/HAg7BO     
    
    
    Amazon's cloud services cleared for US government use http://prsm.tc/ZHNfih     
    
    
    Practical Data Science with R http://prsm.tc/BeLRDQ     
    
    
    Big Data is headed to HR http://prsm.tc/wIuJlK     
    
    
    Fred Wilson: Yahoo Will Put Tumblr on Same Level as Facebook, Twitter http://prsm.tc/IWGLl8     
    
    
    @rshah702 thank you so much! :)    
    
    
    Inside Google's Secret Lab http://prsm.tc/QRb47x     
    
    
    People Getting Dumber? Human Intelligence Has Declined Since Victorian Era, Research Suggests http://prsm.tc/RP2kk3     
    
    
    Researchers discover why we laugh when tickled - and the answer is not funny http://prsm.tc/DltvC0     
    
    
    Seven Strategies for Simplifying Your Organization http://prsm.tc/PnItNc     
    
    
    Google Launches Quantum Artificial Intelligence Lab http://prsm.tc/UrrArB     
    
    
    Google’s Dead-Simple Tool For Making UX Decisions: 2 Jars Of Marbles http://prsm.tc/VtnRoE     
    
    
    The Real Reason Hadoop Is Such A Big Deal In Big Data http://prsm.tc/qf35dR     
    
    
    The Race to Scale: How Fast Should You Accelerate? http://prsm.tc/6qnqJI     
    
    
    Americans No Longer the Center of the Online Universe, and Other Surprises From Mary Meeker’s Epic Slide Deck http://prsm.tc/vKIEfc     
    
    
    Poll Results: Hadoop YARN vs. pre-YARN http://lnkd.in/upwRyi     
    
    
    Coffee vs. beer: which drink makes you more creative?  https://medium.com/what-i-learned-today/f7fcb3b786b1 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    We all spend too much time on small ideas. Let's follow Elon Musk. http://prsm.tc/gP9jeB     
    
    
    .@bitSecure We have shirts for your whole team if you like! :) Just send us the address and sizes.    
    
    
    Is the Sample Good Enough? Comparing Twitter’s Streaming API with Twitter’s Firehose http://prsm.tc/wg35LH     
    
    
    The 10 Best Pieces of Advice for Entrepreneurs http://prsm.tc/p45cxC     
    
    
    Friends, Supporters, please vote Datameer into the top 10 Big Data Startups for @CIOonline http://startup50.com/BigData-42  -- single click, no signup    
    
    
    @lordcoke Thank you!    
    
    
    Nice! @Datameer made it into the "The 100 Companies That Matter Most in Data".
http://www.dbta.com/Articles/ReadArticle.aspx?ArticleID=89876 …    
    
    
    3 Ways Your Content Marketing Strategy Can Use Big Data http://prsm.tc/rf2eTJ     
    
    
    5 Women CEOs Who Are Saving Tech http://prsm.tc/xvA3fY     
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/4frk0Rif6n    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tracking the progress of large-scale Query Engines http://prsm.tc/Grd9bV     
    
    
    @marked_man Thanks!    
    
    
    Al Gore: The information explosion is a tool to help solve the climate crisis http://gigaom.com/2013/06/06/al-gore-the-information-explosion-is-a-tool-to-help-solve-the-climate-crisis/ …    
    
    
    Revealed: The CIA agent who cracked famous coded sculpture outside Langley HQ and it only took him SEVEN years http://prsm.tc/aBD9iX     
    
    
    Google Is Able to Predict Box Office With 94% Accuracy http://prsm.tc/xPQxKq     
    
    
    Apple, it's good to have you back!    
    
    
    NASA Rover Opportunity Makes Big Discovery, Keeps on Truckin' http://prsm.tc/NN9VfZ     
    
    
    @elkingaravito Thanks - please send me more information via email.    
    
    
    Be a good boss: Hire brilliant people and set context and get out of their way. The hard part is the hiring. :) @Datameer    
    
    
    Apple's Next Big Thing: Craig Federighi http://prsm.tc/WybBcT     
    
    
    A New Framework for Customer Segmentation - Judy Bayer and Marie Taillard http://prsm.tc/LUR8Mv     
    
    
    What is the role of big data in marketing? http://prsm.tc/iVIPaW     
    
    
    How to Get Yourself to Do the Things That Scare the Sh*t Out of You http://prsm.tc/dgPGAL     
    
    
    @MisterLavish Welcome on board!    
    
    
    @tunvall thank you!    
    
    
    Game theory is no longer just for economists. http://prsm.tc/SEaxNv     
    
    
    Hey next gen entrepreneurs! Learn to designing products, not to code! 
http://gigaom.com/2013/06/18/meet-the-design-focused-minds-behind-the-designer-fund-video/ …    
    
    
    My Secret to Reading A Lot of Books http://prsm.tc/0ACgX8     
    
    
    25 Habits Of People Who Are Happy, Healthy & Successful http://prsm.tc/JN6du9     
    
    
    Datameer in the New York Times. pic.twitter.com/yawXOqY3ew    
    
    
    The best way out is always through. [Robert Frost]    
    
    
    Datameer introduces Smart Analytics! http://www.datameer.com/learn/videos/product-datameer30.html …    
    
    
    Introducing Datameer 3.0! Read the release here http://bit.ly/12ZrklG  & check out my blog http://bit.ly/12Ztxxq  #bigdata    
    
    
    @npohle @gfknurago Thank you!    
    
    
    What the Companies Winning at Big Data Do Differently http://prsm.tc/K1qqcI     
    
    
    @dvellante Looking forward to it… :)    
    
    
    @ColinJWhite thank you.    
    
    
    Climbing the Los Gatos hills with Sky Christopherson, who used data to help the US women's cycling team win Silver! pic.twitter.com/AzxZ4Ed83u    
    
    
    How to Get Everything You Want. Seriously http://prsm.tc/hMfmLl     
    
    
    Very true: 5 Secrets Entrepreneurs Will Never Reveal http://prsm.tc/yCGrM0     
    
    
    Guide to Big Data Analytics, great free e-book at:
http://lnkd.in/WjUN3F     
    
    
    Measuring Management At BrAun 1960s v. Apple 2000s http://prsm.tc/aIctGH     
    
    
    @tonycosentinovr Thank you!    
    
    
    How does LinkedIn's recommendation system work? http://prsm.tc/Y7meok     
    
    
    Realtime Big Data Analytics with Storm -  Scale Warriors of Silicon Valley (Mountain View, CA) http://prsm.tc/MQe9hK     
    
    
    Measure learning not results! http://blogs.hbr.org/anthony/2013/07/how_to_innovate_faster.html … http://prsm.tc/9tl5uD     
    
    
    How Dropbox Scaled From 2,000 to 200 Million Users http://mashable.com/2013/07/30/dropbox-scaling/ … http://prsm.tc/G9f2zf     
    
    
    Nate Silver Gets Real About Big Data http://prsm.tc/lryASP     
    
    
    Cascading on the run.... congrats http://prsm.tc/erHWPd     
    
    
    New analysis on the blog -- "Big Data" Even Bigger in the News… One Year Later http://bit.ly/1eK58wF     
    
    
    @GS_PatSteller :) Vielen Dank! Bin schon gespannt auf den zweiten Teil. :)    
    
    
    Datameer-CEO: „Leider wird Innovation auch missbraucht“ http://www.gruenderszene.de/allgemein/datameer … via @gruenderszene    
    
    
        
    
    
    Big data won't be mature for at least five years, Gartner predicts http://bit.ly/18FVpGm     
    
    
    Interactive 3D Visualization Technology and Software http://prsm.tc/0lbhap     
    
    
    Email Open and Click Behavior by Gender and Income http://prsm.tc/K1Nqn6     
    
    
    Early Prediction of Movie Box Office Success Based on Wikipedia Activity Big Data http://prsm.tc/R4d8id     
    
    
    Announcing Beta Release of Apache Hadoop 2 http://hortonworks.com/blog/announcing-beta-release-of-apache-hadoop-2/ … http://prsm.tc/jMyuuO     
    
    
    MIT Prof. Michael Stonebraker: “The Traditional RDBMS Wisdom is All Wrong” http://prsm.tc/ywEeTK     
    
    
    Paul Graham on Building Companies for Fast Growth http://prsm.tc/hOLLu1     
    
    
    Hadoop Beginner's Guide http://www.wowebook.org/hadoop-beginners-guide.html … http://prsm.tc/cfEjUy     
    
    
    The unprofitable SaaS business model trap http://venturebeat.com/2013/07/24/the-unprofitable-saas-business-model-trap/#.UhunX5J1qSk.twitter …    
    
    
    Why the market for 3D printing will triple in five years http://qz.com/118678     
    
    
    http://techcrunch.com/2013/08/25/uberauto/ … http://prsm.tc/Jfmvrh     
    
    
    StackOverflow Co-Founder Jeff Atwood Builds A $150 Keyboard For Coders (And Others Who Type All Day) http://prsm.tc/zBwfjD     
    
    
    Sizing The Big Data Market: No One Has A Clue http://prsm.tc/SrKXS5     
    
    
    How-to: Select the Right Hardware for Your New Hadoop Cluster http://prsm.tc/yLaayI     
    
    
    Book: Twitter Data Analytics - free download http://prsm.tc/QY0Z65     
    
    
    Cassandra Advances Into the Top 10 Most Popular Database Engines http://prsm.tc/rd1my3     
    
    
    big data now in main stream movies:
http://www.ioug.org/media/hzdjtpgv.jpg …    
    
    
    @jtke Thank you… :)    
    
    
    Need Help with Database Scalability? Understand I/O http://prsm.tc/HQA9wS     
    
    
    Data Analysis: Just one component of the Data Science workflow http://prsm.tc/E3UkS3     
    
    
    Apache Samza: LinkedIn's Real-time Stream Processing Framework http://prsm.tc/svsJ1G     
    
    
    LinkedIn’s Market Cap Passes Salesforce, Long The Bellwether Symbol Of Cloud Services http://prsm.tc/QFsY3c     
    
    
    Why Big Data Is More About Variety and Less About Volume http://prsm.tc/FoYHEz     
    
    
    Snubbed By Oracle, Workday's Duffield And Bhusri Hit Jackpot http://prsm.tc/fWsFq7     
    
    
    Stealthy Dopant-Level Hardware Trojans
http://people.umass.edu/gbecker/BeckerChes13.pdf …    
    
    
    Big Data Investments Currently Earn 50 Cents For Every Dollar Invested - because folks build not buy. http://prsm.tc/W3PLp0     
    
    
    What I Wish I'd Known as a Struggling CEO http://prsm.tc/yostuw     
    
    
    Datameer Smart Analytics is now available. Self-service data mining for Hadoop: http://bit.ly/19OCqcu  Big thanks to our awesome engineers!    
    
    
    How Great Entrepreneurs Think http://prsm.tc/Dp3etY     
    
    
    How to Get Good at Making Money http://prsm.tc/zYRzHc     
    
    
    Economies of Unscale: Why Business Has Never Been Easier for the Little Guy http://prsm.tc/paIlKx     
    
    
    @alexgizis work in progress. Stay tuned.    
    
    
    There’s a .00006% Chance of Building a Billion Dollar Company: How This Man Did It http://prsm.tc/tXMIEM     
    
    
    Foursquare Data Set http://prsm.tc/srn1PM     
    
    
    How AirBnB Founders Took Paul Graham's Advice to Heart http://prsm.tc/Co3yFX     
    
    
    Angel-Backed Companies Are Taking Longer To Close Their First Venture Rounds http://prsm.tc/ghUzaq     
    
    
    Really enjoyed the conversation, chalk talk & beer with @ted_dunning from @mapr Video: http://bit.ly/1bHG4uu  #BigDataBrews    
    
    
    Turnes out developers actually do not like SQL that much.
https://i.imgur.com/toGKy21.jpg  
So why do we duck tape SQL on Hadoop than?    
    
    
    How the Latest Smartphones Could Turn Us All Into Activity Trackers and create even more data. http://prsm.tc/tF6Dxq     
    
    
    How to Build a Data-Driven Marketing Team http://prsm.tc/G9XFqx     
    
    
    Big Data in the News http://prsm.tc/GQ2ad1     
    
    
    Predictive Analytics World, San Francisco, March 2014 http://prsm.tc/E1CKeN     
    
    
    Scaling to Petabytes, While Keeping Costs Low — Cassandra Powers ElasticInbox's Metadata Store http://prsm.tc/XqTGAt     
    
    
    Your tweets can reveal your personality: IBM study http://prsm.tc/hbm6sU     
    
    
    Big Data Could Create an Era of Big Discrimination http://prsm.tc/3vghxP     
    
    
    CIOs and the Big Data Challenge http://prsm.tc/pKcJ8I     
    
    
    Stallman: How Much Surveillance Can Democracy Withstand? http://prsm.tc/R5pxy8     
    
    
    Interactive Machine Learning http://prsm.tc/QXdmsp     
    
    
    How Quantum Computers and Machine Learning Will Revolutionize Big Data http://prsm.tc/fNZ0h2     
    
    
    Apache Software Foundation Announces Apache Hadoop 2 : http://prsm.tc/rxJLZ4     
    
    
    Reid Hoffman Gives Invaluable Startup Advice And Reveals LinkedIn's Series B Pitch Deck From 2004 http://prsm.tc/2xBaNa     
    
    
    Computing experts from 37  countries call for ban on killer robots http://prsm.tc/ZVaNyP     
    
    
    Book: Machine Learning and Statistics, by Lion Solver http://prsm.tc/VGRGeM     
    
    
    Missed the train? Complain about it: "Please Stop Chasing Yellow Elephants, TIBCO CTO Pleads" http://prsm.tc/OlKttM  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Statistical models can predict a Kickstarter’s success within 4 hours http://prsm.tc/Q9YT5L     
    
    
    How Quantum Computers and Machine Learning Will Revolutionize Big Data http://prsm.tc/NXgJqK     
    
    
    50 Inspiring Young Entrepreneur Quotes http://prsm.tc/DowVeS     
    
    
    Making Analytics Pay In The Enterprise http://prsm.tc/nL78qw     
    
    
        
    
    
    @jwfbean Thank you Jeff! We will make up with this - maybe we skip the music and go straight for the drinks. ;)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Announcing Apache Ambari 1.4.1 http://prsm.tc/1cBqPn     
    
    
    Announcing Apache HBase 0.96.0, More than 2000 issues resolved! http://prsm.tc/CYCLo5     
    
    
    @merv Yes! I like small incremental releases.
But a lot of our customers just can't keep up with the speed of open source. :(    
    
    
    LA City Controller opens the data floodgates with new online resource http://prsm.tc/YQUEg0     
    
    
    Hands-on: Mozilla's Lightbeam is info porn for privacy geeks http://prsm.tc/Ih3q4Q     
    
    
    Design Thinking and Data Science http://prsm.tc/SjhyMW     
    
    
    GraphChi: How a Mac Mini Outperformed a 1,636 Node Hadoop Cluster http://prsm.tc/dA929P     
    
    
    ‘Big Data’ Is Bunk, Obama Campaign’s Tech Guru Tells University Leaders http://prsm.tc/sorY92     
    
    
    Cutting Sees Hadoop Receding Into Background http://prsm.tc/KIFzog     
    
    
    Hadoop is Not Enough for 'big Data', Says Facebook Analytics Chief http://prsm.tc/hcg3cX     
    
    
    Hadoop Community, let's help save the elephants. New $49 Datameer Charity Edition. 100% of proceeds go to ProWildlife http://bit.ly/1aZLESE     
    
    
    Welcome To The Unicorn Club: Learning From Billion-Dollar Startups http://prsm.tc/6fcWP1     
    
    
    Save the Elephants Infographics http://lnkd.in/bRz4VNt     
    
    
    http://www.datameer.com/save-the-elephants/infographic.html …    
    
    
    “Failure is an option here. If things are not failing, you are not innovating enough.” – Elon Musk    
    
    
    How does YARN compare to Mesos? http://prsm.tc/yccR3x     
    
    
    How Many Lines of Code Does it Take? http://prsm.tc/mAqAja     
    
    
    Storytelling for Data Analysts http://prsm.tc/BdoYYc     
    
    
    Your Facebook Network Can Predict Whether You'll Get Dumped Within The Next 60 Days http://prsm.tc/pGIlZB     
    
    
        
    
    
    Is Having Grit The Key To Success?
http://www.npr.org/2013/11/01/240779578/is-having-grit-the-key-to-success …    
    
    
    Googlers say “F*** you” to NSA, company encrypts internal network http://prsm.tc/mEagTe     
    
    
    Great session about pro and cons #SQL on #Hadoop with @johnlmyers44    
    
    
    Online Algorithms in High-frequency Trading http://prsm.tc/HrAYNy     
    
    
    To Drive Growth, Dive into Data http://prsm.tc/47YVwj     
    
    
    UPS Advances Sustainable Operations With Big Data http://prsm.tc/CF6hY4     
    
    
    Amazon plans to lower the cost of processing big data in the cloud http://prsm.tc/ocq9Zp     
    
    
    A Wonderfully Simplified Map of San Francisco's Bicycle Infrastructure http://prsm.tc/WPSDHv     
    
    
    Data Visualization 101 http://prsm.tc/d916qS     
    
    
    @techmilind not my fav but I'm willing to try. :)    
    
    
    Former Airbnb engineers simplify Mesos to manage data jobs in the cloud http://prsm.tc/WO7ZP8     
    
    
    How long do disk drives last? http://prsm.tc/JLbQm8     
    
    
    Does Your Company Actually Need Data Visualization? http://prsm.tc/HOvdeV     
    
    
    In rare 1983 speech, Steve Jobs alluded to the iPad, Siri, the App Store, mainstream Internet connectivity... http://prsm.tc/QATm7a     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Want Big Data Success? Hire a Biologist (As @datameer CTO Peter Voss is) http://prsm.tc/cvWNER     
    
    
    Google BigTable - Facts http://prsm.tc/YCoszx     
    
    
    Play Framework Grid Deployment with Mesos http://prsm.tc/iFDazI     
    
    
    Hadoop co-founder believes the future of big data is the Enterprise Data Hub http://prsm.tc/nllkmA     
    
    
    @pemullen not sure I can make it. Will try though.    
    
    
    128 billion hyperlinks - publicly available http://prsm.tc/rexALJ     
    
    
        
    
    
    A simplified graphical approach to machine learning http://prsm.tc/j1Soms     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: The Brain - and Soul - of Capitalism http://s.hbr.org/1fAG5B1     
    
    
    KDnuggets Review of Analytics Marketplaces: The Next Big Thing for Big Data http://prsm.tc/FgCrEx     
    
    
    Marissa Mayer: Your Job Is to Play Defense for Your Employees http://prsm.tc/Xct2Fv     
    
    
    Neuroscientists Develop 5D Data Visualization Technique http://prsm.tc/8BZYBx     
    
    
    The difference between networking and not working is just one letter.    
    
    
    Check out part 2 of my conversation with Michael Stack, the chair of the Apache HBase project: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u_OSzqbvOp4 …    
    
    
    Why #Hadoop is so fast adopted in all companies. @ted_dunning
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xyV_kO_8Bww …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Fight Fraud with Big Data Analytics http://prsm.tc/QCcrc5     
    
    
    My prediction: 2014, The Year of Big Sensor Data http://bit.ly/1c4Zrv3  #IoT    
    
    
    Python Displacing R As The Programming Language For Data Science ?http://prsm.tc/JnFFku     
    
    
    Fun new #BigDataBrews with @Piccolbo, we talked about #RHadoop, #R & #Hadoop http://bit.ly/IrmncI     
    
    
    @actbrilliant Phil Schelly CTO of Sears used it first in context with #Hadoop e.g.: http://info.datameer.com/Web-Hadoop-Data-Hub-Sears.html … or in many conference keynotes    
    
    
    Yelp graph: checkin-based business clustering http://prsm.tc/Efc2P1     
    
    
    Best thing I bought online all year. Grab poverty by the horns: #GiveAGoat http://www.heifer.org/one     
    
    
    Probabilistic Programming in Quantitative Finance http://prsm.tc/N0oqGw     
    
    
    Biggest source of funding for most startups is actually surprising http://prsm.tc/sTFNgp     
    
    
    THANK YOU to everyone who helped us donate an amazing $10,000 to saving elephant orphans.  http://bit.ly/IY0eTU     
    
    
    In Head-Hunting, Big Data May Not Be Such a Big Deal
http://www.nytimes.com/2013/06/20/business/in-head-hunting-big-data-may-not-be-such-a-big-deal.html?pagewanted=all&_r=1& …    
    
    
    Big Data & Brews: Michael Zeller, CEO of Zementis, part 1: http://youtu.be/rt4TVjD5BFM  via @youtube    
    
    
    LinkedIn CEO Jeff Weiner Explains The Difference Between Managers And Leaders http://prsm.tc/O17gDW     
    
    
    New #BigDataBrews with @MichaelZeller today - part 2: http://youtu.be/g9clPcPaiXg  #PMML #predictive    
    
    
    Apache Kafka - A Different Kind of Messaging System http://prsm.tc/5WxWwP     
    
    
    Forget Academia. Startups Are the Future of Knowledge http://prsm.tc/DJGOP4     
    
    
    