Anyone.. HTC One launch webcast link????    
    
    
    So, HTC has some private webcast for media..    
    
    
    @kunalgangar do u have any login details that can work?    
    
    
    @kunalgangar seems like..    
    
    
    HTC One launched; packs 4.7-inch 1080p display, Ultrapixel camera

http://androidos.in/2013/02/htc-one-launch/ …    
    
    
    Entry level consumer Ubuntu tablet requires 2GB RAM, Dual-core Cortex A15.. #fail    
    
    
    @nileshgr sure.. but what about pricing.. component cost will increase overall tablet pricing.    
    
    
    @nileshgr n anything less dan smooth experience does nt really matter. Android tabs can give smooth experience wid dual-core A9, 1GB RAM    
    
    
    @nileshgr Yes, but those are high-end phones.. these are required specs for "entry-level" tablet..    
    
    
    Second system crash in two days..    
    
    
    @GautamPW Nope, Windows 7... seems to be app specific issue causing the system to crash..    
    
    
    Looks like I will have to buy a new laptop earlier than expected... Dell you suck...    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz Who is going to give me 1 lakh for Apple or Sony    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz for me it is..    
    
    
    Why doesn't Google allow '.' in custom URLs for Google+ pages, Facebook does..    
    
    
    @ManpreetAtDell Vostro V131, Frequent system crashing due to hardware issue, as the warranty has expired, I am not sure how much u can help.    
    
    
    The free '1TB Google Drive storage for 3 yrs' given with Chromebook Pixel costs more than the device price. USD 1800>USD 1299.    
    
    
    I like Chromebook Pixel, would love to buy it, but the price is just too much.. something around $900-1000 would have been fine.    
    
    
    Time to flash Ubuntu on Galaxy Nexus..    
    
    
    Damn.. no way to add hidden Wi-Fi SSID in current dev preview of Ubuntu for Galaxy Nexus...    
    
    
    Asus to launch Memo Pad in India on Feb 27    
    
    
    Decent pricing ..RT @androidosblog: LG Optimus G priced at INR 30,990, available online in India  http://androidos.in/2013/02/lg-optimus-g-india/ …    
    
    
    BB Z10 is going to be priced INR 39,500 n India    
    
    
    @BipinBihari_ First week of March @modibimal    
    
    
    Tired of Micromax, Lava and Karbonn launching Android phones every other day.. just piling up crap in the market.    
    
    
    No inclination 2 provide quality products 2 d consumers, just quantity. no wonder we don't see ny HTC, Sony or Samsung coming out of India.    
    
    
    It is a FonePad teaser not Padfone.. all these tech blogs.. just rehashing stories..    
    
    
    WebOS lives! LG to resurrect it for smart TVs

http://reviews.cnet.com/8301-13970_7-57570990-78/webos-lives-lg-to-resurrect-it-for-smart-tvs/ …    
    
    
    Damn... wordpress making uploaded image corrupt...    
    
    
    @nileshgr turns out, it was something related to my PC, n I kept cursing wordpress the whole day. Still have to figure out the PC part..    
    
    
    @nileshgr Yes, every browser.. i tried uploading an image to imgur, which also got corrupted then I realized that it is sum PC issue.    
    
    
    @nileshgr I thought so too, running scan right now.. but seems unlikely as I am more than careful.    
    
    
    @WhatTheBit Not really. they are streaming it via Youtube    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 u realized just now :P there are Ubuntu OS phones too    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 not really.. the first Firefox phones will come in mid-2013 and are budget phones, no threat to Android.    
    
    
    Lots of praise for Chromebook Pixel.. now, waiting for price-cut :P    
    
    
    Chromebook Pixel, Nexus Q show that Google can indeed make good hardware, if only the software had not failed them in both cases.    
    
    
    Asus Memo Pad packs some positives, but the single core processor inside, mars the deal. At 10K, it is slightly expensive.    
    
    
    One can always choose Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 311 over Memo Pad for only INR 2.5K extra..    
    
    
    The display of Galaxy Nexus looks so nice after using Galaxy Grand for five hours.. :P    
    
    
    I have realized that anything bigger than Galaxy Nexus is too big for me...    
    
    
    @josematthew low res.. display as such seems fine, bt as soon as u look at high-res display like d one in G-Nex, u realize what u r msising.    
    
    
    India is d 13th country to Google Play Books, others - Australia,Canada,Spain,Germany,Italy,UK,South Korea,Japan,Brazil,France,Russia & US    
    
    
    Mobile phones to get costlier #budget2013    
    
    
    After Prison Break, now Arrow also has 'Scylla.'    
    
    
    Where are the Smart App updates for Android? Whenever I see an app update in progress on my phone, it is always downloading the full app.    
    
    
    @tsuvik that is certainly weird.. I did see a few smart app updates when the feature was introduced initially but never since then..    
    
    
    Is Gmail down? getting Error 502    
    
    
    yes, it is down...  #gmail    
    
    
    @nkumar_ did u try the web version?    
    
    
    @nileshgr still not working for me @nkumar_ pic.twitter.com/w4PbK4RuHK    
    
    
    #gmail is finally working.    
    
    
    FITH Media has changed the name of Nikal Padi to Slumdog Plumber & Pipes Puzzle, looks like the colloquial reference didn't work for them.    
    
    
    @BenedictEvans Not publicly but at the Google's MWC 2013 round-table - it is still 1.3 million per day  @WhatTheBit    
    
    
    @BenedictEvans yes, probably because the growth is stagnating @whatthebit    
    
    
    I am reviewing this tablet and it has latest version of Play Store and for some reason it is not showing any paid apps, e-books. #weird    
    
    
    Kindle Fire has been officially added to CM :)    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 nope.. still the same..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 :P koi nhn beta..    
    
    
    Sony Xperia Z is the first smartphone to be wholly developed by Sony since its split from mobile phone partner Ericsson last year: Reuters    
    
    
    HTC One has been priced cheaper than Xperia Z and Note II in UK, I hope same happens in India    
    
    
    :) RT @ianbetteridge: Today's tech journalism, in one easy GIF. http://bit.ly/WHA0FP     
    
    
    Samsung Galaxy S 4 or Samsung Galaxy S IV, I think it is going to be the former..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 no.. dnt even think about these crappy chinese tablets..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 sure..    
    
    
    Six hours to go for Samsung Galaxy S 4 announcement    
    
    
    @AppAndWinBB Was reading about that only just now :) @androidosblog    
    
    
    @AppAndWinBB I think Samsung is going to surprise us by showing a different design than the leaked one.    
    
    
    @NihaMasih Oye can I call you right now?    
    
    
    Samsung Galaxy S 4 press event is beginning..    
    
    
    Almost 300,000 people watching the Galaxy S 4 event live-stream right now..    
    
    
    Finally....    
    
    
    So the leaks were true...    
    
    
    I like some of the Samsung Galaxy S 4 customizations but I would rather prefer HTC One    
    
    
    Had breakfast at 7am for the first time in years..thanks to an all-nighter.. #gs4    
    
    
    Why is this one person posting about Galaxy S 4 launch event now.. it is over ..    
    
    
    Sony needs to start innovating on the software front, else they will be left behind..    
    
    
    @AppAndWinBB Yes.. :P    
    
    
    Time to take a quick nap..    
    
    
    Almost done with Galaxy S 4 stories...    
    
    
    Lava is now launching new Android phones just because it can..    
    
    
    Three phones with almost same specs, really Lava...    
    
    
    Price of Xperia Z is already 1K down on Flipkart    
    
    
    The current rumours of Motorola X Phone being a series of devices makes sense..    
    
    
    I don't believe single one of these Nexus 5 rumours...    
    
    
    Next-gen Nexus 7 will have Qualcomm processor - Digitimes    
    
    
    @NihaMasih I think someone else wrote that..?    
    
    
    @NihaMasih and is it raining in Delhi?    
    
    
    @NihaMasih ok.. i am in train na.. so didn't know :)    
    
    
    S 4 Indian version to feature Exynos 5 Octa is such a non-story...    
    
    
    LG is also working on a Smart Watch: Report

http://androidos.in/2013/03/lg-smart-watch/ …    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz Here is ur phone review http://androidos.in/2013/03/huawei-ascend-g600-review/ …    
    
    
    @NihaMasih frm whr did u get an iphone?    
    
    
    @NihaMasih oh... the stupid app name is Twitter for iPhone..    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz main hamesha se expert tha :P    
    
    
    70pc of first 10 million Galaxy S 4 units to come with Snapdragon 600 CPU: Report

http://androidos.in/2013/03/samsung-galaxy-s-4-chip-issues/ …    
    
    
    @ShopnShipIndia wht will be d landing price for this one http://www.pcm.com/p/Apple-MacBook-Pro/product~dpno~9418743~pdp.iadfdhc …    
    
    
    These rumours na..... none of the rumours that have appeared about Motorola X or Nexus 5 are close to reality. ..    
    
    
    Google+ Android app updated, gets in-built Snapseed photo enhancements

http://androidos.in/2013/03/google-android-app-updated/ …    
    
    
    Nice... great Holi gift from Google.. begins selling Nexus 7 from Google Play in India    
    
    
    Google begins selling Nexus 7 via Google Play for INR 15,999

http://androidos.in/2013/03/google-nexus-7-play-india/ …    
    
    
    @surajkala sure.. am doing a post with all details.. will include in that..    
    
    
    Nexus 7 being sold in India are actually getting shipped from Singapore..    
    
    
    @MirRafae oops.. corrected...    
    
    
    Or it seems like they are shipping from Singapore.. will need to dig more to get a final confirmation..    
    
    
    Was the delay in Canvas HD shipments had something to do with Ericsson patent lawsuit?    
    
    
    @surajkala 2-3K more than fair, but i think it is still a decent price. @DJain1989    
    
    
    India is the tenth country where Google is selling Nexus device(s) via Google Play.    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz abe it is a tablet... u wanted a phone..    
    
    
    So many mistakes in this WSJ report on Nexus 7 release in India: http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887324789504578384111477142162.html …    
    
    
    Just a read a review and the reviewer constantly dubbed the smartphone from a Chinese OEM as an indigenous product...    
    
    
    He also praised the indigenous smartphone industry.. do we have something like that in India ?    
    
    
    Google launches Google Play Movies in India

http://androidos.in/2013/03/google-play-movies-india/ …    
    
    
    Damn this internet.. not working.. hav to use Vodafone EDGE to file stories    
    
    
    Only select yashraj movies in Google Play as Hindi movies... Google need more partnerships... but certainly a good start...    
    
    
    Many movies are way cheaper to buy on Google Play Movies than Apple iTunes..    
    
    
    @NihaMasih coz for that you need to be a normal person in the night and sleep :P    
    
    
    India is the 13th country to get Movie rentals, purchases in Google Play..    
    
    
    According to Firstpost, the Google Play Movies prices suck.. really.. so, now u want movies at the cost of pirated discs..    
    
    
    Everytime I see the Firstpost's Google Play Movies article on Google News, I feel like killing myself..    
    
    
    Such a shoddy piece, and that's what happens when news sites start hiring content writers to do the job of journalists...    
    
    
    Now seeing more Hindi movies on Google Play ..still difficult for find, problem with discovery..    
    
    
    @tsuvik I too thought the same earlier, but I just saw more movies by searching 'exact movie names' or navigating through 'related movies'    
    
    
    @devangvira yes... I hope they do that.. Youtube rentals have better discovery than Google Play Movies..    
    
    
    Is it possible that FB will show HTC One on April 4, with Blinkfeed getting replaced by its custom FB-centric widget...?    
    
    
    wow @zeenews is going one step ahead of @firstpostin and blatantly copy-pasting content... @ZRG_DNA @androidosblog    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz You people do know that there is sumthng called "Phone" @NihaMasih    
    
    
    @nixxin was it shipped from Singapore or India?    
    
    
    @Harshal_F1 that is full HD, but 128 (out of 1920) pixels are used in on-screen navigation @androidosblog @Techmeme    
    
    
    @jainrounak which source?    
    
    
    @jainrounak Dear Rounak, I don't even know about ur blog.. seeing it for the first time today... GLbenchmark is a pretty popular .. contd..    
    
    
    @jainrounak ...source for spotting new devices..and everyone know about it. and now u will say Slashgear, which did d same just ... contd..    
    
    
    @jainrounak ...the same story just after me also stole it from ur blog..    
    
    
    @jainrounak ya right... u r crazy to even think that I read or follow ur blog on Twitter.. u can think whatever u want..    
    
    
    @syamant http://support.google.com/googleplay/bin/request.py?contact_type=contact_policy&policy=hardware … @nixxin @googleplay pic.twitter.com/J5jcLuNjRO    
    
    
    @syamant great. hope u get a replacement device soon..    
    
    
    LOL.. Google is running an April Fool's prank in Google Analytics too :P    
    
    
    :P RT @SamsungMobileSA: Introducing the sleek, new #GALAXYSV... pic.twitter.com/qtAOMD2DPi    
    
    
    So, it is confirmed that Nexus 7 3G or 32GB Wi-Fi only versions won't go on sale via Google Play..(at least for now)..    
    
    
    Not feeling well at all... :-|    
    
    
    I am amazed at how the same Firstpost story continues to rank on Google News again and again with new post timings. Some blackhat news SEO.    
    
    
    @Harry_Jerry almst evry news, i monitr d tech sectin n almst evry stry appears multipl times, ex: seen dis twice 2day http://www.firstpost.com/tech/death-of-ipad-mini-asus-launches-32gb-nexus-with-3g-for-21900-683086.html …    
    
    
    So, after Gawker, Times Internet partners with Business Insider to launch BI India    
    
    
    Lifehacker India and Gizmodo India launching this month...    
    
    
    It is LIVE RT @androidosblog: Watch Facebook’s Android event here [Live]

http://androidos.in/2013/04/facebook-event-live/ …    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris I credited two different sources 4 dat story, nw do u want me 2 scour d  internet to find nd credit everyone who did that story    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris nd dont get me started.. i will tell u several stories, which wer picked up frm @androidosblog by gizbot and never got credited    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris and there is nothing called 1st report courtesy. i will credit what my sources are ...    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris coz ppl make public accusations here that hav no basis..like d one u just made... which "experienced" person does that..    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris byee.. anywys i jst read d gizbot report, it ws posted in march nd der wer no details, which wer posted by me or ny site 2day    
    
    
    Lava launches IRIS 455 Android phone with dual-core CPU

http://androidos.in/2013/04/lava-launches-iris-455-android-phone-with-dual-core-cpu/ …    
    
    
    Google Paid This Man $100 Million: Here's His Story http://www.businessinsider.com/neal-mohan-googles-100-million-man-2013-4 … via @sai    
    
    
    @MMXNewscaster Yes.. tell me for @androidosblog    
    
    
    HP Slate 7 Europe pricing revealed – €149, sales might begin on June 1

http://androidos.in/2013/04/hp-slate-7-europe-pricing-revealed-e149-sales-might-begin-on-june-1/ …    
    
    
    Micromax to launch ultra-cheap Canvas Viva A72 phablet soon

http://androidos.in/2013/04/micromax-to-launch-canvas-viva-a72-phablet-soon/ …    
    
    
    Does BuzzFeed Know the Secret? http://nymag.com/news/features/buzzfeed-2013-4/ …    
    
    
    Looks like, 4 someone who does not want to spend a fortune, HTC First seems like a pretty great device n it lets you use use stock Android..    
    
    
    I just wish HTC would have put Snapdragon 600 instead of 400 in HTC First and I would have gladly bought the phone.    
    
    
    @kunalgangar Yes, in a way, there are still many differences, but it would be great to see a high-end Android phone with 4.3-inch display..    
    
    
    I wonder why @ICICIBank_Care uses crappy courier companies to send bank communication, have issues with them every time.    
    
    
    Seem like India is the first country to see the launch of Xperia SP, correct me if I am wrong..    
    
    
    This is what happens when someone forces the world to use a single link shortening service. All hell breaks loose... #twitter #links    
    
    
    Twitter links are working now...    
    
    
    @GautamPW just saw it... that would be great.. sure go ahead...:)    
    
    
    LOL ... RT @NDTVGadgets: Iran developing its own "Islamic Google Earth" http://ndtv.in/14h82JT     
    
    
    Five Reasons PC Sales Have Plunged - ABC News http://abcn.ws/XH8myl  by @JoannaStern via @ABC    
    
    
    Dead City is so addictive..    
    
    
    @GautamPW Yes, I saw it and it was decent..but it got me thinking and I found a neat tool to create very decent Android apps..    
    
    
    @GautamPW check out the result of that tool - https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.androidos.in&hl=en …    
    
    
    @GautamPW No, all that is for coders and i am not one... there are lots of online tools that allows users to create RSS-based app, which 1/2    
    
    
    @GautamPW 2/2 I had checked out earlier, but none of them this good..    
    
    
    @GautamPW Yes, i saw that lifehacker app today itself.. its a third-party app and yes, it uses the same tool..    
    
    
    @GautamPW There ws an app earlier, which ws made using a similar tool, bt those guys stopped developmnt, so d app ws not compatible with ICS    
    
    
    Seems like there is no news.. everybody is just waiting for Facebook Home..    
    
    
    Facebook Home is just 258KB, seems like everything is included in Facebook app and Messenger..    
    
    
    At the current speed, Facebook Home will take hours to become visible properly in Google Play    
    
    
    E-Commerce sites hav increasingly startd 2 put product listings 4 un-announced products wid leakd details jst 2 get link-backs n traffic.    
    
    
    The Micromax Canvas 3D listing on Saholic is one such example...    
    
    
    You Lookin’ at Me? Reflections on Google Glass. http://dthin.gs/124cSGO     
    
    
    No tweets ... something wrong with Twitter?    
    
    
    Just finished the finale of "Spartacus" series and it was worth it...    
    
    
    The second coming of Facebook http://cnnmon.ie/ZaZXBM  via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    DNA has revamped their website, nice effort, a modern looking design.    
    
    
    Other news websites also need redesign in India, everyone is just trying to cram as much news they can on the homepage...    
    
    
    So, the Alcatel One Touch smartphone launch press release comes with a specs sheet that is actually copied and pasted from GSMArena.    
    
    
    SLOW SLOW NEWS DAY....    
    
    
    Turns out while I was quietly watching the latest episode of Castle, there was a small earthquake in Delhi. I didn't even feel it ...    
    
    
    is it just my connection or the AllthingsD live-stream is really messed up?    
    
    
    I don't know why but Google really hates my blog... hardly any search visibility...    
    
    
    @TheAngrez thanks...    
    
    
    Announcement at d New Delhi Railway Station - "Roof Traveling is not fun" - Really, didn't know people traveled on d train roof for FUN...    
    
    
    Google working on a gaming service like Apple Game Center and Amazon GameCircle?

http://androidos.in/2013/04/google-game-center-amazon-gamecircle-competitor/ … Tip @Techmeme    
    
    
    Amazon should bring LoveFilm to India..    
    
    
    It Wasn't Sunil Tripathi: The Anatomy of a Misinformation Disaster - Alexis C. Madrigal - The Atlantic http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/04/it-wasnt-sunil-tripathi-the-anatomy-of-a-misinformation-disaster/275155/ …    
    
    
    Is Apple Looking For A Replacement For CEO Cook?

http://www.forbes.com/sites/genemarcial/2013/04/21/is-apple-looking-for-a-replacement-for-ceo-cook/ …    
    
    
    It is interesting how everyone (globally) can watch Amazon's new original TV series pilots ..    
    
    
    @z0mer I have changed the link in via.. :)    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz no.. it is actually more, 750,000 devices every 12 hours, 1.5 million daily @shailichopra    
    
    
    AndroidOS.in version 1.1 now live in Google Play 

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.androidos.in …    
    
    
    HTC One nowhere to be seen as Samsung gets ready to launch Galaxy S4 in India , this is what leads to poor HTC sales...    
    
    
    Fly, Lemon Android phones - more Chinese crap in the Indian market..    
    
    
    Google X benchmark leak is so fake..    
    
    
    GSM Insider takes leaks from Chinese, Japanese websites and then posts them as their own.. really....    
    
    
    Does anyone have an Android 4.2.2 running device apart from Nexus and is there Photosphere present?    
    
    
    It has begun ... Samsung Galaxy S4 India launch event, watch it live 

http://goo.gl/lph8O     
    
    
    @sumeet_jnj http://androidos.in/2013/04/samsung-galaxy-s4-india-launch/ …    
    
    
    Samsung launches Galaxy S4 in India, priced at INR 41,500

http://androidos.in/2013/04/samsung-launches-galaxy-s4-in-india-priced-at-inr-41500/ …    
    
    
    4th generation Intel Core processors coming in 38 days or 3,337,200,000,000,000 nanoseconds pic.twitter.com/DhgHv4OGZf    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 lol :P    
    
    
    Not even Android 4.2 on-board RT @androidosblog: Samsung announces Galaxy Tab 3, Wi-Fi version goes on sale in May

http://androidos.in/2013/04/samsung-announces-galaxy-tab-3/ …    
    
    
    Some exclusive reports from one Indian blog are so amusing.. they hardly have any real info...    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 try http://m.androidos.in  on your phone and let me know if it works fine..    
    
    
    @mobstac can you guys reply to ticket 1440 on the support site, I am not able to redirect users to mobile site because of this..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 nah... just wanted to see if it was working for others too..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 yes... got it done today mrng... hav 2 finish anothr thing den all d mobile visitors will get automatically redirected to this.    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 great... so two things are done.. android app and mobile site..    
    
    
    Samsung phones, Google on top in Opera’s State of the Android Mobile Web in India report

http://androidos.in/2013/05/samsung-phones-google-on-top-in-operas-samw-report/ …    
    
    
    This looks like a winner RT @androidosblog: HTC M4 press render leaked, looks very much like HTC One

http://androidos.in/2013/05/htc-m4-press-render-leaked-looks-very-much-like-htc-one/ …    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 INR 25,490    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 it is actually quite decent, nice specs and good pricing...    
    
    
    Haven't The Verge had enough of Paul Miller...    
    
    
    Google Play on Nook HD tablets is a win-win for both Google and B&N    
    
    
    But I am sure Google has bent many rules to let B&N bring Google Play support for Nook HD tablets...    
    
    
    Nook tablets are looking so much more interesting now... having used the Nook Color - I know Nook tablets are great value for money..    
    
    
    When did Youtube add 144p video quality option?    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 2.3    
    
    
    Power cut.. damn it... it is becoming a daily affair....    
    
    
    So, Gizmodo India is live.. well sort of, only one story from the India staff... gizmodo.in    
    
    
    No leaks for Nexus 7 successor so far, even though it is expected to be announced in next 7 days...    
    
    
    Lots of devices just got another way to get Android 4.2.2 RT @androidosblog: CM 10.1 RC release rolling out now http://androidos.in/2013/05/cyanogenmod-10-1-rc-release-rolling-out-now-for-40-devices/ …    
    
    
    @nkumar_ surprising, I have it installed in my phone.. pic.twitter.com/0lbAJYmGyp    
    
    
    @nkumar_ seems like it is not officially supported..   http://support.google.com/earth/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=2516855&topic=2508753&ctx=topic … weird that it works for me on every device..    
    
    
    So, Tikona is not working right now and recharged MTS data card to work and it sucks big time..    
    
    
    @androidcreature they might not be coming as a company, but I think they have tied up with AndroidGuruz to sell Find 5 in India..    
    
    
    @androidcreature they are saying "coming soon," whr did u see "available tomorrow" ?    
    
    
    @reckless True, even Motorola XT720 Milestone had Xenon flash, never sold much..    
    
    
    Sony says entertainment businesses not for sale http://reut.rs/1695M7Z  via @reuters    
    
    
    Bloomberg’s culture is all about omniscience, down to the last keystroke http://qz.com/83862  via @qz    
    
    
    Why You Should Scrap That Ladder-Climbing Plan And Go Backpacking Around The World, Instead

http://www.fastcompany.com/3009589/why-you-should-scrap-that-ladder-climbing-plan-and-go-backpacking-around-the-world-instead …    
    
    
    Forbes India Magazine - How the Rise of Third Party Marketplaces can Alter Indian E-Commerce http://forbesindia.com/article/real-issue/how-the-rise-of-third-party-marketplaces-can-alter-indian-ecommerce/35209/0 …    
    
    
    @Javed_Del it has been available for quite some time in Google Play..    
    
    
    Who is taking the Nexus 4 pre-orders... ???? Why am I seeing all these India pre-order stories...    
    
    
    The Nexus 4 on pre-order at Flipkart packs 16GB of internal storage 

http://androidos.in/2013/05/google-nexus-4-india/ …    
    
    
    Is Google letting you try Play Music All Access in India? Keeps giving me server error..    
    
    
    @tsuvik I think so, but it is giving me the option to try it for free for 30 days..and when I select the free trial - server error..    
    
    
    Google's cloud music locker has also been revamped..    
    
    
    @nkumar_ where did u get the pricing?    
    
    
    @nkumar_ ok... still waiting for their event to start.. they haven't mentioned anything in the press release..    
    
    
    @PanasonicInNews What happened to the live-stream?    
    
    
    Dan Brown's Inferno is INR 1680 in Google Play Books, INR 348 on Kindle & INR 329 in Flyte, what's wrong with Google...    
    
    
    @androidcreature nice.. i hope there aren't any more delays... let me know if you get a unit on April 22... thanks..    
    
    
    @androidcreature i meant 'May'..    
    
    
    Croma is selling HTC Butterfly at INR 40,499, the phone is finally getting closer to what would have a decent price..need one more price-cut    
    
    
    @androidcreature thanks... will update the post with this...    
    
    
    @MyXOLO Are you guys sure that the update for A800 is Android 4.2, not Android 4.1.1?    
    
    
    Why is India not in the list of 170 countries where Kindle Fire HD is available ???    
    
    
    How Android Vendors Can Compete With Samsung | Tech.pinions http://shar.es/ZI48L     
    
    
    @GurmanBhatia I heard u r planning to intern sumwhr? let me knw if u r free ..i might hav sumthng..    
    
    
    Rest of the Facebook Home might be crap... but Chatheads is one thing Facebook got right..    
    
    
    @tejajuloori yes.. you don't need Facebook Home, just use the latest version of Facebook Messenger..    
    
    
    Why is everyone doing Galaxy Young duos availability story now.. it has been available for almost two months now...

http://androidos.in/2013/04/samsung-galaxy-young-y-plus-india/ …    
    
    
    The new tech palaces: visionary HQs, or cursed trophies? http://reut.rs/14Wr2Kn  via @reuters    
    
    
    RAM is here in less than 24 hours.. that's  why i like to shop from Flipkart.. :)    
    
    
    @Djkrimp Really... no credit... http://igyaan.in/48138/white-nexus-4-16gb-goes-on-sale-in-india/ … @iGyaan    
    
    
    @devangvira der was some issue with the feed, I have fixed it now.. it should be working fine, in case you still c old articles - sync once    
    
    
    Flipkart to Shutdown Flyte MP3 Store; To Exit Digital Music Business http://www.nextbigwhat.com/flyte-mp3-shutdown-297/ …    
    
    
    Flipkart has confirmed that Flyte MP3 Store is shutting down on June 17, 2013, just got a mail..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 it is spelled as Mikandi    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 haha.... pta rakhna padta hai...    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 k    
    
    
    With 8GB RAM in the laptop.. I can finally open as many tabs as i want :P    
    
    
    How can all these Android blogs report about this HTC and Android 4.3 story, this is so fake... and dnt even ask about the source..    
    
    
    So tempted to buy HTC One with Nexus experience.. it might be the replacement for my Galaxy Nexus    
    
    
    How can companies justify not putting at least full HD display in laptops priced more than 1 lakh..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 :)    
    
    
    Is there a non-voice calling phablet? :P sumone just used "voice-calling phablet" in headline..    
    
    
    Lenovo K900 also comes wid jst 8.8GB of free internl storage in 16GB version like Galaxy S4. Luks like Samsung isn't d only 1 with bloatware    
    
    
    For the first time ever Toshiba tablets are going to be available within days of announcement..    
    
    
    Excite Pro seems to be a great competitor to Xperia Tablet Z on paper, however it is d real world performance that matters d most..    
    
    
    Computex is mainly a Taiwan event but where is HTC?    
    
    
    Sony announces Xperia M & Xperia M dual, available in Q3, 2013

http://androidos.in/2013/06/sony-announces-xperia-xperia-dual-q3-2013/ …    
    
    
    Sony just announced its first Android 4.2-powered phone - Xperia M dual 

http://androidos.in/2013/06/sony-announces-xperia-xperia-dual-q3-2013/ …    
    
    
    It is so surprisng dat despite packing d same specs,single SIM n dual-SIM versions of  Sony phons run on differnt Android versions at launch    
    
    
    wow, http://housing.co.in  indeed looks nice.. great interface..    
    
    
    Amazon Launches In India

http://www.amazon.in/b/ref=footer_press?_encoding=UTF8&node=1592137031 …    
    
    
    Don't get excited folks, there is no Intel powered S4 coming...    
    
    
    Lenovo India to launch a bunch of Android phones today, K900 included..    
    
    
    Has HTC India lost it... Why is it launching ICS running phones now...    
    
    
    @nkumar_ thanks :)..    
    
    
    BB Q10 at 45K, are you kidding me.. no matter how great the keyboard is.    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 hota hai.. happened to me once :P    
    
    
    @nkumar_ must be a staged roll-out.. will take days to appear for everyone.. @Facebook    
    
    
    @nkumar_ Yes, dat is indeed a bit strange, seems nobody has got d update till nw, which shouldn't happen even 4 staged roll-out. @Facebook    
    
    
    Edward Snowden: the whistleblower behind revelations of NSA surveillance http://gu.com/p/3gec7/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    @nadeem112 Spend a little more and get Nexus 4 or you can choose Sony Xperia SP    
    
    
    @nadeem112 One X is also good, you can go for it..    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper thanks for the invite but please use @gauravshukla instead of @androidosblog    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper and I will joining in the next hour, as I told Shraddha...    
    
    
    @adravid_20 hey, I will be joining in the next hour    
    
    
    @adravid_20 sure, if you want to..    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Waiting to see the iOS' flatter design from Apple, they have been keeping the same UI for a long time now. #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Sort of, but they still have a long way to go @sizzler_Chetan @binoyxj #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Also, WP seriously needs some other manufacturer to take it seriously. Nokia alone cant do evrythng #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper not really, but then every other flagship smartphone is also getting hyped these days #tvpchat    
    
    
    @sunnyvjkumar I would seriously like to take a look at this research @TheViewspaper #tvpchat    
    
    
    @kunalgangar lol, what's that...    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper yes, in a way..but if you are a careful Android user, you dnt need to worry about security #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Platform wars - Android, no doubt.. #tvpchat    
    
    
    @SoccerAnalyst I wish I was kidding..:P Nokia and WP are nowhere  #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Recently gave an Asha series phone.. #tvpchat    
    
    
    @adravid_20 numerical keypad for easy access + decent support for basic apps, nothing too techie #tvpchat    
    
    
    @adravid_20 they are just trying to stay afloat, given the prices of BB10 devices in India, I dont see them gaining much traction #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Thanks for having me, it was great talking to everyone on the panel #tvpchat    
    
    
    Breaking: Amazon launches Kindle Fire HD tablets in India, available starting June 27

http://androidos.in/2013/06/amazon-kindle-fire-hd-tablets-india/ …    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 man of steel dekh li?    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 yay, ye toh Eros main bhi lagi hai.. wahan chalenge...    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 Yes, ek 12:30 hai.. phir ek 6:30..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 3D hai Eros main... bolo sham ko? ya kal    
    
    
    @nkumar_ this has been present for years..    
    
    
    @Karanbajaj They have stopped selling Apple products...just accessories now...    
    
    
    Liked d new HOT (House of Technology) store at Nehru Place... spacious, plenty of demo devices, proper sections, unusual for a place like NP    
    
    
    @asymco 91,287 as per the latest count on their site.. http://www.amazon.com/s/ref=nb_sb_noss?url=search-alias%3Dmobile-apps&field-keywords= …    
    
    
    What.... Cinema (part of video on Instagram) is not available in their Android app... only for iPhone 4S and 5.    
    
    
    Why aren't Instagram videos automatically muted like Vine videos...    
    
    
    @tsuvik probably, but a video I just played was so loud that sum kind of volume control or a mute button at least would make sense...    
    
    
    @tsuvik Yes, so let there be sound, but add a mute button while it is playing, it least that would save ppl from loud videos..    
    
    
    Sony has Xperia, LG has Optimus, Samsung has Galaxy, even Huawei has Ascend; Dear HTC, where is your identifiable branding for Android phns?    
    
    
    HTC does not seem to be able to decide between One and Desire    
    
    
    @raunaqkumaran In 2012, dey hd three "One" series phones n only 1 of dem ws flagship, in 2013 they hav one, not sure wat will happen in 2014    
    
    
    @raunaqkumaran they need to decide and stick to a strategy.. and then there are Butterfly phones, their branding is going haywire.    
    
    
    @raunaqkumaran Not every consumer tracks smartphones like fans or bloggers, HTC needs to give dem sumthing to remember, sumthng to indentify    
    
    
    Why is everyone doing Google Earth for Android update stories now, as far as I can see on Google Play, last update was on June 6..    
    
    
    This is what happens when one blog does a wrong story and others just follow it without even bothering to check for themselves    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 poor kids they don't know what they are getting into...    
    
    
    Almost evry tech site is talking abt irony of FB using Google Groups 4 beta-testing of its Android app - it is a necessity, not their choice    
    
    
    How much effort does it take to do a quick Google search before publishing stuff online..    
    
    
    Is there something wrong with @ideacellular today... no network... ??    
    
    
    @nkumar_ oops.. thanks..    
    
    
    Impressed with @ideacellular service, they replaced my faulty SIM in 5 mins and new SIM got activated in less than an hour..    
    
    
    Tizen is not dead, Samsung is working pretty hard on it, however rumours of the delay in the launch of first device are correct..    
    
    
    Something wrong wid @mobstac ? http://m.androidos.in  getting lot of 502 Bad Gateway errors for d last 30 mins, had 2 deactivate redirection    
    
    
    CC @naganaga https://twitter.com/gauravshukla/status/352798742925164544 …    
    
    
    @feedly Why are you picking up old posts from http://www.androidos.in/feed/ , even though the actual feed does not show any old posts..    
    
    
    ll someone frm @feedly respnd or fix it https://twitter.com/gauravshukla/status/354213227007193089 …

We r getting so many complaints from Feedly users although our RSS is fine.    
    
    
    CM 10.1.2 update rolling out now, contains fix for another Android security bug

http://www.androidos.in/2013/07/cyanogenmod-10-1-1/ …    
    
    
    @josematthew this is a problem with feedly, do this - https://twitter.com/androidosblog/status/354442979336921088 …    
    
    
    @josematthew that should not happen, I am seeing the latest articles at my end - http://cloud.feedly.com/#subscription%2Ffeed%2Fhttp%3A%2F%2Ffeeds.feedburner.com%2Fandroidosfeeds …    
    
    
    @josematthew gr8 :)    
    
    
    Finally figured out how to use Doubleclick ad server...    
    
    
    If only Indian telcos provided 20-30 GB of data under INR 1,500, I would gladly keep 3G as my main internet connection    
    
    
    Hav been using 3G as my main data connection 4 last 7-8 days nd it hs turned ot 2 be more reliable than Tikona, Reliance or Airtel Broadband    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 haha, ab main MTNL lene wala hun :P    
    
    
    @akarri Idea (which is in fact using Vodafone network to provide 3G in Delhi)    
    
    
    I think there is something fishy going on in @Flipkart Affiliate. 80-90pc of the affiliate sales being shown cancelled every month.    
    
    
    Newsroom Season 2 ... Yay...    
    
    
    Whats happening with @mobstac today, mobile site down for d third time for 5-10 mins (bad gateway), cc @naganaga    
    
    
    @bookmyshow should now remove @_pvrcinemas from "Cinemas For Which We Do Not Sell Tickets" #QAFail    
    
    
    I have noticed that Phonearena can publish any and everything. Just send them random news tips and they will publish it..    
    
    
    Whats with this Note 2 and S3 skipping Android 4.2.2 for 4.3, the source hardly seems credible and it is all over the place.    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 good... dekho dekho..    
    
    
    So, there is no Tab 3 10.1 announcement today.. only Tab 3 7-inch and 8-inch    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 it just got nine Emmy nominations...    
    
    
    Samsung Galaxy Tab 3 hands on [Images]

http://www.androidos.in/2013/07/samsung-galaxy-tab-3-hands-on-images/ …    
    
    
    Waiting for MTNL Delhi to install my new broadband connection for the last 12 days... Such poor service and no point of contact..    
    
    
    Despite d presence of multiple ISPs in Delhi, not a single one offers decent service. Changed from Reliance to Airtel to Tikona and now MTNL    
    
    
    @rahul1810 Checked yesterday.. not in my area..    
    
    
    Not a good day to fall sick..    
    
    
    @asymco coz it runs on a stripped down version of Chrome OS..    
    
    
    Lost hope with MTNL DELHI ... recharged my Idea 3G again....    
    
    
    Hav talked 2 evry MTNL official including AGM bt landline/boradband still nt workng, classic statement frm every official: aj kara dete hain    
    
    
    @nkumar_ yes, already filed a complaint using this link itself.. they closed the complaint after two days without resolution..    
    
    
    @nkumar_ tried opening the same complaint again recently but it gives error (duplicate complaint) even though the last one is closed..    
    
    
    @nkumar_ and escalation hasn't helped a bit, Area manager is of no use, despite multiple calls no solution..    
    
    
    @nkumar_ it shows "no pending complaints" when I check the status of last complaint    
    
    
    @sanjaybafna Not GM until now, but considering the experience till now, nt sure if he would be of any help. Will try calling his office 2day    
    
    
    @sanjaybafna thanks..    
    
    
    Tired of seeing stories for every damn little leak (even meaningless ones) when the product is getting announced in two days..    
    
    
    Haha.. RT @romainguy: I love Apple Insider http://appleinsider.com/articles/13/07/29/google-appears-ready-to-ditch-android-over-its-intellectual-property-issues …    
    
    
    Will be blogging Moto X launch from train today...    
    
    
    All major tech blogs have their Moto X posts ready thanks to an embargoed Moto X unveiling by Google for the select few.    
    
    
    Want Moto X as my next Android phone, time for a change..    
    
    
    Didn't take long | No longer available for free | Download 40 HarperCollins India e-books for free from Google Play http://www.androidos.in/2013/08/download-40-harpercollins-india-e-books-for-free-from-google-play/ …    
    
    
    Asus working on Nexus 10 successor: Report

http://www.androidos.in/2013/08/asus-working-on-nexus-10-successor-report/ …    
    
    
    Looks like folks at http://Yatra.com  forgot to renew their domain.... this is epic.. pic.twitter.com/pWNkviuS2S    
    
    
    "Android is better" http://paulstamatiou.com/android-is-better … via @Stammy    
    
    
    Wow, d non-agency tech stories filed at @IndianExpress r just copy-paste, take one para from here, another from there and u r dne #fail #wtf    
    
    
    Finally watched the HTC commercial... what is this... and they hav included an Aks song for like 5 secs..    
    
    
    @Javed_Del I think der r decnt mid-range Android devices bt its d lack of marketing. Every1 else is focusing on highend devices except Nokia    
    
    
    @Javed_Del Nokia knows it cant compete with Android phones in high-end segment so they focus on marketing their mid/entry level devices.    
    
    
    @Javed_Del I am not talking about local OEMs, Sony (also Samsung to a bit) has some decent devices in this range.    
    
    
    An exclusive coming up...    
    
    
    @evleaks why have you deleted your LG G2 tweet (Verizon variant)?    
    
    
    @evleaks ignore last tweet, found it at other sources, it was already out..    
    
    
    Seriously, The Next Web is the first site to report on Uber India launch, can't Indian blogs/ sites even break India-related stuff?    
    
    
    .. Probably because they are busy looking at their feed readers/ twitter or Google news to find what others are reporting and rewrite it.    
    
    
    @varunkrish may be they were, but Indian sites/ blogs are expected to be on top on stuff related to at least India.    
    
    
    @varunkrish bt considering their story was jst two paras at first and nw they are updating it, it does not look like they had PR beforehand    
    
    
    @varunkrish @nextbigwhat @medianama this is old story, published when Uber job listings were spotted suggesting impending India launch    
    
    
    If d product value shown by Samsung during d import of Galaxy Gear prototypes in India is ny indication, it is going 2 cost around INR 20K.    
    
    
    @kunalgangar Yes, a bit but nt double or triple. u r right, 20K makes no sense but that is what it seems right now.    
    
    
    @varunkrish no, they wouldn't, that's why just taking this as an indication...    
    
    
    @kunalgangar I doubt, look at the rumoured specs, they are way better than Sony's smartwatch.    
    
    
    @Jessicalessin there is a huge difference between Xiaomi and Micromax, while Xiaomi designs its own devices, Micromax just re-brands @qz    
    
    
    Homeland season 3 has already begun...:)    
    
    
    Disruptions: More Connected, Yet More Alone

http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/09/01/disruptions-more-connected-yet-more-alone/?_r=0 …    
    
    
    So, a mock-up of Note 12.2 is floating around on tech sites as a leaked image. Really, it is not even a slow news day..    
    
    
    iBall launches Andi 4a Projector smartphone for INR 18,999

http://www.androidos.in/2013/09/iball-launches-andi-4a-projector-smartphone-inr-18999/ … pic.twitter.com/X9JvbZWpML    
    
    
    ... spent hours figuring out Litecoin mining and it is up and running at last...    
    
    
    Wow, Nokia is cheaper than Motorola :P    
    
    
    Steve Ballmer email to Microsoft employees on Nokia Devices & Services acquisition

http://www.microsoft.com/en-us/news/Press/2013/Sep13/09-02email.aspx …    
    
    
    @narenbalaji even if we account the value of Nokia patents, which as per Fortune is around $4bn, it is still cheaper @modibimal    
    
    
    @narenbalaji Coz they were overvalued, no one is going to make that mistake again @modibimal    
    
    
    It is Android 4.4 ppl, not 5.0.    
    
    
    So, almost everything from Sony's presser has already leaked in detail.    
    
    
    Qualcomm Uplinq keynote speech is also scheduled for later today.. what is so special abt Sep 4??????????????/    
    
    
    Sony presser has started #ifa2013    
    
    
    Sony is talking about its cameras right now.. nothing so far on Android front.. #ifa2013    
    
    
    In related news, Asus' #ifa2013 presser is also set to begin in a little while..    
    
    
    Sony has just launched a handycam with 4K recording support.. #ifa2013    
    
    
    Xperia Z1 has finally been officially announced... #ifa2013    
    
    
    Asus #ifa2013 press has begun..    
    
    
    @kunalgangar no live-stream..    
    
    
    Samsung press event at #IFA2013 is live..    
    
    
    Leaked Galaxy  Gear specs are nowhere near reality...    
    
    
    Galaxy Gear has been priced at $299 in US... ..India price - probably INR 20K.    
    
    
    Both Qualcomm Toq and Galaxy Gear cost $300, really.. who are these companies targeting..    
    
    
    @googledrive will someone fix Google Docs viewer... https://docs.google.com/viewer  #error502 #fail    
    
    
    Yahoo's new logo looks bad.....boring...    
    
    
    @pranavmistry How many Indian languages does Gear actually support? Do you have a fixed number?    
    
    
    "Don't forget to mention Android" notification on Shin's Galaxy Gear in Samsung press event was really clever..    
    
    
    Considering how everyone was saying the last time that Samsung does not even mention the word "Android" at the Galaxy device announcements..    
    
    
    @MAHESHTELECOM Can you pl tell the exact model number of this dual-SIM version?    
    
    
    Galaxy Nexus is finally working fine after I did a clean install of Android 4.3 from factory image..    
    
    
    @yoast can you pl officially add this to wordpress seo plugin - http://luckyboost.com/app-installs-for-twitter-card-with-wordpress-seo-plugin/ …    
    
    
    Sorry, Jeff Bezos, the news bundle isn’t coming back http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/the-switch/wp/2013/09/05/sorry-jeff-bezos-the-news-bundle-isnt-coming-back/ …    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 nice.. lage raho...    
    
    
    The Best Tech News Site That Isn’t a Tech News Site That Didn’t Exist Yesterday http://dthin.gs/19uvmSI     
    
    
    iSpy: How the NSA Accesses Smartphone Data http://spon.de/ad1NB  via @SPIEGELONLINE    
    
    
    Just yesterday, I was looking for something like this | Timeline of Edward Snowden's revelations  via @AJAM http://alj.am/17udQwR     
    
    
    @samirontwittter don't worry, try again after sometime and it will show the update.    
    
    
    Who the hell at @afp wrote this -  "Now a group of 500 Indian tech start-ups have banded together" 

http://www.hindustantimes.com/technology/Chunk-HT-UI-Technology-OtherStories/Indian-tech-companies-launch-campaign-to-name-next-version-of-Android-Ladoo/SP-Article1-1119959.aspx …    
    
    
    Following some brands on Twitter is a mistake, just un-followed @IntelIndia for their retweets..    
    
    
    Why do brands retweet every damn tweet they get during their promotional event/ contests/ etc..    
    
    
    Something wrong with @firefox  these days. Crashes at least two/ three times every day...    
    
    
    @nkumar_ I use both, but @firefox has increasingly become more and more frustrating..    
    
    
    Google trying new ad format on search page... this one is huge .. pic.twitter.com/4AVYB8IFFC    
    
    
    @nkumar_ @googlechrome is decent but hogs lot more RAM compared to @firefox, also I wish there was a manual sync option in Chrome.    
    
    
    @firefox Really, whr in my tweet did I mention flash? whole browser is crashing not flash...    
    
    
    So, iPhone 5c will most probably retail around INR 35K in India...    
    
    
    Star World Premier seems like a winner, finally someone is trying 2 tap viewers dat want 2 watch US shows at d same time as their US release    
    
    
    lol, an Indian tech news site is 'exclusively' reporting that a phone, which already runs on Android 4.2.2, is getting Android 4.2.2 update.    
    
    
    @sonamg haha... just wait n see, in d next few hours half of d indian tech news site, will carry d same story..    
    
    
    @sonamg over half of the tech blogs r lyk this, kis kis ko expose karo :)    
    
    
    @iSpiideyyy their statement was primarily about the exclusive part ..@AndroidFavorite    
    
    
    So, half of the TV series part of AXN's 'end of the world' thing have gotten less than 5 stars in IMDB user ratings..    
    
    
    Waiting eagerly for Person of Interest Season 3...  one more week to go...    
    
    
    Wow, ain't folks at Computer Emergency Response Team-India (CeRT-In) super-fast #fail http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/tech/tech-news/software-services/Email-SMS-stealing-virus-targeting-Android-users-in-India/articleshow/22714119.cms …    
    
    
    Time to uninstall @firefox from my laptop, tired of frequent crashing, even crashed in its own safe-mode..    
    
    
    So, the iOS version of BBM is already live in New Zealand but Android version is still missing in action.. https://itunes.apple.com/nz/app/bbm/id690046600?mt=8 …    
    
    
    @sameer_7_oberoi did u check the home-screen mode, switch it to basic or standard from easy mode.    
    
    
    @NihaMasih u watched it??    
    
    
    Not a good day to fall sick...    
    
    
    @RanjithThiru Thanks Ranjith    
    
    
    Update: 3G version now selling for INR 16,999 at Flipkart | Nexus 7 get another price-cut, now starts INR 9,999

http://www.androidos.in/2013/09/nexus-7-get-another-price-cut-now-starts-inr-9999-amazon/ …    
    
    
    @fully_bully Yet 2 handle Xperia C as it hasn't bn launched, Nexus 5 is expected latr next month, nt sure abt d Lumia ques, as i dnt use WP    
    
    
    @optronindia http://shopap.lenovo.com/in/en/smartphones/a-series/a706/#techspecs …    
    
    
    @optronindia I haven't used the phone so can't confirm, but what is different in specs on the actual phone?    
    
    
    @NihaMasih coz they are not meant to work :P    
    
    
    @NihaMasih waise u r nt alone, i hav over 30 tabs open each with a dffrnt stry but I have having tea nd watching 'the originals'.    
    
    
    @NihaMasih am*    
    
    
    HBO Asia's first original series Serangoon Road looks interesting... just watched the first episode...    
    
    
    LG G Pad 8.3 just got priced $510 in South Korea, weren't there rumours of $299 price-tag :P    
    
    
    @CelkonMobile Thanks but I will have to decline the offer. We do not accept gifts from the companies about which we write.    
    
    
    Amazon has stopped taking international Chromecast orders. So, it was an accident or bug that opened international orders in d first place.    
    
    
    As usual nothing starts in India on time #androidland    
    
    
    Spent last 4 and 1/2  hours attending/ commuting for a good for nothing press event. What a waste of time..    
    
    
    What the hell, Sony Vaio Pro 13 touchpad is already giving me problems...    
    
    
    @MirRafae http://www.sony.co.in/product/svp1321xpn …    
    
    
    @MirRafae mine is slightly lower model - right link: http://www.sony.co.in/product/svp1321wsn … Found the problem today itself, will be calling them tomorrow..    
    
    
    @CenaFanForLife What is your phone's home-screen mode right now? Check it in settings..    
    
    
    Aquos Phone EX announced by NTT Docomo today has a 490PPI display.    
    
    
    So, HTC had a press meet in  Singapore earlier today where it showcased One Max and other devices..    
    
    
    Still not officially announced though. #onemax    
    
    
    @Kamaltekwani most of the leaked specs are reportedly true..    
    
    
    It isn't just Acer, HP is also launching a Chromebook in India..    
    
    
    India seems to be the first market to get Acer C720 Chromebook, it is going on sale in Oct-end, Nov elsewhere.    
    
    
    To make Chromebooks work in India, we need 3G models, which are priced well.    
    
    
    Durga Puja pandal at Mela Grounds, C R Park. pic.twitter.com/AH5YskZ1DE    
    
    
    Durga Puja pandal, Navapalli Puja Samiti, C R Park pic.twitter.com/qoTHAaagWI    
    
    
    @Ajmal_Farooq It will probably get Android 4.3 update.. not confirmed though..    
    
    
    @diler55 nothing confirmed until now..    
    
    
    After this #fail exclusive http://www.android.gs/sony-planning-xperia-z-google-edition-says-insider/ … I find it hard to believe this http://www.android.gs/nexus-5-price-to-be-399-because-of-nexus-4-lte-launch-says-insider/ …    
    
    
    @Jessicalessin @amir u write dat Fire OS  "isn’t compatible wid Android apps," which is wrng, it is in fact more compatible than other forks    
    
    
    @Jessicalessin @amir talking about http://jessicalessin.com/2013/10/15/amazon-has-discussed-teaming-up-with-htc-on-phones/ …    
    
    
    Blogger-journalist Glenn Greenwald to leave Britain’s Guardian newspaper http://wapo.st/1gIU0E5  via @washingtonpost    
    
    
    @amir @Jessicalessin I dnt think it is "must" 4 most apps. I hav bn using 1st-gn KF 4 a long time n hv sideloaded several apps without issue    
    
    
    @amir @Jessicalessin Also as Amazn states here(native Android app compatibility) https://developer.amazon.com/sdk/fireos.html  75pc of Android apps work just fine    
    
    
    @amir @Jessicalessin link might talk abt tablt apps but it is valid 4 mst phn apps 2 coz Amzn dubs phn apps incompatibl coz of poor user-exp    
    
    
    Time of install Ubuntu Touch on my Galaxy Nexus...    
    
    
    In the 50 stories listed on Business Insider India, only three are from their India newsroom, really.. India Edition?    
    
    
    @chupchap not sure.. bt i heard sumtime back that they planned to hire 5-6 ppl..    
    
    
    Windows 8.1 upgrade really takes a lot of time...    
    
    
    Where does your Wikipedia donation go? Outgoing chief warns of potential corruption

http://www.dailydot.com/business/sue-gardner-log-rolling-corruption-wikimedia-chapters/ …    
    
    
    Twitter Likely to Kill Its Music App http://dthin.gs/19iif8c     
    
    
    In Perpetual Reinvention, SoftBank Eyes Shift to Mobile Content http://jessicalessin.com/2013/10/21/in-perpetual-reinvention-softbank-eyes-shift-to-mobile-content/ …    
    
    
    @charlesarthur @reckless most of Chromebook makers are mainly targeting schools, other education-related market..    
    
    
    @vscmuthu Try again after sometime or update via Kies..    
    
    
    New Nexus 10 Google Play listing and press render is so fake...    
    
    
    @nikitiwari email at gaurav@androidos.in @androidosblog    
    
    
    @nikitiwari and I have already got your press release    
    
    
    Watch the Google+ event here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=al0k1Dia6E0 …    
    
    
    BlackBerry met with Facebook on possible bid: WSJ http://on.wsj.com/HqOlWn     
    
    
    Twitter hit with $124 million lawsuit over private stock sale http://reut.rs/1gcDP3i  via @reuters    
    
    
    I just don't understand the people who have issues with Nexus 5 India pricing. INR 28,999 is a quite decent price...    
    
    
    If you continue swiping right on the home-screen of the new Google launcher, it shows you Google Now.. nice..    
    
    
    New Google launcher is working nicely on Galaxy Nexus..    
    
    
    @akarri It might work but then HTC and even ROM devs have long abandoned Desire, so it is unlikely that u will ever get KitKat on Desire..    
    
    
    Hong Kong media magnate buys stake in HTC: Report

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/hong-kong-media-magnate-buys-stake-htc/ … pic.twitter.com/VM5zFKuVLw    
    
    
    Moto G will be the first Motorola smartphone to reach India in over 15 months

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/motorola-reveals-moto-g-announced-november-13/ …    
    
    
    @diler55 still unconfirmed... but seems likely..    
    
    
    Advent launches Vega Tegra Note 7, coming to UK on November 15 for £180

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/advent-launches-vega-tegra-note-7-coming-uk-november-15-180/ … pic.twitter.com/eqWqZzqKlN    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz how is that 99acres fault? These are free user-listings, even you can list a flat and say anything in the description..    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz You can blame the broker who posted the listing but I don't see 99acres' fault.    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz how do you plan to regulate a website where thousands of users post listings everyday?    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz Infoedge has sum PR firm, dnt remember d name...call their office tomorrow mrng n they will connect u to 99acres    
    
    
    @sonamg Kitkat :P    
    
    
    @sonamg get a Nexus... Nexus 4 or 5, both are gr8 and u will be happy for the next two years..    
    
    
    @MrFriendism the official launch is still unconfirmed but it is expected to arrive next week or next to next week.    
    
    
    @khiladikataria Not many details are available at this point but I am sure Google would have thought about the x86 compatibility.    
    
    
    @sonamg it is most prob coming in the next ten days.. and it is LG-made and so is Nexus 4..    
    
    
    @sonamg okay... LG isn't that bad..and in this case think of LG as you would think of Foxconn in the case of iPhones    
    
    
    @sonamg achcha, if dnt lyk LG nd u r frustratd wid sammy, who do u lyk? does Motorola work 4 u, coz dey r also coming bck 2 India wid Moto G    
    
    
    So, several tech blogs are reporting Moto X images as Moto G... seriously ppl..    
    
    
    Why is Book My Show acting up..    
    
    
    LOL, it is moto x ppl, not Moto G.. RT @NDTVGadgets: Moto G press render leaked ahead of November 13 launch http://ndtv.in/1hpZkzb     
    
    
    One makes a mistake and others just follow.. why not, they nvr learnt anything apart from re-writing..    
    
    
    @bookmyshow_sup It is fine nw, but earlier it was giving problems wid movie and cinema selection.. no cinemas found etc..    
    
    
    @scurtsy It is Moto X, not Moto G. evleaks is talking about Moto Maker for Verizon in his tweet.

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/mobile-phones/10436484/Moto-G-press-image-leaks-ahead-of-launch.html …    
    
    
    @evleaks you need to be a little more clear in ur tweets, otherwise this happens: http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/mobile-phones/10436484/Moto-G-press-image-leaks-ahead-of-launch.html …    
    
    
    Sony Xperia Z1s makes an appearance on Sony website

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/sony-xperia-z1s-makes-appearance-sony-website/ … pic.twitter.com/1f8Ar567UR    
    
    
    Moto G revealed in detail: Press shots and full specifications leaked 

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/retailer-listings-reveal-moto-g-press-shots-specifications/ …    
    
    
    ASUS launches 27" WQHD LED-backlit monitor for INR 44,250..    
    
    
    @nileshgr WQHD resolution is the key here..    
    
    
    @google really loves sulekha, 9 out to 10 search results from one site..  #fail @theamitsinghal @mattcutts pic.twitter.com/goMsH02fsX    
    
    
    Nexus 5 expected to be available via Google Play in India by the end of this week...    
    
    
    Google unveils Android tablets with Google Play for Education

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/google-unveils-android-tablets-google-play-education/ … pic.twitter.com/Q4O5FwuC7Y    
    
    
    So Guardian has listed - only 1GB of RAM, no NFC, no 4G - as the cons in Moto G, really what do you want in $179 phone?? #fail    
    
    
    Seriously, this Business Standard reporter could have at least got the product names right.. http://www.business-standard.com/article/companies/htc-mulls-more-handsets-on-windows-8-113111800473_1.html …    
    
    
    @iansherr they are talking about domestic sales (South Korea only)..    
    
    
    Nexus 5 now available in India via Google Play, priced starting INR 28,999

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/nexus-5-now-available-google-play-inr-28999/ …    
    
    
    @sameer8019 Depends on ur storage needs. If don't store too much data (movies, music etc) in ur phone, go for 16GB else 32GB.    
    
    
    @sameer8019 unless u r going to save 5GB of music on ur phone, u don't need 32GB model, however if you want to be on d safe side go for 32GB    
    
    
    @kunalgangar @DJain1989 That is strange, even I can see Black 16GB Nexus 5 in stock..    
    
    
    Hangouts 2.0 update is finally  here.. pic.twitter.com/B1MSZ3qNkd    
    
    
    @DJain1989 Google Play issues, still showing available here..  @kunalgangar    
    
    
    @MrFriendism thanks akshay, glad you like it..@androidosblog    
    
    
    @MrFriendism Google Play is acting up.. it sometimes shows the phone in stock and sometimes doesn't.. Order if you can..    
    
    
    @phonesleak how do u know... and are you saying it is not Nexus 10?    
    
    
    @Javed_Del you already got shipping email?    
    
    
    @Javed_Del nice.. I hope I am not too far behind in the queue..  haven't received 'shipped' notification yet..    
    
    
    Nexus 5 order finally shipped :)    
    
    
    @lalpra 8AM, don't worry, it was showing Nov 24 in mine as well...    
    
    
    @ManishRajora the list price - INR 28,999    
    
    
    @Hemangbudhdeo For review, sure..    
    
    
    @sameer8019 I keep most of my data in cloud... so, yes..    
    
    
    @PrateekBhargava Google play    
    
    
    @lalpra I think the price is quite decent.. It might not exactly match US pricing but it is still great..    
    
    
    First Nexus 5 orders are already being delivered and stupid Bluedart has delayed my shipment..    
    
    
    @uhaish same here..    
    
    
    Yay, Nexus 5 is here.. :)    
    
    
    @uhaish Seems like delay message is wrong, just got mine..    
    
    
    @Saanjh85 sure...    
    
    
    @tsuvik @uhaish thanks :)    
    
    
    @sonamg sure... :)    
    
    
    @sameer8019 yes    
    
    
    @sameer8019 no..    
    
    
    Damn it, Nexus 5 is not detecting my SIM, which is working perfectly fine in Galaxy Nexus..    
    
    
    @Hyper_Lazy Yes    
    
    
    @Javed_Del Yes,  around 5... is it showing the flight delayed message in tracking?    
    
    
    @Javed_Del Yes, probably..    
    
    
    Liking Nexus 5 so far, apart from the slightly boring front of the device.. voice commands working perfectly in Google Now..    
    
    
    @razarahil Got it just 6 hours back...    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 I dnt think there is a problem in Nexus 5, found an old SIM and tried using that and Nexus 5 recognized it    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 Will go to Idea shop tomorrow and get a new microSIM..    
    
    
    Got a microSIM from Idea as the normal-turned-microSIM was somehow not working in Nexus 5..    
    
    
    Enough UC Browser, stop spamming my inbox..    
    
    
    Nexus device updates not released country-wise unless there are different variants.. so, why these Nexus 4 update in India stories...    
    
    
    @pratik_LFC Got it in 5 mins, was activated within an hour..    
    
    
    @pratik_LFC haven't been disappointed so far, but need to spend a little more time  with it..    
    
    
    HTC launches Mini+, Fetch and Power Flip Case accessories in India

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/htc-launches-mini-fetch-power-flip-cover-accessories-india/ … pic.twitter.com/udgqn54l8d    
    
    
    @nandu79 Just read your FE story on Newsstand, it is available since day one in India... https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.magazines …    
    
    
    @nandu79 Maybe, anyways, I installed it within 30 minutes of the official announcement..    
    
    
    @WhatTheBit It has just been announced for NTT Docomo, will be available around Dec-end.. so not really out..    
    
    
    Noticed that Adblock Plus has started blocking Outbrain's sponsored recommendations too..  #justanobservation    
    
    
    The Samsung KitKat update schedule leak looks so fake..    
    
    
    I hope Moto G changes how other smartphone makers look at mid-range/ budget smartphones..    
    
    
    In less than a year Bitcoin's value has gone from $12  to $740 ... next six months are going to be interesting..    
    
    
    Just realized that I have written Facebook of Android instead of Facebook for Android in a post.. damn it..    
    
    
    @uhaish it is working pretty good..    
    
    
    @uhaish but it will only work when you are on home-screen... if you were trying elsewhere..    
    
    
    @uhaish ohk..    
    
    
    HTC announces HTC One in gold colour

http://www.androidos.in/2013/11/htc-launches-htc-one-gold-colour/ … pic.twitter.com/euF78SxTjp    
    
    
    Washington Post honors researcher who has ‘shared more Pulitzer Prizes than anyone in the newsroom’ | Poynter.: http://www.poynter.org/latest-news/mediawire/231314/washington-post-honors-researcher-who-has-shared-more-pulitzer-prizes-than-anyone-in-the-newsroom/#.UpQOpF_gDDg.twitter …    
    
    
    Now that ChatOn has SMS/ MMS integration, Samsung might remove messaging app in its Android 4.4 devices.    
    
    
    The Dirty Secret of Black Friday 'Discounts'
 http://on.wsj.com/1gcsbTm     
    
    
    Want any more permissions @facebook ??? pic.twitter.com/WCIBR83Xxr    
    
    
    So, I put my email address on  MakeMyTrip and don't even complete d transaction nd the stupid site creates an user account for me #spammers    
    
    
    Do we already have Bitcoin Billionaires.. ? If not we will probably have some in the next few months..    
    
    
    @Javed_Del Der is no new KitKat UI, it is pretty much same as Jelly Bean; d new Google launcher ws already revealed to be Nexus 5 exclusive    
    
    
    @Javed_Del probably coz it includes proprietary elements.. n Google doesn't want them 2 be available as part of Android 4.4 open-source code    
    
    
    @Javed_Del but non-availability on Nexus device is a little surprising..    
    
    
    I wish it was that simple.. :P pic.twitter.com/KOKdZFmO81    
    
    
    Android 4.4 updates for non-nexus devices are coming faster than earlier Android versions..    
    
    
    @priceBaba Google is giving headsts in d box with Nexus 5 when bought frm Google Play, and AFAIK, same is true 4 all Nexus 5 bought in India    
    
    
    @annkur Yes, LG is including the cost of selling phones in brick and mortar stores in the form of that extra 1K @SourceX_4447    
    
    
    @annkur Well that's what LG said in a statement regarding the disparity in LG (not necessarily offline) and Google Play pricing..    
    
    
    @annkur Even the online stores like Flipkart and all are also selling the phone with that extra 1K as they get the phone from LG..    
    
    
    @annkur they are just not taking too much profit (if there is much), they buy the phone in bulk from LG and sell at their own price..    
    
    
    @annkur not sure about that..    
    
    
    @SourceX_4447 Google Play listing is a global template n AFIAK headsets are not offered nywhere wid Nexus 5 bought from Google Play @annkur    
    
    
    @SourceX_4447 they should ideally change it, seems to have been overlooked as it is an India-specific thing.. @annkur    
    
    
    Nexus 5 review is almost done.. should go live tomorrow..    
    
    
    @Harshal_F1 Yes, saw just now..    
    
    
    @NagpalManoj thanks for letting me know.. have updated the post to reflect the change..@androidosblog    
    
    
    Android 4.4.1 update rolling-out for Nexus 5, Nexus 4 & Nexus 7 LTE (2013)

http://www.androidos.in/2013/12/android-4-4-1-update-rolling-nexus-5-nexus-4-nexus-7-lte-2013/ …    
    
    
    Will Tech News Junkies Actually Pay for Scoops?

http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-12-05/will-tech-news-junkies-actually-pay-for-scoops …    
    
    
    Woah.. the latest Scandal episode was the most scandalous one I have seen in a long time..    
    
    
    While I have been mostly satisfied with Vaio Pro 13, the touchpad is a disappointment..    
    
    
    At INR 26,990 pricing, the 3G version of Samsung Chromebook would have made more sense to launch in India (and it exists)..    
    
    
    Huawei PhoPad... really... they couldn't get a worse name...    
    
    
    None of the new Desire smartphones has been rightly priced.. and Desire 700 pricing is plain stupid..    
    
    
    WIth Moto G debut expected next month, I don't see anyone choosing Desire 501 over Moto G...    
    
    
    Everyone seems to be getting Android 4.4.2 update expect me... looks like I will have to sideload it...    
    
    
    @Harshal_F1 was waiting for the OTA, didn't sideload 4.4.1 ...    
    
    
    Snapdragon 410 seems to have been made keeping China in mind...  but India will also benefit with this..    
    
    
    4.4 to 4.4.2 update for Nexus 5 is 53.9 MB ... this is quite big..    
    
    
    @nkumar_ how big was 4.4 to 4.4.1?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @toptenmails Nexus updates are not country-specific.. they roll-out globally.. except in carrier-specific variants..    
    
    
    @toptenmails the updates are rolled-out in phases... so not everyone get them right-away..    
    
    
    @passerby16 what do you mean by self-developed smartphones? - phone from smaller smartphone vendors?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @passerby16 there are several smartphone vendors in India, which have launched many decent sub-$200/300 smartphones..    
    
    
    House of Cards Season 2 trailer http://youtu.be/jFhJjCmYi1M     
    
    
    How many kidneys do I need to sell for this.. RT @Gizmodo: A fully loaded new Mac Pro will cost you $14,000: http://gizmo.do/vaxp5K3     
    
    
    @nonuahuja1998 hello    
    
    
    @nonuahuja1998 what do you mean by that..    
    
    
    @nonuahuja1998 personally I haven't used Q2000, so can't tell what kind of a flash it is using..    
    
    
    @nonuahuja1998 You can check that in the demo units present at various shops..    
    
    
    @nonuahuja1998 It has been launched...you should ask big retailers..    
    
    
    @nonuahuja1998 check youtube, there are various video reviews..    
    
    
    "Crackdown" really! it is an advisory @TheNextWeb: BTC exchanges in India suspend services as authorities crack down on d virtual currency    
    
    
    @jonrussell Thnks 4 d link bt both d exchnges hd sspended their operations aftr d RBI advisory nd d suspension had nothing 2 do wid dis raid    
    
    
    @jonrussell the headline suggests as if the raid had sumthng to do wid the suspension.. @TheNextWeb    
    
    
    Is HTC really going to call its next flagship - One Two, i thought that was a made-up name..    
    
    
    Anyone.. HTC One launch webcast link????    
    
    
    So, HTC has some private webcast for media..    
    
    
    @kunalgangar do u have any login details that can work?    
    
    
    @kunalgangar seems like..    
    
    
    HTC One launched; packs 4.7-inch 1080p display, Ultrapixel camera

http://androidos.in/2013/02/htc-one-launch/ …    
    
    
    Entry level consumer Ubuntu tablet requires 2GB RAM, Dual-core Cortex A15.. #fail    
    
    
    @nileshgr sure.. but what about pricing.. component cost will increase overall tablet pricing.    
    
    
    @nileshgr n anything less dan smooth experience does nt really matter. Android tabs can give smooth experience wid dual-core A9, 1GB RAM    
    
    
    @nileshgr Yes, but those are high-end phones.. these are required specs for "entry-level" tablet..    
    
    
    Second system crash in two days..    
    
    
    @GautamPW Nope, Windows 7... seems to be app specific issue causing the system to crash..    
    
    
    Looks like I will have to buy a new laptop earlier than expected... Dell you suck...    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz Who is going to give me 1 lakh for Apple or Sony    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz for me it is..    
    
    
    Why doesn't Google allow '.' in custom URLs for Google+ pages, Facebook does..    
    
    
    @ManpreetAtDell Vostro V131, Frequent system crashing due to hardware issue, as the warranty has expired, I am not sure how much u can help.    
    
    
    The free '1TB Google Drive storage for 3 yrs' given with Chromebook Pixel costs more than the device price. USD 1800>USD 1299.    
    
    
    I like Chromebook Pixel, would love to buy it, but the price is just too much.. something around $900-1000 would have been fine.    
    
    
    Time to flash Ubuntu on Galaxy Nexus..    
    
    
    Damn.. no way to add hidden Wi-Fi SSID in current dev preview of Ubuntu for Galaxy Nexus...    
    
    
    Asus to launch Memo Pad in India on Feb 27    
    
    
    Decent pricing ..RT @androidosblog: LG Optimus G priced at INR 30,990, available online in India  http://androidos.in/2013/02/lg-optimus-g-india/ …    
    
    
    BB Z10 is going to be priced INR 39,500 n India    
    
    
    @BipinBihari_ First week of March @modibimal    
    
    
    Tired of Micromax, Lava and Karbonn launching Android phones every other day.. just piling up crap in the market.    
    
    
    No inclination 2 provide quality products 2 d consumers, just quantity. no wonder we don't see ny HTC, Sony or Samsung coming out of India.    
    
    
    It is a FonePad teaser not Padfone.. all these tech blogs.. just rehashing stories..    
    
    
    WebOS lives! LG to resurrect it for smart TVs

http://reviews.cnet.com/8301-13970_7-57570990-78/webos-lives-lg-to-resurrect-it-for-smart-tvs/ …    
    
    
    Damn... wordpress making uploaded image corrupt...    
    
    
    @nileshgr turns out, it was something related to my PC, n I kept cursing wordpress the whole day. Still have to figure out the PC part..    
    
    
    @nileshgr Yes, every browser.. i tried uploading an image to imgur, which also got corrupted then I realized that it is sum PC issue.    
    
    
    @nileshgr I thought so too, running scan right now.. but seems unlikely as I am more than careful.    
    
    
    @WhatTheBit Not really. they are streaming it via Youtube    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 u realized just now :P there are Ubuntu OS phones too    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 not really.. the first Firefox phones will come in mid-2013 and are budget phones, no threat to Android.    
    
    
    Lots of praise for Chromebook Pixel.. now, waiting for price-cut :P    
    
    
    Chromebook Pixel, Nexus Q show that Google can indeed make good hardware, if only the software had not failed them in both cases.    
    
    
    Asus Memo Pad packs some positives, but the single core processor inside, mars the deal. At 10K, it is slightly expensive.    
    
    
    One can always choose Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 311 over Memo Pad for only INR 2.5K extra..    
    
    
    The display of Galaxy Nexus looks so nice after using Galaxy Grand for five hours.. :P    
    
    
    I have realized that anything bigger than Galaxy Nexus is too big for me...    
    
    
    @josematthew low res.. display as such seems fine, bt as soon as u look at high-res display like d one in G-Nex, u realize what u r msising.    
    
    
    India is d 13th country to Google Play Books, others - Australia,Canada,Spain,Germany,Italy,UK,South Korea,Japan,Brazil,France,Russia & US    
    
    
    Mobile phones to get costlier #budget2013    
    
    
    After Prison Break, now Arrow also has 'Scylla.'    
    
    
    Where are the Smart App updates for Android? Whenever I see an app update in progress on my phone, it is always downloading the full app.    
    
    
    @tsuvik that is certainly weird.. I did see a few smart app updates when the feature was introduced initially but never since then..    
    
    
    Is Gmail down? getting Error 502    
    
    
    yes, it is down...  #gmail    
    
    
    @nkumar_ did u try the web version?    
    
    
    @nileshgr still not working for me @nkumar_ pic.twitter.com/w4PbK4RuHK    
    
    
    #gmail is finally working.    
    
    
    FITH Media has changed the name of Nikal Padi to Slumdog Plumber & Pipes Puzzle, looks like the colloquial reference didn't work for them.    
    
    
    @BenedictEvans Not publicly but at the Google's MWC 2013 round-table - it is still 1.3 million per day  @WhatTheBit    
    
    
    @BenedictEvans yes, probably because the growth is stagnating @whatthebit    
    
    
    I am reviewing this tablet and it has latest version of Play Store and for some reason it is not showing any paid apps, e-books. #weird    
    
    
    Kindle Fire has been officially added to CM :)    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 nope.. still the same..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 :P koi nhn beta..    
    
    
    Sony Xperia Z is the first smartphone to be wholly developed by Sony since its split from mobile phone partner Ericsson last year: Reuters    
    
    
    HTC One has been priced cheaper than Xperia Z and Note II in UK, I hope same happens in India    
    
    
    :) RT @ianbetteridge: Today's tech journalism, in one easy GIF. http://bit.ly/WHA0FP     
    
    
    Samsung Galaxy S 4 or Samsung Galaxy S IV, I think it is going to be the former..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 no.. dnt even think about these crappy chinese tablets..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 sure..    
    
    
    Six hours to go for Samsung Galaxy S 4 announcement    
    
    
    @AppAndWinBB Was reading about that only just now :) @androidosblog    
    
    
    @AppAndWinBB I think Samsung is going to surprise us by showing a different design than the leaked one.    
    
    
    @NihaMasih Oye can I call you right now?    
    
    
    Samsung Galaxy S 4 press event is beginning..    
    
    
    Almost 300,000 people watching the Galaxy S 4 event live-stream right now..    
    
    
    Finally....    
    
    
    So the leaks were true...    
    
    
    I like some of the Samsung Galaxy S 4 customizations but I would rather prefer HTC One    
    
    
    Had breakfast at 7am for the first time in years..thanks to an all-nighter.. #gs4    
    
    
    Why is this one person posting about Galaxy S 4 launch event now.. it is over ..    
    
    
    Sony needs to start innovating on the software front, else they will be left behind..    
    
    
    @AppAndWinBB Yes.. :P    
    
    
    Time to take a quick nap..    
    
    
    Almost done with Galaxy S 4 stories...    
    
    
    Lava is now launching new Android phones just because it can..    
    
    
    Three phones with almost same specs, really Lava...    
    
    
    Price of Xperia Z is already 1K down on Flipkart    
    
    
    The current rumours of Motorola X Phone being a series of devices makes sense..    
    
    
    I don't believe single one of these Nexus 5 rumours...    
    
    
    Next-gen Nexus 7 will have Qualcomm processor - Digitimes    
    
    
    @NihaMasih I think someone else wrote that..?    
    
    
    @NihaMasih and is it raining in Delhi?    
    
    
    @NihaMasih ok.. i am in train na.. so didn't know :)    
    
    
    S 4 Indian version to feature Exynos 5 Octa is such a non-story...    
    
    
    LG is also working on a Smart Watch: Report

http://androidos.in/2013/03/lg-smart-watch/ …    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz Here is ur phone review http://androidos.in/2013/03/huawei-ascend-g600-review/ …    
    
    
    @NihaMasih frm whr did u get an iphone?    
    
    
    @NihaMasih oh... the stupid app name is Twitter for iPhone..    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz main hamesha se expert tha :P    
    
    
    70pc of first 10 million Galaxy S 4 units to come with Snapdragon 600 CPU: Report

http://androidos.in/2013/03/samsung-galaxy-s-4-chip-issues/ …    
    
    
    @ShopnShipIndia wht will be d landing price for this one http://www.pcm.com/p/Apple-MacBook-Pro/product~dpno~9418743~pdp.iadfdhc …    
    
    
    These rumours na..... none of the rumours that have appeared about Motorola X or Nexus 5 are close to reality. ..    
    
    
    Google+ Android app updated, gets in-built Snapseed photo enhancements

http://androidos.in/2013/03/google-android-app-updated/ …    
    
    
    Nice... great Holi gift from Google.. begins selling Nexus 7 from Google Play in India    
    
    
    Google begins selling Nexus 7 via Google Play for INR 15,999

http://androidos.in/2013/03/google-nexus-7-play-india/ …    
    
    
    @surajkala sure.. am doing a post with all details.. will include in that..    
    
    
    Nexus 7 being sold in India are actually getting shipped from Singapore..    
    
    
    @MirRafae oops.. corrected...    
    
    
    Or it seems like they are shipping from Singapore.. will need to dig more to get a final confirmation..    
    
    
    Was the delay in Canvas HD shipments had something to do with Ericsson patent lawsuit?    
    
    
    @surajkala 2-3K more than fair, but i think it is still a decent price. @DJain1989    
    
    
    India is the tenth country where Google is selling Nexus device(s) via Google Play.    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz abe it is a tablet... u wanted a phone..    
    
    
    So many mistakes in this WSJ report on Nexus 7 release in India: http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887324789504578384111477142162.html …    
    
    
    Just a read a review and the reviewer constantly dubbed the smartphone from a Chinese OEM as an indigenous product...    
    
    
    He also praised the indigenous smartphone industry.. do we have something like that in India ?    
    
    
    Google launches Google Play Movies in India

http://androidos.in/2013/03/google-play-movies-india/ …    
    
    
    Damn this internet.. not working.. hav to use Vodafone EDGE to file stories    
    
    
    Only select yashraj movies in Google Play as Hindi movies... Google need more partnerships... but certainly a good start...    
    
    
    Many movies are way cheaper to buy on Google Play Movies than Apple iTunes..    
    
    
    @NihaMasih coz for that you need to be a normal person in the night and sleep :P    
    
    
    India is the 13th country to get Movie rentals, purchases in Google Play..    
    
    
    According to Firstpost, the Google Play Movies prices suck.. really.. so, now u want movies at the cost of pirated discs..    
    
    
    Everytime I see the Firstpost's Google Play Movies article on Google News, I feel like killing myself..    
    
    
    Such a shoddy piece, and that's what happens when news sites start hiring content writers to do the job of journalists...    
    
    
    Now seeing more Hindi movies on Google Play ..still difficult for find, problem with discovery..    
    
    
    @tsuvik I too thought the same earlier, but I just saw more movies by searching 'exact movie names' or navigating through 'related movies'    
    
    
    @devangvira yes... I hope they do that.. Youtube rentals have better discovery than Google Play Movies..    
    
    
    Is it possible that FB will show HTC One on April 4, with Blinkfeed getting replaced by its custom FB-centric widget...?    
    
    
    wow @zeenews is going one step ahead of @firstpostin and blatantly copy-pasting content... @ZRG_DNA @androidosblog    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz You people do know that there is sumthng called "Phone" @NihaMasih    
    
    
    @nixxin was it shipped from Singapore or India?    
    
    
    @Harshal_F1 that is full HD, but 128 (out of 1920) pixels are used in on-screen navigation @androidosblog @Techmeme    
    
    
    @jainrounak which source?    
    
    
    @jainrounak Dear Rounak, I don't even know about ur blog.. seeing it for the first time today... GLbenchmark is a pretty popular .. contd..    
    
    
    @jainrounak ...source for spotting new devices..and everyone know about it. and now u will say Slashgear, which did d same just ... contd..    
    
    
    @jainrounak ...the same story just after me also stole it from ur blog..    
    
    
    @jainrounak ya right... u r crazy to even think that I read or follow ur blog on Twitter.. u can think whatever u want..    
    
    
    @syamant http://support.google.com/googleplay/bin/request.py?contact_type=contact_policy&policy=hardware … @nixxin @googleplay pic.twitter.com/J5jcLuNjRO    
    
    
    @syamant great. hope u get a replacement device soon..    
    
    
    LOL.. Google is running an April Fool's prank in Google Analytics too :P    
    
    
    :P RT @SamsungMobileSA: Introducing the sleek, new #GALAXYSV... pic.twitter.com/qtAOMD2DPi    
    
    
    So, it is confirmed that Nexus 7 3G or 32GB Wi-Fi only versions won't go on sale via Google Play..(at least for now)..    
    
    
    Not feeling well at all... :-|    
    
    
    I am amazed at how the same Firstpost story continues to rank on Google News again and again with new post timings. Some blackhat news SEO.    
    
    
    @Harry_Jerry almst evry news, i monitr d tech sectin n almst evry stry appears multipl times, ex: seen dis twice 2day http://www.firstpost.com/tech/death-of-ipad-mini-asus-launches-32gb-nexus-with-3g-for-21900-683086.html …    
    
    
    So, after Gawker, Times Internet partners with Business Insider to launch BI India    
    
    
    Lifehacker India and Gizmodo India launching this month...    
    
    
    It is LIVE RT @androidosblog: Watch Facebook’s Android event here [Live]

http://androidos.in/2013/04/facebook-event-live/ …    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris I credited two different sources 4 dat story, nw do u want me 2 scour d  internet to find nd credit everyone who did that story    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris nd dont get me started.. i will tell u several stories, which wer picked up frm @androidosblog by gizbot and never got credited    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris and there is nothing called 1st report courtesy. i will credit what my sources are ...    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris coz ppl make public accusations here that hav no basis..like d one u just made... which "experienced" person does that..    
    
    
    @AkanshaSris byee.. anywys i jst read d gizbot report, it ws posted in march nd der wer no details, which wer posted by me or ny site 2day    
    
    
    Lava launches IRIS 455 Android phone with dual-core CPU

http://androidos.in/2013/04/lava-launches-iris-455-android-phone-with-dual-core-cpu/ …    
    
    
    Google Paid This Man $100 Million: Here's His Story http://www.businessinsider.com/neal-mohan-googles-100-million-man-2013-4 … via @sai    
    
    
    @MMXNewscaster Yes.. tell me for @androidosblog    
    
    
    HP Slate 7 Europe pricing revealed – €149, sales might begin on June 1

http://androidos.in/2013/04/hp-slate-7-europe-pricing-revealed-e149-sales-might-begin-on-june-1/ …    
    
    
    Micromax to launch ultra-cheap Canvas Viva A72 phablet soon

http://androidos.in/2013/04/micromax-to-launch-canvas-viva-a72-phablet-soon/ …    
    
    
    Does BuzzFeed Know the Secret? http://nymag.com/news/features/buzzfeed-2013-4/ …    
    
    
    Looks like, 4 someone who does not want to spend a fortune, HTC First seems like a pretty great device n it lets you use use stock Android..    
    
    
    I just wish HTC would have put Snapdragon 600 instead of 400 in HTC First and I would have gladly bought the phone.    
    
    
    @kunalgangar Yes, in a way, there are still many differences, but it would be great to see a high-end Android phone with 4.3-inch display..    
    
    
    I wonder why @ICICIBank_Care uses crappy courier companies to send bank communication, have issues with them every time.    
    
    
    Seem like India is the first country to see the launch of Xperia SP, correct me if I am wrong..    
    
    
    This is what happens when someone forces the world to use a single link shortening service. All hell breaks loose... #twitter #links    
    
    
    Twitter links are working now...    
    
    
    @GautamPW just saw it... that would be great.. sure go ahead...:)    
    
    
    LOL ... RT @NDTVGadgets: Iran developing its own "Islamic Google Earth" http://ndtv.in/14h82JT     
    
    
    Five Reasons PC Sales Have Plunged - ABC News http://abcn.ws/XH8myl  by @JoannaStern via @ABC    
    
    
    Dead City is so addictive..    
    
    
    @GautamPW Yes, I saw it and it was decent..but it got me thinking and I found a neat tool to create very decent Android apps..    
    
    
    @GautamPW check out the result of that tool - https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.androidos.in&hl=en …    
    
    
    @GautamPW No, all that is for coders and i am not one... there are lots of online tools that allows users to create RSS-based app, which 1/2    
    
    
    @GautamPW 2/2 I had checked out earlier, but none of them this good..    
    
    
    @GautamPW Yes, i saw that lifehacker app today itself.. its a third-party app and yes, it uses the same tool..    
    
    
    @GautamPW There ws an app earlier, which ws made using a similar tool, bt those guys stopped developmnt, so d app ws not compatible with ICS    
    
    
    Seems like there is no news.. everybody is just waiting for Facebook Home..    
    
    
    Facebook Home is just 258KB, seems like everything is included in Facebook app and Messenger..    
    
    
    At the current speed, Facebook Home will take hours to become visible properly in Google Play    
    
    
    E-Commerce sites hav increasingly startd 2 put product listings 4 un-announced products wid leakd details jst 2 get link-backs n traffic.    
    
    
    The Micromax Canvas 3D listing on Saholic is one such example...    
    
    
    You Lookin’ at Me? Reflections on Google Glass. http://dthin.gs/124cSGO     
    
    
    No tweets ... something wrong with Twitter?    
    
    
    Just finished the finale of "Spartacus" series and it was worth it...    
    
    
    The second coming of Facebook http://cnnmon.ie/ZaZXBM  via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    DNA has revamped their website, nice effort, a modern looking design.    
    
    
    Other news websites also need redesign in India, everyone is just trying to cram as much news they can on the homepage...    
    
    
    So, the Alcatel One Touch smartphone launch press release comes with a specs sheet that is actually copied and pasted from GSMArena.    
    
    
    SLOW SLOW NEWS DAY....    
    
    
    Turns out while I was quietly watching the latest episode of Castle, there was a small earthquake in Delhi. I didn't even feel it ...    
    
    
    is it just my connection or the AllthingsD live-stream is really messed up?    
    
    
    I don't know why but Google really hates my blog... hardly any search visibility...    
    
    
    @TheAngrez thanks...    
    
    
    Announcement at d New Delhi Railway Station - "Roof Traveling is not fun" - Really, didn't know people traveled on d train roof for FUN...    
    
    
    Google working on a gaming service like Apple Game Center and Amazon GameCircle?

http://androidos.in/2013/04/google-game-center-amazon-gamecircle-competitor/ … Tip @Techmeme    
    
    
    Amazon should bring LoveFilm to India..    
    
    
    It Wasn't Sunil Tripathi: The Anatomy of a Misinformation Disaster - Alexis C. Madrigal - The Atlantic http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/04/it-wasnt-sunil-tripathi-the-anatomy-of-a-misinformation-disaster/275155/ …    
    
    
    Is Apple Looking For A Replacement For CEO Cook?

http://www.forbes.com/sites/genemarcial/2013/04/21/is-apple-looking-for-a-replacement-for-ceo-cook/ …    
    
    
    It is interesting how everyone (globally) can watch Amazon's new original TV series pilots ..    
    
    
    @z0mer I have changed the link in via.. :)    
    
    
    @journalistreyaz no.. it is actually more, 750,000 devices every 12 hours, 1.5 million daily @shailichopra    
    
    
    AndroidOS.in version 1.1 now live in Google Play 

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.androidos.in …    
    
    
    HTC One nowhere to be seen as Samsung gets ready to launch Galaxy S4 in India , this is what leads to poor HTC sales...    
    
    
    Fly, Lemon Android phones - more Chinese crap in the Indian market..    
    
    
    Google X benchmark leak is so fake..    
    
    
    GSM Insider takes leaks from Chinese, Japanese websites and then posts them as their own.. really....    
    
    
    Does anyone have an Android 4.2.2 running device apart from Nexus and is there Photosphere present?    
    
    
    It has begun ... Samsung Galaxy S4 India launch event, watch it live 

http://goo.gl/lph8O     
    
    
    @sumeet_jnj http://androidos.in/2013/04/samsung-galaxy-s4-india-launch/ …    
    
    
    Samsung launches Galaxy S4 in India, priced at INR 41,500

http://androidos.in/2013/04/samsung-launches-galaxy-s4-in-india-priced-at-inr-41500/ …    
    
    
    4th generation Intel Core processors coming in 38 days or 3,337,200,000,000,000 nanoseconds pic.twitter.com/DhgHv4OGZf    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 lol :P    
    
    
    Not even Android 4.2 on-board RT @androidosblog: Samsung announces Galaxy Tab 3, Wi-Fi version goes on sale in May

http://androidos.in/2013/04/samsung-announces-galaxy-tab-3/ …    
    
    
    Some exclusive reports from one Indian blog are so amusing.. they hardly have any real info...    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 try http://m.androidos.in  on your phone and let me know if it works fine..    
    
    
    @mobstac can you guys reply to ticket 1440 on the support site, I am not able to redirect users to mobile site because of this..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 nah... just wanted to see if it was working for others too..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 yes... got it done today mrng... hav 2 finish anothr thing den all d mobile visitors will get automatically redirected to this.    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 great... so two things are done.. android app and mobile site..    
    
    
    Samsung phones, Google on top in Opera’s State of the Android Mobile Web in India report

http://androidos.in/2013/05/samsung-phones-google-on-top-in-operas-samw-report/ …    
    
    
    This looks like a winner RT @androidosblog: HTC M4 press render leaked, looks very much like HTC One

http://androidos.in/2013/05/htc-m4-press-render-leaked-looks-very-much-like-htc-one/ …    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 INR 25,490    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 it is actually quite decent, nice specs and good pricing...    
    
    
    Haven't The Verge had enough of Paul Miller...    
    
    
    Google Play on Nook HD tablets is a win-win for both Google and B&N    
    
    
    But I am sure Google has bent many rules to let B&N bring Google Play support for Nook HD tablets...    
    
    
    Nook tablets are looking so much more interesting now... having used the Nook Color - I know Nook tablets are great value for money..    
    
    
    When did Youtube add 144p video quality option?    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 2.3    
    
    
    Power cut.. damn it... it is becoming a daily affair....    
    
    
    So, Gizmodo India is live.. well sort of, only one story from the India staff... gizmodo.in    
    
    
    No leaks for Nexus 7 successor so far, even though it is expected to be announced in next 7 days...    
    
    
    Lots of devices just got another way to get Android 4.2.2 RT @androidosblog: CM 10.1 RC release rolling out now http://androidos.in/2013/05/cyanogenmod-10-1-rc-release-rolling-out-now-for-40-devices/ …    
    
    
    @nkumar_ surprising, I have it installed in my phone.. pic.twitter.com/0lbAJYmGyp    
    
    
    @nkumar_ seems like it is not officially supported..   http://support.google.com/earth/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=2516855&topic=2508753&ctx=topic … weird that it works for me on every device..    
    
    
    So, Tikona is not working right now and recharged MTS data card to work and it sucks big time..    
    
    
    @androidcreature they might not be coming as a company, but I think they have tied up with AndroidGuruz to sell Find 5 in India..    
    
    
    @androidcreature they are saying "coming soon," whr did u see "available tomorrow" ?    
    
    
    @reckless True, even Motorola XT720 Milestone had Xenon flash, never sold much..    
    
    
    Sony says entertainment businesses not for sale http://reut.rs/1695M7Z  via @reuters    
    
    
    Bloomberg’s culture is all about omniscience, down to the last keystroke http://qz.com/83862  via @qz    
    
    
    Why You Should Scrap That Ladder-Climbing Plan And Go Backpacking Around The World, Instead

http://www.fastcompany.com/3009589/why-you-should-scrap-that-ladder-climbing-plan-and-go-backpacking-around-the-world-instead …    
    
    
    Forbes India Magazine - How the Rise of Third Party Marketplaces can Alter Indian E-Commerce http://forbesindia.com/article/real-issue/how-the-rise-of-third-party-marketplaces-can-alter-indian-ecommerce/35209/0 …    
    
    
    @Javed_Del it has been available for quite some time in Google Play..    
    
    
    Who is taking the Nexus 4 pre-orders... ???? Why am I seeing all these India pre-order stories...    
    
    
    The Nexus 4 on pre-order at Flipkart packs 16GB of internal storage 

http://androidos.in/2013/05/google-nexus-4-india/ …    
    
    
    Is Google letting you try Play Music All Access in India? Keeps giving me server error..    
    
    
    @tsuvik I think so, but it is giving me the option to try it for free for 30 days..and when I select the free trial - server error..    
    
    
    Google's cloud music locker has also been revamped..    
    
    
    @nkumar_ where did u get the pricing?    
    
    
    @nkumar_ ok... still waiting for their event to start.. they haven't mentioned anything in the press release..    
    
    
    @PanasonicInNews What happened to the live-stream?    
    
    
    Dan Brown's Inferno is INR 1680 in Google Play Books, INR 348 on Kindle & INR 329 in Flyte, what's wrong with Google...    
    
    
    @androidcreature nice.. i hope there aren't any more delays... let me know if you get a unit on April 22... thanks..    
    
    
    @androidcreature i meant 'May'..    
    
    
    Croma is selling HTC Butterfly at INR 40,499, the phone is finally getting closer to what would have a decent price..need one more price-cut    
    
    
    @androidcreature thanks... will update the post with this...    
    
    
    @MyXOLO Are you guys sure that the update for A800 is Android 4.2, not Android 4.1.1?    
    
    
    Why is India not in the list of 170 countries where Kindle Fire HD is available ???    
    
    
    How Android Vendors Can Compete With Samsung | Tech.pinions http://shar.es/ZI48L     
    
    
    @GurmanBhatia I heard u r planning to intern sumwhr? let me knw if u r free ..i might hav sumthng..    
    
    
    Rest of the Facebook Home might be crap... but Chatheads is one thing Facebook got right..    
    
    
    @tejajuloori yes.. you don't need Facebook Home, just use the latest version of Facebook Messenger..    
    
    
    Why is everyone doing Galaxy Young duos availability story now.. it has been available for almost two months now...

http://androidos.in/2013/04/samsung-galaxy-young-y-plus-india/ …    
    
    
    The new tech palaces: visionary HQs, or cursed trophies? http://reut.rs/14Wr2Kn  via @reuters    
    
    
    RAM is here in less than 24 hours.. that's  why i like to shop from Flipkart.. :)    
    
    
    @Djkrimp Really... no credit... http://igyaan.in/48138/white-nexus-4-16gb-goes-on-sale-in-india/ … @iGyaan    
    
    
    @devangvira der was some issue with the feed, I have fixed it now.. it should be working fine, in case you still c old articles - sync once    
    
    
    Flipkart to Shutdown Flyte MP3 Store; To Exit Digital Music Business http://www.nextbigwhat.com/flyte-mp3-shutdown-297/ …    
    
    
    Flipkart has confirmed that Flyte MP3 Store is shutting down on June 17, 2013, just got a mail..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 it is spelled as Mikandi    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 haha.... pta rakhna padta hai...    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 k    
    
    
    With 8GB RAM in the laptop.. I can finally open as many tabs as i want :P    
    
    
    How can all these Android blogs report about this HTC and Android 4.3 story, this is so fake... and dnt even ask about the source..    
    
    
    So tempted to buy HTC One with Nexus experience.. it might be the replacement for my Galaxy Nexus    
    
    
    How can companies justify not putting at least full HD display in laptops priced more than 1 lakh..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 :)    
    
    
    Is there a non-voice calling phablet? :P sumone just used "voice-calling phablet" in headline..    
    
    
    Lenovo K900 also comes wid jst 8.8GB of free internl storage in 16GB version like Galaxy S4. Luks like Samsung isn't d only 1 with bloatware    
    
    
    For the first time ever Toshiba tablets are going to be available within days of announcement..    
    
    
    Excite Pro seems to be a great competitor to Xperia Tablet Z on paper, however it is d real world performance that matters d most..    
    
    
    Computex is mainly a Taiwan event but where is HTC?    
    
    
    Sony announces Xperia M & Xperia M dual, available in Q3, 2013

http://androidos.in/2013/06/sony-announces-xperia-xperia-dual-q3-2013/ …    
    
    
    Sony just announced its first Android 4.2-powered phone - Xperia M dual 

http://androidos.in/2013/06/sony-announces-xperia-xperia-dual-q3-2013/ …    
    
    
    It is so surprisng dat despite packing d same specs,single SIM n dual-SIM versions of  Sony phons run on differnt Android versions at launch    
    
    
    wow, http://housing.co.in  indeed looks nice.. great interface..    
    
    
    Amazon Launches In India

http://www.amazon.in/b/ref=footer_press?_encoding=UTF8&node=1592137031 …    
    
    
    Don't get excited folks, there is no Intel powered S4 coming...    
    
    
    Lenovo India to launch a bunch of Android phones today, K900 included..    
    
    
    Has HTC India lost it... Why is it launching ICS running phones now...    
    
    
    @nkumar_ thanks :)..    
    
    
    BB Q10 at 45K, are you kidding me.. no matter how great the keyboard is.    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 hota hai.. happened to me once :P    
    
    
    @nkumar_ must be a staged roll-out.. will take days to appear for everyone.. @Facebook    
    
    
    @nkumar_ Yes, dat is indeed a bit strange, seems nobody has got d update till nw, which shouldn't happen even 4 staged roll-out. @Facebook    
    
    
    Edward Snowden: the whistleblower behind revelations of NSA surveillance http://gu.com/p/3gec7/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    @nadeem112 Spend a little more and get Nexus 4 or you can choose Sony Xperia SP    
    
    
    @nadeem112 One X is also good, you can go for it..    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper thanks for the invite but please use @gauravshukla instead of @androidosblog    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper and I will joining in the next hour, as I told Shraddha...    
    
    
    @adravid_20 hey, I will be joining in the next hour    
    
    
    @adravid_20 sure, if you want to..    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Waiting to see the iOS' flatter design from Apple, they have been keeping the same UI for a long time now. #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Sort of, but they still have a long way to go @sizzler_Chetan @binoyxj #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Also, WP seriously needs some other manufacturer to take it seriously. Nokia alone cant do evrythng #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper not really, but then every other flagship smartphone is also getting hyped these days #tvpchat    
    
    
    @sunnyvjkumar I would seriously like to take a look at this research @TheViewspaper #tvpchat    
    
    
    @kunalgangar lol, what's that...    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper yes, in a way..but if you are a careful Android user, you dnt need to worry about security #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Platform wars - Android, no doubt.. #tvpchat    
    
    
    @SoccerAnalyst I wish I was kidding..:P Nokia and WP are nowhere  #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Recently gave an Asha series phone.. #tvpchat    
    
    
    @adravid_20 numerical keypad for easy access + decent support for basic apps, nothing too techie #tvpchat    
    
    
    @adravid_20 they are just trying to stay afloat, given the prices of BB10 devices in India, I dont see them gaining much traction #tvpchat    
    
    
    @TheViewspaper Thanks for having me, it was great talking to everyone on the panel #tvpchat    
    
    
    Breaking: Amazon launches Kindle Fire HD tablets in India, available starting June 27

http://androidos.in/2013/06/amazon-kindle-fire-hd-tablets-india/ …    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 man of steel dekh li?    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 yay, ye toh Eros main bhi lagi hai.. wahan chalenge...    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 Yes, ek 12:30 hai.. phir ek 6:30..    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 3D hai Eros main... bolo sham ko? ya kal    
    
    
    @nkumar_ this has been present for years..    
    
    
    @Karanbajaj They have stopped selling Apple products...just accessories now...    
    
    
    Liked d new HOT (House of Technology) store at Nehru Place... spacious, plenty of demo devices, proper sections, unusual for a place like NP    
    
    
    @asymco 91,287 as per the latest count on their site.. http://www.amazon.com/s/ref=nb_sb_noss?url=search-alias%3Dmobile-apps&field-keywords= …    
    
    
    What.... Cinema (part of video on Instagram) is not available in their Android app... only for iPhone 4S and 5.    
    
    
    Why aren't Instagram videos automatically muted like Vine videos...    
    
    
    @tsuvik probably, but a video I just played was so loud that sum kind of volume control or a mute button at least would make sense...    
    
    
    @tsuvik Yes, so let there be sound, but add a mute button while it is playing, it least that would save ppl from loud videos..    
    
    
    Sony has Xperia, LG has Optimus, Samsung has Galaxy, even Huawei has Ascend; Dear HTC, where is your identifiable branding for Android phns?    
    
    
    HTC does not seem to be able to decide between One and Desire    
    
    
    @raunaqkumaran In 2012, dey hd three "One" series phones n only 1 of dem ws flagship, in 2013 they hav one, not sure wat will happen in 2014    
    
    
    @raunaqkumaran they need to decide and stick to a strategy.. and then there are Butterfly phones, their branding is going haywire.    
    
    
    @raunaqkumaran Not every consumer tracks smartphones like fans or bloggers, HTC needs to give dem sumthing to remember, sumthng to indentify    
    
    
    Why is everyone doing Google Earth for Android update stories now, as far as I can see on Google Play, last update was on June 6..    
    
    
    This is what happens when one blog does a wrong story and others just follow it without even bothering to check for themselves    
    
    
    @joydeep1985 poor kids they don't know what they are getting into...    
    
    
    Almost evry tech site is talking abt irony of FB using Google Groups 4 beta-testing of its Android app - it is a necessity, not their choice    
    
    
    How much effort does it take to do a quick Google search before publishing stuff online..    
    
    
    Is there something wrong with @ideacellular today... no network... ??    
    
    
    @nkumar_ oops.. thanks..    
    
    
    Impressed with @ideacellular service, they replaced my faulty SIM in 5 mins and new SIM got activated in less than an hour..    
    
    
    Tizen is not dead, Samsung is working pretty hard on it, however rumours of the delay in the launch of first device are correct..    
    
    
    Something wrong wid @mobstac ? http://m.androidos.in  getting lot of 502 Bad Gateway errors for d last 30 mins, had 2 deactivate redirection    
    
    
    CC @naganaga https://twitter.com/gauravshukla/status/352798742925164544 …    
    
    
    @feedly Why are you picking up old posts from http://www.androidos.in/feed/ , even though the actual feed does not show any old posts..    
    
    
    ll someone frm @feedly respnd or fix it https://twitter.com/gauravshukla/status/354213227007193089 …

We r getting so many complaints from Feedly users although our RSS is fine.    
    
    
    CM 10.1.2 update rolling out now, contains fix for another Android security bug

http://www.androidos.in/2013/07/cyanogenmod-10-1-1/ …    
    
    
    