Flirting at the grocery store. Shopping says I'm responsible. My selection of trail mix, jerky and gummi bears says I'm single. 

Nailed it!    
    
    
    Are you subversively mocking me, or are you actually enjoying yourself? Her: You don't date a lot, do you? Me: How does everyone know that?    
    
    
    Drinks served in bucket-form are not 'whimsical'.    
    
    
    Yes, I have inadequacies, but I earn points for the sheer quantity and effortlessness with which I acquire them, right? No, huh. Nerts.    
    
    
    @AcidCityMag Of course!    
    
    
    Bachelors are a lot like pregnant women, in that we both see the appeal in dill pickle and chocolate chip cookie sandwiches.    
    
    
    CNN reporting epic drugs, prostitution and weapons in Mexico. Wow, their tourism board sure has my number.    
    
    
    Coercing coworkers to confabulate via sock puppet has been surprisingly simple to implement. Lamentably.    
    
    
    @sousveillance I'm going to need you to direct all comments to the sock, please.    
    
    
    Do you know why they call me 'Hatter'? Alice: Because you wear a hat? Hatter: ...No.    
    
    
    If Alice in Wonderland has taught us anything, it's that crazy chicks are much more charming in film than in real life.    
    
    
    I have one squeaky shoe. I'm not sure yet if this is the worst or greatest thing that's ever happened to me.    
    
    
    Definitely the best. A squeaky shoe is the closest I'll get to a cartoon surreptitiously tiptoeing with staccato accompaniment... For now.    
    
    
    Yes, 18 year-old me would be disappointed, but 4 year-old me would think it's rad that I can stay up late and eat all the cookies I want.    
    
    
    I really thought I'd own a pair of nunchucks by now.    
    
    
    Wearing pajamas outside does not make me a ninja, but it's a step in the right direction.    
    
    
    Happy discounted green-food-colouring-day eve everyone!    
    
    
    I finally tried out a snuggie. It lives up to the hype.    
    
    
    @meggyc4 Oh yes, it looks ridiculous. I wouldn't suggest wearing it out of the house. Although you'd be my new hero if you did.    
    
    
    @Wedding_crasher Huge. I haven't been this excited since spray hair launched.    
    
    
    Her: Just try.
Me: There is no try. Only do or do not.
Her: Then do.
Me: I'll try.
Her: [profanity].    
    
    
    @jacklynatlas Thanks!    
    
    
    Why must all my girlfriends live inside the TV?    
    
    
    I don't grasp the intricacies of wine and cheese parties, but I'm pretty sure this nacho/chablis amalgam isn't the intention.    
    
    
    We can have wieners and Kraft dinner, or Kraft dinner and wieners. Her: Can we have both? Me: I'm not making two meals.    
    
    
    Turns out putting my glasses on whilst wearing my contacts will not give me mega-vision; unless mega-vision is blurry and hurty.    
    
    
    Ugh. Wine hangover – the wrath of grapes.    
    
    
    Office flirting is like shopping for an expensive watch – I don't need it and can't afford it, but it's be nice to think about.    
    
    
    MBA: Don't re-invent the wheel. Me: Makes sense; the wheel's remained completely unchanged for millennia, right? MBA: Right... wait.    
    
    
    Pretty blonde girl: That's SO exciting – what night is Fashion Week this year? Me: I love you. #LGFW    
    
    
    It's not right that Cadbury has all the chocolate-egg-laying-bunnies in captivity. Where's @peta when you need them?    
    
    
    Also, the Cadbury people get really bitchy when you call and ask why they don't make free-range chocolate eggs.    
    
    
    @CanadianSkin Hard boiled eggs become miniature fondue pots... I'd buy it.    
    
    
    Apple. Cherry. Black currant. Wood? So pretentious. Why can't wine ever taste grapey?    
    
    
    I'm sitting with three women who have decided to discuss men. It bothers me a little that I can't provide any insight into the male mind.    
    
    
    The brain loves pancakes. The tummy does not.    
    
    
    No, you're going down in the ANNALS of history. Two n's... it matters. This is almost as bad as the time you told me you had a rapist's wit.    
    
    
    Fashion Week, Day 2... already tired. I'm pretty sure I just broke whatever the coffee equivalent of the sound barrier is. #LGFW    
    
    
    @la_motte Thanks!    
    
    
    For those who missed it... Gaudet FW2010. #LGFW  http://twitpic.com/1bv5lk    
    
    
    No, I didn't mean "count". Stop trying to class up my email, spellchecker.    
    
    
    Fashion Week, Day 3: A pretty girl just gave me a free cupcake. I know it's her job, but I'm still a little completely in love. #LGFW    
    
    
    I may have proposed to cupcake girl. I don't think it will work out – she's "not into creepy losers", which I guess is code for lesbian?    
    
    
    Lundström FW 2010. Fuzzy. 
 http://twitpic.com/1c5iju   #LGFW    
    
    
    Actually, it's pronounced "puh-dan-tik".    
    
    
    Learning one song on guitar doesn't make me a guitarist, but I stalk ONE person...    
    
    
    That was a joke... I don't know any songs on guitar.    
    
    
    How do I look? Me: Is that a leotard? Uh, nice. And you're a leo, so it makes sense. Her: huh? Me: I love you.    
    
    
    Andy The-Ahn FW2010. Shiny.  http://twitpic.com/1cf9qr    
    
    
    In case anyone's keeping score, the dude in the pleather cape (with popped collar) just won fashion week. #LGFW    
    
    
    Fashion week highlight in the pit: I need you to shoot a self portrait. Photog 2: Of who? Photo 1: Of "whom". 

#LGFW    
    
    
    So long, Fashion Week. Until October, I'll be waiting for Gaudet. 

Jesus. Even I groaned at that. #LGFW    
    
    
    Today could only be lazier if I were wearing a colostomy bag.    
    
    
    Follow Friday – friendly fashion folks: @fashioninmotion @theFlist @jennawakani @amyverner @brasandranties @finalfashion @ashleyrowe #FFFFF    
    
    
    To the neighbourhood child who swears the rabbit in our yard is the easter bunny: do not eat the chocolate eggs.    
    
    
    Buddy: Kristin Davis is a hottie. 
Me: Yeah. I'd city her sex.
Buddy: [...]
Me: I shouldn't guy-talk.    
    
    
    Argh. Fine. I promise to stop referring to the shopping channel as "cat lady porn".    
    
    
    Growing my hair out. It's messy, but more worrying that I've reached a point in life where 'hair growing' can be counted amongst my hobbies.    
    
    
    Very funny. 
Me: Thanks, but that was meant more as a cry for help than a joke. 
Her: Well, it made me laugh.    
    
    
    Hello indie manchild. So, exactly how drunk was your mom when she laid out your clothes this morning?    
    
    
    Just once, it would be nice to send a post-date email without "Mulligan?" as the subject line.    
    
    
    Gummi worms and beer, together at last.    
    
    
    To the white, suburban teenage rap-stars in training: diamonds are a woman's best friend, not a man's. Get it together.    
    
    
    @finalfashion Only if the big dogs are wearing collars made of smaller dogs.    
    
    
    @finalfashion True. Do they sell those at the mall?    
    
    
    The tummy wants what the ass cannot have.    
    
    
    Overheard: Why'd you have to say "sausage fest". Now I want some meat... wait.    
    
    
    Bullet points hide poor grammar in the same way loud music hides fart smell.    
    
    
    "My inbox doesn't have a Twitter". 

My mom: giver of life, and decades of unintentional entertainment.    
    
    
    Audi A4, double-parked in front of an occupied wheelchair space – the douchebag hat-trick. Wow.    
    
    
    A chubby child on my street has discovered how to build bike jumps. This should end well.    
    
    
    Ouch. The chubby child has reached a maturing point quicker than usual. To his credit, the first two jumps were pretty rad.    
    
    
    Me: [robot dancing]
Her: [crickets]
Me: Would you believe that drives the ladies wild?
Her: ...No.    
    
    
    Gin should come with a warning label.    
    
    
    More conflicts need to be solved via dance-off.    
    
    
    What's a "relationship"?    
    
    
    It seems I've reached the age where I can look at my watch several times and still have no idea what time it is. So, I have that... [sigh].    
    
    
    LG Fashion Week, Day two. Seventies-y.
#LGFW pic.twitter.com/Cyefgfd6    
    
    
    I'm not immature, I'm a performance artist. I call this piece "boy as girl, in man". 

The reviews haven't been positive.    
    
    
    Today I learned that the passport photo girl gets really bitchy when provided with unsolicited art direction.    
    
    
    In my defense, the shots were too contrasty to be documentary, and not emotive enough to be art. Where's your sense of craft, Black's?    
    
    
    Sometimes I feel pretty grown up and accomplished. Then I remember how often I use my fingers as a counting aid.    
    
    
    What do I wear? Her: Anything. Fashion is about confidence. Me: But I'm not confident. Her: Then go nude. Me: ... yeah? Her: [profanity].    
    
    
    Today we're playing the office floor is made of lava, except the lava is piles of paper and I don't care if you step on them.#springcleaning    
    
    
    No, I don't have a costume. I was going to dress up as a mature, responsible adult, but I have no idea what that looks like.    
    
    
    It's not a suit, it's a grown-up costume. Her: That explains the marker stains, but the cape? Me: Batman's a grown up. Her: ...Touché.    
    
    
    You didn't lose your dignity, you gained quotation marks around it. #PositiveThinking    
    
    
    If there's a lesson we can learn from the Kentucky Derby, it's that mint juleps are essentially liquified amnesia. Has anyone seen my pants?    
    
    
    Few things are as aggravating as waking up to a spectacular ass day, then running into no one of importance the entire day.    
    
    
    The five second rule only applies if there's someone else in the room, right? 

Also, how long can pizza be on the floor and remain edible?    
    
    
    WOW. Dinner looks amazing! Her: AND it's all-natural. Me: Oh, that's not going to work. I only eat super-natural chickens. Her: [crickets].    
    
    
    11:11:11 11/11/11.
So that's what happens when you turn it up to eleven. Neat, but anti-climactic.    
    
    
    Soo... turns out 'hung parliament' doesn't mean what I thought it did.    
    
    
    I only watch America's Next Top Model for the articles.    
    
    
    No, I never said that, as far as you know.    
    
    
    Well, I've made a complete mess of things, so I'm going out for a few hours to relax. Future me's going to be pissed when he gets home.    
    
    
    Why must it be a case of the Mondays; maybe you're just an asshole?    
    
    
    If I have to add heat before it goes in my tummy, it counts as cooking.    
    
    
    Argh. Fine, but 'fuckwittage' ought to be a word... don't I get half points for that? No, YOU'RE immature. Whatever. Scrabble's stupid.    
    
    
    The Skippy people have it all figured out – everything new should come with a peanut on top.    
    
    
    A drop shadow is a designer's way of telling his client he's out of ideas.    
    
    
    Turns out indelible and inedible are two very different things.    
    
    
    Ah, mistletoe – one of my most beloved toes, along with camel and tippy.    
    
    
    Meatball should be a sport.    
    
    
    Golly, all those French words sure do make you sound educated. You know what would impress me even more? Learning their English equivalents.    
    
    
    Finally went to the YouTubes to see what a Justin Bieber is – Interweb, even with all your glorious pornography, you disappoint me.    
    
    
    It's not fair that the freezer doesn't get to have a light.    
    
    
    Correction: Turns out my freezer has a light, but it was disconnected. I think it may be hiding something.    
    
    
    Okay, my freezer is definitely into some things. I just found a stash of chicken carcasses in the back corner. I'm thinking voodoo ritual?    
    
    
    We need a Skype so your brother's baby can eat with me and your father. Me: I don't know what that means. Mom: Don't you work on computers?    
    
    
    Screw it. I'm keeping it. At least this way my Scooby-doo lunchbox filled with jelly beans is 'on brand'. I just made myself feel bad.    
    
    
    Yes, I'm single. How does everyone know that?    
    
    
    I feel like such a fraud at cocktail parties, like I've wandered into the grown-up section of life.    
    
    
    Dear Economy, You suck. Nobody likes you. Drop dead. No, wait... that's worse... whatever, just stop sucking. Love, Pete [Hugs!]    
    
    
    Her: It's extra fine. 
Me: Exceptionally mediocre won't cut it. Do you have anything good? 
Her: [crickets]. 
I hate Christmas shopping.    
    
    
    Really? Eel Porn? What's the matter with you, Japan?  http://tinyurl.com/42hjxv    
    
    
    "Good artists borrow. Great artists steal" – Me    
    
    
    Whether or not pudding can be considered 'sauce' depends not on what pudding is,  but how it is being used.    
    
    
    Incidentally, resist the urge to put pudding on spaghetti. Or rice. Or steak – any meat, really, isn't a good idea. Don't judge me.    
    
    
    Even though it's casual Friday, hot pants are inappropriate office clothing. Marvellously, gloriously inappropriate.    
    
    
    Wine and hot dogs, together at last. [sigh].    
    
    
    LOVE Haiku Friday / Makes it all sound more high-class; / Ass penis fart poop.    
    
    
    Overheard: "...I swear dude, if you didn't like girls, you'd be so gay."    
    
    
    I've taken to re-enacting the gang scene from West Side Story whenever I walk down a hallway towards someone. To date, no one's played along    
    
    
    Dr: Have you ever abused drugs? Me: You can't abuse an inanimate object. You can defile one, though... you're not asking about that, right?    
    
    
    Me: I just heard a great joke. Her: Awww. Were they making fun of you? Me: Well, yes. But still... ouch.    
    
    
    Take away the sword and mad-skills, and a Ninja is just a weird dude wandering around at night in a black onesie. So I'm almost a ninja–Rad!    
    
    
    Apparently the word "ninja" in Japanese, literally translates to "spy". Dictionaries are fun!    
    
    
    Umm... for the record, I am not a spy – though if I was, I couldn't tell you. Quite the catch-22.    
    
    
    So to recap: I am NOT a spy, and this is NOT my spy homepage: http://www.icouldtellyoubuttheniwouldhavetokillyou.com/    
    
    
    Kudos to Lost for making the Matrix trilogy look well thought out. #LostFinale    
    
    
    This morning I went to check on the bunny I planted
last year to see if my chocolate eggs had sprouted – nothing.
Frickin' winter.    
    
    
    It's amazing how much hatred can be developed towards a total stranger simply by driving behind him for two minutes.    
    
    
    Also, to the dude in the white 3-series: get out of the way, you mobile traffic jam.    
    
    
    I wish procrastination was a marketable skill.    
    
    
    New cologne? Me: Yup. Her: What is it? Me: It's called "office"; a combination of inefficacy and discontent. Like it? Her: Nope. Me: [sigh.]    
    
    
    It 'feels' like 36º? Stop telling me how I feel, weatherlady. Keep this up and I may be forced to end our imaginary relationship.    
    
    
    Where cupcakes are concerned, one should always go 'mini', given the option . The frosting-to-cake ratio is far superior.    
    
    
    Internet, today I learned that there is no tactful way to tell your date you've broken their toilet.    
    
    
    The only discernible difference between a Social Psychologist and a jerk that messes with random people is a PhD. Also, I need a PhD.    
    
    
    Max Headroom, I m-m-miss you... http://tinyurl.com/5avz5h    
    
    
    Watching Discovery; Apparently Stephen Hawking has no time to lecture. Really? Someone can't just hit [play]?    Kidding... Hawking's great.    
    
    
    Grey's anatomy DVD: check. Chocolate eggs: check. Appletini: check. Snuggling pillow: check. It's going to be a successful long weekend.    
    
    
    "I'm a lady" she announced, broadly.    
    
    
    I had cookies for breakfast.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Jesus!    
    
    
    Wait, that's Christmas; what's Good Friday? 
Really?!? 
We celebrate that? 
Doesn't seem like a 'good' day at all. WTF?    
    
    
    Now eating cookies and chocolate milk naked in front of the TV seems a little immature and deliciously inappropriate. Sorry Jesus. My bad.    
    
    
    Nothing says 'cool' like a $1200 carbon fiber hood on an $800 civic.    
    
    
    Pro tip: 40 ounces of Roberto Cavalli makes pointless, repetitive conversations with four retired relatives seem interesting.    
    
    
    And by 'interesting', I mean painfully repetitive in spite of a truly heroic amount of alcohol consumption on my part.    
    
    
    Just because it's a holiday doesn't mean you have to go buck on the meat consumption. General rule: a hunk of beef is not an 'appetizer'.    
    
    
    A new can of tennis balls is the perfect balance of fuzziness and yellow smell. Take note, golf balls.    
    
    
    Bob Saget, you're a dirty old man, and I love you for it. http://tinyurl.com/2ubtqf    
    
    
    No matter how large the media spend gets, drinkable yogurt will never be the 'cool kids' drink of choice. Get over it, YOP folks.    
    
    
    Leprechauns freak me out.    
    
    
    Clurichauns, however, are the bee's knees.    
    
    
    Austrians make the best monoculars.    
    
    
    Thank-you Oren Lavie. It's been far too long since I've heard a decent xylophone riff. http://www.orenlavie.com/    
    
    
    A mug or 'to go' cup? Me: Mug, please. Her: We only have 'to go' cups. Me: You're lucky you're pretty. I haven't written a letter all week.    
    
    
    Learning sales is a lot like learning to be a crack whore. Not particularly difficult, but the better I get at it, the worse I feel.    
    
    
    It's Springtime!   http://tinyurl.com/d6vm5o    
    
    
    Birthdays are your body's way of telling you you're not getting enough alcohol.    
    
    
    Just because they make leggings in your size doesn't mean you have to wear them.    
    
    
    Upon closer inspection, I don't think they are her size. How did she get those things on?    
    
    
    @ClutchPR Okay, I'm catty... Bottom line, trends are great, but fashion is about looking your best. If it makes you look bad, don't wear it.    
    
    
    @ClutchPR And I'm sure you look lovely in leggings.    
    
    
    This tweet is redeemable for one free tummy-rub (sorry, no dudes; I have enough problems).    
    
    
    Weekly ego-boost: Your ass looks spectacular today. You been running? Yoga, eh? Nice.    
    
    
    Flip flop sound is the only foot-sweat-based noise that's acceptable in an office environment. Sadly.    
    
    
    I often forget why I don't eat Pop-Tarts, so I buy a box, eat a box, then remember why I don't eat pop-tarts. I should just write it down.    
    
    
    Hey! I just did!    
    
    
    If you were a jelly bean, what colour would you be? Her: Green. Me: If you're not going to answer seriously, don't bother. Her: [profanity].    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/3c9un - Quite possibly the worst (and therefore greatest) homemade Star Wars costumes ever.    
    
    
    Skittles changed the 'melon berry' package to 'berry explosion'. The flavours are STILL the same. WTF? http://www.melonsarenotberries.com    
    
    
    This makes me smile. And sing. Poorly. And loudly.  http://tinyurl.com/cvkol9    
    
    
    I just had a telemarketer try and sell me a telephone. Me: Are phone calls the best means to find folks who need phones? Him: [silence]    
    
    
    If you took that apart and moved the pieces individually, it'd be a lot easier. Fine, whatever. 

I hate the gym.    
    
    
    "Are you kidding? Of course I want to hear about how you feel your cat is upset with you!" ...is what I SHOULD have said. Dammit.    
    
    
    If emotional issues were money, I'd have two less problems.    
    
    
    This secret agent training facility looks top notch. 
Her: This is a Starbucks. We sell coffee. 
Me: Wow. You guys are good.    
    
    
    My DIY coloured bubble experiment was not as successful as I would have liked. Also, what gets ink out and dish soap stains out of carpet?    
    
    
    A project required super-permanent 'sticks to anything' ink. I love that at 27 years old, I still don't have the foresight to put gloves on.    
    
    
    Now I look like I got a little frisky with a bottle of white-out. Eep.    
    
    
    I just learned that sneezing inside a motorcycle helmet is both hilarious and super-dangerous.    
    
    
    Riverdance is due for a comeback.    
    
    
    Sales douche: It's made from 'space-age materials'. Me: You mean plastic? Far out...    
    
    
    Given that people are in space right now, it's safe to say all materials are space-age materials, no?    
    
    
    My dad just asked me if his computer had 'the Internet on it'. This is going to be a difficult conversation.    
    
    
    Grrr. Fine, Dad. I'll put the internet on your computer. Yes, the whole internet. Just for you. (Don't judge me. It's just easier this way).    
    
    
    You've got a video camera and a giant octopus, and the best idea you have is to make a documentary? Get it together, National Geographic.    
    
    
    See, dad? Every newspaper around the world is online. Just type it into Google. Pop: Do they have the Toronto Star on this thing?    
    
    
    Um, yes, they have the Toronto Star online. It's also on the kitchen table. Think more globally. Dad: The Parry Sound Star?    
    
    
    Parry Sound doesn't – whatevs, fine, let's go there. Dad: Hey! I can see what the weather's like at the cottage! Me: Ugh. Let's try YouTube.    
    
    
    Did my taxes. I'm not going to say it went poorly, but I spent the last few hours in a dark room curled up chanting 'motherfucker'. Eep.    
    
    
    Fine, I don't "need" to be naked for this, but I don't have to be not naked, right? No, YOU'RE difficult.  I hate going to the dentist.    
    
    
    Ladies, I love you all, I truly do. But why do you insist on screaming just because it's raining? It doesn't keep you dry – umbrellas do.    
    
    
    Wet pants are uncomfortable for several reasons.    
    
    
    If I was a stripper, this would totally be my blanket song. Milli Vanilli, you sing what I feel. http://tinyurl.com/2ca527    
    
    
    Fine. Just sit there all smug and thwart-y like. But this isn't over, Tylenol bottle; I own power tools. Who's child-proof now, bitch?    
    
    
    Success! Headache's gone, but I'm still downing a dozen of these pills. I've earned it. I'll shotgun a Red Bull and let 'em fight it out.    
    
    
    I've been reading Monocle magazine and brother, I don't even own one. I can't believe they keep letting me get away with this.    
    
    
    @scroll Finally! I can let the whole world know about my crush... anonymously! Is there anything technology can't do?    
    
    
    Oh sure, but the dog drags it's ass across the carpet and everyone giggles; double standard!    
    
    
    He's talking smack? Let's tag-team his ass... I meant that to sound less gay than it did. Er, I mean not gay at all. I shouldn't smack talk.    
    
    
    Oh sweetie, when the label said 'slim fit', that wasn't a promise.    
    
    
    Having a great ass day; seems like a waste burying it in a chair at the office.    
    
    
    Weekly ego boost: That's a fabulous blouse; goes great with your shoes. Is it new? Really, marked down, too? Beauty. [hugs!]    
    
    
    @twot Excellent call; I've been looking for a way to introduce awkward tension into the all-male office.    
    
    
    @twot Very true; tension is fun, but you don't have to wear pants to work. You're living the dream. Lousy pants; messing up my world. Grrr.    
    
    
    I'm not health-poor, I'm mucus-rich.    
    
    
    My 250th tweet! I was going to say something poignant, or at least relevant, but I need to stay consistent. [sigh].    
    
    
    I never remember this metric/imperial conversion garbage. Anyone know how many snack packs there are in a dinner?    
    
    
    If there's a bad ukulele solo, I haven't heard it.    
    
    
    Me? I make midget thai-ladyboy Andromimetophiliac films; very avant-garde. Her: Oh. Where did you learn to act shorter? Me: I love you.    
    
    
    FACT: Wherever you go, within a block or two there will be a Chinese restaurant (except China; they just call them restaurants there).    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/3rnw9 - What the hell is the matter with people?    
    
    
    Seriously. The Bacon Bra is one of the top 25 Google Searches in the US... WTF? http://tinyurl.com/cyffow    
    
    
    I mean, cooked bacon makes sense, but raw? That's asking for trouble.    
    
    
    I'm confused; if muffin-top is bad, does that mean muffin-stump is good? Because she didn't seem to appreciate me calling her muffin-stump.    
    
    
    My pop just asked me to find a "pirated copy of Foxfire" for him... I'm going to install Dope Wars and see if he notices.    
    
    
    Any solvent that removes spray glue from skin burns with the fire of a thousand suns when it gets on your giblets. I've heard.    
    
    
    My ethnicity? Ukrainian. Her: Where's Ukrainia? Me: Thank God you're pretty. Your hair's like spun gold. Her: I like hair, it's fun [giggle]    
    
    
    WOOT! The world's biggest sing-along starts today! Also, something about soccer. Ole, oleoleole, ole, o-le!    
    
    
    I would've bet money that door was a 'push'. It was a 'pull'. Dammit.    
    
    
    @zolora It counts as a date if you manage to get a little action.    
    
    
    Plan 'A' involved selling my eggs to an affluent couple desperate for a child. Turns out I don't have eggs. I need a plan 'B'. Or some eggs.    
    
    
    Sexy? Me: Heck yeah those two-sizes-too-small fishnets are sexy. And by sexy, I mean makes me want to buy a ham. Her: [profanity] Me: What?    
    
    
    Your role here is largely decorative, isn't it? Her: Hmm? Me: I love you.    
    
    
    I wish I had a giant bunny. I'd name her Moose; she'd like the irony. Plus, I'd have giant carrots; maybe pretend to be a smurf sometimes.    
    
    
    Her: I can't find my keys. Me: Well, they're always in the last place you look. Her: How could you possibly know that? Me: I love you.    
    
    
    @FakePatForan and by 'countless', you mean that it's hard for you to count things, not that there are many, right?    
    
    
    Worthy of T-Pain. http://tinyurl.com/cdzehp    
    
    
    If a cute brunette tweets about seeing a slightly effeminate weird guy car dancing at a traffic signal, don't believe her; she's a witch.    
    
    
    Just looked at my closet and thought 'OMG, I have nothing to wear'. You took away my last bit of masculinity, fashion. Not cool. I needed it    
    
    
    Somehow I've managed to get more socially awkward with age. That wasn't the deal, life. I want a refund. Or better yet, an exchange.    
    
    
    @jyotika Nope. I'm actually more disappointing in person than ever. I'm getting better at 140 character dick jokes, though...    
    
    
    Excessive alcohol consumption is not always the most viable social lubricant for a given situation.    
    
    
    I just finished watching a 3 hour documentary on Boston's big dig project. Unsurprisingly, it was a very boring process.    
    
    
    Happy Monday, Twitter!  I spent the weekend learning how to dance a jig. I hope yours was as successful. #Productive_weekend    
    
    
    No I don't play sports; I went to art school. But I can draw sports and then discuss how I feel about them with the group; that's close, no?    
    
    
    Highlight of every episode of Ice Road Truckers: "oh geez, it's slippy".    
    
    
    Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game. Good game.
#worldcup    
    
    
    Fire!

 http://twitpic.com/8bp08a     
    
    
    Today I learned that complimenting a woman's accent, only to discover it's actually a lisp, is an unfavourable preamble to a dinner invite.    
    
    
    Wal-Mart's eco-bags are made from polyethylene and nylon. Consumers say pay attention to the environment, so they cockpunch it. So evil.    
    
    
    Coffee and vodka counts as a martini if I'm at the Drake, but if I put it in Tim's travel mug at home it's weird? I need better glasses.    
    
    
    If you have to write the name on the costume, you're not trying hard enough.    
    
    
    I am puppy-sitting. My self-esteem has never been higher.    
    
    
    Someone needs to invent spray marshmallows. Soon, please.    
    
    
    I spent the morning convincing a 40 Year-old co-worker that Macs have lights inside that turn on when the case is closed. #productivity    
    
    
    No, it works the opposite way a fridge does; that's why computers get hot instead of cold.    
    
    
    He's spent the last ten minutes on all fours looking for light leaks from the fan vents. I would feel bad if I wasn't so amused.    
    
    
    @PunchPR I want one.    
    
    
    @PunchPR I think it's a slow loris, though I'd settle for a monkey. Or an ewok.    
    
    
    Living the dream. Well, mine, anyhow. Via @PunchPR: http://tinyurl.com/cu6d7p    
    
    
    Today is world Graphic Design Day. If anyone asks, we don't promote it purely for the irony. http://tinyurl.com/dycfao Via @DesignObserver    
    
    
    I attempted to make my own spray marshmallows with an air compressor and can; unsuccessfully. What gets marshmallow out of...um, everything?    
    
    
    Annnd now I'm sticky. The bad kind of sticky.    
    
    
    Man, I wish I had a Scottish accent. Then things would be different.    
    
    
    @actually_nate What if your hands stayed the same size, but everything else got smaller? Just saying... I might know a guy.    
    
    
    Gin for dinner.
Again. 

Being a grown up is rad.    
    
    
    Spent the last 20 minutes sculpting an ewok out of cappuccino ice cream.    
    
    
    Also, my waitress has a serious attitude problem. Must be the heat.    
    
    
    Here's the thing; a backhanded compliment isn't really a compliment at all, though I can see how people make that mistake.    
    
    
    Also, I was just referred to as an 'ironically cool collection of awkward moments'. Eep.    
    
    
    Weekly ego-boost: you look magnificent in that top today. It really makes you eyes *pop*. [hugs!]    
    
    
    Dear old dude, I realize mobile phones are smaller these days, but the microphones are actually better. Inside voice, please. Love, Pete    
    
    
    Oh, you've accidentally pressed the speakerphone button and you can't turn it off. Rad.    
    
    
    The only difference between a stalker and an eager sales rep is a bad suit. Well that, and I'm not a sales rep.    
    
    
    That was a joke, relax. Yes you. I saw you tense up a little through the window.    
    
    
    Just saw a man get into an argument, albeit one-sided, with a goose. I'm taking it as an impromptu reminder that things could be much worse.    
    
    
    Her: These dishes aren't going to clean themselves. 
Me: You're probably right, but I'm going to give it another few days to be sure.    
    
    
    Drinking Starbucks breakfast blend even though it's dinner time. I don't just flirt with danger, I get it drunk, cop a feel and never call.    
    
    
    Love that sweater – very Jackie-O. You need a pearl necklace. 
Her: Yeah, want to give me one? Wait.    
    
    
    Two penguins standing on the beach, one says to the other: You made me get all dressed up for this?    
    
    
    I'm being rhetorical?    
    
    
    Fact: A pretty woman will magically materialize the second I start aisle dancing to the muzak version Britney's Toxic at the store.    
    
    
    Fact #2: Any woman I see subsequent to Fact #1 will not introduce herself.    
    
    
    My pants are loose. Apparently the economy is so bad, even my ass is in recession.    
    
    
    Loose pants is a problem; I just mooned a boardroom full of people. Well, partially; I guess you could say I half-assed it.    
    
    
    It bothers me a little that my bum is an economic indicator. Ideally, I don't want it to indicate anything.    
    
    
    Though I suppose it's better than being a smuggling indicator. Eep.    
    
    
    And no, my butt does NOT want a 'stimulus package'. Smart ass.    
    
    
    I'm getting off track; I need a loose-pants solution. I hate wearing a belt with a tie; too ostentatious.    
    
    
    That's a lie. I don't do it because the only belt I own is a Batman replica utility belt. Don't judge me. You know you want one.    
    
    
    Great news! Current economic indicators suggest my ass-recession has bottomed out.    
    
    
    I spend way too much time thinking about my bum.    
    
    
    I'm Mr. Bucket, *pop*, buckets of fun! http://tinyurl.com/fhmx5    
    
    
    The only thing I know how to say in French is "who's your daddy", but you'd be surprised how far that'll get you.    
    
    
    @FakeStudiolit Oh yeah? Don't make me come over there...    
    
    
    [Jazz hands]    
    
    
    Today I learned that the only thing messier than a three year-old playing is a three year-old cleaning.    
    
    
    I'm creating a new program on TV involving origami puppets that drone on incessantly for no particular reason; calling it 'Paper View'.    
    
    
    I'm already in talks about a network spin-off with a more diverse cast; rock, paper, scissors.    
    
    
    HGTV execs, I have only two words for you: 'Construction Paper'.    
    
    
    And of course, a viable BT competitor; 'The Morning Paper'. @KevinFrankish: watch out.    
    
    
    Also, I need to stop keeping fancy paper swatch books at my desk, even though I fold a mean lilly.    
    
    
    The sheer volume of people who do things the same way for no other reason than because that's the way they've always done them worries me.    
    
    
    Addendum: With the exception of cookie monster. That guy had it all figured out.    
    
    
    Free alcohol + 200 strangers + my special brand of awkward = good times.    
    
    
    Correction: by "good time", I mean incredibly socially awkward.    
    
    
    The older I get, the more I realize that life was a lot easier before puberty.    
    
    
    Also, when the hell did I become Charlie Brown? Not cool.    
    
    
    If you aren't underweight, you can't eat tablet-sized candy (smarties, sweet tarts, etc) without sharing; thems the rules. Smartie, please.    
    
    
    How come I only remember that I have mad ninja skills when I'm drinking?    
    
    
    Without fail, wherever I go, a kind woman realizes I can't make it on my own and helps me function at an adult level. Thanks, ladies!    
    
    
    No. It does not, nor will it ever, need a fucking starburst.    
    
    
    Twitter Essentials: @Scroll @Zolora @SecretSquirrel @AmyVerner @SniffyJenkins @TheMime #Follow Friday    
    
    
    Foodies: Please stop combining two foods I like to make a new one that disgusts me.    
    
    
    Raspberry yogurt mixed with chocolate pudding seemed like a logical combination. And by logical, I mean I had both in my fridge.    
    
    
    In hindsight, I probably shouldn't have accepted that wager. On the upside, the fireman let me sit on the truck!    
    
    
    My tummy hurts... too much candy. On the upside, I now have a nougat centre.    
    
    
    @caitlinquarry Hehehe... inappropriate, spontaneous laughter is the second best kind of laughter.    
    
    
    Oh. My. God. A Toys 'R' Us is now within walking distance of home; no more fighting crosstown traffic for Play-Doh related emergencies. Woo!    
    
    
    You're cold and bitter, but I still love you, Gin.    
    
    
    Just so we're all clear; we're going to blame the earthquake on the G20, right? Damned hippies.

#G20 #Earthquake    
    
    
    W00T! We won an award! Special thanks to @Designedgemag 

http://tinyurl.com/38oe6l8    
    
    
    Hey Gin, why do you do this to me? We're supposed to be a team.    
    
    
    Ah, who am I kidding, I can't stay mad at you. Come here...    
    
    
    It's about playing to your strengths; for example, what I lack in ability I more than make up for in ineptitude.    
    
    
    There is a shocking lack of innovation within the bungee cord industry.    
    
    
    MC Hammer claimed to be too legit to quit, then quit. 

Postmodern meditation on legitimacy, or ironic blunder? Discuss.    
    
    
    If you didn't want me to do the running man, you shouldn't have been playing Young MC's wicked-rad rhymes. The blame here is 50/50.    
    
    
    A woman smiled at me today and I couldn't speak for five minutes. So no, I will never have a threesome.    
    
    
    I keep dreaming I'm being eaten by a muppet. 
Am I gay for cookie monster, or is my new fuzzy blue blanket just not working out? 
Her: [...]    
    
    
    Thanks a bundle for that book on productivity. Maybe next we can split a barbecued pig to learn about dieting?    
    
    
    OW OW OW CRAP ICE CREAM HEADACHE DAMMIT FRICKIN CHOCOLATE  OW    
    
    
    The only difference I see between an artful, sultry seductress and a bar tender is how I settle up. But make no mistake; either way I pay.    
    
    
    Is it weird that a girl who has a penchant for pens thoroughly does it for me?    
    
    
    That's it. I've been asked to 'download Twitter' for the last time. If you're over 35, just get off the interwebs. Maybe try a book instead?    
    
    
    I just saw a goose goose a goose. Didn't know they actually did that. Neat.    
    
    
    I love weddings. They're so romantic. 

And by romantic, I mean I have a pretty decent shot at making out with that skanky bridesmaid.    
    
    
    If wearing too much cheap perfume got you drunk, this wedding would be a lot more entertaining.    
    
    
    For the past three weeks, I've been able divide my dirty laundry into candy or marker-stained piles. Evenly. At least I'm consistent.    
    
    
    Also, what gets candy and marker stains out?    
    
    
    Weddings are one of the few occasions left where mad chicken dancing skills are asset.    
    
    
    Dear self, what's the matter with you? Get it together. Love, me.    
    
    
    Weekly ego boost: I noticed your nails match your shoes; good call. They both look fantastic. [hugs!]    
    
    
    The more I think about it – and I think about it a lot – the more I realize Teddy Ruxpin was a seriously creepy toy.    
    
    
    The indistinguishability between confidence and ignorance is increasingly problematic.    
    
    
    Self proclaimed social media experts: spamming me about how awesome you are does little to
legitimize your claim. #Unfollowed    
    
    
    First dates have taught me that few women share my penchant for slightly effeminate, self deprecating anecdotes and Star Trek.    
    
    
    Old marketing folk: Uploading a half-assed video to YouTube does not mean you've "gone viral".    
    
    
    There's nothing worse than making coffee, forgetting about it, and then discovering that your only mug doesn't fit in the office microwave    
    
    
    And that's not hyperbole. It's the worst thing that's happened. Ever. Grrr...    
    
    
    I'm not ashamed to admit that I'm a little jealous that women can wear ponchos without necessitating a complete Mexican theme. Looks comfy.    
    
    
    I think the only difference between being self-employed and unemployed is how consistent tomorrow's plans are.    
    
    
    'Concise Oxford English Dictionary and Thesaurus' seems unnecessarily long. I'd have called it 'Word List'.    
    
    
    And if you need to specify 'English', the dicitonary probably won't help you. Just saying... no need for verbosity.    
    
    
    More things need to be made from tennis ball fuzz.    
    
    
    Hiya Interwebs! I've been drinking with a buddy and I have been drinking. Sooo... what are you wearing?    
    
    
    Oh my. That's hot. Tell me more – and feel free to talk dirty.    
    
    
    Oh. My. God. Internets, I knew you were into some things, but that is DISGUSTING. Where do you even find that many midget amputees?    
    
    
    Scratch that. I don't want to know. And let's never speak of this again.    
    
    
    Gorgeous day. I wish I could whistle.    
    
    
    Christmas shopping at the LCBO. it's amazing how much my life turned out the way I thought.    
    
    
    Extra large, double double, please. 
Double double. 
Extra large. 
Double double.

I got a medium French vanilla. 
Damn you Tim Horton's.    
    
    
    Motorcycle jumpers get applause when they miss a jump and survive. I didn't die today, either. I get nothing. Weak.    
    
    
    'Badass' teenagers: Lose the bicycle helmets if you're trying to look like a rebel. Maybe the bikes altogether. #tool    
    
    
    Did I say I was Brazilian? Sorry, I meant Dutch. 
#WorldCup    
    
    
    Two obviously unpopular teenagers are standing on a  bridge overlooking traffic, holding a video camera. This will not end well for someone.    
    
    
    I never understood what the prince saw in Rapunzel; any abandoned, imprisoned chick with freaky long hair probably has some serious issues.    
    
    
    Same thing with Goldilocks. Blonde is hot, but the overly picky personality would be a chore. She had some serious boundary issues, too.    
    
    
    If Peanut Butter were a chick, I'd marry her. Life would be perfect. Then I'd find her in bed with Jam. Cheat on me with a musician? WTF PB?    
    
    
    It's a little disconcerting that most of my fantasies involve things not working out for me.    
    
    
    Though it's probably more concerning that I'm fantasizing about marrying Peanut Butter in the first place...    
    
    
    If you have to tell me you're an industry leader, you're not.    
    
    
    Maybe I'm overly optimistic, or just naive, but I'm constantly amazed by the sheer volume of people who are slimy for no reason.    
    
    
    Sycophants: Wipe your nose and call it a day – it's not working.    
    
    
    @jyotika Good call! I actually know of a superhero supply store in Brooklyn. Problem. solved. http://www.superherosupplies.com/    
    
    
    The interwebs gods are being too generous to me today. Awesome.

http://www.awkwardboners.com/    
    
    
    @jyotika I promise nothing.    
    
    
    Life doesn't present enough opportunities to wear a cape.    
    
    
    Philippe Starck, you are correct. I am but a super-monkey. That sounded more profound with a French accent.    
    
    
    The Swedish people have too strong a foothold in the gummy market.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday America! You guys are alright, so we talked to Mexico and decided you can keep riding bitch on our continent. [hugs!]    
    
    
    I am at my best when I don't consider the consequences.    
    
    
    Weekly ego boost: I just thought I'd tweet to remind you how wonderful you are. [hugs!]    
    
    
    It is never funny to ask someone if you may lick their armpit... apparently.    
    
    
    I’m wearing what I’m wearing, but I’m not *wearing* it today. Ever have those days?    
    
    
    Although my ass does look pretty nifty in these pants.    
    
    
    It bothers me that there's no specific term for someone who's compulsively ambiguous. Isn't that just enabling them?    
    
    
    Fashion Week, day one: pretty.
#WMCFW
http://twitpic.com/8vu937     
    
    
    It's so hot, I'm pretty sure Environment Canada just declared my swamp ass a protected wetland.    
    
    
    I dated a chick that looked like a model once. At least I thought I did; turns out 'bipolar' isn't another word for model.    
    
    
    The liver is evil and needs to be punished. Cheers!    
    
    
    What am I wearing? I'm nude. And cold. Well, that's not completely true; I am wearing suspenders. 

My co-workers think I'm weird.    
    
    
    I'm taking the Winne the Pooh and the Honey Tree approach; just sit still and whine a little until someone fixes everything.    
    
    
    If a lesbian says "you look hot tonight", does it count?    
    
    
    Seniority is a corporation's way of deterring youthful ambition.    
    
    
    Debate: If you were going on a road trip cross-country, and could bring any cereal mascot with you, who would it be?    
    
    
    Apparently, my answer of the 1996 US women's gymnastics team from the wheaties box is cheating... Although I maintain it would be fun.    
    
    
    @pyroboyee Three words: bird shit everywhere.    
    
    
    Fact: The number of beautiful women I will run into whilst running errands is directly related to how unkempt I look.    
    
    
    Ratzillia followed immediately by Hogzilla. Discovery channel, I love you.    
    
    
    Far too few products are available in jerky-form.    
    
    
    @Scootch1 I just threw up a little.    
    
    
    So, it turns out I'm the reason products need to be labelled "caution: contents hot". My tongue hurts.    
    
    
    I think they only let adults drink because adults are the only ones with reasons to drink.    
    
    
    If you replace the names, listening to men talk about hockey sounds exactly like women talking about Gossip Girl.    
    
    
    I think self doubt can be a good thing. But I'm probably wrong. And dumb. Sorry for wasting your time just now.    
    
    
    Elephantine men donning Dri-Fit shirts in the office give off the same vibe as teenagers who put racing stripes on '86 Chevettes.    
    
    
    It's amazing how many women confuse social ineptitude with playing it cool.    
    
    
    Old white dude with unjustified sense of entitlement: I was wrong to drive on your highway. Thanks for cutting me off to remind me.    
    
    
    Also, I think it's awesome the way your gold chain accents your grey chest hair. It's a hard look to pull off, but you make it work.    
    
    
    Why do they even make hot chocolate without mini marshmallows? That's like a boob with no nipple; alright idea, but kind of pointless.    
    
    
    The s'mores people are a little presumptuous. Maybe I'm feeling chubby and don't want s'mores. Maybe I want s'nuffs? So much attitude.    
    
    
    Grocery shopping invariably pisses me off. Now I'm all punchy. I'm going to the pudding section; it's like visiting the puppies at PetSmart.    
    
    
    If the puppies were edible and chocolate – which I maintain would be rad. I'd crossbreed them with mini marshmallows. Then life would rock.    
    
    
    You'd be amazed how many times a day I hear "I have no idea what to say to that". Meh.    
    
    
    Ugh. That man is the human equivalent of finding a pubic hair on a bar of soap.    
    
    
    "Oh yeah, I'll Twitter you". I love the way dad's speak.    
    
    
    Someone just quoted one of my tweets to me; I feel like a rock star, but without the drugs, women or music.

It's not a great feeling.    
    
    
    There's some weird stuff on the internet these days. Long story short, I’ll never look at balloon knots the same way again.    
    
    
    Permission doesn't age well.    
    
    
    You did what? Me: I've already said too much. On a completely unrelated subject, thanks for being such a sound sleeper. Her: [pissed]    
    
    
    Just walked by what could only be a giant midget - big midget ass, oompa loompa walk, but regular height. Fantastic.    
    
    
    Motorbike maturing point: getting nailed in the neck by a bee at 120km/h stings like... um... a bee.    
    
    
    Just ate a pudding cup with a fork; partly because I'm a badass who scoffs at rules, and partly because I can't find a clean spoon.    
    
    
    Okay, mainly because I can't find a clean spoon. Or pants. What the hell happened to all my pants?    
    
    
    Ah... dryer. The spoons were there too, though I'm not sure why. I think they might be up to something.    
    
    
    Ah, family Christmas, you're the most wonderful thing in the world I hate so fucking much.    
    
    
    That website is pretty special. The guy did it in MS Word because apparently Front Page 98 is for Pros only. Wow.    
    
    
    Bought new tweezers. And now, for no apparent reason, I wanna make a teeny tiny something.    
    
    
    Gym guy to pretty girl: I can dead lift 500 lbs. Me: I can't. But we could shop and share our feelings maybe? Who'd you rather? Check. Mate.    
    
    
    Male Colleague: Thanks for being so flexible. Me: You should see me after I stretch. MC: [immensely uncomfortable silence].    
    
    
    Hey, mullet; just because you're rolling in an '86 IROC doesn't mean you have to crank your Metallica mixtape. Buck the stereotype. Please.    
    
    
    Finally. http://www.hiyoooo.com/    
    
    
    The mothball-smelling cougar across from me has me thinking my aspirations of becoming a sniffer dog are likely best left unfulfilled. [Gag]    
    
    
    Though, if I'm not a sniffer dog, dry humping guests probably won't go over as well.    
    
    
    I need to find a way to make money disappointing women; I'm tired of doing it pro bono.    
    
    
    Without access to a mom, how does one go about getting a button re-attached? Let's say I'm asking for a friend.    
    
    
    Also, without access to a mom (or grocery store where I can project a helpless baby bird vibe until a nice lady helps) how do I get dinner?    
    
    
    I need to start a rent-a-mom service. 
Or at least hire one of those special-ed ladies to follow me around. 
I'm huuuuuungry.    
    
    
    @MolsonIsMyDog PIZZA PIZZA Good call! If they also re-attach buttons, this'll be my most successful evening in weeks! [sigh].    
    
    
    Sometimes I worry that while picking lint out of my bellybutton, I'll undo the knot and my bum will fall off.    
    
    
    Spent the last few hours teaching my turtle to play fetch. Unsuccessfully. Despite my efforts, George seems to lack motivation.    
    
    
    In New York, they just call them minutes.    
    
    
    Don't respect those who do things the way they've always been done for no other reason than because that's the way they've always done them.    
    
    
    The one good thing about a hangover is that it makes my overwhelming sense of regret much more palatable.    
    
    
    (punchline)... Aw, SNAP! I've got my funny pants on today. Her: All your pants look funny. Me: Okie, that was pretty good. But still, ouch.    
    
    
    The closest I get to cooking is making coffee. Her: making coffee isn't cooking. Me: You've never seen me make coffee. Check. Mate.    
    
    
    The corpulent child on my street has decided bee catching is a hobby worth exploring. This will not end well for him.    
    
    
    I just read an article entitled "Romantic ways to say you're getting fat". You'd think a writer would understand what 'romantic' means.    
    
    
    Overheard: You're wrong. I don't judge people, you do.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/5xf3f - He looks like I feel. Frickin Mondays.    
    
    
    #3wordsaftersex Maybe next time?    
    
    
    If I shave a dirty word into the neighbour's cat, the hair will grow back, right? I probably should have asked this 15 minutes ago.    
    
    
    Her: I hate that fashion models look so emancipated. Me: I might have let that slide if you were thinner.    
    
    
    Today I learned that my 'clicks be kickin'. 

And that clicks means shoes and kicking is good. Thanks, pleasant random urban youth!    
    
    
    You know how italics are all slanty? I'm like that all the time.    
    
    
    The older i get, the more I realize the difference between being weird and eccentric is income. Some day I hope to be eccentric.    
    
    
    I've been up for around 40 hours now... I'd worry about the hallucinations, but they assure me they're real.    
    
    
    My kitchen contains three tic-tacs, a can of tuna and a ketchup packet I'm pretty sure came with the house. So, yes. I am single.    
    
    
    Breakfast consisting of 2 egg whites, 3 cookies, coffee with chocolate milk, and sugar. Take that, adulthood.    
    
    
    @mattyaustin I tried the thrills gum bath too, but grew tired of getting gum in my hair. So sticky.    
    
    
    Weekly ego boost: You smell great today. But more importantly, thanks for being you. [hugs!]    
    
    
    Watching 40 year-olds talk internet marketing is a like watching teenagers discuss how much responsibility they have. #noclue    
    
    
    I decided to sell sperm for extra cash. In hindsight, going door-to-door was not the best sales technique.    
    
    
    I wish my office had a moat.    
    
    
    I'm looking pretty jazzy, and feeling a little frisky. I guess that means it's going to be a challenge keeping my hands off myself.    
    
    
    Whether or not Febreze constitutes a shower is not a question of liquids, but of the quantity used.    
    
    
    Also, arguing about Febreze vs. showers is a good way to piss off a woman. Apparently. [sigh.]    
    
    
    Which is complete BS; It's not like I was putting bounce sheets in my undies. Um... or some other thing I just made up that I don't do...    
    
    
    Sorry for disrupting your idea exchange and ass-itch reduction session. I was thirsty, and your establishment seemed like a logical choice.    
    
    
    Sometimes I get confused. I thought the Starbucks coffee sign out front meant you sell coffee. I didn't realize you don't need new customers    
    
    
    Thanks for helping me to understand, and for treating me like crap in the process; I needed to be taken down a notch. Love, Pete    
    
    
    Man's explored other worlds using less technology than what's in my smartphone, but I can't I buy a bag of M&Ms that are all blue? #WTF    
    
    
    Pretty blonde girl that just just saw me freak out for no apparent reason: it was a bee.    
    
    
    Dear life,

You win. Well played, sir.    
    
    
    Thanks for tattling about sentences ending with prepositions. This is precisely the sort of thing up with which I will not put.    
    
    
    First post-holi-day back at work... Gah. Only the chanting flying monkeys from Oz could possibly understand this level of tedium.    
    
    
    ...annnd now I want a monkey.    
    
    
    I wish you could freebase coffee.    
    
    
    Regardless of how long you've been dating her, or how lovingly you suggest it, 'fucktard' will never be a well-received pet name.    
    
    
    Happy Monday. I spent the weekend mocking turtlenecks. I hope yours was more successful.    
    
    
    When did we get so many varieties of band-aids? I shouldn't have to choose between 'prevents infection' and 'promotes healing'.    
    
    
    Feeling especially productive today. Going to get a jump on things by apologizing to every woman I know in advance. I'm sorry. #productivity    
    
    
    So, I put you on my list and I'm 'a lunatic', but Craig does it and you're stoked? Weak.    
    
    
    @sousveillance There can be no healing without muppets.    
    
    
    Ugh, fine. Yelling at birds does not constitute "dabbling in falconry". Though I maintain it's a good start.    
    
    
    I'm going to start asking tedious people if they were directed by James Cameron.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I like my coffee like I like my women; exotic, overpriced and caffeinated.    
    
    
    What, I can't wear my hat to the meeting? Because I can downside the antlers.    
    
    
    Dear old dude that's still 'with it', 

Mousse is for eating, not for man hair.    
    
    
    Though not all mousse, brother. Trust me. 
Read the label first.    
    
    
    If I had a horse, I'd name him Leonard. He'd want me to change it, but I'm not taking advice from a horse with a loser name like Leonard.    
    
    
    "Mature for your age"
Is not the same as "mature".    
    
    
    Million dollar idea: Free energy. 

You're welcome.    
    
    
    I can't help but think that life would be a lot easier if I was good at stuff.    
    
    
    Yeah... I'm pretty sure you didn't just screw me over because you're an 'aries'. You did it because you're a dick.    
    
    
    Overly zealous homeowner, six-foot step ladder. Both in poor shape. This should be interesting.    
    
    
    The perpetual tedium of the office is making me that thing – like smart, but the other way.    
    
    
    I live every week like it's shark week.    
    
    
    It's been fifteen minutes, there are smears everywhere and I still haven't gotten all the fucking foil off. I hope chocolate can feel pain.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/6m378 - I cleaned the studio. I found pipe cleaners. It's been a big day.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/6mkwy  I made a monkey.    
    
    
    I get it; you don't like being a waiter. Now that we've bonded, can you please bring me my gin salad? Thanks! [hugs!]    
    
    
    Just lost a staring contest with my turtle. Damn he's good. Though in fairness, I've had 6 drinks to his 1. I'll try  again in an hour...    
    
    
    He just. Keeps. Staring. http://yfrog.com/4b4hnj    
    
    
    If you don't bother asking the names of their kids, you won't have to remember the names of their kids. 
No one gives advice like I do.    
    
    
    'Chief Vision Officer'. Are you kidding me? This is what I attract. And this is why I drink. Happy Friday.    
    
    
    Cyclists: put some drawers on, please. Mobile ass crack I'm a helmet isn't a great look.    
    
    
    Yes, as a matter of fact, I do need a gin powered race boat.    
    
    
    No, You're unneccessary. And you can totally power things with gin. Case in point: me. 

Check. Mate.    
    
    
    Sharing photos of your cat dressed up in her new wig is not the way to land a husband.    
    
    
    Garfield was right; Mondays suck. I have a lot to learn from that cat.    
    
    
    Best part of working from home? I haven't worn socks in 5 days. Conveniently, it's also the most depressing part of working from home.    
    
    
    Me: I love you. You're sweet and comforting, like cheesecake. Her: Fail. 

Dammit.    
    
    
    I love getting your passive aggressive notes because I know that when I ignore them, you won't confront me about it.    
    
    
    New year's resolution: acquire something rocket-powered.    
    
    
    What's a male spinster called? 
Actually never mind, that should give me something to do this weekend. [sigh].    
    
    
    I just spent 45 minutes convincing an older coworker that emailing me chain letters and such will use up all the internet. #Productivity    
    
    
    Design doesn't matter? How many of these companies do you think grossed more than a billion dollars last year? http://tinyurl.com/dxbulf    
    
    
    You were flirting with me? 
Her: God, you're obtuse. 
Me: Me? Maybe you just suck a flirting? 
Her: Smooth. 
Me: Dammit.    
    
    
    Oh, sure, you've never thought of filling an inflatable ball pit with marshmallow goo.    
    
    
    Mmm. You smell nice. What's it called? Me: desparation. Her: I've never heard of that. Who makes it? Me: Society. [sigh.]    
    
    
    It's amazing how many people give me advice about other people's advice.    
    
    
    That was your sister? 

Friday just got interesting.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/78aup  Woot! New haircut day! 

Just let me have this. I don't get out much.    
    
    
    To the dark orange stinky man that just sat next to us on the patio: sun bathing is NOT the same as bathing.    
    
    
    Yes.
http://failblog.org/    
    
    
    I don't think it's fair that penguins can't smile. At the very least, their tummies should change colour or something.    
    
    
    I wish my tummy could change colour. That'd be awesome.    
    
    
    With a colour changing tummy, combined with my rarely exercised ability to smile, I'd be a shoe in for penguin-leader.    
    
    
    And as your penguin leader, I promise to bring back Pingu. 

Immediately. 

That is all.    
    
    
    More things need to smell like new tennis balls.    
    
    
    arfbdbvlkvberaergv! Bug in my mouth. In. My. Mouth. 
Motorcycle sex appeal in action. Ladies!    
    
    
    Nothing on TV, so I've been amusing myself with vodka and shadow puppets. I'm not sure which is more entertaining, but both are a challenge.    
    
    
    It's amazing how quickly a bit of thinking  can turn excitement into dread.    
    
    
    I wish I had a parrot-monkey – then I'd finally have a reason to invent banana crackers. I'd name him Gizmo. 

Annnnd now I want a mogwai.    
    
    
    The neighbor's dog keeps barking at me until I pet him. I think I'm starting to understand what dating's like for women.    
    
    
    I just discovered that if I bite a chunk of cheese just right, I can use it as a spoon.    
    
    
    I also discovered cheese and pudding don't taste that bad together. Big day.    
    
    
    It's hot and I'm hungry. Why has no one invented pizza slurpees? Fricking foodies.    
    
    
    I'm standing between a pawn shop and porn store, thinking this will be the last year we let my dad pick the dinner venue.    
    
    
    I know I'm going to be productive this week – I even put my pants on before noon. At least I think these are my pants.    
    
    
    Hmmm... upon closer inspection, I don't think these are my pants. They certainly don't seem to fit properly.    
    
    
    Shit. My pants, just backwards. All better now. 

As I was saying, it's going to be a productive week.    
    
    
    Billy Bee honey bear, why do you fight with me when I love you so?    
    
    
    I had to decapitate the honey bear to make my sandwich. A touch sadistic I guess, but also gooey goodness. Now my fingers are sticky.    
    
    
    Hipster chick: If you need a belt for your shirt, you're not working the shirt properly.    
    
    
    Ungrateful children. Admittedly, the free pet hamster birthday piñata didn't work *exactly* as planned, but still, where's the thank-you?    
    
    
    Settle down, that was a joke; it was really more of a box on a rope than a piñata.    
    
    
    The neighborhood bunny has taken a shine to me. Neato. 

 http://twitpic.com/89ytc    
    
    
    I think the little punk just mooned me. Oh, it's on...   
 http://twitpic.com/8a0ov    
    
    
    If you do moon a rabbit, note that getting caught by a neighbor chasing a bunny without pants on is surprisingly difficult to explain. Eep.    
    
    
    Woke up to find 2 Italian guys with power tools at my front door. Thought I was in a mob movie. 

Turns out we're renovating the bathroom.    
    
    
    20 years of experience is only impressive if those years were spent doing the job well.    
    
    
    Admittedly, I was a scant fervid in my body grooming today. On the upside, I'm pretty sure I'm now hypo-allergenic. Ladies!    
    
    
    Glitter and hot pants and tramp stamps. Oh my.    
    
    
    I don't get drunk. 
I get awesome.
#Vegas    
    
    
    Pro tip: Spelling shop 'shoppe' doesn't automatically make your store quaint. Especially if the words 'adult' and 'novelty' precede it.    
    
    
    Projects evolve organically; I must surrender to the process for something truly wonderful to emerge. Her: So, you didn't do the laundry?    
    
    
    I wish more things tingled to let you know they're working.    
    
    
    Procrastination is the mother of creativity. At least, that's what I tell people when their work's not done. Don't judge me. It's my process    
    
    
    Today I learned that giving a three year-old candy does not constitute "feeding a three year-old dinner", even if it was dinnertime. Pfft.    
    
    
    No clean knives, and now my fingers are icky. I wish they made peanut butter in squeezie tubes.

Screw it. I'm making my own...    
    
    
    Took a toothpaste tube and stuffed it with peanut butter. It works, but is a bit minty. Still, it seems more successful than the paint tube.    
    
    
    Weekly ego boost: I love what you're doing with your hair these days; you look wonderful. But more importantly, you are wonderful. [hugs!]    
    
    
    I saved that spider and it didn't even write 'thanks' in it's web. Good thing I didn't kill it; illiterate spiders need the most love.    
    
    
    Umm... what gets glitter out?    
    
    
    Happy Canada Day! I'm going to spend the whole entire day getting drunk and lighting fireworks; WOOT! I don't have the day off, but whatevs.    
    
    
    How come they can make bubblebath, but not bubbleshower?    
    
    
    Why can't we have an adult conversation? Me: Fine. What are you wearing? Her: Idiot. Me: Name calling? You're so immature.    
    
    
    Damn, that girl's got some city miles on her.

#iheartruralvernacular    
    
    
    Universal Google image search truth: no matter what you type, you will get porn.    
    
    
    Though, in fairness, I was searching for porn.    
    
    
    Damn. If you were ten years younger and I was ten years older, I'd marry you right now. Her: We're the same age. Me: [sigh]. I know.    
    
    
    Met a nice girl today. And by 'met', I mean stared at for 10 minutes. And by 'nice', I mean didn't freak out. 

She won't call.    
    
    
    Anyone know where I can borrow a chicken, rubber suit and spray glue? 

Uh, I'm asking for a friend.    
    
    
    I kick ass at connect the dots. Her: [...]. Me: Literally, not figuratively. Her: Oh, yes. I'm sure you do! Me: [sigh].    
    
    
    Four people have asked if I was lost today. Each time I was within ten feet of my office. I don't think this new haircut is working out.    
    
    
    Meeting new women is 20% getting lost and winding up somewhere new, and 70% helpless baby bird vibe.    
    
    
    A lovely woman just corrected my maths; the system works.    
    
    
    My parents were full of empty threats; soap really doesn't taste that bad.    
    
    
    How come it always takes me six beers to remember that I've got mad dancing skills?    
    
    
    You have a blackberry, send me three words and STILL use SMS shorthand? srsly? u r so kewl. do that 4ever. girlz luv illiteratz.    
    
    
    If I ever have to join the army, I'll be a sniper; seems like grown-up hide and seek. Or the Military channel's lying to me, not sure which.    
    
    
    Kittens!

http://kittenskittenskittens.tumblr.com/    
    
    
    Note to my fellow motorist: your super-loud muffler would impress me more if your hood matched the rest of your car. #why?    
    
    
    There's more than one way to skin a cat. Me: We talking about sex? Her: Idiot. Me: Don't judge me, freaky-cat-sex-skinner. Her: [profanity].    
    
    
    The older I get, the more I realize that feeling productive isn't about what I've done, but how much I have left to do. #Mondays_suck    
    
    
    Hi! You've been here awhile and we haven't met. Me: No worries, you aren't missing anything. Her: Awww. Me: See? You're caught up. [sigh.]    
    
    
    Turns out that chicken soup isn't just chicken stew with more water. Also, sick women don't appreciate effort without results.    
    
    
    200,000 flickr views! 

I don't feel like more of a dork, but there it is...    
    
    
    It's your first MRI; are you afraid of tight spaces? Me: no, but I am afraid of gowns. Can I do this nude?

Nurses have no sense of humour.    
    
    
    Hiya web agency, maybe 'click to enter' on your non-smartphone friendly site isn't the best way to position yourself as cutting edge?    
    
    
    I am watching Battlestar Gallactica. And enjoying it.

I think this is my brain's way of telling me women don't find me undesirable enough.    
    
    
    Inverse interest rule: The more PowerPoint-y something is, the duller it will be.    
    
    
    My hair dryer broke; sucks it doesn't blow, but that makes me giggle enough that I don't mind buying a new one. I hope the vacuum breaks.    
    
    
    @caitlinquarry Good advice. Nothing drives the ladies wild like mad curling skills.    
    
    
    I had cookies for breakfast.    
    
    
    Blackjack? I hardly know her. Wait, that's not right. It was something about cards. These are hard...    
    
    
    Poker! 

That's what I... nevermind.    
    
    
    I wish it was Friday. Her: It is Friday. Me: Damn, I'm good... now I wish I was rich. Her: [...] #TGIF    
    
    
    The best part about my morning robot dance is that I don't know how to robot dance; it really captures the essence of my day.    
    
    
    Surprisingly few women are able to offer adequate proof they're not vampires.    
    
    
    That's me! Woot!

RT @fashioninmotion: CasaLife designers Expo- featuring Biddell, Hewson, @Studiolit http://tinyurl.com/luncay    
    
    
    It's cute that you think not stooping to my level will stop me. Wrong, but cute. 

Children are so naive.    
    
    
    Everyone knows hardcore is the best kind of core. Suck it, crazy core Skittles.

www.melonsarenotberries.com    
    
    
    Every Monday it gets a little more difficult to tell whether I'm really good at lucid dreaming, or really bad at reality.    
    
    
    Pancakes need to be wrapped around more things.

Er, food-related things. Like waffles. Man, I could go for some panffles right now...    
    
    
    I love it when my socks match my undies. 
Her: You're not wearing any socks. 
Me: [...] 
Her: [Profanity].    
    
    
    Women are complicated. You like motorbikes. You like babies, but I put them together and I'm 'irresponsible'... WTF?    
    
    
    I worry that I'll never eat chocolate cupcakes with peanut butter frosting. And that my life is meaningless. But mostly the cupcake thing.    
    
    
    Mmm... You smell like candy. Her: Thanks, but it's not perfume. I just ate some gummi penguins. Me: I love you.    
    
    
    Her: You got me drunk and sick.
Me: It takes two to drink, my dear.
Her: Don't be stupid, it only takes one...
Me: [...]
Her: ...dammit.    
    
    
    You blinked after you said that; is that a double euphemism? Her: Idiot. Me: You're the one sending mixed signals. Her: [Profanity].    
    
    
    I wish I could pee purple just once.    
    
    
    Wow, you put your photo on your business card. 

Stay classy, real estate brokers.    
    
    
    Er, no, my kissing's not out of practice, I was totally aiming for your eyeball. It's the new thing the kids do. I saw it on the internets.    
    
    
    Dear North America, 
You do not have enough marsupials with funny names. 
Please add two. 
Love, Pete. 
[Hugs!]    
    
    
    Turns out that cute psychologist only wants me for my mind. [sigh].    
    
    
    For those of you wondering how many bags of giant marshmallows I can eat before feeling sick, the answer is almost one. My tummy hurts.    
    
    
    @tatvictoria I think the key is small doses; do they sell Lucky Charms? Those Irish think of everything – Shamrock shakes, now this... WOW.    
    
    
    @tatvictoria OOOooo! Will they cut them into fun shapes if I ask real nice-like?    
    
    
    I only fly Air Canada, because I think it's important to occasionally test the limits of my patience and understanding. #Grrr...    
    
    
    Classy is a relative measure. Evidently.    
    
    
    I love mailing letters, because stamps are one of the few things you can lick before giving to another person.    
    
    
    I've never met an ass I couldn't beat in a staring contest.    
    
    
    Careless exaggerations are a million times worse than the Nazis.    
    
    
    There is no elegant way to pick a wedgie.    
    
    
    Actually, she said I was artistic, not autistic; though I can see how you'd make that mistake. Thanks for the colouring book.    
    
    
    Oh. 
Really? 
Umm... in the interest of academic curiosity, what happens if I didn't know those were supposed to be taken orally?    
    
    
    Yes, the only reason I bought Turkey Jerky is because it rhymes, but that doesn't make it any less delicious.    
    
    
    This is my new niece, Elyse... I'm pretty sure that name was chosen just for the rhyme potential. #baby!

 http://yfrog.com/e6vwdj    
    
    
    Why do newspaper websites suck (rhymes with 'Rational Ghost')? It's like they're archaic designers that fear tech- oh. right. never mind.    
    
    
    I miss the Snapple lady.    
    
    
    You put your pants on one leg at a time? That seems inefficient. Her: Like thinking before speaking? Me:  Yeah, like- oh. Right. Sorry.    
    
    
    Now that they're all okay, it is very hard not to make a Chilean miner joke. 

Must. Resist. Sinking. To that level. 

Damn.

#Chileanminer    
    
    
    Long story short, my operational assumption was flawed; the snowman army will have to wait until winter. Another wasted weekend.    
    
    
    Her: You don't talk much, huh?
Me: Not really. I'm sort of like a monk that way.
Her: So, you're a little monk-y?
Me: I love you.    
    
    
    Grover is an underrated muppet.    
    
    
    @finalfashion And Dr. Grover. http://tinyurl.com/l3jzhb    
    
    
    Tried to convince a 4 year old that blue freezies are smurf purée. She said no, and called me a stupidhead. 

Damned observant children.    
    
    
    @paiiige I blame television. Kids just aren't watching enough television.    
    
    
    Why is there a bathtub in the centre of the room. Her: you ask a lot of questions, eh? Me: ...touché.    
    
    
    Fashion week, day one: anyone else feel fat? #LGFW    
    
    
    No, he's not expecting my call, unless he's psychic. Oh, crap, is he psychic? Spooky. Her: I'll take a message.

Business is hard.    
    
    
    Thanks for the Birthday wishes all! Consider this the digital version of a hug that lasts a little too long, then isn't talked about.    
    
    
    Fashion week, day two: half way through the day and I haven't proposed to anyone. I think I might be maturing.    
    
    
    @nikkibettinelli Challenge accepted, Madame.    
    
    
    @nikkibettinelli Yes, dear.    
    
    
    There's a special feeling that occurs when you realize that you are chatting up a girl with your face covered in chocolate. #shame #LGFW    
    
    
    @daniellemeder Thanks for not putting 'hetero' or 'man' in quotation marks. #SmallVictories    
    
    
    @nikkibettinelli I couldn't find a canary. Would you settle for a spray painted pigeon? I maybe know a guy...    
    
    
    Rachel Mara, LGFW, DAY 3... Pretty.
 http://twitpic.com/2zfkg0    
    
    
    Processing photos after shooting is sort of like talking after sex; necessary but painful.

Joe SS11 #LGFW  http://yfrog.com/n1osauj    
    
    
    Oh IT dude, you're right, everyone's dumb but you. So, why do you have a windowless basement office?    
    
    
    Rubber pants: pro or con? Let's say I'm asking for a friend.    
    
    
    How many crackers does one have to eat before getting cracker-poisoning? 

If it's a box, I think I have cracker-poisoning.    
    
    
    Also, eating more crackers does not seem to cure cracker-poisoning. 
I thought it might be a cyclical thing. 

It is not. 

My tummy hurts.    
    
    
    @1inAmelia Goldfish, naturally. I can't pretend to be a shark if I'm eating saltines. Well I can, but it's harder.    
    
    
    @sharawadgis Two litres of ginger ale cures cracker-poisoning? Eep! What cures ginger ale poisoning? 

See? I'm learning.    
    
    
    Listening to Wooly Bully; long story short, someone needs to bring back the toga. Soon. @Karl_Lagerfeld, I'm counting on you, sir.    
    
    
    Thanks for playing along: @sharawadgis, @1inAmelia, @paiiige, @tatvictoria, @amyverner, @finalfashion and the king, @scroll. #FollowFriday    
    
    
    Yes, I smell like sandalwood, orchids and vanilla, but that doesn't mean you get to call it perfume. It's cologne, or man-stink. Okie?    
    
    
    If I had a brontosaurus crane, I wouldn't waste it at a quarry. Fred Flintstone had no vision.    
    
    
    @timing_delivery Well played, sir.    
    
    
    Free candy is the greatest thing to happen since the advent of candy. Or free... whichever happened most recently. #FreeCandyIsSweet!    
    
    
    My mom's friends say I'm a catch, so I have that going for me.    
    
    
    @twot You're sweet for noticing. [hugs!]    
    
    
    My microwave has a coffee button AND a hot dog button, so why can't my oven have a pizza button? Get it together, GE.    
    
    
    LGFW, Day 4: Romona Keveza. Pretty.
#LGFW

 http://yfrog.com/e4nsehj    
    
    
    Oh, sweetie. Shaking your phone will not help get better reception.    
    
    
    It's stormy and a wet kitty just walked by, so naturally, this will be in my head for days. Snarf! 

http://tinyurl.com/5j5xuj    
    
    
    Today I decided to substitute women with alcohol. It's more attainable, but I may have just proposed to a bottle of tanqueray.    
    
    
    LGFW, Day 5: Denis Gagnon. Fringe-y.
#LGFW

 http://yfrog.com/jopsehj    
    
    
    The older I get, the more I'm convinced my life is one very elaborate practical joke.    
    
    
    No, it's not safe. It's dangerous, just like me, baby. Her: Then pour your coffee into a mug before you microwave it, badass. Me: Yes'm.    
    
    
    I've tried to start a wave three times today without success. Folks these days lack team spirit.    
    
    
    The speed limit says 60, but I'm doing 64, because I'm a badass that doesn't play by the rules. Ladies!    
    
    
    Dear roadblock, if you spent less time trying to cover you're ass, there'd be time do things at a level that doesn't require ass covering.    
    
    
    I need a monkey. http://tinyurl.com/ynhbtv    
    
    
    On the upside, my inability to robot dance is clear evidence that I am not a cyborg.    
    
    
    If you make it idiot-proof, someone will just make a better idiot.    
    
    
    My niece as a Lobster; Best costume. Ever.

 http://yfrog.com/18mcptj    
    
    
    Today I learned never to ask if a woman is dressed up like a tranny unless I'm absolutely sure she's wearing a costume. #Ooops    
    
    
    I like your trench coat. Me: Thanks! I'm a big fan of anything double breasted. Her: Me too. Me: I love you.    
    
    
    No animals were harmed in the making of this tweet.    
    
    
    To the drunk chubby guy reeking of cheap cologne who decided to dress up as God's gift to women: Let me know how that works out for you.    
    
    
    Being a professional creative with a light workload is like being a behavioral kid with a pack of matches.    
    
    
    To the teenager sitting beside me at Starbucks: telling your girlfriend she's a bitch will only result in her being a bitch. #dickmove    
    
    
    Be quiet. This chocolate is emotionally nutritious.    
    
    
    Note to self: If I'm at a bar watching a hockey game with a group of guys, do not say "No nachos for me, I'm feeling chubby".    
    
    
    I need a cover letter, so I've been making a list of my skills. So far I have problem drinking and not cleaning up after myself.    
    
    
    This is an odd first date venue. Her: This is a doctor's office. Me: Role playing? Hey, whatever works for you. The things I do for women...    
    
    
    Today I learned that babysitting does not actually involve sitting.    
    
    
    Gin. Her: That's cash, not cards. Me: I know. I'm ordering. Her: Staples doesn't sell gin. Me: Your service has gone downhill. For shame.    
    
    
    They say it's lonely at the top, so I guess that means I'm at the top? Wow. I really thought it would get better than this.    
    
    
    I hate eating out. How am I supposed to know what I want without pictures?    
    
    
    5 different salad choices, each has at least 2 different meats. I don't think these folks understand what 'salad' is.    
    
    
    Seriously. What kind of hack chef says "you know what this garden salad needs? 3 kinds of Meat. And bacon". WTF?    
    
    
    Oh, my mistake. One salad is listed as having a 'vegetarian option'. Vegetarian salad. Go figure.    
    
    
    Screw it. Can I just have a glass of gin, hold the bacon?    
    
    
    When I'm finally in charge, farting in elevators will be punishable by public horse-whipping. With real horses.    
    
    
    I wish mainlining caffeine was a socially acceptable office practice.    
    
    
    Corn on the cob is super-fun. Her: Sure is. And probably way easier to grow than creamed corn.  Me: Pretty AND dumb. This could work...    
    
    
    An electronic sign has just told me that the DVP, which I'm currently on, is moving slowly. Thanks, MTO.    
    
    
    Mashed potatoes are an under-utilized sculpting medium.    
    
    
    Back, then tail, then tummy. My turtle has no ass. I guess that's why he doesn't wear pants.    
    
    
    I really need a rubber tree.    
    
    
    @sharawadgis a topiary named Balls, eh? There's a trimming joke in there somewhere...    
    
    
    'Pay no attention to the man behind the curtain' is, apparently, an inappropriate reference to make at GAP changerooms.    
    
    
    A root beer float is not a balanced breakfast. A root beer float is not a balanced breakfast. A root beer float is not a balanced breakfast.    
    
    
    @sharawadgis SO happy. [hugs!]    
    
    
    I need a ringtone that sounds like flip-flops.    
    
    
    It's not right that chile is served hot.    
    
    
    Grimace was a crazy bastard.    
    
    
    I'm not a 'chin' guy per se, but I certainly notice when it's not there.    
    
    
    Million dollar idea: chocolate pudding and peanut butter filled gummi balls. You're welcome.    
    
    
    @twot Good call; we co-brand and package them with pepto-bismol samples. Synergy.    
    
    
    @twot Add in edible super balls and I'm sold. I get a 20 point consulting fee for this, right?    
    
    
    @twot You've never wanted to eat a super bouncy ball? That saddens me.    
    
    
    Pro tip for the MBAs: Quotation marks are not emphatics (i.e. I am dating a WOMAN is very different than saying I am dating a "woman").    
    
    
    Mmm. What's that smell? Me: Patchouli, amber and dark cacao. I also just ate a fruit roll-up. Her: Who makes it? Me: General Mills, I think.    
    
    
    I bet ewoks taste like venisson.    
    
    
    If you can't dance good, dance loud.    
    
    
    I'm wearing my fancy undies... Me: I WAS wearing my edible undies, but my perpetual snacking has forced me to go commando. Her: [profanity].    
    
    
    For no particular reason, I've decided that every day this week I'm going to treat one person as if they were a hallucination.    
    
    
    What does this have that makes it suitable only for hands? My soap is pretentious. And my forearms are dirty.    
    
    
    The portly preteen on my street has discovered girls. Sadly, they seem underwhelmed by his knowledge of xbox related trivia.    
    
    
    The Dairy Queen by my office is selling discount ice cream to raise money for diabetes. Quality marketing effort, DQ.    
    
    
    I miss the sound of cordurouy.    
    
    
    @JDvB Not exclusively my thighs, but yes.    
    
    
    I have an irrational fear of being reincarnated as a pocket.
Her: I don't think it works that way.
Me: You can't prove that.
Her: ...touché.    
    
    
    I'm not really that messed up, I'm just addicted to interventions.    
    
    
    The thing about women is-HA! You thought I knew something about women! Sucka-wait... that's no good... crap [sigh].    
    
    
    Going uphill is bad, and going downhill is bad. So, I guess things are going flat?    
    
    
    Wal-Mart: Where the miserable and the cheap unite to share their love of standing right in the fucking middle of the aisle. Grrr...    
    
    
    Can I count on you to support Breast Cancer? Me: No, I'm anti-cancer. Her: [...] Me: We're not going to be friends, are we? Her: Nope.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Trying to make everyone happy usually results in pissing everyone off.    
    
    
    The epic battle between the sun-tots and the smoggies needs to be made into a feature length movie. Soon.    
    
    
    It doesn't count as drinking alone if I'm in public, right?    
    
    
    To the pale redhead with no sense of humour: for the last time, it'll grow back. Sheesh.    
    
    
    How come the only foods that have stripes are minty? That's BS. Everyone knows mint tastes green, not stripey. Frickin foodies. Grrr...    
    
    
    Today I learned that chair-dancing alone in a coffee shop to Ace of Base muzak is not a good way to meet women. [sigh].    
    
    
    I'm not too lazy to clean, it's research. I'm trying to discover a milk state between yogurt and cheese. I'm going to call it 'Gurtch'.    
    
    
    The more entrenched in bachelorhood I become, the less I differentiate between 'edible' and 'non-toxic'.    
    
    
    My buddy's 5 year-old just made me the worst hot dog I've ever had. How come they have to make Play-Doh taste so salty?    
    
    
    Nothing bad ever comes in nugget-form.    
    
    
    Also, someone needs to invent cheese nuggets. I'm not sure what they would be, but they sound deep-fried and tasty, no?    
    
    
    While we're at it, nougat nuggets should be a thing. I reckon I would buy them just so I could say "can I interest you in a nougat nugget?".    
    
    
    Can squirrels swim? Actually, nevermind, I'm sure he'll be fine... forget I asked.    
    
    
    They make yellow now! Nail polish is so much fun. Me: That's the dumbest thing I've heard all weekend. Hang on, I gotta tweet this...    
    
    
    Not enough folks say 'on the morrow'. Damned teenagers. I'm going to bring it back. On the morrow.    
    
    
    Today I learned that fort building isn't encouraged at my office. And that HR finds little humour in my 'no girls allowed' policy.    
    
    
    More things need to come with corks, be they functional or decorative.    
    
    
    I'm a Threadless Twitter shirt – take THAT high school guidance counsellor! http://tinyurl.com/nff3gv    
    
    
    I've got sand in my trousers, which is not ideal.    
    
    
    I'm afraid of tassels. And baby pickles, but for a different reason.    
    
    
    Aeroplan? 
No. 
Esso plan? 
No. 
Rewards plan? 
No plans.
You just take it day by day, huh?

Best gas station cashier. Ever.    
    
    
    $75 in anti-wrinkle cream and all I have to show for it is a ruined, wrinkly shirt.

There you have it; the worst joke I will ever make.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Three words: edible finger puppets.

Necessity really is the mother of invention.    
    
    
    Peanut butter 
+ Spoon 
+ Saltines 
- Pants 
= Best Saturday Ever    
    
    
    Fuck! Chipped a tooth on a penny. Turns out my cookie jar and swear jar are the same jar. Neither seems to be working properly.    
    
    
    Four tellers, all incredibly attractive. My bank is sexist. Wonderfully, gloriously sexist.    
    
    
    Using air quotes whilst referencing your street cred is a good way to squander said street cred.    
    
    
    Weekly ego boost: By the by, your legs have been looking great lately! You been running more? Jazzercise, eh? Nice. [Hugs!]    
    
    
    One minor oversight and I'm eating microwaved hotdogs on hamburger buns for dinner – possibly the perfect food-based analogy for my life.    
    
    
    Also, today I learned never to serve a date microwaved hotdogs on hamburger buns for dinner. Turns out it is not the thought that counts.    
    
    
    Million dollar idea: edible bubbles (chocolate mint, maybe). Also, I get a free lifetime supply if anyone makes it. Or money. To buy bubbles    
    
    
    Gummi deficiency is a thing, right? 
So, these are just bear-shaped supplements.    
    
    
    Why doesn't anyone sell unicorn cookies? For shame, deliciousness industry.    
    
    
    Oh honey, speaking loudly does not help your mobile phone's reception.    
    
    
    Volcano lairs must be difficult to decorate. I can think of surprisingly few retailers that cater to a lava/laser motif. For shame, Ikea.    
    
    
    I guess that's why evil headquarters are always grey with stainless steel. Probably best for productivity to keep things professional.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Yes. 
http://monsterscereal.blogspot.com/    
    
    
    One isolated incident resulting in a small stain at lunch, and I'm forever referred to as 'honeypants'. Office culture blows.    
    
    
    I need to stop wearing cashmere. I've wasted three hours today wondering what it would be like to be a muppet. #productivity    
    
    
    Whittlin' is a severely underrated pastime.    
    
    
    Hey, I know you! 
Her: I know you too.
Me: Yep. But I knew you first.
Her: Huh?
Me: Exactly. See the crap I have to deal with? Sheesh.    
    
    
    My grocery store moved the peanut butter beside the coffee. Now I only need to visit one aisle; best day ever! [sigh].    
    
    
    There's nothing quite like an all-night art exhibition to make one realize how spectacularly pervasive ignorance has become. #nuitblanche    
    
    
    I wish cars were available in tasteful prints.    
    
    
    WOOOT! I just found 5 bucks and a jelly bean in these pants! YES!    
    
    
    I've decided to use the 5 bucks to buy more jelly beans – seems to have a certain symmetry to it.

How many jelly beans can I get for $5?    
    
    
    Gahbrffft! Pthay! Hmfgragraffftph! 

That was not a jelly bean.    
    
    
    How much Purrell-on-toast-until-this-gross-mystery-taste-goes-away can I get for five bucks?    
    
    
    @jyotika I wish I had magic boot-producing-Paris-sending pants, too. I wager they'd be corduroy.    
    
    
    High school field trip at the office today. 10 years later and teenage girls still show no interest in me. Meh. At least I can buy beer now.    
    
    
    Pastafarian? Oh, I get it. Golly, your playful choice of Facebook 'religious view' sure shows me how clever and progressive your are. Putz.    
    
    
    Ooey, gooey, rich and chewy inside. Tender, cakey, kinda flakey outside...    
    
    
    What? No, I'm having a great time. Tell me more about your cats...    
    
    
    I love New York, people here give you directions even if they don't know your destination. So friendly.    
    
    
    I just bought a package of chocolate covered chocolate fudge cookie dough snacks. #godblessAmerica    
    
    
    I just ate a package of chocolate covered chocolate fudge cookie dough snacks. I'm pretty sure I now have diabetes. And fudge poisoning.    
    
    
    En route to SoHo, tried to count the number of times I overheard someone dropping the F bomb; I lost count at awesome.    
    
    
    Best NYC moment so far: spending half an hour arguing with a stranger as to whether or not a horse is actually a unicorn-zebra chimera.    
    
    
    I maintain it's a chimera. And that crazy dudes on the street lack a sense of whimsy.    
    
    
    Fashion Week, Day 1: Women seen=many Women met=none Fashion Week, Day 2: (See day 1).    
    
    
    I'm pretty sure whoever said 'consistency is a virtue' wasn't single. [sigh]. #LGFW    
    
    
    Like every other photographer, I'm in it for the chicks.  http://twitpic.com/4chlk5     
    
    
    An existence consisting solely of alone time interspersed with small bouts of playtime with happy/drunk people... I wish I was a frisbee.    
    
    
    Hey pretty blonde girl, can I get a photo? In a big fan. Her: You like my show? Me: You have a show? 

I love #lgfw    
    
    
    FYI, the Naked News people are utterly humourless about the irony of their fashion week coverage. #lgfw    
    
    
    @SavelSells Yep. I lucked out on career day.    
    
    
    I'm thinking of starting a blue grass grassroots movement, but I fear that the grass is always greener.    
    
    
    Weren't we all supposed to have robot slaves by now? WTF, science? I want a robot.    
    
    
    During today's meeting I learned that I can fit two smarties in my navel. And that working from home kicks ass.    
    
    
    @sousveillance Nestle Smarties, of course. I also learned that 2 smarties equals one chocolate M&M. And that one peanut M&M gets stuck.    
    
    
    I never got a chance to eat Urkel-Os. Dammit.    
    
    
    Fashion Week, day one. 
Sheer-y.

#LGFW http://twitpic.com/4esld1    
    
    
    Fashion Week, day two.

Carpety.

#LGFW
http://twitpic.com/4f0r4b     
    
    
    Fashion Week, day three.

Shiny.

#LGFW
http://twitpic.com/4fct87     
    
    
    My banana just squished instead of peeled. This is the worst thing that's happened. Ever. To me. Regarding peeling. Of bananas.    
    
    
    It's just sitting there all smug and thrwarty-like. Fucking banana. You're just prolonging the inevitable. I'm going 24 on your ass...    
    
    
    Mr. Banana, let me show you all the knives and other implements I own... then I'm going to slice open an orange and make you watch.    
    
    
    I dissected my banana in front of all the other bananas, in case another one wants to be a hero. Then I drowned it in milk and Rice Krispies    
    
    
    I need to stop watching TV an hour before I eat. Dinner just got a little too intense.    
    
    
    I can't wait until I'm old enough to rock beige velcro orthotic runners with a brown suit. 

You, strange old dude, are my hero.    
    
    
    Fashion Week, day four.

Fuzzy.

#LGFW
http://twitpic.com/4fr3rv     
    
    
    Being a bar of soap would suck.    
    
    
    Drinking with a group of twenty year olds doesn't make me feel old; it makes me feel smart.    
    
    
    [sniffle]. I'm sick. And the sheer volume of mucous I can produce in a 24 hour period terrifies me. Where does this stuff keep coming from?    
    
    
    Swine Flu paranoia benefit: if you cough in a crowd, it parts like the Red Sea - very handy when you're in a hurry.    
    
    
    Ah gravity, thou art a heartless bitch.    
    
    
    My mom just asked me what 'the webnets' were. 

So, to recap: my mom's more ironically cool than your mom.    
    
    
    I had some very productive business meetings today. And by business meetings, I mean I ordered some Madballs online.    
    
    
    Why is there a bear on my peanut butter and honey, but not my bread? WTF? Yogi liked sandawiches. Though I gather he's not the average bear.    
    
    
    This is bullshit. When I'm in charge, rocket-powered products will be cheap and plentiful.    
    
    
    Hello saucy little vixen; my outfit whispers come hither, but my social ineptitude screams Eeep! A girl! 

Chicks dig mixed signals, right?    
    
    
    The Dutch sure do make a mean cheese.    
    
    
    Eat anything and everything, nap for a few months, then wake to nice weather and mating. 

Squirrels have it all figured out.    
    
    
    Weekly ego boost: You, my dear, are wonderful. If you weren't imaginary intertubes folk, I'd totally make an awkward pass at you. [Hugs!]    
    
    
    How come Yogi had a tie and collar, but no shirt?

And yes, that's the only Yogi-related inaccuracy I have a problem with.    
    
    
    If anything, wouldn't a horse shoe in your bum be a sign that you're not lucky?    
    
    
    My Skittles and M&M bowls got mixed together. Now I'm stuck eating S&Ms. I should be upset, but I kind of like that I don't like it.    
    
    
    Wow. Escalators don't fuck around.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Along with women and respect, I can now add cable to the list of things I don't get. Get it together, Rogers. Soon. I need this. [Sigh].    
    
    
    The only thing that makes me feel older than plucking grey nose hair is being comfortable talking about plucking grey nose hair.    
    
    
    I think my Rice Krispies are broken. All I'm getting is static; where's the snap? The crackle? The pop?    
    
    
    Great meeting, middle manager. But how do you expect me to expect the unexpected? If I expect it, doesn't that mean it's NOT unexpected?    
    
    
    I don't get invited to a lot of team meetings.    
    
    
    I'm not getting drunk and gorging on pizza. I'm carb loading for a marathon. Her: You signed up for a marathon? Me: One step at a time...    
    
    
    The hamburglar got a bad wrap. I think it was Grimace. I mean, just look at him; he's an anthropomorphized purple blob! There is no justice.    
    
    
    Hi Team,
Lamest. Orgy. Ever.
Cheers,
Pete

I kick ass at writing meeting recap emails.    
    
    
    Show me how innovative you are by ripping off someone else... does Bell not realize that we get Apple ads in Canada? Great job, guys!    
    
    
    Hiya tech support! My internet connection is down. Her: Have you visited our online support centre? Me: Have we dated?    
    
    
    @chesebrough_j That IS spooky. No one ever relates to me – it's sort of my 'thing'.    
    
    
    I wish they actually made hero cookies.    
    
    
    Quitting smoking is the quickest way to realize that everyone around you is a complete asshole.    
    
    
    Argh. Fine. I promise to stop referring to the Royal Wedding as cat lady porn.

#RoyalWedding    
    
    
    How much paranoia is too much? Her: I think any amount is unhealthy. Me: Really? Hmm... why would you say that? Her: [profanity].    
    
    
        
    
    
    Risky behaviour is the very best kind of behaviour.    
    
    
    Fruity Pebbles taste like neither fruit nor pebbles. WTF?    
    
    
    If they can get away with calling a product something it isn't, so can I – henceforth I shall be known as "handsome competent adult".    
    
    
    Him: I'm glad they got Bin Laden. It's a great day for democracy.
Me: Sure. Did you vote yet?
Him: I'm not going to bother.

#osama #vote    
    
    
    My duster tastes funny.    
    
    
    These days, surprisingly few of my wild goose chases involve wild geese. Perhaps this means I'm maturing?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Realizing the motorcycling season is over is sort of like finding out a relationship has run its course – except without the sense of relief    
    
    
    GREAT hair day – righteous moss such as this ought not be cooped up in a studio, however leaving would require pants. This one's a tuffy...    
    
    
    Maybe I'll just stand near a window and hope someone notices...    
    
    
    I don't think my window plan worked; the neighbors seem more interested in my lack of pants than my good hair day. Weirdos.    
    
    
    @MoreCoffeePls Pantsless videoconference... perfect! 

If more technology means less clothes, will I eventually get to ride a jetpack naked?    
    
    
    I totally take back all those times I didn't want to nap when I was younger.    
    
    
    If I sleep all day and wake up at happy hour, it's socially acceptable to put gin in my cereal, right?    
    
    
    Oranges become marmalade while raspberries become plain old jam? Come on, raspberry. Aim a little higher; you're better than this.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Okay, I lied. I'm totally ready to eat mock hot dogs for breakfast – have been for years. I wish I had some jam for this hot dog...    
    
    
    @jinooky I couldn't do it. The starch-to-wiener-meat ratio is all screwy without a bun...    
    
    
    Fine, telling anyone who'll listen I want to make a My Pet Monster movie is not the same as "being in talks" to make a movie. Dream killer.    
    
    
    Times Square – everything that's right and wrong with America condensed into one square block. #NYC http://twitpic.com/4waqsf    
    
    
    @OwenMorgan7 Thanks!    
    
    
    I love Wal-mart; it's the one place on earth I can buy discount tube socks, gummi bears and still be considered comparatively attractive.    
    
    
    If you've ever bought new clothes to avoid doing laundry, you might be a bachelor.    
    
    
    I need a new camera – this one makes me look fat.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Accidentally using the wrong toothbrush is a lot like eating a urinal cake; gross, but minty.    
    
    
    I didn't hump the company's leg either - where's my treat?    
    
    
        
    
    
    I wish I knew how to moonwalk. Granted, it doesn't come up that often, but I bet it would if I knew how.    
    
    
    I respect your willingness to stay hip by wearing skinny jeans. Shame about that ass, though.    
    
    
    Did the Carmen San Diego empire shut down, or is it just really well hidden?    
    
    
    A day and a half before Christmas and I haven't started shopping. I am drunk, though. So that's something...    
    
    
    Why isn't there a light in this thing? I think my freezer is hiding something.    
    
    
    I think I just got mind raped. Also, "mind raped" is now a thing.    
    
    
        
    
    
    What kills parrots? 
Actually if it's not gin, never mind – we're all good.    
    
    
    I don't think it's fair that the pole gets credit; the girls do all the dancing.    
    
    
    Ankle boot muffin top is the very saddest muffin top of them all.    
    
    
    Man, I wish I had some nerf right now.    
    
    
    Is there a way to show sarcasm in email without emoticons? Me: Like... punctuation? Her: Are you being sarcastic? Me: We'll never know.    
    
    
    @MissBrittanyDow Thanks – it was nice shooting alongside you, too!    
    
    
    Er, no. I totally meant to put my shirt on backwards. Chicks dig rebels, right? [sigh].    
    
    
    Happy New Year!

My New Year's resolution is not to make any New Year's resolutions... dammit... I broke that one quicker than usual.    
    
    
    I got a cramp during my post-run stretch. I think I may have been doing it backwards.    
    
    
    iPod, from now on you're staying home. My sexy coffee shop chair dance seems to be attracting the wrong crowd.    
    
    
    What the hell was Waldo involved in that required such a deft ability to conceal himself in plain sight?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Kids aren't legally people, right? I mean, if one got seriously injured by say... a snowball? Listen, I need a place to stay for a while.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Yeah, I've been told I can be intimidating. Is it the cape? It's the cape, isn't it?    
    
    
    @dropthefish Indeed I did, though all I remember is the giant eyelashes.    
    
    
    @melissadavis SNAP!    
    
    
    Hot date tonight! At Tim Horton's. With my buddies. Who are dudes. That still counts, right? I really don't remember.    
    
    
    Motorcycling is one if the few activities that makes wearing leather pants and a helmet seem cool.    
    
    
    Never trust a bald barber.    
    
    
    GAWF! Burrito juice in my eye. I'm not going to say how – chicks dig an air of mystery, right?    
    
    
    @mdirocco Thanks!    
    
    
    Well, it took a lot of procrastination, but I finally managed to finish the new website – WOOT! 

http://studiolit.com    
    
    
    I'm not fluent in Portuguese, but from what I gather, my neighbours are. And hate each other.    
    
    
    There's a finite amount of time one can use an electric razor in the bathroom before roommates start asking questions.    
    
    
    Sashay, sashay, pivot, pause... *jazz hands*!

Best meeting entrance. Ever.    
    
    
    Approaching random Body Shop customers and whispering "It puts the lotion on it's skin" is not funny. Apparently. I hate the mall.    
    
    
    Today I learned NEVER to refer to management as "the olds". In a meeting. With the management. #oops    
    
    
    This is my new motorbike. 
It is a tad rad.

 http://twitpic.com/5827nb     
    
    
    This is an artist's rendering of me on my new motorbike.

 http://twitpic.com/58284y     
    
    
    I'm beginning to accept that I may never be a professional gangster rapper.    
    
    
    Ever download a recipe, waste an hour trying to make that recipe, and then find yourself asking why the fuck you didn't just order a pizza?    
    
    
    Today I learned that while baking impresses women, attempted baking does not.    
    
    
    I see you complaining, but all I can hear is a muffled trumpet.    
    
    
    The older I get, the more I realize adulthood is just childhood without the need to ask permission.

Also, I had pudding for breakfast.    
    
    
    Hipster chick: A pithy, profanity-laden critique of the relative merits of a screw top wine doesn't make you sound as classy as you think.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm not saying I deserve an award for cleaning my studio. I'm saying I would like one.    
    
    
    Who's winning the hockey match?
Her: Game. It's a game.
Me: I know, but people seem to take it seriously.
#Canucks    
    
    
    Who's your team?
Me: Uh... Cincinnati?
Her: The 'C' stands for 'Canucks'.
Me: Oh... Just kidding. I'm rooting for Brooklyn.
Her: (profanity)    
    
    
    What do you call bad kerning? 
Keming! 

That kills at design conferences.    
    
    
    Walk of shame be damned. Henceforth, we shall refer to it only as the march of glory.    
    
    
    @steviepeters Stride of pride: brilliant!    
    
    
    Skipping is an underutilized mode of transport.    
    
    
    Huh? People "make" their beds? What does that even mean? Like, from scratch? Every night?    
    
    
    I think I'll help those cute girls by staring at them. Then they can say "what's up with that creepy dude" when the conversation slows.    
    
    
    @unreuly Finally, some recognition. [hugs!]    
    
    
    Innis & Gunn ice cream float for dinner. And they said I'd never amount to anything. Pfft.
#LivingTheDream    
    
    
    That molotov guy sure makes a funny tasting cocktail.    
    
    
    I'm not abandoning my theory until it's been thoroughly tested. Maybe there's a particular *flavour* of alcohol that makes you rich.    
    
    
    Dating is a lot like cooking, in that all my attempts result in minor burns and epic failure.    
    
    
    Time well spent. Now I can add 'able to endure half-assed, superfluous PowerPoint presentations" to my resume skills list.    
    
    
    Oh sweetie, it's not an "apéritif" if you're pairing it with pizza, pickles and twinkies. It's pre-drinking. Good hustle, though.    
    
    
    God I hate my arms, I hope they burn and die... wait.    
    
    
    Yeah, I've been seeing this blonde chick. I don't think it'll work out.
Her: Bummer. What's her name?
Me: God, you sound like her.    
    
    
    I really need to make a friend named Huckleberry.    
    
    
    W00T! We won an award! Thanks @DesignEdgemag for a fun evening. Glad I went.    
    
    
    How will I know it's you? Me: look for the six year old boy trapped inside a twelve year old girl's body. Her: Er... oh.  She won't show.    
    
    
    I didn't "moon" you. I gave you a chance to take a photo of my ass and make a fortune selling it to TMZ when I'm famous. So, you're welcome.    
    
    
    Happy Monday, Twitter! My weekend was an epic triumph of liquor over experience. I hope yours was as successful.    
    
    
    I eat raw meat, but only on rare occasions.    
    
    
    Evidently, a business meeting isn't the ideal time to discuss one's navel, but in my defense, there's some neat stuff going on down there.    
    
    
    Whoever said there's no such thing as a stupid question probably isn't attending the same meetings as me.    
    
    
    @Chantellecutal Indeed I am. Recent-ish work is on my website: www.studiolit.com    
    
    
    You try to give out some leftover candy to a few random kids, and not even a thank-you? Folks just don't appreciate kindness these days.    
    
    
    Socks wedged in the lint trap. My ninja undies were with them. Coincidence? Or attempted corpse disposal after drowning them in the wash?    
    
    
    Smurfette had it going on.    
    
    
    Me: So, what are your thoughts on US foreign policy?
Her: BWHAAALRGH!

My 10 month-old niece. More articulate than most of my dates. [sigh].    
    
    
    Follow Friday; is that still what the kids are calling it? Meh. @FinalFashion @Twot @AmyVerner @unreuly @CMYKinky @GeekiGirl #FF    
    
    
    Egad! I think I'm developing a penchant for intelligent women – quick, someone tell an off-colour midget joke to make sure I'm not maturing!    
    
    
    Happy Valentine's Day! 

I heart you forever and ever, imaginary intertubes folks. Hugs!    
    
    
    Mingling at a bar on Valentine's Day is a little like going hunting with a rocket-launcher; fun, but not very sporting.    
    
    
    Turns out interpretive dance is frowned upon as a business presentation technique. Also, no one appreciates a flawless pas de chat anymore.    
    
    
    My turtle's famous! Special thanks to @AmyVerner and @Toronto_Life – http://tinyurl.com/yg5u8mj    
    
    
    To clarify – "my turtle" is not a euphemism. God, it'd be a good one though...    
    
    
    You're a broker; is investing in my future insider trading? Her: I wouldn't recommend you as a long term investment. Me: Wow. You're good.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Headline: "There Were No Losers At The Westminster Dog Show". 

I beg to differ.    
    
    
    Robot monkey, or monkey-powered robot? Discuss.    
    
    
    I feel lazy today. I'm going to chase that feeling. With lunch beer.    
    
    
    FYI, today I'll be responding with "well played, Sir" regardless of what you say, because everyone needs a win sometimes.    
    
    
    A water-skiing elephant. Yes.

 http://twitpic.com/14exbo    
    
    
        
    
    
    In Soviet Russia, puck shoots you.    
    
    
    @Alison_Potstra Awww... Hugs!    
    
    
    @paiiige Agreed; if you're wearing sequins, you're not playing a sport.    
    
    
    If anyone asks, we let the Americans win because they're our guests, and it's the polite thing to do.    
    
    
    I bet unicorn steak tastes like cinnamon buns.    
    
    
    Of course I'm wearing a my little pony shirt to a client meeting. How else will they know I'm awesome?    
    
    
    Sitting in a sports bar with 5 guys, waiting for olympic hockey to start is the wrong time to order a blue raspberry martini. Evidently.    
    
    
    Nothing bad ever gets served in a cone. #DeepThoughts    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    What's the opposite of a freckle?    
    
    
    Bachelor innovation no. 27: peanut butter in coffee – it's easy, means less shopping and serves as a handy meal replacement. You're welcome.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I was told I don't share my feelings often enough. So, here: I love you, Internet... Though mainly for the sex stuff.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Okay America, let's get this out of the way. No, we don't really have sexy mounties and giant beavers. And we're sorry about Nickelback.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Oh, I get it. Novelty hair colours tell the world you're a badass hipster that thinks outside the box. Edgy.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I wish my alarm clock wasn't so assertive. How can something shaped like Snoopy be such a pushy little bastard? Grrr...    
    
    
    "I'll Twitter you". I love the way dads speak.

I would have gone with "I'll social your media", but I'm not a parent.    
    
    
    A logo is a brand in the same way a belch is an aria.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Okay, fine. My camera and I will take responsibility for adding ten pounds. How do you explain the other 195?    
    
    
    Flirting at the grocery store. Shopping says I'm responsible. My selection of trail mix, jerky and gummi bears says I'm single. 

Nailed it!    
    
    
    Are you subversively mocking me, or are you actually enjoying yourself? Her: You don't date a lot, do you? Me: How does everyone know that?    
    
    
    Drinks served in bucket-form are not 'whimsical'.    
    
    
    Yes, I have inadequacies, but I earn points for the sheer quantity and effortlessness with which I acquire them, right? No, huh. Nerts.    
    
    
    