I'm glad you all enjoyed seeing us on the Tonight show tonight! Or at least the East coast folks at this point ;) thanks for the love!    
    
    
    Good Morning World!    
    
    
    @Auntie2010Grad happy birthday!    
    
    
    Come one, Come All! #BOBBYCHURCH “@timothybloom: This will be a lovers affair, come with love! pic.twitter.com/RWr4DaZutV”    
    
    
    @mikeybzwifey uh oh! Giggles?    
    
    
    #TourLife pic.twitter.com/NU17iuFTzg    
    
    
    Happy Friday to ya!    
    
    
    @NIENIE69 sure no prob    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 HA!    
    
    
    Nothing like a lil Sam Cooke to put ya in a good mood- #legend    
    
    
    U rock! “@NIENIE69: @TheRealJoshPaul  just got my tickets for Bobby church.....and Daughty tomorrow. What a great weekend to be me ...lol”    
    
    
    Music, style, food, love, and life should never be bland. Mix it up, and fear not. Life is short, make sure you make the most of it. #truth    
    
    
    Bland is such a boring word ;)    
    
    
    @kristancfan yes but 'Chores' you have to do. 'Bland' you dont    
    
    
    @EvanSeinfeld DAMN BRO!!!    
    
    
    @kristancfan never :)    
    
    
    I watched a really cool documentary on a tour that @MumfordAndSons did w a bunch of other cool bands,they traveled by train!looked like fun!    
    
    
    Casino Morongo, here I come!    
    
    
    TRAFFIC....SUCKS!!! So it's nap time :) #vanrides pic.twitter.com/X6agXvTmy6    
    
    
    @32pinkbutterfly thank u!!    
    
    
    Thanks to all that came out tonight at Morongo Casino! It was fun! However... I did lose some $$$$$    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @Bootsy_Collins !!! #legend    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 :)!    
    
    
    RIP Lou Reed-    
    
    
    It's an early one today, good morning!    
    
    
    HOME!!    
    
    
    Up early today for no apparent reason, just... Up! #teamnosleep    
    
    
    @MrsG37 nope, I'm up solo. Like Han Solo    
    
    
    @TRitter429 I cannot make the walls rumble just quite yet. I must wait until at least sunrise ;) #morningbass    
    
    
    Come Shake a tail feather with us Nov 17 at the Troubadour in Hollywood! @timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker @heapsnheaps #BOBBYCHURCH    
    
    
    @DaughtrySuit happy bday to ya    
    
    
    @InaAlagic @DaughtrySuit Annnd a very Happy Bday to you too!    
    
    
    This new @arcadefire record is FIRE!! #Reflektor    
    
    
    Happy Halloween! Be safe out there!    
    
    
    @RiveraBarb in character ;) #dedicated    
    
    
    @JaimeRKOFan how bout an early Happy Bday to ya!    
    
    
    Good morning!    
    
    
    I changed my image a lil for Halloween- pic.twitter.com/Cq6QCAf2d9    
    
    
    The strange thing is, I actually had those clothes somewhere deep in the depths of my closet! #NerdAtHeart?    
    
    
    I'm wondering what the cut off age for trick or treating is? 14? 15? 16? Exceptions can be made w a good costume, but no costume? No candy!    
    
    
    I saw teenagers out there hoarding, w no costume and just a plastic bag in their hands! Ya gotta put in some effort kids!    
    
    
    @Feral_Girl naked girls??    
    
    
    @BriannaNegrete_ I agree w that :)    
    
    
    @Michelles0107 nice!    
    
    
    I LOVE the Holiday Season :) I get into it. I mean, I Really Really get into it!    
    
    
    Have a funky Friday :) listen to somethin that makes your booty shake. Try 'Lickin Stick' by the great James Brown    
    
    
    @NewRockHammer @Drumzilla70 @fher1286 good times!    
    
    
    I've just suffered a serious pain in my ass dealing with phone issues....    
    
    
    @NewRockHammer home yes, there no. Just saw your pic    
    
    
    Good morning to you :)    
    
    
    I've got an entire store to myself :) I like to call this, 'my' store pic.twitter.com/PGMjIqqrJu    
    
    
    These have taken me from coast to coast, and country to country- I love my Chucks #converse pic.twitter.com/Od2RNteMiu    
    
    
    @LyndseyROCK1005 slip on's?! For real?!    
    
    
    @LyndseyROCK1005 :)    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 nice, or just the steppers :)    
    
    
    @kristancfan I had a few choices.1)Stare at the ceiling in the dark2)wander around the house in the dark3)roll to Starbucks    
    
    
    @NewRockHammer let's go!    
    
    
    Getting ready for a PARRRRRTAY! pic.twitter.com/1dmUMCfphv    
    
    
    #saloonparty pic.twitter.com/WurANV34rh    
    
    
    It's a good day :) #blueskies #coffee pic.twitter.com/XKU4QWw89u    
    
    
    NOV 17 Come see Me, @timothybloom, @Matthewrholmes, and @pbesecker- BOBBY CHURCH! At the Troubadour in Hollywood!! #music    
    
    
    Buongiorno my friends, early to bed- early to rise I suppose. I fell asleep at a wild n crazy 7:45 pm last night. #oldmanlivin    
    
    
    Wow! Read that Dave Grohl will be producing stuff in the new Zac Brown album. That should be crazy! Looking forward to it -    
    
    
    @TamsterRN life is grand :)    
    
    
    Beautiful! “@Discovery: What percent of Alaska is covered in glaciers? http://bit.ly/1a3hFM1  pic.twitter.com/UN3lQQCCqU”    
    
    
    Look at that face! #cheese pic.twitter.com/D6WgWSkyTk    
    
    
    BOBBY CHURCH LIVE!! Come see us!@timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker Nov 17! #MustSee #music #BobbyChurch pic.twitter.com/jzL3ReMZeA    
    
    
    Yes, what he said “@JoelMadden: Be yourself”    
    
    
    First time this year I get to use this! It's a chilly one out there tonight. #cozy #relaxing pic.twitter.com/HN6hqjsc8I    
    
    
    @ThisDudeRiots ha! OG!    
    
    
    @ThisDudeRiots great! Hope you're well!    
    
    
    Tattoo Day mañana w my boy @ZoOmBie_NatiOn !    
    
    
    @themerchdude hmmm... Not sure I understood the sarcasm either    
    
    
    @themerchdude yeah I gotcha! I'm good! Workin, livin, lovin etc etc. how u doin    
    
    
    @themerchdude nice, for sure. Be safe out there!    
    
    
    I'm gonna enjoy the fire, and just chill for once. Have a pleasant and happy evening my friends. #goodnight    
    
    
    Tattoo time!    
    
    
    Work in progress w @ZoOmBie_NatiOn -#tattoo pic.twitter.com/HOJiVIVJOa    
    
    
    Top O' the Mornin to ya!    
    
    
    I'm off to NY today for work, early early mornings. Tattoo turned out cool, not quite finished with the piece but I like it!    
    
    
    “@mrscantz: I can't rest” I feel u    
    
    
    I'm always in awe of the beauty of  sunrise - #goodmorning pic.twitter.com/qAhiH8yJu2    
    
    
    New York Bound, see ya soon! #coldweather pic.twitter.com/YcO2Cgg5vU    
    
    
    @elviofernandes yeah... I couldn't be seen with broken glasses out in the public now could 'eye'- oh wait... Too late    
    
    
    #BOBBYCHURCH Video coming soon!!!#music #ChurchOnTheMove    
    
    
    Saw ya sooN NYC!    
    
    
    Mile High T-Party! Let's do this #WifiInTheSky    
    
    
    @SheaOakes didn't know there was one    
    
    
    @jma51 we shoot next week!    
    
    
    @USMarineMom29 you'll find out soon!    
    
    
    @theKLK flight is pretty tame so far    
    
    
    @mer1217 great!    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 whoooo hoooo! Wow! Almost 10,000 people put up w my silliness?!!    
    
    
    @reet_petite I'm a music guy.I'll write 1,000 songs for someone else to put their thoughts and melody onto.I inspire- and make yo ass shake    
    
    
    @rhodygrl86 spend time w my fam :)    
    
    
    @rhodygrl86 all of the above. :)    
    
    
    Must. Stay. Hydrated. #flights pic.twitter.com/burKZRpvFV    
    
    
    @JaimeRKOFan no thoughts, just play    
    
    
    I was invited to a Renaissance Fair this weekend...I'm somewhat frightened to go! #pirates #wenches #whiskey #peasants #steed    
    
    
    @Chelsi_Smith yes, #bigassturkeylegs    
    
    
    While I'm up here at  25,000 feet trying to amuse myself,id like 2 follow some more people here on twitter!Who wants a follow from Ol JP?    
    
    
    @SheaOakes I try, I try    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 @kellieprime Instagram I actually have to put in the names and look for people! It's easier here :)    
    
    
    @Kim_A1 thanks!    
    
    
    @christine_estes meeting Stevie Wonder!    
    
    
    Rest time, chat soon!    
    
    
    Hello NYC!    
    
    
    Check out my good friends book!  “@ellefsondavid: More book signings coming up
Megadeth @megadeth #mylifewithdeth http://fb.me/1QfDBmqwx ”    
    
    
    @ellefsondavid @Megadeth no prob bro, proud of u!    
    
    
    Perfect!“@kelliepickler: My date to the #CMAawards #JackDaniels ;) pic.twitter.com/ibYUtecxEX”    
    
    
    Good Mornin!    
    
    
    AWESOME!! “@RollingStone: Dave Grohl jammed with the Zac Brown Band last night at the #CMAs. Watch: http://rol.st/1bcfjJT ”    
    
    
    @FairyLittle93 it's all music to me    
    
    
    @Krystle_Hill1 funny u should say that! ;)    
    
    
    Back home today! Quick lil trip!    
    
    
    #LookingUp pic.twitter.com/2cl9tYr5PX    
    
    
    Stay Positive & Stay Happy my friends #FoodForThought :) pic.twitter.com/Ty5mmLOHbs    
    
    
    @itsadrock yep, hip:) Bobby Church the 17th at the Troub! Come thru!    
    
    
    THIS is a DOPE Guitar!!!!! pic.twitter.com/qRs4JVfFLG    
    
    
    @Plemonspfs oh it's not mine! I just like it!!    
    
    
    @itsadrock NOV. Next week,Sunday    
    
    
    @missktbspa thank u! Home for a day or two, relaxing :) enjoy your day    
    
    
    “@Kninjaplease: It's gonna be that kind of day... pic.twitter.com/abzowBU0cb”oh damn... Be careful    
    
    
    @Cheralyn6 @krbronson @heapsnheaps @theTroubadour see ya soon!    
    
    
    Have a Happy Friday!    
    
    
    “@YO_RANDYJACKSON: #fbf to when I was a model pic.twitter.com/fmqdZBvEGu” Stud!    
    
    
    @DamienFahey haaaaaaaaaa!    
    
    
    BOBBY CHURCH LIVE!!! Come see us Nov 17th @theTroubadour @timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker #SOUL #RockNRoll pic.twitter.com/2RccDz9o4F    
    
    
    Have ya ever listened 2 a complete strangers story 4 longer than 10 min, thought 2 yourself u r full o' sh!t?!#idid pic.twitter.com/lw3nLSj7V0    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 :)!    
    
    
    “@BonJulie1: @TRitter429 @TheRealJoshPaul $200 flight to LA?!?!!! That's cheaper than mine!! DO IT TRACY!! :)”yeah!    
    
    
    @TheOrlandoJones funny! Enjoy the weekend, and don't forget about that moonshine!!    
    
    
    @caityybabyy536 :)    
    
    
    @gestes84 nice! Part 2 comin soon    
    
    
    Praying for my friends in the Philippines-Weather the Storm, my thoughts and prayers are with you all.    
    
    
    Shooting a #BobbyChurch video one week from today! I'm excited!!!!    
    
    
    @LaurHof11 yep, when ya see it ;)    
    
    
    BOBBY CHURCH LIVE!!! Come see us Nov 17th @theTroubadour @timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker #SOUL #RockNRoll pic.twitter.com/q6jltuCZzA    
    
    
    A 6 PAC in seconds! HA! #christmasiscoming pic.twitter.com/0IPAqxlvEq    
    
    
    @TRitter429 haha! Yeah!    
    
    
    It's a beautiful day! #smile pic.twitter.com/JyayVfoigB    
    
    
    Having an early Birthday dinner for lil Josh tonight.Can't believe he's turning 17- Im extremely proud of the man he is becoming #timeflies    
    
    
    @TheRealDevinB crazy huh?!    
    
    
    @TheRealDevinB will do bro! Thanks- I'll be in la next week, let's catch up    
    
    
    @MleEarls :)!    
    
    
    @DebraCopelan oh yes! Enjoy that one!    
    
    
    @DannyCooksey thanks brotha! I will, tell the Cookseys hello!    
    
    
    “@Eleven7Music: View from the new office...not a terrible thing to stare at.  #LA pic.twitter.com/oE00OF7Hgh”gorgeous!    
    
    
    Come One, Come All!!! #RealDeal (Flyer design by Lil Josh) he knows his Dad ;) pic.twitter.com/2nhmvl3G78    
    
    
    #Wok-ano! pic.twitter.com/nS43NaVZyz    
    
    
    Good Morning World!    
    
    
    @theKLK @BonJulie1 Cheers to 10K ;)!    
    
    
    @debbgould haha cute :)    
    
    
    Come down and hang, 1 week from today! Doors open at 7:30! #BobbyChurch @timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker pic.twitter.com/CLn7zvhVpH    
    
    
    Max is in da Studio workin today! :) #Music #MusicIsLife pic.twitter.com/4HfodKHHoA    
    
    
    Words We Live By- #Love #Live pic.twitter.com/Wwuk6fgFBn    
    
    
    I'd like to take a moment to honor all who have served. Thank You! Happy Veterans Day #VeteransDay    
    
    
    Good Morning? Let's make it a great one! #crazyearlywakeupcall    
    
    
    @TRitter429 just Starbucks :) I leave mañana    
    
    
    @TRitter429 staring at the ceiling got quite mundane ;)    
    
    
    @tweetheart1982 nice!    
    
    
    @CHRIS_Daughtry @Mrsdaughtry Happy Anniversary to ya! Enjoy    
    
    
    @Macdaisy3 hangin out at home relaxin :)    
    
    
    @KAnnWilliamson aw thank you so much!    
    
    
    @CarolynMaddox11 that's great!    
    
    
    Recognize this guy? My dad happened to come across this on Yahoo tonight!:) #FerrisBuellerFunFacts @JenniferGrey pic.twitter.com/Nm6vbZaFoS    
    
    
    Look up '12 Ferris Bueller Fun Facts' from the family that actually lived there on abc news :)    
    
    
    @artydi exactly!    
    
    
    @daughtry71 it is a classic! Too bad I got cut from it!    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 well, I shot the movie ;) didn't quite end up in the final cut    
    
    
    @sweetnicolerose yeah actually :)    
    
    
    @rockphotogirl I played ferris' lil brother    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 haha, I'm always an angel! :) I honestly don't remember    
    
    
    I've had sooo many crazy experiences throughout my life & career starting from a very early age. And I'm still here kickin'! Never givin up!    
    
    
    Goodnight my friends! #BeEpic    
    
    
    Glad you got to get a preview of the new #Daughtry album! Your enthusiasm and support mean the world, thank you! #BAPTIZED    
    
    
    Now on my way to LA to begin the Bobby Church Extravaganza! See ya soon @timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker #Nov17 @theTroubadour    
    
    
    @ellefsondavid happy birthday!    
    
    
    THIS SUNDAY! #BOBBYCHURCH pic.twitter.com/d3W2CvNRQD    
    
    
    #sunshine pic.twitter.com/YfDbuoClaa    
    
    
    My Dancin Shoes #chucks #converse #BobbyChurch pic.twitter.com/9oIlAOlurZ    
    
    
    #keepitclean pic.twitter.com/0HeWkOQFlb    
    
    
    Finally relaxing for the night!    
    
    
    Good Morning friends,please help me wish lil Josh a happy 17th Birthday! I'm not there w him today, so Let's give him a big HAPPY BIRTHDAY!    
    
    
    Thanks guys, he'll see all of your tweets in a bit!    
    
    
    Lil josh says THANK YOU ALL! #birthday    
    
    
    @TheDenDolls I like it!    
    
    
    Who's goin to 'Church Sunday?Join the congregation! BOBBY CHURCH LIVE SUNDAY!Tix $8 advance $10 door @theTroubadour pic.twitter.com/HjGqhtZQt5    
    
    
    Los Angeles, it's a beautiful day :)    
    
    
    HUNGRY!! #thai #LA pic.twitter.com/OZRgeOSugO    
    
    
    Now THIS is a rock n roll bathroom #wow pic.twitter.com/Y4vzK1eAW8    
    
    
    New Holiday wear? #holidayshopping pic.twitter.com/npXK5gFkzo    
    
    
    @lovelees good Ol Target'    
    
    
    @timothybloom at work! @bobbychurchband See us live this Sunday @theTroubadour w @heapsnheaps !!#bobbychurch #Music pic.twitter.com/mIpr84yZxN    
    
    
    Watching a very cool documentary about @Charles_Bradley #awesome #funk    
    
    
    Good morning World!    
    
    
    Shootin' a #BOBBYCHURCH video today!I'm very excited!It's an amazing feeling,grabbing the bull by the horns and making things happen #proud    
    
    
    @TRitter429 we are shooting a video for our song 'We Came, We Saw'    
    
    
    @Tygart12 happy bday to u :)    
    
    
    BOBBY CHURCH FANS! If you're coming to see us @theTroubadour tomorrow we'd like to thank u tonight & have a special invitation for you!    
    
    
    If ya got tix2the Bobby Church show 2morrow@theTroubadour &would like to come visit the set of our video shoot late this evening lemme know!    
    
    
    Look what BOBBY CHURCH is drivin tonight! #musicvideo pic.twitter.com/2MDRAkXhbA    
    
    
    @CHRIS_Daughtry happy birthday to your kiddos!    
    
    
    Come to CHURCH tonight! BOBBY CHURCH! 9pm @theTroubadour #livemusic    
    
    
    @BVBShinigami @CHRIS_Daughtry looks exactly like us! :) good job and keep creating!    
    
    
    “@heapsnheaps: We are so damn excited for tonight! @theTroubadour @bobbychurchband” YES!    
    
    
    Getting Ready to SLAY!!! See ya soon! #BobbyChurch pic.twitter.com/ZihCEnZOEa    
    
    
    “@badseedrising1: Watching our good friend @TheRealJoshPaul and his band @bobbychurchband kill it!!” Thank you guys!!! You seriously rock!    
    
    
    Thank you to ALLLL that came out to support BOBBY CHURCH tonight! From near and far, people came together :) for music. And for fun!    
    
    
    #BobbyChurch pic.twitter.com/ju2d5xUMfr    
    
    
    A lil Silliness @timothybloom @pbesecker and I before #BobbyChurch show! I had a great time :) pic.twitter.com/axpRx2bc3H    
    
    
    @thedenonline @bobbychurchband aw thank u so much for comin! Love u!!    
    
    
    Good Morning World!    
    
    
    I'm here on set for @TheTalk_CBS getting ready to play some music!    
    
    
    @Dani_caca :)    
    
    
    Just finished doing @TheTalk_CBS, was fun! Very cool folks, AND I got to meet Carol Burnett!    
    
    
    AND got to meet one of my boyhood crushes @THEsaragilbert :) #goodtimes    
    
    
    “@kraddyodaddy: #hungover #monday” that means You did Sunday right! #sundayfunday    
    
    
    “@kraddyodaddy: @TheRealJoshPaul Right!?? It was a Sunday funday #jameson #foursomeinthebathroom” #WHOOPWHOOP! Hahaha, hope you're well bro!    
    
    
    @badseedrising1 @chrisbaseford you go Mason!    
    
    
    It's been a looooonnnnnng Day    
    
    
    @daughtryluv have to go! See ya soon! Thank u for comin :)    
    
    
    @1DEZIPAIGE @theTroubadour @timothybloom @pbesecker @Matthewrholmes U ROCK GIRL!    
    
    
    @kdubbb143 yeah! I'm sure we will    
    
    
    @1DEZIPAIGE :)    
    
    
    I saw this on Instagram and HAD to share it. Look at this tattoo!!!!!! The artist is AMAZING! pic.twitter.com/MCh1S3FJVP    
    
    
    Guys! #Baptized is out today! Get it! #Daughtry    
    
    
    “@LisaG_325: @TheRealJoshPaul got it!  Now waiting for some #bobbychurch😃” Yes!    
    
    
    Tonight we r doin @JimmyKimmelLive, check it out!    
    
    
    @bruceymangotham there's no 'best'. Just write when and wherever you begin to feel    
    
    
    I actually shaved today- #clean or...cleaner :) pic.twitter.com/gDcOBb21yZ    
    
    
    @JimmyKimmelLive #Daughtry pic.twitter.com/6HfMsddphZ    
    
    
    Thanks for having us @jimmykimmel, and thank u to all that came out to all of the shows this week!    
    
    
    Just saw another great tattoo via Instagram, done by @christianmarektattoo SICK Work! #tattoo pic.twitter.com/ru2FTfVOiU    
    
    
    @TRitter429 no, not for that one    
    
    
    Airplane #selfie- I'm only half awake on this one, it's been a long week! I'm NY bound :) pic.twitter.com/WBYcKEL7LG    
    
    
    @theKLK something like That!    
    
    
    Yep, I Spy @elviofernandes tpartying. In deep concentration :) pic.twitter.com/E4mQrLg5vF    
    
    
    @sarahcolonna but did u sing along?    
    
    
    @lisag325 haha :)    
    
    
    @rockphotogirl I was def a supporter ;)    
    
    
    For this years JP Christmas album,I may write a song called 'Waiting For Santa Clause'whatcha think. Cover ideas ;)! pic.twitter.com/sbkBezbtQ1    
    
    
    This airplane boredom is Makin me silly :) #funphotos    
    
    
    The flight attendant just walked by me and said, wow, you must be a banker- with all of those tattoos! I said no, a politician :)    
    
    
    @sarahcolonna ohhhhh come on Sarah, u don't gotta lie to kick it;)    
    
    
    @AshleyRam87 @elviofernandes ok, we'll make it a bigger party    
    
    
    @DonnieCanDEWMe @amym213 u better text her back....    
    
    
    TPARTY MMMMKKK!    
    
    
    @elviofernandes @rockphotogirl yes, it was really quite extensive and exhausting. I actually list 37 pounds during that    
    
    
    @Candiceexo_ my day is going and going and going on and on like that damn rabbit in the battery commercials. But in a good way :)    
    
    
    @julynda22 lakers    
    
    
    @cleothetiger @elviofernandes hopefully I'll be home watching festivities on tv    
    
    
    @theKLK aw, I'll be out at some point!    
    
    
    @Tarheel_in_SC ? Not sure    
    
    
    @MrsG37 as soon as I get some time, for sure    
    
    
    @jjcat73 @bobbychurchband hopefully soon, we r def Makin moves :)    
    
    
    @elviofernandes @shell1377 HA!!    
    
    
    @elviofernandes @kellieprime no fair, I missed that one    
    
    
    @njdaughtrygirl it's a wonderful life and a Christmas Story    
    
    
    @nkotbgal21 both ;)    
    
    
    @TRitter429 as soon as I get 48 hours to record it :)    
    
    
    @amym213 I won't be at that show. Hi btw    
    
    
    @USMarineMom29 it's being worked on, it's gotta be done right!    
    
    
    @njdaughtrygirl @elviofernandes 1)for a In n Out burger to just appear in front of me right now 2)to keep the weather a calm cool 72 degrees    
    
    
    @njdaughtrygirl @elviofernandes 3) compassion and love be ingrained in DNA in all humans    
    
    
    @havetosmile hmmmm..? Google?    
    
    
    @Blenda73 I was 18, my sons name    
    
    
    @Lyfe_Rox @elviofernandes in 1980 I was still wearing diapers! Well maybe....    
    
    
    @elviofernandes @shell1377 u gotta earn the title of 'Selfie B Hawkins'    
    
    
    @njdaughtrygirl a live shrimp    
    
    
    @JustJenNiffer hmmmm.... Not sure I believe in luck    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 I was 5 and played an outdoor festival w my grandpa    
    
    
    @Tarheel_in_SC no    
    
    
    @JustJenNiffer @elviofernandes bus!    
    
    
    @Bratty31 I sing a little bit, not my fav thing to do    
    
    
    I'm gonna get back to my plane ride guys n gals- have a great evening!    
    
    
    @elviofernandes @shell1377 true story :) or Selfina Gomez    
    
    
    @julynda22 @elviofernandes home w my family. That's who I choose    
    
    
    @davidjschuler haha, yeah man, I keep hearing that!    
    
    
    Good morning NY! pic.twitter.com/Zd73hlZEQb    
    
    
    @meliamaccarone you're welcome!    
    
    
    Just took a refreshing walk around NYC, brisk but nice. It's beginning to feel a lot like Christmas :)    
    
    
    @MaxDaughtryFan no, just Chris I believe    
    
    
    @alycou22 no, sorry dear :)    
    
    
    Well.... Another one down...I just can't keep glasses alive!!! #RIP pic.twitter.com/fGF61iWUah    
    
    
    @AudraNucc backpack dropped on em    
    
    
    @YazFerris happy bday!    
    
    
    Done w work for the day, now my travel day begins. #home    
    
    
    @Pookeejcavobass the good Ol days!    
    
    
    I'm sure that I'll be TPartying  it up on these flights, get ready :) #youreinvited    
    
    
    @Pookeejcavobass @bobbychurchband for sure my bro! Happy Thanksgiving to u (early)!    
    
    
    @amym213 cute!    
    
    
    I have a lot of patience, but I hate waiting. Make sense?    
    
    
    We'll chat once I get up in the air- :) #TGIFQnA    
    
    
    @ClovisCDJR comin home!    
    
    
    Look who moved in next door:) #steely #planes #HappyFriday pic.twitter.com/tG6s51howC    
    
    
    Lets do this, #TGIFQnA TPARTY! From above, 35,000 feet!    
    
    
    @mitziruff my answer was Imagine, Overjoyed by Stevie    
    
    
    @Miss_Andi enormous consumption of homemade food, and love from loved ones :)    
    
    
    @kellieprime he's great, gettin big    
    
    
    @shell1377 continued health and happiness. And, coffee :)    
    
    
    @dionne2015 not quite sure about legions of fans, but once in a while someone will come up and say hello    
    
    
    @ShauniMcTaggart Always!    
    
    
    @mtsbpc I won't be at that one, but have fun!    
    
    
    @Blenda73 I really want to go to Thailand. I've never been    
    
    
    @LovingDaughtry8 what's that?? ;)    
    
    
    @Stephthekid50 shout out!!!!!    
    
    
    @TRitter429 lately, yea    
    
    
    @Tanning_Girl grrrreat    
    
    
    @darcylynn I'm a huge fan of mashed potatoes, love me love em    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 @bobbychurchband now THAT I can answer, I love a song @timothybloom  and I wrote called The Enemy. it hits home    
    
    
    @daughtry71 awesome! Have fun!    
    
    
    @OstiChris hey!!    
    
    
    @Diver43 I completely agree! #PARTY!!    
    
    
    @alycou22 haha, I honestly have no clue. Maybe 4 or 5?    
    
    
    @Michelles0107 soon I hope, I gotta book some stuff! Request us!    
    
    
    Let me ask YOU a question, who's havin FUN on this glorious Friday?!    
    
    
    @Kim_A1 as soon as we finish editing, you'll see it!    
    
    
    @TheJennzilla thank u    
    
    
    @songkat haha, bed head    
    
    
    @shell1377 @Pink yeah, I love @pink    
    
    
    @TRitter429 make it extraordinary    
    
    
    For those who ask what my fav tune is on the #baptized album, I'm not quite sure which is my favorite yet. Still listening & sifting thru :)    
    
    
    @sbbrooksie that's e-z, hello    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 haha no prob not!    
    
    
    @menacoll22 everyday is my favorite day. Everyday is a new adventure    
    
    
    @dionne2015 actually steely is attempting to watch the movie that's playing wout headphones    
    
    
    @johnny_tt man, I'd love to! Gotta figure it out    
    
    
    @JodiRacanati good job!    
    
    
    @crystald411 why thank u :)    
    
    
    @HoldinMyHorsies not quite yet    
    
    
    Who do u think I should follow on this here twitter thang? Anyone fantastic and interesting? Someone you know I'd love?    
    
    
    @HoldinMyHorsies @BonJulie1 @ladyvalerie811 it's honest, real music, that will make you shall dat ass    
    
    
    @planetmummel I like a few teams, obviously my local teams- @lakers @Dodgers @chargers    
    
    
    @Kkaa2213 haha, I don't get thru my timeline very often, but I try    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 I have no clue what else to say in response to that. Except, sorry you're disappointed?    
    
    
    @La_La_05 who's on first?! ?    
    
    
    @theKLK no what's on third!    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 no it was a reply that didn't go thru!    
    
    
    'Sorry' was a reply to a comment :)    
    
    
    I cannot wait to get home!    
    
    
    Enjoy your Friday my friends, make it great!    
    
    
    @HoldinMyHorsies there is no dog house. All there is is opinions and individual lives :)    
    
    
    I saw @RevoltTV the other day, was cool! Actually played videos! Thank u @iamdiddy    
    
    
    I want to record @bobbychurchband tracks in Bass Lake, CA, Miami, and London! Those spots inspire me #inspiration #magic    
    
    
    @TRitter429 only if it's with Prince!!    
    
    
    One flight down, only one to go!    
    
    
    D-E-L-A-Y-E-D.......    
    
    
    @Krystle_Hill1 nah, can't drink tonight, gotta be superDad    
    
    
    @Krystle_Hill1 stuck in LA in a tiny commuter terminal- for 2 hours    
    
    
    @xCHRISFx that's the bad thing! NO STARBUX    
    
    
    This is getting ridiculous... Now the terminal is on a lockdown no flights going in or out.... I think I'm done flying for a while    
    
    
    They are reopening the terminals... I just wanna go home!! #toomuchtoask?    
    
    
    Progress, I'm boarding!    
    
    
    @marc_benton hell yes they do    
    
    
    Home! #cheers the Banquet Beer pic.twitter.com/FV5k6e9fTh    
    
    
    Pumped! Gonna watch the @MannyPacquiao fight tonight!!!    
    
    
    @MannyPacquiao whoop some A$$!! #PacRios    
    
    
    #Pacquiao!!!! Good fight!    
    
    
    Happy Sunday to you! #Funday    
    
    
    @angelahillman34 live shrimp    
    
    
    One of my fav things to do :) #familytime pic.twitter.com/l1533WWcYt    
    
    
    @travisbarker big fan bro, you're killin out there- we gotta jam out sometime! Be well-JP    
    
    
    Good morning to you my friends    
    
    
    @TherealETHX nah man, I was watchin cartoons w the kiddos. #familytime    
    
    
    Dec 1 is gonna be a BUSY day- 2 shows, 1 day. #daughtry #BOBBYCHURCH #losangeles    
    
    
    @JaimeRKOFan huh    
    
    
    @CHRIS_Daughtry thank u sir, it's not THAT difficult to do ;) see ya soon    
    
    
    I stir-fried it up tonight 4 the fam,was good if I do say so myself.My fav thing about me on cooking duty is I don't gotta do dishes! #WIN    
    
    
    @NIENIE69 Rooftop 3100 on Wilshire    
    
    
    Lazy Dogs- #cozy pic.twitter.com/WBIcFpQKZ0    
    
    
    @Cheralyn6 huh    
    
    
    BOBBY CHURCH DEC 1! @Twenty7magazine @timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker pic.twitter.com/xHohoG9LT4    
    
    
    Hangin at one of my fav spots near home, Neighbors- you guys are so good to Ol JP #friends    
    
    
    @Firelight_Lu @bobbychurchband @timothybloom :)    
    
    
    @CHRIS_Daughtry @mbsings I celebrate his entire catalog! #goodtimes    
    
    
    Gonna get on the drums today and record some stuff, it's been a minute! Wish me luck :)    
    
    
    @LC_McWhirt well happy bday to ya    
    
    
    These 2 are amazing :) #futurelegends pic.twitter.com/62YgflrON3    
    
    
    @sarahcolonna thank u :)    
    
    
    @melisa32 happy birthday!    
    
    
    I like this record! @arcadefire And yes, I still love havin 'physical copies of music! #Music pic.twitter.com/VKfNabcnkS    
    
    
    @clrfldcdaughtry because I travel so often, I like stayin home    
    
    
    @MaryfkaCrazy thanks! Same to you    
    
    
    It was movie marathon 4 the Pauls yesterday.FreeBirds(for the kids of course) then on to Hunger Games.I never wanna see/smell popcorn again    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 haha, please DONT! :)    
    
    
    @clrfldcdaughtry it's not that I don't like it, it's that being at the movie theatre for 5 hrs is a lil much :)    
    
    
    @JustJenNiffer :)    
    
    
    Have a Wonderful Wednesday my friends!    
    
    
    Just pulled this guy out of retirement, time to spice it up a bit. #bass pic.twitter.com/31cxXY9GfF    
    
    
    @LyndseyROCK1005 wow... The UN-Smart Car #scary    
    
    
    I can't help but wonder... Where has all of the ROCK N ROLL GONE?!! #truth    
    
    
    @sunrize619 I actually didn't make anything :) but thank you for the reply    
    
    
    @longagobc modulus!    
    
    
    I love ALL music, I play ALL music, I listen to ALL music- but Good Lord, I miss ROCK music! #PrayingForTheReturnOfRock    
    
    
    So today, in honor of Rock n Roll, I am going to plug my bass into 6 of my 8X10 cabs, and play as loud and as proud as I can. :) #LOUDER    
    
    
    My playlist today has been:Zeppelin,BlackSabbath,Rage,The Transplants,Them Crooked Vultures, White Stripes,Suicidal,and The Who. #energy    
    
    
    @LilyHart888 he's a Legend :)    
    
    
    I heard that the day b4 Thanksgiving is 1 of the biggest drinking days of the year,if you're Rollin out 2 party it up have fun&BE CAREFUL!    
    
    
    And finally, I want to wish each and every one of you a very Happy Thanksgiving. May you enjoy enjoy enjoy! #Thanksgiving    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving! #GiveThanks    
    
    
    “@ClaudeKelly: More importantly: a prayer for those less fortunate than I today, and everyday.” Amen!    
    
    
    @iamstefstokes @Matthewrholmes @Lovebettie @MrBrendanJay @GigspotsSam @Springwood_ right back to ya! Hope you enjoy the day!    
    
    
    LA!! Check this out, and come be a part! #livemusic #BOBBYCHURCH Dec 1st! pic.twitter.com/7xGAxKIk9z    
    
    
    Mmmm mmmmm Good! I'm a cookin fool! #HappyThanksgiving pic.twitter.com/9vAAEDUznz    
    
    
    “@ChrisAnokute: We ate, we saw, we crashed.. And today we'll do it all over again. #donttouchmyleftovers” YES! #BOBBYCHURCH!    
    
    
        
    
    
    “@TidewaterTina: @TheRealJoshPaul Never too early for Christmas tunes, right JP? #TheColorRed pic.twitter.com/hXktl9a4E5” :)    
    
    
    It's been a mellow yellow day 2day- Now gonna go hang  4 a bit w some grown ups at #Neighbours b4 I gotta roll back to LA mañana.#GoodTime    
    
    
    @TRitter429 nah, I don't do crowds- especially shopping crowds :)    
    
    
    Was lookin thru my closet and found this old gem, directly from the Hoff himself- #DontHasseltheHoff #justsaying pic.twitter.com/OkPXTM2OE2    
    
    
    Now Playing: The Police 'Every Little Thing She Does is Magic' #amazing    
    
    
    AND THIS! pic.twitter.com/Deaem3hm9C    
    
    
    @TRitter429 only during private house parties ;)    
    
    
    Support your family, support your friends, and support what u believe in. Most importantly,don't expect anything in return :) #RealAndTrue    
    
    
    @altnation on XM radio AWESOME! #FYI :)    
    
    
    Smooches, I'm LA bound! pic.twitter.com/Hp6tCWoRCS    
    
    
    LA :) #sunsets pic.twitter.com/6SbQkxRl8K    
    
    
    RIP Paul Walker....    
    
    
    Some things just make you smile- I think I really want one #itsthelittlethings pic.twitter.com/y8uLUCyOHu    
    
    
    Good Mornin!    
    
    
    Doin the Hollywood Christmas Parade 2day w #Daughtry should be fun!Then off to @bobbychurchband show-I love this time of year #tistheseason    
    
    
    Luckily, this guy can sew... Thank you @Matthewrholmes #inhousetailor pic.twitter.com/1H53nCSx1a    
    
    
    #LA it's a beautiful day in the neighborhood! pic.twitter.com/agjpv1Wz1R    
    
    
    Lets do this! #ready pic.twitter.com/43i6VpVAfA    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 oh it's goin! Both shows    
    
    
    “@CHRIS_Daughtry: Watching my boy @TheRealJoshPaul kill it with @bobbychurchband pic.twitter.com/bw67J9Z4Ex” thank u for comin bro!!    
    
    
    @Firelight_Lu @bobbychurchband oh yes :)    
    
    
    I had a great time yesterday! Thanks to all that came out, love you all :) #HappyMonday    
    
    
    @SheaOakes it was awesome! Unfortunately no I won't be at that one    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 I couldn't keep it on!    
    
    
    @Coco02bailey sure, let's book it!    
    
    
    @Jenuine9 @SheaOakes I believe it's acoustic trio?    
    
    
    My boy @DustinJackPhoto came out last night and took some pics, he's awesome! Follow him! pic.twitter.com/cakIGv2egg    
    
    
    “@Firelight_Lu: @TheRealJoshPaul @bobbychurchband Told my coworker I got 3 hours sleep because I was in church until 2 am...  Lol”:)    
    
    
    Doing the @ArsenioHall show 2morrow, I'm excited! #whoopwhoopwhoop    
    
    
    When I was 13,I sent a letter and a cassette tape of me playin bass to the @ArsenioHall show.I wanted to get up there & jam on the show(cont    
    
    
    I wanted to let him know how much I loved the showed and watched all the time, and loved the house band(cont)    
    
    
    I didn't expect any response, but thought it was worth a try. But a few weeks later I received a letter from the show (cont)    
    
    
    It said how much they appreciated me, and encouraged me to keep pursuing my dream. I'll remember that forever :) #inspire    
    
    
    Now 2morrow, it comes full circle and I get to play on the show! @ArsenioHall #thankful    
    
    
    Another cool pic by @DustinJackPhoto- here's @timothybloom in the zone last night! @bobbychurchband #BOBBYCHURCH pic.twitter.com/6eEbvCPZNJ    
    
    
    And another from last night, @pbesecker killin it! #Rockstar #BOBBYCHURCH thank u @DustinJackPhoto pic.twitter.com/HWSjcEnxyI    
    
    
    @kIMberlee__ thank u :)    
    
    
    “@elviofernandes: Bobby Church y'all.  Wow.” Thank u sir :)    
    
    
    @JUSTCALLMEJMO and I puttin in WORK! He's a damn good musician!!! #musicianmovement pic.twitter.com/jQY5ZUnWpU    
    
    
    @davidjschuler @Matthewrholmes I gotta check it out    
    
    
    Just heard a @3doorsdown tune while waiting for my ride to the show, I miss those fellas! #goodguys    
    
    
    My boy @OnreeGill and I are chillin chillin chillin @ArsenioHall show :) #goodtimes pic.twitter.com/AOSUmzwa77    
    
    
    The @Pharrell song 'Happy' is AWESOME! #happy    
    
    
    #goodtimes :) pic.twitter.com/lEw7l8RJy7    
    
    
    “@CHRIS_Daughtry: Thanks for having a us! @ArsenioHall and great to meet @RealJohnnyGill pic.twitter.com/Hz3wDEL4tG”'twas fun!!    
    
    
    @daughtryluv thank you!    
    
    
    #Sunshine #appreciate :) pic.twitter.com/j67RQD6MJR    
    
    
    I think that my favorite thing in the world is to see a child smile #pure #fromtheheart    
    
    
    @elviofernandes yes! Belly laughs!    
    
    
    I am watching @ginnyluke track the most beautiful angelic sounds that I've ever heard! @bobbychurchband track #TheEnemy    
    
    
    @Firelight_Lu where?    
    
    
    @Firelight_Lu trio    
    
    
    Quick trip home for a few to do some Christmas tree decorating, then back to LA I go. #tistheseason :)    
    
    
    Someone's happy to see me! #Molson #mansbestfriend pic.twitter.com/dxmcr8zMEX    
    
    
    And so are theeeeeeeese guys! #family pic.twitter.com/mOwuMiOQ2X    
    
    
    Today is the first time that I've slept past 10am- nothin like sleep in your own bed :) It's Friday! Enjoy it!    
    
    
    “@SuzieQ_23: @TheRealJoshPaul I bought u a shirt.. pic.twitter.com/ldP1M0J3kF” sweeeeet!!!!!!!    
    
    
    “@Lakers: He's back Sunday. pic.twitter.com/2yd59siBkk”!!    
    
    
    @Cheralyn6 great! All done. Same to u!    
    
    
    Before n After :)  #tistheseason pic.twitter.com/X6KLaDXWtd    
    
    
        
    
    
    MERRY CHRISSSSSSTMAS! #hohoho pic.twitter.com/cL7iqPib1N    
    
    
    I can't help it, I love the Holiday season :) #justjolly    
    
    
    #truth A lil Fun, and A Lotta Heart :) pic.twitter.com/dwcDlyGeoG    
    
    
    Good morning to you my friends, it's a chilly one!    
    
    
    @ddritzenhein true, that's exactly why I don't live in those places    
    
    
    @angelahillman34 ouch...    
    
    
    @kellypolark unfortunately I won't be at that one, it's an acoustic affair. But enjoy!!    
    
    
    @TSweet6661 hahaha, that's my cue to head to warmer weather!    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 @kristancfan yuck    
    
    
    I feel like the kid on 'A Christmas Story', all bundled up to where I can't move my arms or legs! #waddling pic.twitter.com/cZ0FOsiFbF    
    
    
    @TidewaterTina last I checked about 98.6? ;)    
    
    
    @imjennise I wish!    
    
    
    “@kristancfan: THIS makes me smile pic.twitter.com/wJKv9FmGvZ” :)    
    
    
    “@lyfizgud: @TheRealJoshPaul Sooo bummed you will not be in Milwaukee tonight !!😢I just found out!!”I'm sorry, I'll see ya next time!    
    
    
    My boy and I are Christmas shopping for Mom- can't believe I have a 17 year old.I'm proud to be his Father #family pic.twitter.com/I7AdpxYmdP    
    
    
    Well, back to LA I go    
    
    
    “@sarahcolonna: I hate it when I get hit in the face with balls. #HappyHolidays pic.twitter.com/Fb1UHDeQiQ” yes.... Me too... HAPPY HOLIDAYS!    
    
    
    @sarahcolonna YES!    
    
    
    I slept for 8 hours straight! Like the wise words of mr James Brown state, 'I Feel Good'! #sleep does a body good    
    
    
    @ImAud happy bday to u    
    
    
    @Matthewrholmes @MichaelPetted thank u! Happy to do it! #family    
    
    
    @richardmarx just popped up on my iPod, dammit! He's a bad ass! #truth    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 @MichaelPetted @Matthewrholmes thanks guys    
    
    
    Drivin home from LA,made a pit stop for gas and got back into the car.I noticed how quiet it was.It was a very beautiful silence #soothing    
    
    
    “@richardmarx: Dude...you are! But tnx “@TheRealJoshPaul: @richardmarx just popped up on my iPod, dammit! He's a bad ass! #truth"thank u!    
    
    
    Finally made it home!Flyin' 2 Seattle mañana for a cool show w @CHRIS_Daughtry and the guys. Last few weeks have been busy,BUT busy is good!    
    
    
    @MrsMysteryGal huh    
    
    
    @L_shannon_22 awww you're awesome    
    
    
    @Coco02bailey  I just get on the plane and go :) I'll figure it out when I get there    
    
    
    A little bit of heaven :) #happydays pic.twitter.com/OeCCkO9SfE    
    
    
    Nothin says true love like sharing a case of Bud Light on the porch at 9am.I just passed a couple doin just that on my way to the airport.:)    
    
    
    #sharingiscaring    
    
    
    @alycou22 oh I'm sure we'll meet up when showtime comes around:)    
    
    
    Seattle! (Very Cold) Seattle! I've arrived :) #winter    
    
    
    I'm somewhat trapped in my hotel room tonight.No hotel restaurant,No hotel bar,nothin nearby that I can get to.What will I do w myself???    
    
    
    @indigo_15 nope, no room service    
    
    
    @xCHRISFx happy bday    
    
    
    @theKLK haha, yeah but not one anywhere near where I am!    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 what's that?!    
    
    
    @stacie_twry in Seattle or just outsode    
    
    
    @Jenuine915 I did get to order dominos lol    
    
    
    HBO and Twitter it is- #tourlife    
    
    
    @LaurHof11 @theKLK @KatieGr80 can't get it where I am at the moment    
    
    
    @Apryl_74 not yet, I have a hard time dedicating time to television    
    
    
    @fredericah20 on a military base    
    
    
    @xoshahd going great!    
    
    
    @nedinachristina @ImAud I used to be!    
    
    
    #HasBeen A Dream, A Desire, A Life- Shirt by Lil Josh, proudly representing his Dreams #positive #liveyourdream pic.twitter.com/WCUlvx9agV    
    
    
    Watching @SarahKSilverman on HBO, love her love her!    
    
    
    Tonight has actually turned out really cool, hung out w Josh Steely for a bit and he showed me a lot of his music.If it's ever avail,GET IT!    
    
    
    I just heard something that someone said on TV. 'Why not appreciate all kinds of creativity,sport,and art. It all relates"    
    
    
    There is more out there than what you are forced to hear or watch. Please explore creativity. If you truly appreciate art, discover.#Listen    
    
    
    “@RevoltTV: YOU DON'T HAVE TO MAKE A CRAZY MARKETING SCHEME FOR YOUR ALBUM TO SELL OUT. You just need good music.” Yes!    
    
    
    Good Mornin to you. :)    
    
    
    @Diver43 aw thank u!    
    
    
    @Jenuine915 yep, hung and listened to music w Ol Steely    
    
    
    @FairyLittle93 today? 'I Feel Good' - James Brown :)    
    
    
    @NIENIE69 I WISH! It's far away    
    
    
    @nedinachristina :)    
    
    
    “@jimdunlopusa: “@History_Pics: @JimiHendrix driving a dune buggy, 1968 http://twitter.com/History_Pics/status/410845565002743808/photo/1pic.twitter.com/odA0CYaFOb ””awesome!    
    
    
    @LaLa_Bellissima :)    
    
    
    It was extremely gratifying playing for our troops & families as well as working w the @WWE! I'd love to do it again! #humble #appreciate    
    
    
    I truly love seeing the faces of our troops no matter where we are enjoying a little bit of entertainment! It soothes my soul like no other    
    
    
    These are my favorite shows :)    
    
    
    @meliamaccarone aw you're awesome!    
    
    
    At the airport tryin to head home, last night was a lot of fun! Thanks to all of u troops that came out, and thank u to @WWE    
    
    
    @patuduLR Greetings!    
    
    
    Guess what?!!! Another delayed flight.... #justmyluck    
    
    
    Enjoy the day my friends, I'm on the plane! #home    
    
    
    @Maria423 :) Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @jckid96 happy 17th bro!    
    
    
    Finally home, it's been a loooong day of travel- #safensound pic.twitter.com/6bXOKj1fSi    
    
    
    Back to Lossssss Angeles!    
    
    
    Good Ol LA #traffic pic.twitter.com/1G0D0Yughp    
    
    
    @julynda22 @Cheralyn6 no guys, I was completely stopped :)    
    
    
    #teamnosleep    
    
    
    @Punky4Daughtry hi!    
    
    
    It's been movie night for me, on my 3rd. Hours, End Of Watch, now on to Argo(again). could be worse :)    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 @Punky4Daughtry :)    
    
    
    “@UberFacts: When a male honey bee climaxes during sex, his testicles explode and he dies.” Um.. Ouch    
    
    
    @Hayley_B84 oh yes, thank the good Lord    
    
    
    Heard the new @Beyonce tonight, WOW! She threw some sexy onto this one! #QueenBey    
    
    
    @BriannaNegrete_ happy bday to ya!    
    
    
    “@richardmarx: @VerticalHorizon @Stageit Can you play stuff that doesn't suck ass?” HA!!    
    
    
    Hangin w @timothybloom talkin music, making plans. 2014 is gonna be a very good year #BobbyChurch #Music #realandtrue    
    
    
        
    
    
    “@MarkTremonti: Happy 11th anniversary to my perfect wife @victremonti, you're the greatest! pic.twitter.com/8NbJXqC5be” happy Anniversary!    
    
    
    Good Morning! Or... Early afternoon! Or night, or well... Just GOOD something! #goodday    
    
    
    @Cheralyn6 well have a happy birthday to u    
    
    
    @kat528_ no, not tonight. I'm home :)    
    
    
    “@benjaminmadden: The @tameimpala record Lonerism is my fav right now- nice work guys makes me excited about music”I know! I love it as well    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 @Maria423 good times!    
    
    
    @tommystone yes sir    
    
    
    My friends Suicidal Tendencies are in town tonight, gonna go check em out! It'll be good to see the guys,it's been a minute #punkrock    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 @TRitter429 nice!!! Merry Merry Christmas! :)    
    
    
    Nothin like the energy of a punk rock show! #punk pic.twitter.com/okDzl5HfF2    
    
    
    It's beginning to feel a lot like Christmas for my lil guy! #love #family pic.twitter.com/IIo5VwZfri    
    
    
    @sarahcolonna @MillerLite Awesome! Haha!    
    
    
    Jaco says, #SMILE pic.twitter.com/nry61V5OHq    
    
    
    @Cheralyn6 my thoughts on Fireball? Not sure I've thought about it much. Just pretty much drank it    
    
    
    @Pookeejcavobass @The_HollowKC @The_HollowMI haha, bass jam is cool :)    
    
    
    @ddritzenhein shouting out to ya!    
    
    
    @tommystone yeah man! Same to you!    
    
    
    “@nineinchnails: Our performance on @acltv will air April 5 on @PBS pic.twitter.com/99GxYAdrGN” Amazing! @PinoPalladino on bass!!!    
    
    
    This is FANTASTIC! pic.twitter.com/mKwnOSzsI5    
    
    
    You MUST commit and strive to be the very best at everything that you do!#motivation    
    
    
    @Matthewrholmes likewise bro!    
    
    
    Well friends it's time for me to finish up my Smirnoff Ice and call it a night. Be safe out there :) #tonight    
    
    
    @Krystle_Hill1 uh yeah! Duh ;) since when have I ever even looked at one of those! Haha    
    
    
    @Krystle_Hill1 sarcasm- my humor is on fire tonight    
    
    
    Good Morning World!    
    
    
    I got me a coffee, it's as big as a whale and I'm ready to set sailllll!    
    
    
    @thepeterbyrne not too sure about the schedule brotha    
    
    
    @patba1968 have a very Happy Birthday! Enjoy it :)    
    
    
    #coffee :) pic.twitter.com/XCv0t0Touo    
    
    
    @MsDaynaBayna well at least you'll get to relax! #brightside    
    
    
    Who has fantastic New Year's Eve Plans?!    
    
    
    “@timessquareball: @TheRealJoshPaul Right here.” Allllways Fantastic!    
    
    
    “@DusPerrinPhotos: Who could forget @TheRealJoshPaul's cover of "Joy To The World"? Still nothing like it! http://www.tunecore.com/widgets/show/94524 …” Thanks!    
    
    
    “@Diver43: Have you guys listened to @TheRealJoshPaul The Color Red JP Christmas yet.  It's awesome” aw thank u :)    
    
    
    On the Kit in w my kiddo! #Music #love pic.twitter.com/iGIf944baE    
    
    
    Road trip today! Just because :) Never lose your spontaneity! #grownuptime    
    
    
    :) that's my boy! #smart pic.twitter.com/5zaj0js59o    
    
    
    @HoldinMyHorsies that's what I thought!We were playing a game where we would ask each other questions and our answers had 2 be drawings!    
    
    
    Peace :) #ocean pic.twitter.com/wu449CJBZg    
    
    
    Standing in line to meet Santa is not as fun as one might think. Especially for 2 hours! I better get a candy cane! ;) #MondayMadness    
    
    
    @Miss_Andi I'm ALWAYS nice! Just ask Santa!    
    
    
    This is amazing... Get up to the from of the line and Santa gets up to go on his hour lunch! Well...I guess Santa's gotta eat too #hohoho :)    
    
    
    @xo_Nelz ugh....!!!    
    
    
    Well, these guys are smilin! #CuteOverload #merrychristmas pic.twitter.com/RNE5ojtZrC    
    
    
    @missktbspa @Jasonwademusic @CHRIS_Daughtry merry Christmas!    
    
    
    Happy Holidays! May Peace and Love fill each and every one of your souls- Love, The Paul Family #HolidaySpirit pic.twitter.com/gtQr2pRRrf    
    
    
    @Steelers1972 @CheryeDavis HA! Exactly    
    
    
    “@ChrisAnokute: Merry Christmas All. I'm good for the rest of the week. Jamison and music!!! pic.twitter.com/LE5zl4LJ72”Perfect!Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    :) pic.twitter.com/HGEUILlBVw    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 haha. Ho ho ho    
    
    
    “@BVBShinigami: Look what I just got. :D It's absolutely amazing, @TheRealJoshPaul! pic.twitter.com/mxdJP00dyY” thank u! Enjoy    
    
    
    @Matthewrholmes ohhh man I remember that! Merry Christmas bro! Love to your fam    
    
    
    @TherealETHX Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @timothybloom @theKLK @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    “@ClaudeKelly: There is no better male voice than Mr. Nat King Cole's.” Legendary    
    
    
    @thepeterbyrne you too man!    
    
    
    Merry Christmas!!! #sohappy    
    
    
    Ohhhhh Man, the house is gonna get loud! #drumsX2 #MusicFam pic.twitter.com/teRa8ctgym    
    
    
    I hope that your Christmas Day has been amazing. What is your favorite thing of the day? Any cool goodies?    
    
    
    @JustJenNiffer sorry to hear that    
    
    
    @Miss_Andi awww    
    
    
    @TherealETHX post a pic!    
    
    
    @andrewmcmanus24 I'm sure they'll be announced pretty soon!    
    
    
    @RosieBowMusic nice!    
    
    
    @StaceyGillard :)    
    
    
    @PhillyKim34 cool!    
    
    
    I posted a few cute little videos of my 2 lil ones playing their new drums for the 1st time on Instagram:ITSJOSHPAUL yea,I'm a proud dad :)    
    
    
    @TherealETHX nice!    
    
    
    @andrewmcmanus24 haha not at all    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 my kids would go nuts    
    
    
    @missktbspa perfect :)    
    
    
    Enjoy the rest of your Day and Night, if you plan on sippin on the Ol 'Eggnog' be safe! God Bless    
    
    
    Happy Bday @CHRIS_Daughtry !    
    
    
    @SheaOakes haha, no not quite yet    
    
    
    @Chelsi_Smith http://farmersonly.com ! Lol    
    
    
    @SheaOakes :)    
    
    
    @soul4dgame take that extra step :)    
    
    
    @TheDenDolls awesome!    
    
    
    I laugh when I walk into a music store & they try & sell me on some CHEAP stuff for 3X the price like I don't know my craft! #ThisIsMyBiz    
    
    
    I feel bad for the people who don't know the difference and get ripped off... Do fair honest business,don't try and take advantage of folks!    
    
    
    @cupcakee75 haha- my point is to follow the Golden Rule! :)    
    
    
    About to kick back and watch 'American Hustle'! #Movietime :)    
    
    
    @SuzieQ_23 Ha!    
    
    
    Please Please Please can I have a treat Dad?! #dogslife pic.twitter.com/jkOYCdCn3U    
    
    
    @kellieprime was good!    
    
    
    Olllllll Bella is gettin up there in age- Kinda Grouchy, Kinda Loud, but we love her :) #family pic.twitter.com/tL15Z6NUU9    
    
    
    Saw 'Wolf of Wall Street' last night, @LeoDiCaprio and @JonahHill did a great job!    
    
    
    @MB20RTfan no not this time :)    
    
    
    @AudraNucc it is however 3 hours long    
    
    
    @MB20RTfan can't be judged for liking what ya like!    
    
    
    @fredericah20 NOT a family movie. I repeat- leave them kids at HOME!    
    
    
    Links like Jaco got some work done ;) he got a kick outta this #freshlyinked haha! pic.twitter.com/9oMITrZcDC    
    
    
    @JaimeRKOFan @TributeToTroops enjoy!    
    
    
    @TRitter429 maybe... But AWESOME!    
    
    
    @NIENIE69 creepy is cuddling w a thanksgiving turkey before you throw it in the oven. THAT kinda stuff is creepy :)    
    
    
    I got a very cool Christmas gift :) pic.twitter.com/4J3WFU89yQ    
    
    
    @NIENIE69 hahaha, not this year......    
    
    
    “@WolfpackAlan: YOCO = You Only Cute Online.” HAHAHAHAHA!    
    
    
    @OTE_6 haha    
    
    
    @jessdomain that is Awesome!    
    
    
    @jessdomain thank you, same to you! #PutOnThoseDancinShoes    
    
    
    “@RodneyJerkins: andersonsilva snaps his leg in half!!!! I feel sick!!!! #UFC http://instagram.com/p/ifomp4MCYa/ ”so so nasty....    
    
    
    Happy Bday @pbesecker !!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    @pbesecker yes sir!    
    
    
    Happy to have @timothybloom and fam at my house! #family    
    
    
    @timothybloom absolutely!    
    
    
    @TheCatRoom @hollicraddock we are so very sorry for your loss. He was a great man, and I'm privileged to have known him. Love to your fam    
    
    
    Appreciate the obvious, and the simple. #sunset #beauty pic.twitter.com/Dhkp5ZTE3U    
    
    
    @rockphotogirl nice! Look at that face ;) only a mother could love! #BassFace    
    
    
    @timothybloom is allll smiles tonight! #goodtime pic.twitter.com/38ZJUhxia4    
    
    
    “@bobbychurchband: Ohhhhhhh yeah! Fun doin radio! #heavymetal http://twitter.com/bobbychurchband/status/417742397804531712/photo/1pic.twitter.com/ySUSiTcyQ4 ” Good Times! @timothybloom    
    
    
    “@travisbarker: Who said Monday's aren't meant for cruisin' #Chevytough #HeavyChevy #Grillin #CaliforniaLove http://instagram.com/p/ij0dW3NWG4/ ”NICE!    
    
    
    Ive had a really great time workin and hangin w @timothybloom and family up here at my house! #family    
    
    
    @timothybloom #bloomingpauls !    
    
    
    “@timothybloom: "@TheRealJoshPaul: @timothybloom #bloomingpauls !" #paulsblooming!” Or the #Paulooms ;) Safe Travels!    
    
    
    Went to hang at Shaver Lake yesterday, was beautiful! pic.twitter.com/tfPpJoRiTT    
    
    
    @timothybloom and I today after some radio work, photo by @maddymads12 #BobbyChurch pic.twitter.com/EJXI3zjIkt    
    
    
    @maddymads12 @bobbychurchband @timothybloom you are a very very talented young lady! We love you! #thefuture    
    
    
    “@ClaudeKelly: #nowplaying: "In Your Eyes" - Peter Gabriel” one of my favs of all time    
    
    
    @DonnieCanDEWMe @amym213 get well soon!'    
    
    
    @elviofernandes happy new year to you brother!    
    
    
    GOOD MORNING! I'm ready for the New Year, are you?! #2014 pic.twitter.com/HB9MOLrN0p    
    
    
    @TRitter429 :)    
    
    
    @TRitter429 exactly! Make it what you want it to be! #2014    
    
    
    @Tygart12 I'm tweetin' ya!    
    
    
    Here's a shot of @timothybloom & I jammin on the radio yesterday-Acoustic Stylings of Bobby Church ;) #HappyNewYear pic.twitter.com/Id8P2uR9qJ    
    
    
    As 2013 comes to a close, I really want to thank all of you for your continued love, support, and pure and genuine awesomeness! #BestOf2013    
    
    
    Now let's do it bigger and better! #2014!    
    
    
    I'm gonna watch the Ball drop tonight! How bout you?! #NewYearsEve #balldrop    
    
    
    Party Animals, have fun & be SAFE tonight! And please, don't drink and drive. #NewYearsEve    
    
    
    @sarahcolonna nothin wrong w a lil cheese :) HAPPY NEW YEAR!    
    
    
    Starting the morning off right,COFFEE!  Im ecstatic that I didn't wake up w a hangover today,just a sip instead of a gallon;) #HappyNewYear    
    
    
    @Tygart12 hahaha! Yeah, I've used that one too. The 'Flu' :)    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 New Years resolutions are similar in a way to procrastination.'Tomorrow I'll do this', 'Starting Tomorrow' etc- soooo(cont)    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 I just try and determine what it is I need to do,prioritize,and get it done today & everyday.    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 so today for instance, I know instead of the keyword being TRY, it's going to be DO! Happy New Year!    
    
    
    “@markhoppus: My wife is listening to Fleetwood Mac's "Landslide" and looking wistfully out the window. Am I about to get divorced?”HAHA!    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 be Merry, Be Mellow, and work a lil but today    
    
    
    Max and Jaco say #HappyNewYear :) pic.twitter.com/ihP2Wou8eC    
    
    
    @PhillyKim34 thank you!    
    
    
    @EvaMarieWWE_ :) thank u, they're my cool lil dudes    
    
    
    @debbgould I say just live, live happy. Don't worry about what anyone 'types' about you. The internet isn't real, human contact is real :)    
    
    
    @EvaMarieWWE_ same to u!    
    
    
    @Tygart12 one year apart    
    
    
    I just attempted doing the Brazilian buttlift video...um... Yeah.......#whyaskwhy    
    
    
    @mitziruff :)    
    
    
    Aw man, James Avery aka Uncle Phil on Fresh Prince of Bel Air passed away! #RIPJamesAvery    
    
    
    @mrsjc2u oh just go on over to my Instagram acct..you'll get a bit of my workout ;)    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 happy bday!    
    
    
    It's amazing what a smile & a 'Good Morning' can do 4 your day-so tell someone Good Morning w a smile! #goodmorning pic.twitter.com/Me7EjJndDT    
    
    
    I walked into the coffee spot this morning & as I passed a few complete strangers, I was greeted delightfully w smiles and good mornings :)    
    
    
    @teamfilanmahone happy birthday to ya    
    
    
    While home, it seems like early morns r my time to blow up twitter timelines. Everyone else is asleep here!So I say, twitter friends it 'tis    
    
    
    @missktbspa hello!    
    
    
    @TherealETHX thank u sir, I tried to dapper it up for a few ;)    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 good Mornin!    
    
    
    “@TheCarlyMarie: “@Z3TROC: If I ever go missing... 

#TheFamily pic.twitter.com/EoNUVUVeCa”😂👌” HAHAHA! Awesome    
    
    
    #tipsforsuccess #tipsforhappiness :) pic.twitter.com/XNK9DiBLgr    
    
    
    Hometown @bobbychurchband show this month!! What's up Clovis/Fresno?!! Details comin! Keepin' it in the Family-
#LiveMusic #Clovis #Fresno    
    
    
    And from what I hear, there's another one in Los Angeles as well :) #ChurchOnTheMove    
    
    
    Um @twitter the selection of 'similar to me' accounts that you have provided are not very similar to me #hmm    
    
    
    I guess I should say,I'M playing my town of residence show w my band @bobbychurchband this month - #minordetails #technicallyspeaking :)    
    
    
    @kellieprime @bobbychurchband its on a FRI :)    
    
    
    @KAnnWilliamson @bobbychurchband do it!    
    
    
    @carneymichael wtf was in those chips?!    
    
    
    @TamsterRN cheers!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Must Hydrate:) pic.twitter.com/WYoIIokgje    
    
    
    I hope that all of you in that cooooolllllld ass storm stay warm and safe! #brrrr    
    
    
    @Maria423 I've never LIFTED a snow shovel!    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 that's beautiful!    
    
    
    @elviofernandes the Tundra... The Tundra man....    
    
    
    @elviofernandes man, u should really think about gettin a couch! Or a fireplace at least! pic.twitter.com/kKzzzIJxoj    
    
    
    @elviofernandes HAAAA    
    
    
    I LOVE watching the sunrise :) #nofilter pic.twitter.com/To6WzQqiXE    
    
    
    @TRitter429 Jan 24, and Jan 27    
    
    
    Always remember :) pic.twitter.com/mP7a2xyzwF    
    
    
        
    
    
    Lookin 'HARD' in the studio-actually...I was freezing and my neck was stuck like that-#99problems&MyNeckIsOne pic.twitter.com/3yav5WOzf1    
    
    
    “@indigo_15: @TheRealJoshPaul #YoureHavingNeckProblems #IFeelBadForYouSon :)” HAAA! There ya go    
    
    
    @TRitter429 awesome! He says thank u!    
    
    
    “@CHRIS_Daughtry: Finally...a #selfie with PURPOSE http://instagram.com/p/iuFQ9-mQNh/ ” HA! I've been looking for one of those :)    
    
    
    “@Retro_Co: Ray Charles, 1966 pic.twitter.com/WJWHxU3Jkq” Amazing    
    
    
    @ccody38 @JJMidnightMoon my favorite is the STRAWBERRY! Gets me all warm n fuzzy inside :)    
    
    
    “@adamcarolla: get it on” Yes    
    
    
    I hear the word 'selfie' is no longer sheik.When u wanna post a pic of yourself,I propose we simply call it a #me :) pic.twitter.com/MYeuDog8pQ    
    
    
    Come on kids! It's #MeTime! Post away :)) #me pic.twitter.com/FgkR3MtioZ    
    
    
    @toshajean lots of porpoise :) ohhhh wait... pic.twitter.com/gznREkarYQ    
    
    
    My #me w a porpoise. Man... Can that guy drink!!! pic.twitter.com/lfNuOK47jr    
    
    
    Enjoy your weekend!    
    
    
    @MrsPed jan 24!    
    
    
    @machinegunkelly stay warm out there    
    
    
    Sitting here looking at my Christmas Tree which yes,is still up-I like havin it around.I'll be sad to see u go buddy pic.twitter.com/ciejn4DjCC    
    
    
    Til next year :) #FarewellChristmas    
    
    
    @xCHRISFx was great, haha yeah those things can be dangerous lol    
    
    
    @TRitter429 @BexyNurse true true    
    
    
    Good Morning!    
    
    
    'It's sooo good when it touches your lips!' #liquidcrack!!! pic.twitter.com/6WbTY5TPb7    
    
    
    @mtsbpc Starbucks!    
    
    
    I'm a very proud coffee addict :)    
    
    
    @ChrisAnokute YESSS!!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Big Poppa is 'Charged' up for his San Diego Chargers! @chargers pic.twitter.com/M0hhqShyXI    
    
    
    @RichRedmond @dwdrums @Jason_Aldean have a good run!    
    
    
    @DannyCooksey hahaha!    
    
    
    @timothybloom and I are on @907KFSR this evening hangin and playin a lil music! Check it out! #BOBBYCHURCH pic.twitter.com/U6Ab5mGDCa    
    
    
    And another :) sometimes ya just feel like playin! #music http://instagram.com/p/iz8xKaRFij/     
    
    
    @amym213 the date is confirmed! 8pm.    
    
    
    Thank u for tuning in and hangin w @timothybloom and I on @907KFSR tonight!If u aren't already give Bobby Church a follow!@bobbychurchband    
    
    
    Watching the best of @jimmyfallon , I can't breathe! He's hilarious!!!    
    
    
    Sometimes ya just feel like playin! Just for the love of playin #music Wake up! Wake up! Make it a… http://instagram.com/p/iz8xKaRFij/     
    
    
    @elviofernandes yuck... Got your snuggie??    
    
    
    #putinthework http://instagram.com/p/i2S3k1xFrV/     
    
    
    @SuzieQ_23 they r smilin!    
    
    
    Took this picture just a few moments ago right in my back yard. I look up into the sky and thank God… http://instagram.com/p/i2W_WfRFg6/     
    
    
    Little Spaghetti face is feelin ornery tonight! :) pic.twitter.com/jq8b3FDwrM    
    
    
    @elviofernandes ohhh snap! But yes it's true :)    
    
    
    Had to repost this as a daily reminder #truth http://instagram.com/p/i2d5EzRFq1/     
    
    
    @cheesecake_f nice!    
    
    
    Today's been a loooong day, time to just sit back and relax-    
    
    
    @richardmarx you MUST BE referring to Mr belvedere correct?! ;) enjoy! #belvederebuzz    
    
    
    @SheaOakes :)    
    
    
    Ooohhhhh Like Lightning! #coffee #tripleshot http://instagram.com/p/i6j2DwRFrG/     
    
    
    Good Morning Friends!    
    
    
    Well, I suppose my coffee was supposed to be for you @CHRIS_Daughtry ? Don't worry, I'll save it for you;) pic.twitter.com/EYl9MPCkmj    
    
    
    Just walked back in from gettin coffee to this. I'm not sure what superhero he is supposed to be, but… http://instagram.com/p/i6uFdTRFni/     
    
    
    @hckfresno what's up?!    
    
    
    @Matthewrholmes haha!    
    
    
    @sarahcolonna is she offering gas money at least?!    
    
    
    Those are awesome! “@PabstBlueRibbon: Beer goggles. Want 'em?  Enter here: http://bit.ly/K3FcTZ  http://twitter.com/PabstBlueRibbon/status/421048569194233856/photo/ …    
    
    
    Ahaha! #lilhipsters pic.twitter.com/9EQD92u4OZ    
    
    
    Head to Biloxi for work mañana,got 3 flights to get there.We'll see how THAT goes. I'm believing it's going to be smooooth sailin'#ibelieve    
    
    
    “@PerezHilton: It's sure gonna suck when we're old and have to wear adult pampers! Things I think about. #PeoplesChoiceAwards” yeah...Me too    
    
    
    @PerezHilton haha! Yeah, Im there w ya! We're gonna make those Grown up pampers look SWEEEEET! Enjoy the day man!    
    
    
    @CHRIS_Daughtry exactly what I thought! See ya in a bit    
    
    
    Good Morning Friday!    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 was smooth, long- but smooth. #travel    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Good Morning! http://instagram.com/p/i_sj0ixFuJ/     
    
    
    This is where I am, where are you?! #biloxi #HardRock http://instagram.com/p/i_9Z0ExFjE/     
    
    
    #truth http://instagram.com/p/jAFmBSRFuD/     
    
    
    Good morning world! At the airport waitin for delayed flights...#Awesome #takemehome    
    
    
    Meet my neighbors #score! http://instagram.com/p/jCtiQoxFkH/     
    
    
    Home finally!    
    
    
    Home sweet home #me #goodmorning pic.twitter.com/mpvWCCPJtW    
    
    
    @patba1968 yep I'll be there    
    
    
    @tinakaos greetings to all in Germany!    
    
    
    @tinakaos not sure of all of the details, but you'll usually find at least one of us after a show    
    
    
    We are rootin for the @chargers today! #footballsunday pic.twitter.com/7avmH2r4q3    
    
    
    @tinakaos 3rd times a charm :) enjoy your day    
    
    
    @DannyCooksey #teamfoolio HAHAHAHA!    
    
    
    @JimShearer I was wondering the same thing    
    
    
    AIRGUITAR!!!!!!!! #airguitar #metallica #familyaffair http://instagram.com/p/jF1Kd8RFoQ/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Check out lil Josh! #coolkid #prouddad http://instagram.com/p/jGIWECRFvQ/     
    
    
    “@WOWFactsOfLife: It has been scientifically proven that too many birthdays can kill you.”a long & thorough study has shown this 2 be true    
    
    
    @MattTheBhoy @CHRIS_Daughtry wanna get over there man, I'm Irish!    
    
    
    Uh oh look out, jacos reppin @Yankees pic.twitter.com/BbLnM2uqCd    
    
    
    Um... Wow.... Huge news- is the FBI involved? Not like we have starving children around the world or anything #probe pic.twitter.com/4jMblEdWOL    
    
    
    Next up, 'JP at the center of the missing sugar packet from Starbucks Probe' details coming soon ;) #silliness    
    
    
    Good Morning to ya    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 haha, yeah you too!    
    
    
    @iamstefstokes be strong... Be strong    
    
    
    “@iamMarkRonson: this is really really good http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3KG27nG8WRw …” that is really really cool    
    
    
    Unfortunately the @bobbychurchband show in Clovis,CA at Neighbors has been cancelled. I apologize for any inconvenience this may cause-    
    
    
    Lookin forward to seeing my good friends @3doorsdown tonight! #reunited lol!    
    
    
    @njdaughtrygirl happy birthday to you. :)    
    
    
    The guys killed it tonight! @3doorsdown really really great show- pic.twitter.com/bJdmSuOXsZ    
    
    
    Whoop! @Brad3DD pic.twitter.com/AoPDcdKCzK    
    
    
    “@Chris3dd: Visit from my brother @TheRealJoshPaul great to see you my brother! pic.twitter.com/iAEMlxyEDi”it was really great seeing u too!    
    
    
    @Chris3dd you guys put in a helluva show!    
    
    
    I think I like Ol @HarryConnickJR on @AmericanIdol #cool    
    
    
    Lil Josh, @brad3dd and @justintc84 hangin out after the show - thanks again guys for your hospitality,… http://instagram.com/p/jQGyxuxFsY/     
    
    
    Good morning to ya! Mass amounts of coffee is currently being consumed. #tired    
    
    
    @ShauniMcTaggart awesome!    
    
    
    @themerchdude yep, the important thing is to do it from the heart. Not to get seen doing it. #charitywork    
    
    
    @clrfldcdaughtry not yet!    
    
    
    @Kninjaplease good seeing you too man! #family    
    
    
    My friends going to @NAMM - I'll be there Thurs the 23rd, let's meet up! #NAMM    
    
    
    @ChrisAnokute yes sir, take the day by storm. On my way to NYC this morn. Make every moment count! #work    
    
    
    Good Morning World, leavin for work again today. So glad that they've added a starbux to this airport!    
    
    
    Hello NYC, you are cold!!!#brrr    
    
    
    I did watch a few movies on the flight- loved The Butler, and I'd never heard of it before but Parkland was good too :)    
    
    
    #NYC http://instagram.com/p/jVS_xwxFgR/     
    
    
    Streets of NY #NYC #madisonsquaregarden http://instagram.com/p/jW3_-RxFkI/     
    
    
    Who's ready NYC?!! @955PLJ #almostready #Daughtry    
    
    
    And no, I'm not sitting on BCrads Lap! #preshow http://instagram.com/p/jXpVZvRFq7/     
    
    
    Who's ready to have some fun?! pic.twitter.com/SHn2cfAICO    
    
    
    Thank you NY!    
    
    
    Finally back at the hotel.My favorite introduction of 2night was:'you have tattoos, and I have one on my wrist so we should know eachother'    
    
    
    @955PLJ @jaz907 @CHRIS_Daughtry @TheCatRoom @elviofernandes @therobindiaz thank you!    
    
    
    It was awesome to see so many familiar faces last night! Now, I'm headed home! Thank you all!    
    
    
    At the airport quite a bit early, who's awake?! #TeamNoSleep    
    
    
    @ShauniMcTaggart great!    
    
    
    @theKLK hello to u    
    
    
    @Punky4Daughtry :)    
    
    
    @Punky4Daughtry haha, I'm on the lily pad :)    
    
    
    @patba1968 that sounds really dangerous...    
    
    
    @melisa32 thank u!    
    
    
    @havetosmile you rock!    
    
    
    @itsjamiepuccio aw thank you, good to see u too!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tryin to hurry home, I have a date w this beautiful lady :) #anniversary pic.twitter.com/WNSWaWk2yc    
    
    
    “@EHX: Check out the new pedals from Electro-Harmonix at Namm this year! http://www.ehx.com/assets/reviews/ehx-new-gear-guide-2014.pdf … pic.twitter.com/KcBlKKuyKb”Comin by!    
    
    
    “@Fascinatingpics: Most Powerful Photo! http://twitter.com/Fascinatingpics/status/425409994495119361/photo/1pic.twitter.com/ZHcSchxYic ” that picture is amazing    
    
    
        
    
    
    @indigo_15 good fascinating! Otherwise I'd just say man, I've met some jack asses today :)    
    
    
    Ladies and Gents, I ALMOST made it wout any delays- I suppose I should just plan for it every time! Oh well :)    
    
    
    I love seeing motivated people. People with enough drive and fire to leave no room for anything other than success!    
    
    
    Met a young lady who said she was gonna be a surgeon.I made the mistake of saying 'u want 2 be a surgeon?'She corrected me saying I WILL BE!    
    
    
    @julynda22 happy bday to ya    
    
    
    @LisaG_325 none to fresno    
    
    
    @TRitter429 ha!! Me too :)    
    
    
    Well at least it's not Snakes on a Plane- see you guys! Adios #PropsOnAPlane pic.twitter.com/bmEGRNUZDY    
    
    
    Thanks @YardHouse :) pic.twitter.com/n5OEEq8caU    
    
    
    @LawsonGema should be fun!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @BonJulie1 @sarahcolonna I'm just talkin about skateboarding in the grocery store!    
    
    
    Just a smile can make a day :) #love pic.twitter.com/dRpQmzUFcw    
    
    
    I saw @LoneSurvivorUSA last night.It's a very very powerful movie- #wow #speechless    
    
    
    Good Mornin world :)    
    
    
    Pic I forgot to post the other day, #California http://instagram.com/p/jesBLWxFgO/     
    
    
    #californiaskies http://instagram.com/p/jesYDYxFg5/     
    
    
    @richardmarx a huge one! Like angry monster, hurtful    
    
    
    @Cheralyn6 unfortunately I will not be there    
    
    
    Busy Busy week! Got NAMM tomorrow, Party Fri, headed to NYC on the weekend!    
    
    
    And proud to announce that my son made the Honor roll!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Me and 3/4 of my dudes! #PaulBoys http://instagram.com/p/jfi-M3RFsh/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Home finally, saw some cool and def unexpected things at NAMM. this was one of them- #wtf #wolves pic.twitter.com/ZHGpEcwgnK    
    
    
    This was kinda wacky too pic.twitter.com/76f2g97j9t    
    
    
    @waltwalters you too man, be safe out there!    
    
    
    Gonna be a fun night! Got some friends in town, and at the tattoo shop as we speak! Then off to NYC mañana! #goodtime    
    
    
    @thepeterbyrne @chargers ??? Haha! Denver I guess    
    
    
    @amym213 nah, alcohol makes u bleed more- and inhibits the judgement on tattoo choices :)    
    
    
    Arrrrggghhhhhhh!! pic.twitter.com/3S91yWHiaf    
    
    
    I'm glad you all enjoyed seeing us on the Tonight show tonight! Or at least the East coast folks at this point ;) thanks for the love!    
    
    
    Good Morning World!    
    
    
    @Auntie2010Grad happy birthday!    
    
    
    Come one, Come All! #BOBBYCHURCH “@timothybloom: This will be a lovers affair, come with love! pic.twitter.com/RWr4DaZutV”    
    
    
    @mikeybzwifey uh oh! Giggles?    
    
    
    #TourLife pic.twitter.com/NU17iuFTzg    
    
    
    Happy Friday to ya!    
    
    
    @NIENIE69 sure no prob    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 HA!    
    
    
    Nothing like a lil Sam Cooke to put ya in a good mood- #legend    
    
    
    U rock! “@NIENIE69: @TheRealJoshPaul  just got my tickets for Bobby church.....and Daughty tomorrow. What a great weekend to be me ...lol”    
    
    
    Music, style, food, love, and life should never be bland. Mix it up, and fear not. Life is short, make sure you make the most of it. #truth    
    
    
    Bland is such a boring word ;)    
    
    
    @kristancfan yes but 'Chores' you have to do. 'Bland' you dont    
    
    
    @EvanSeinfeld DAMN BRO!!!    
    
    
    @kristancfan never :)    
    
    
    I watched a really cool documentary on a tour that @MumfordAndSons did w a bunch of other cool bands,they traveled by train!looked like fun!    
    
    
    Casino Morongo, here I come!    
    
    
    TRAFFIC....SUCKS!!! So it's nap time :) #vanrides pic.twitter.com/X6agXvTmy6    
    
    
    @32pinkbutterfly thank u!!    
    
    
    Thanks to all that came out tonight at Morongo Casino! It was fun! However... I did lose some $$$$$    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @Bootsy_Collins !!! #legend    
    
    
    @Chef_Chrissy79 :)!    
    
    
    RIP Lou Reed-    
    
    
    It's an early one today, good morning!    
    
    
    HOME!!    
    
    
    Up early today for no apparent reason, just... Up! #teamnosleep    
    
    
    @MrsG37 nope, I'm up solo. Like Han Solo    
    
    
    @TRitter429 I cannot make the walls rumble just quite yet. I must wait until at least sunrise ;) #morningbass    
    
    
    Come Shake a tail feather with us Nov 17 at the Troubadour in Hollywood! @timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker @heapsnheaps #BOBBYCHURCH    
    
    
    @DaughtrySuit happy bday to ya    
    
    
    @InaAlagic @DaughtrySuit Annnd a very Happy Bday to you too!    
    
    
    This new @arcadefire record is FIRE!! #Reflektor    
    
    
    Happy Halloween! Be safe out there!    
    
    
    @RiveraBarb in character ;) #dedicated    
    
    
    @JaimeRKOFan how bout an early Happy Bday to ya!    
    
    
    Good morning!    
    
    
    I changed my image a lil for Halloween- pic.twitter.com/Cq6QCAf2d9    
    
    
    The strange thing is, I actually had those clothes somewhere deep in the depths of my closet! #NerdAtHeart?    
    
    
    I'm wondering what the cut off age for trick or treating is? 14? 15? 16? Exceptions can be made w a good costume, but no costume? No candy!    
    
    
    I saw teenagers out there hoarding, w no costume and just a plastic bag in their hands! Ya gotta put in some effort kids!    
    
    
    @Feral_Girl naked girls??    
    
    
    @BriannaNegrete_ I agree w that :)    
    
    
    @Michelles0107 nice!    
    
    
    I LOVE the Holiday Season :) I get into it. I mean, I Really Really get into it!    
    
    
    Have a funky Friday :) listen to somethin that makes your booty shake. Try 'Lickin Stick' by the great James Brown    
    
    
    @NewRockHammer @Drumzilla70 @fher1286 good times!    
    
    
    I've just suffered a serious pain in my ass dealing with phone issues....    
    
    
    @NewRockHammer home yes, there no. Just saw your pic    
    
    
    Good morning to you :)    
    
    
    I've got an entire store to myself :) I like to call this, 'my' store pic.twitter.com/PGMjIqqrJu    
    
    
    These have taken me from coast to coast, and country to country- I love my Chucks #converse pic.twitter.com/Od2RNteMiu    
    
    
    @LyndseyROCK1005 slip on's?! For real?!    
    
    
    @LyndseyROCK1005 :)    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 nice, or just the steppers :)    
    
    
    @kristancfan I had a few choices.1)Stare at the ceiling in the dark2)wander around the house in the dark3)roll to Starbucks    
    
    
    @NewRockHammer let's go!    
    
    
    Getting ready for a PARRRRRTAY! pic.twitter.com/1dmUMCfphv    
    
    
    #saloonparty pic.twitter.com/WurANV34rh    
    
    
    It's a good day :) #blueskies #coffee pic.twitter.com/XKU4QWw89u    
    
    
    NOV 17 Come see Me, @timothybloom, @Matthewrholmes, and @pbesecker- BOBBY CHURCH! At the Troubadour in Hollywood!! #music    
    
    
    Buongiorno my friends, early to bed- early to rise I suppose. I fell asleep at a wild n crazy 7:45 pm last night. #oldmanlivin    
    
    
    Wow! Read that Dave Grohl will be producing stuff in the new Zac Brown album. That should be crazy! Looking forward to it -    
    
    
    @TamsterRN life is grand :)    
    
    
    Beautiful! “@Discovery: What percent of Alaska is covered in glaciers? http://bit.ly/1a3hFM1  pic.twitter.com/UN3lQQCCqU”    
    
    
    Look at that face! #cheese pic.twitter.com/D6WgWSkyTk    
    
    
    BOBBY CHURCH LIVE!! Come see us!@timothybloom @Matthewrholmes @pbesecker Nov 17! #MustSee #music #BobbyChurch pic.twitter.com/jzL3ReMZeA    
    
    
    Yes, what he said “@JoelMadden: Be yourself”    
    
    
    First time this year I get to use this! It's a chilly one out there tonight. #cozy #relaxing pic.twitter.com/HN6hqjsc8I    
    
    
    @ThisDudeRiots ha! OG!    
    
    
    @ThisDudeRiots great! Hope you're well!    
    
    
    Tattoo Day mañana w my boy @ZoOmBie_NatiOn !    
    
    
    @themerchdude hmmm... Not sure I understood the sarcasm either    
    
    
    @themerchdude yeah I gotcha! I'm good! Workin, livin, lovin etc etc. how u doin    
    
    
    @themerchdude nice, for sure. Be safe out there!    
    
    
    I'm gonna enjoy the fire, and just chill for once. Have a pleasant and happy evening my friends. #goodnight    
    
    
    Tattoo time!    
    
    
    Work in progress w @ZoOmBie_NatiOn -#tattoo pic.twitter.com/HOJiVIVJOa    
    
    
    Top O' the Mornin to ya!    
    
    
    I'm off to NY today for work, early early mornings. Tattoo turned out cool, not quite finished with the piece but I like it!    
    
    
    “@mrscantz: I can't rest” I feel u    
    
    
    I'm always in awe of the beauty of  sunrise - #goodmorning pic.twitter.com/qAhiH8yJu2    
    
    
    New York Bound, see ya soon! #coldweather pic.twitter.com/YcO2Cgg5vU    
    
    
    @elviofernandes yeah... I couldn't be seen with broken glasses out in the public now could 'eye'- oh wait... Too late    
    
    
    #BOBBYCHURCH Video coming soon!!!#music #ChurchOnTheMove    
    
    
    Saw ya sooN NYC!    
    
    
    Mile High T-Party! Let's do this #WifiInTheSky    
    
    
    @SheaOakes didn't know there was one    
    
    
    @jma51 we shoot next week!    
    
    
    @USMarineMom29 you'll find out soon!    
    
    
    @theKLK flight is pretty tame so far    
    
    
    @mer1217 great!    
    
    
    @BonJulie1 whoooo hoooo! Wow! Almost 10,000 people put up w my silliness?!!    
    
    
    @reet_petite I'm a music guy.I'll write 1,000 songs for someone else to put their thoughts and melody onto.I inspire- and make yo ass shake    
    
    
    @rhodygrl86 spend time w my fam :)    
    
    
    @rhodygrl86 all of the above. :)    
    
    
    Must. Stay. Hydrated. #flights pic.twitter.com/burKZRpvFV    
    
    
    @JaimeRKOFan no thoughts, just play    
    
    
    I was invited to a Renaissance Fair this weekend...I'm somewhat frightened to go! #pirates #wenches #whiskey #peasants #steed    
    
    
    @Chelsi_Smith yes, #bigassturkeylegs    
    
    
    While I'm up here at  25,000 feet trying to amuse myself,id like 2 follow some more people here on twitter!Who wants a follow from Ol JP?    
    
    
    @SheaOakes I try, I try    
    
    
    @KatieGr80 @kellieprime Instagram I actually have to put in the names and look for people! It's easier here :)    
    
    
    @Kim_A1 thanks!    
    
    
    @christine_estes meeting Stevie Wonder!    
    
    
    Rest time, chat soon!    
    
    
    Hello NYC!    
    
    
    Check out my good friends book!  “@ellefsondavid: More book signings coming up
Megadeth @megadeth #mylifewithdeth http://fb.me/1QfDBmqwx ”    
    
    
    