@lloydhollett Christmas comes early in your house!    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc @Thanetrecord it's pretty considerate stabbing someone in A&E, I can't think of a better place    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc @Thanetrecord inconsiderate bitch    
    
    
    Hi twitter, wonder if you can help, I am looking for someone on twitter or Facebook that doesn't have a cupcake business, thanks in advance    
    
    
    I saw this today pic.twitter.com/xZdEQkR7Sy    
    
    
    @Adem @ValleyGame no, no, no    
    
    
    @Gemma_Blythe it's good but I'm in 2 minds    
    
    
    @Gemma_Blythe dunno, I'm going to have another look, I thought it might be better    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye @Gemma_Blythe I don't think most will notice!    
    
    
    @ginger_nats @stefking89 tell her to have another fag!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa @ginger_nats @stefking89 is it a "to do" list???!    
    
    
    If America is #shutdown does this mean I can't get a Big Mac tomorrow?!    
    
    
    Drinking alone again, still, it is Wednesday so as good as time as any!    
    
    
    They have spoken about data roaming on #bbcwatchdog for about 20 years, why do people still get caught out?    
    
    
    You've run out of money? Really #granddesigns    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 if your dad was well fat he would be on #gogglebox now    
    
    
    Something went snap, crackle and pop in the lounge, we have unplugged the telly like its 1982!    
    
    
    @OSLioness hark at us! There's wars going on and we are worried about bulbs! #middleclasswoes #thunder    
    
    
    @posiekins nah, it's all fine, bit of thunder never hurt anyone    
    
    
    @thekeithchegwin had to put my dog down, he wasn't ill, just really heavy    
    
    
    @peterdav2000 although I saw it and thought it was ok rather than "wow"    
    
    
    @stefking89 stop moaning stef!    
    
    
    Just been to the #Broadstairsfoodfest it was crepe.    
    
    
    How do I fix Local Access Only on home broadband?    
    
    
    @adrianstarpool tried that!    
    
    
    Feck you #windows the #icloud fixed it, sorry I doubted you!    
    
    
    @matyd2000 why hello! x    
    
    
    @matyd2000 on a "break" but ready to dabble again!    
    
    
    @matyd2000 always ready (although I think I am in Leeds then!) I'll double check, what's you venue? Thought you were in Southampton way?    
    
    
    They may well be at least one murder tonight. Please find herewith my alibi pic.twitter.com/7TS6n4yIau    
    
    
    @Barrylws5 @BritishGas BG have been installing them since early 2010, register online    
    
    
        
    
    
    @smellynat82 @ginger_nats Barry is not great! (The place, not mr prior)    
    
    
    @ginger_nats @smellynat82 no no, it was raining when I went, and I was " working"    
    
    
    @ginger_nats @smellynat82 almost went on Dave's Coaches Coach Tour in summer. But we didnt.    
    
    
    Disclaimer: just because I just retweeted a lost cat does not mean I have any interest in any cat, ever. Thanks    
    
    
    Bit slow on the uptake but went to paolos kitchen for lunch today, now, that's what I call a burger! Dee lish. Go. Go. Go. #broadstairs    
    
    
    The #sheppey crash victims going on telly to discuss their "emotional stress" are just fishing for a new caravan!    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 that barely covered having the house made more accessible and the 24/7 care!    
    
    
    @posiekins I didn't say "it's lush"    
    
    
    @adrianstarpool not yet i haven't, that will be my next step, thanks    
    
    
    @DanielSheppard5 @GCThanet good stuff dan, thanks for name check!    
    
    
    @DanielSheppard5 mentioning @cwordcomedy    
    
    
    @ThanetStar @ThanetGazette it should just read "No Thanet Mums Smoke During Pregnancy As its A Filthy Habit!"    
    
    
    @themichaelowen don't worry, I'm sure it will T-Cut out    
    
    
    "Di Canio Out!!" Oh. #safc    
    
    
    Is Louis Walsh's house, a coke head and sunita in a white bikini really  suitable for a 17 year old boy? @MrBarrymore was ruined for less!    
    
    
    Disclaimer: I am not suggesting the bloke off west life has a drug habit!    
    
    
    @GlastoFest @GlastoFest: There are now exactly twelve hours fifteen minutes until the Glastonbury 2014 tickets sell out.    
    
    
    Louis saves the young boy? Who knew? #XFactor    
    
    
    He's family look relieved he escaped Louis grasp #XFactor    
    
    
    The older, fatter, blonde bird will not win, you mark my tweet #XFactor    
    
    
    I wonder what @Jeremy_Hunt gets called around the hospital?    
    
    
    @SkySportsNews @SpursOfficial what's all this about? pic.twitter.com/ggRnUKSB5n    
    
    
    @seetickets @GlastoFest fancy!    
    
    
    I went to @GlastoFest once before they improved the ticketing system, I have never been since they improved it.    
    
    
    @GazetteMargate @ConMend got one, he would, dunno if you know him though    
    
    
    @dean_itfc good, pick a job up for me x    
    
    
    @James_Redmond_1 played my little comedy club 2 weeks ago, he is charming and a lovely fella, go follow!    
    
    
    @realdeanporter let's be glad they do then!    
    
    
    @GaryBarlow does not live in New York    
    
    
    I'm not sure but I suspect @maryjblige has weathered a bit? #Xfactor    
    
    
    @theboyroos @RobBrydon @pinkgypsy1 Cardiff I assume    
    
    
    @stefking1989 welcome back stef, you've been sorely missed    
    
    
    @theboyroos @Kevin_McCloud he is legend    
    
    
    @theboyroos @pinkgypsy1 @NicoleScherzy everyone knows what happens when Hannah has had few drinks #pirateparty    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches I am literally beside myself    
    
    
    I have lost a follower, I cannot go on    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 @theboyroos hens behaving badly coming soon to @channel5_tv maybe pick up a few pointers?    
    
    
    @ChrisBComedian dr who?    
    
    
    @GazetteMargate @willscobie no? Where? Specifically? Got any numbers?!    
    
    
    @James_Redmond_1 it ain't looking good for this bird in #holby there may be a job going soon!    
    
    
    @James_Redmond_1 she pulled through, I'll keep you abreast of any future opportunities!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa so you have never heard of carrot. Cake.    
    
    
    I hope @gazzaofficial has remembered to switch his twitter notifications off!    
    
    
    @themichaelowen has shit taste in ties!    
    
    
    Friday October 11th 2013 is a sad day. The heating has gone back on. One is not amused.    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye that WAS the plan! We are the lowest paid, not sure if that's an official stat but it's true!    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye happy to recommend you for insulation?!    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye I'm not choosy, I tell people we can insulate anything!    
    
    
    Just completed my 51st hour of the week! Nice!    
    
    
    Anyone know what was being filmed in #margate today? Big old crew, I reckon @BBCCrimewatch ?    
    
    
    @MartinSLewis I have BG smart meter, 4 hours of heating our 3 bed terrace, is £1.35, reasonably efficient boiler, maybe helpful to share?    
    
    
    @Adem @Andrewq1978 course you get paid, are you not salaried?    
    
    
    I can't do anything right! pic.twitter.com/9Qj0AmB9eT    
    
    
    This came out of a #kinderegg I was certainly effing surprised! #shite pic.twitter.com/Iowdv8fhSt    
    
    
    @stefking1989 no toy, just a mini educational poster and stickers! Bag o shite!    
    
    
    @posiekins just shite    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 @Adem saga should adopt a safety first policy!    
    
    
    Conkers? Can you still get them?    
    
    
    @stefking1989 I fuming steffanie    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 dis you watch strictly earlier #probablymoregayinthetank    
    
    
    @posiekins you googled "Conkers"?    
    
    
    @ChrisBComedian that's their unique selling point    
    
    
    @BBCRadio2 kick start!!  #soundsofthe80s    
    
    
    My biggest regret of 2013 was not seeing The Stones at @GlastoFest or Hyde park.    
    
    
    My biggest regret of 2014 will be stripping completely naked at @theboyroos and @pinkgypsy1 wedding    
    
    
    Before the vows    
    
    
    I was wondering where @dean_itfc was and then he pops up like a rash    
    
    
    My absolute highlight of 2013 was having my tweet favourited by the greatest rock and roll band ever pic.twitter.com/1chvSKLjon    
    
    
    @kevinbridges86 a bar in Ramsgate (fucking miles from you) used to sell it on draft. In pints. Mad.    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 when it appeared you were the first person I though of! It's twitter top trumps!    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 I unfollowed him!    
    
    
    @Adem that's when @pinkgypsy1 said they were shit! Never liked her #itwillneverlast    
    
    
    @OSLioness you got barred from The Royal    
    
    
    @theboyroos @Adem @pinkgypsy1 fuck all bless her, fuck all    
    
    
    I predict @rockgod1970 is desperately tweeting celebs. Between wanks.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Thank god for twitter, how else would I have known its raining?    
    
    
    @Adem we tweeted at exactly the same time! I am outside, do you need owt?    
    
    
    How gay is Will Young!    
    
    
    @GazetteMargate let's hope so, sort of    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 I have googled it, looks ready enough    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 easy not ready    
    
    
    I think a Madeline conclusion is closer than we may think #MadeleineMcCann    
    
    
    @JasonManford ah! So THAT'S why you are back on twitter!!    
    
    
    I used to know a sweet young lad called @dean_itfc , I dunno what happened to him, I think he may have died in the arms of his sweetheart?    
    
    
    @OSLioness @Se_Railway @VirginTrains I used to work in Warrington and it's really not worth £380    
    
    
    Top tip: always ensure you have topped up your fake tan before entering a potentially life threatening hostage situation #emmerdale    
    
    
    #YoureWelcome    
    
    
    Jesus bloody Christ! This bloody shite is on far another bleeding hour now! Kill me now! (No disrespect Hayley!) #CoronationStreet    
    
    
    Most nights. pic.twitter.com/eaDYLY1Np5    
    
    
    Poor David. That's an atrocious suit. #CoronationStreet    
    
    
    Turn that bloody helicopter down! #ramsgate    
    
    
    @dean_itfc get your shit off my shit x #hodder    
    
    
    @eonenergyuk what's new about that? @BritishGas have done that for years?    
    
    
    @ThanetCouncil just about to leave home for work, dust men come along, not sure i can go now!! pic.twitter.com/gwg5hQObRS    
    
    
    Going to the funeral of dear @dean_itfc today (I'm not)    
    
    
    @benny2010 @MoneySavingExp you can, but they won't stay smart    
    
    
    @samjwatkins register online, they are not rolled out per area, you may get one if you ask    
    
    
    @PixelJockeyTH @BBCWatchdog BG will be starting payg smart meter roll out in 2014, loads of credit smart already    
    
    
    @treething @BritishGas you can switch on prepay meters. Obviously.    
    
    
    @PixelJockeyTH they will, you know it    
    
    
    Just got in from work, I calculate in the last 2 weeks I have done a total of 99 hours! #99problems    
    
    
    Next week I can see a battle commencing with @HarveysHQ , this is one battle I will not be losing!    
    
    
    I went to Essex today, surely there must be another way?    
    
    
    @NevWilshire_SBM I can't believe the queues!!    
    
    
    @faithlucy he's about 11!!    
    
    
    @faithlucy Ty was hot at 11    
    
    
    @LHBmargate what sort of establishment are you running there??! #disappointedfromthanet    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches @bbcstrictly @jurassiccoastin I have to say that's a master stroke of Ben to avoid watching SCD what will he do next week?    
    
    
    Just done loads of housework, but don't worry I have left the polish and Hoover out "accidentally" just so notices    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks I don't!    
    
    
    @ConMend leaving the fair shores?i was hoping to do tomorrow but life hates me    
    
    
    @RuskinRap @LHBmargate did you know the owner is "queer"?    
    
    
    @amyeee g'day sweetheart! Tell the boy I text him! x    
    
    
    What's worse? Energy bills going up £2 a week or this? http://m.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-24603008 …    
    
    
    @ThanetCouncil will I have new bin by then? Will my spare blue bin be removed?!    
    
    
    Two far to grown up tweets right there, forgive me.    
    
    
    @treething pp rates are same as credit rates    
    
    
    Go @npowerhq go    
    
    
    @___OST___ @BritishGasHelp I bet you don't    
    
    
    @stefking1989 @kathlaaaa @ginger_nats alright sweethearts, calm yourselves down http://m.thanetgazette.co.uk/articles/news/article/19965295 …    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa @stefking1989 @ginger_nats no.    
    
    
    @TheLockeBoy is this your doing? Spoilsport! pic.twitter.com/o6A6iz2vwk    
    
    
    @martin_barker1 30,000 tonnes! And 5p in pound profit    
    
    
    @amyeee he did bless him! Don't be off galivanting on that day!    
    
    
    @dean_itfc fingers crossed!    
    
    
    Out of town shopping centre. Isle of Sheppey. 2013. pic.twitter.com/sMgqhu1fnJ    
    
    
    I just got a text saying "Go Home you're not welcome round here!" #immigration    
    
    
    So my lower thoracic thing is out of thingy, how do I get that fixed?    
    
    
    @Kent_999s @AshleaJizelle you can't bloody have a bloody pet bloody raccoon! Nob!    
    
    
    Wanking a walrus?! #gogglebox    
    
    
    Good luck @dean_itfc    
    
    
    Fire service going on strike on 4th November? What could possibly go wrong?    
    
    
    @HarveysHQ have yet to reply to my tweet or my email, this does not bode well.    
    
    
    I think @TessDalyTV is a bit pissed on #8outof10cats    
    
    
    I don't think there's anything to dislike about @rustyrockets    
    
    
    @DSMpromotions New Year's Eve? They won't be a tough crowd!!    
    
    
    @DSMpromotions is transport and accommodation provided?? x    
    
    
    @GBPizzaCo stretch to CT11, don't be miserable!    
    
    
    What do heterosexual bachelors watch on a Saturday night in?    
    
    
    All good heterosexual bachelors in on a Saturday night watch #womenbehindbars on catch up    
    
    
    @theboyroos we've changed    
    
    
    @theboyroos some of these slags are hot. Some.    
    
    
    @theboyroos Desiree Hancock 198846 falls into the "not"    
    
    
    @theboyroos you wouldn't. Or Precious. You wouldn't her either.    
    
    
    Some of these birds eat well #womenbehindbars    
    
    
    @qprrforme tee-shirt, shorts, oh, bugger    
    
    
    @theboyroos cos there's laws against that stuff    
    
    
    @davidvitty the potty mouthed bitch!    
    
    
    To me, "incarcerated" means falsely imprisonsed, rather than stamped on your 3 month old baby sons head and got locked up, maybe just me?    
    
    
    @JamesGibbs94 what's a melt?! ( I haven't got bbm by the way)    
    
    
    There's a woman, she exists, she's called Sarah White, check out her sentence and release dates #womenbehindbars pic.twitter.com/mY4vJjkGVu    
    
    
    If you look Naomi Cambell up on google images this is what comes up pic.twitter.com/a6WCleGCQk    
    
    
    What's the actual point in @AVFCOfficial ?? #MOTD    
    
    
    @theboyroos it was suggested by twitter I should follow tough mudder, I haven't    
    
    
    The weather seems a bit rubbish out, no one has pre warned me of this for the last week    
    
    
    @hoogie1 @BritishGasHelp I expect they did, they too have increasing energy prices    
    
    
    @GazetteMargate wetherspoons, as they are the only ones with the money, art works, cos they are cool, vintage markets, and a big wheel!    
    
    
    @GazetteMargate oh and a theatre/music/comedy venue in the motor museum, crazy golf, that's cool too, you can have my ideas, #yourewelcome    
    
    
    #Storm has started causing damage in #Ramsgate already! pic.twitter.com/qfUaD6AmrW    
    
    
    @Shanksy00 it's not looking good, I won't be going out till early Feb at least!    
    
    
    What's not to like about @Andrewq1978 and his current affair commentaries pic.twitter.com/pGZXU3q7VG    
    
    
    Surprise surprise, it's #Margate ere!    
    
    
    @robbeckettcomic it would be a lovely surprise surprise if you came back to margate!    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 how the fuck would I know? Are you watching #SurpriseSurprise ?    
    
    
    IT'S SPITTING! IT'S BLOODY SPITTING!!  RUN FOR THE SHELTERS!! #Storm2013    
    
    
    What will be on the front pages tomorrow "Battered Britain" or "X Rated Gaga" #XFactor    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 switch of your power, get your self safe    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 no, David, it wouldn't    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc @BudgensBroadway as commendable as that is, a few bonio will not cure cancer!    
    
    
    Talking of @ladygaga I just got a nasty gash whilst shaving    
    
    
    @Adem what's wrong with you people? We dismantled the neighbours fence yesterday, no damage!    
    
    
    @Adem not yet    
    
    
    What was I not expecting today? To be struck down by a sudden uncontrollable bout of diarrhoea and having to drive home 30 mins! #asyouwere    
    
    
    @theboyroos ass I weren't!    
    
    
    If you live in Garlinge and ever wondered if they fixed Apple maps, they didnt.    
    
    
    @posiekins probably not technically    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc @LauraSandysMP @willscobie new bins? How very exciting, we just have 2 very over flowing old bins! Ill bring my stuff round!    
    
    
    @themichaelowen @carlo_colucci1 says Michael Owen who happens to be in Australia?!    
    
    
    @FionaBroadstair @mummysallygg what's a Men's Shed?    
    
    
    @uk_james @FionaBroadstair @mummysallygg oh, like a pub!    
    
    
    @Dorcasstj you'll have to go to @FortsCafe    
    
    
    Jesus, Judy off Richard and Judy is looking proper ropey! #theoneshow    
    
    
    @theboyroos @Andrewq1978 @Adem oh, we are starting the "I work more than you" row are we? I'll be in with a shout but don't have bust fence    
    
    
    Today's new experience was equally as unexpected but a whole lot more pleasant than yesterday's. acupuncture.    
    
    
    400 bloody grand for 2 bloody bedrooms! Ridiculous! #granddesigns    
    
    
    @JamieCrouch1 welcome to 2013    
    
    
    @theboyroos @Andrewq1978 @Adem shame    
    
    
    @RamsgateMH can one just pop in or do you do just ticketed events?    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye @EastKentCollege can you think of anything worse than driving a school minibus?!    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye @EastKentCollege also £15 an hour is crap in Sevenoaks, pretty good in ol fannit    
    
    
    @RamsgateMH cool, I'll keep an eye out and hopefully pop by soon!    
    
    
    So, do you go for the job you would love, better prospects but with slightly less money and loads of travel? What would you do?    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye so thats 1 yes, 0 no's    
    
    
    @ThanetGazette @ThanetCouncil are the fireworks to celebrate delivery of my little brown bin? What when the rest arrive? 12 gun salute?    
    
    
    @theboyroos L&D Partner (posh title for trainer)    
    
    
    @dean_itfc is that why you Unfollowed me? Nob    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 is this in your newly refurbished newly refurbished house?    
    
    
    @posiekins already told you that! pic.twitter.com/mTIG6YdGPx    
    
    
    For Sale: unloved and neglected kitchen bin. Sat collecting dust since we upgraded to the latest models. Still do a turn. £0.56 Ono?    
    
    
    @theboyroos I think I will, money isn't everything (helps though!)    
    
    
    @ThanetCouncil in 2013, is it actually possible to talk to a real person about rubbish? It's rubbish!!    
    
    
    @ThanetCouncil that's the point, it doesn't do that, it gives you 9, maybe 10 auto options in a monotone voice followed by an auto voice    
    
    
    @ThanetCouncil I can't, I really cannot be bothered    
    
    
    @Halcruttenden recognised as what?    
    
    
    Ten years ago, I was like a clean, clean Pete Docherty. pic.twitter.com/seUhpSaTFz    
    
    
    @SkyNewsBreak only till 1830 though    
    
    
    @rockthecasbah77 @Baddiel I presume David can get in without a ticket?    
    
    
    @qprrforme you can buy that radiohead CD for 99p a week for 60 weeks    
    
    
    @CliveHart @peterdav2000 done deal then! That's probably a good thing    
    
    
    With @CliveHart all but confirming @jdwtweet for Ramsgate, what now for the @RamsRoyalPav and @ICE_Ramsgate proposals?    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 worried your gas bill will go up to £30 a qtr?    
    
    
    @tiffstevenson bit late in the day for morning after    
    
    
    @dean_itfc that my friend is a tune and a half!    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches you would not believe what I have seen in your mothers cupboards!    
    
    
    @Kent_999s @markyboyblue buggers that strike up    
    
    
    @paulfuller presumably not 4 hrs from Folkestone?! You could walk it in that    
    
    
    I have met and know a lot of very funny people, none come close to #KarlPilkington    
    
    
    Except maybe @JimGutts    
    
    
    @cleveradem how does your garden grow?    
    
    
    @cleveradem will I get this job if I apply?    
    
    
    @SkyNewsBreak 15 years ago?! Bet they are delighted!    
    
    
    So now @lidl make @johnlewisretail style Christmas adverts? The whole world is broken!    
    
    
    @paulfuller I could walk it    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kentfirerescue thank god for that, my house has been on fire for the last 4 hours!    
    
    
    @Longleat @robbeckettcomic Breaking News: Noel Edmonds arrested on historical sexual offences    
    
    
    @SarahMillican75 @RomeshRanga you must love @MarkSimmonsHaHa too, runner up to RR in Leicester, needs to be on telly too!    
    
    
    Friday really is the worst day of the week for a day off, it makes working ALL weekend even harder!    
    
    
    @BritishGasHelp I work for BGMO, do I have to go to work today? Really?    
    
    
    @jaden_cullen118 we have a spare, move in with us?    
    
    
    @JKCorden you got there quick you were only in my telly box last night!    
    
    
    @LHBmargate well that's bloody inconvenient!    
    
    
    @gbPizzaCo I recommend GB Pizza    
    
    
    Chas and dave on @BBCRadio2 with @radioleary, there is absolutely nothing better in the world!    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches poundland?    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc is that a euphemism?    
    
    
    @Obonjo oh, I was asked to do that, but I am working, would have been good to see you, have a good one    
    
    
    @MarnieMemoirs @kentprivateeye Check this out on AMZN: Topsy and Tim: Make a New Friend http://amazon.co.uk/dp/1904351174     
    
    
    @Kent_999s  Are they all sex offenders in HMP Maidstone? More of an orgy than a riot I suspect? #hmpmaidstone    
    
    
    Bloody cheek!! They smashed up #Thanet wing #maidstoneprison    
    
    
    As they are mainly sex offenders was it more of an orgy than a riot?  #maidstoneprison    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa i do like a Sunday morning hammering    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa DON'T talk to them, do not communicate in any way, walk by, are they related to me new neighbours?    
    
    
    I fancy a @CabooseRamsgate breakfast! The best kind    
    
    
    @RamsgateBrewery @gaedd sitting next to where it all began. The boys done good. pic.twitter.com/iv5ZezuS7I    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa let me know if you need a hand to move!    
    
    
    @Adem they are beauty's!    
    
    
    @cleveradem will this bloody stag ever be announced?    
    
    
    @posiekins @artistsmakers not any more but a friend might? How can I put them in touch?    
    
    
    @posiekins @artistsmakers just sent Eric a message, or look him up on FB, he's Eric Storm    
    
    
    @Adem I think @cleveradem is broken    
    
    
    @Adem I am seeing @chrisroos weekend after next, I will tell him what you have arranged!    
    
    
    @Adem I heart this.    
    
    
    @eastcliffrichar let's be honest, only @jdwtweet can really afford it, they've been sniffing around for about 10 years, it needs something    
    
    
    @eastcliffrichar doing, so why not?    
    
    
    @eastcliffrichar no! I would never believe that!    
    
    
    @RamsRoyalPav @gbPizzaCo @ramsgatesounds @mongoose3228 £2m before you start? How will anyone, with respect, you, or JDW make it pay?!    
    
    
    @RamsRoyalPav I agree and if I had the spare £2m I'd chuck it your way!    
    
    
    I will NOT get old #999whatsyouremergency    
    
    
    @qprrforme pop round, it's toasty here    
    
    
    An advert for @O2 4G? I think they should perhaps perfect 3G first?    
    
    
    @qprrforme no, your alright, I've eaten    
    
    
    Safety first, always wear your high viz in the bath. And your clothes. #999whatsyouremergency    
    
    
    @kevinbridges86 @CadburyUK blatant attempt at a free box of chocolate bars there.    
    
    
    I have just lost over 100 emails, how can I enjoy my day? pic.twitter.com/xiT3xKKrYI    
    
    
    @dean_itfc I don't see nothing wrong with a little bump and grind    
    
    
    @dean_itfc no, thank god    
    
    
    @dean_itfc or g-a-y    
    
    
    @dean_itfc going to the ballet. True.    
    
    
    @SarahMillican75 do you get overtime?    
    
    
    @O2 most places I go, and I spend my day travelling round east Kent mainly it's fair to say, I  dont get 3G a lot more than I do get it    
    
    
    @dean_itfc I am on warrant gee's today!    
    
    
    @ginger_nats @smellynat82 @stefking1989 @kathlaaaa so birds, does Hodd need to arrange a hostile takeover?    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa @ginger_nats @smellynat82 @stefking1989 some old tart on FB, although Hodds mum is convinced @waitrose is going up WWX    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa @ginger_nats @smellynat82 @stefking1989 AND The Stanley house is for sale, relocating? Redundant?    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa @ginger_nats @smellynat82 @stefking1989 probably forget you work there    
    
    
    @ginger_nats @smellynat82 @stefking1989 @kathlaaaa some woman put it on a FB group, I saw the Stanley For Sale    
    
    
    On #MasterChef they are using exactly the same saucepans as the ones I wash up!    
    
    
    What's the point in #GrandDesigns ? You either run out of cash or die!    
    
    
    @theboyroos I bet Hugh loves a none!    
    
    
    @theboyroos bone!    
    
    
    No! No @sky phone line and no @02 3G (standard) am I in 1982?!    
    
    
    This news story on @bbcsoutheast contains the words Tiffany, Benefits and Sheerness. I am going to refrain.    
    
    
    Tinterweb still broke, fix it @sky and @o2 a little bit of 3G? Go on, spoil me    
    
    
    People of #thanet rejoice! All 3 of my bins have been emptied! Just one to return. Almost there with #binsaga2012 @ThanetCouncil    
    
    
    @posiekins @ThanetCouncil everything's gone that should be, blue bin was getting a complex!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @FoxClaireLouise @LoveMargate @MargateTownTeam the @LHBmargate @BowsKitchen @aleandcider all get my thumbs up!    
    
    
    @BowsKitchen @FoxClaireLouise @LHBmargate @aleandcider listen up chaps, the nice last from the magazine is coming, don't be shit!    
    
    
    @JackQPRThomson @BritishGas  most original tweet of 2013 award goes to.....    
    
    
    @djjamiejayy @BritishGas @exampleisgod I may be wrong but I think Jamie has the hump about something?    
    
    
    @JackQPRThomson @BritishGas twitter insult of the year award goes to......    
    
    
    @JackQPRThomson pot kettle sweet heart    
    
    
    @davepoflynn @ConMend what time did you have the shit?    
    
    
    Beer really is rubbish    
    
    
    @SkintLondon @aquashard I can't, I'm skint!    
    
    
    @ginger_nats @kathlaaaa Mel roots off the veg says that this would make a lovely Christmas present for a loved one pic.twitter.com/RWBjwyPzuN    
    
    
    @theboyroos http://www.classicsforoccasions.co.uk     
    
    
    @theboyroos ps still well rough    
    
    
    @MartinSLewis @loves_fealty I had £64! "Goodwill payment"    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa @ginger_nats will you be my loved one just so I can buy it, it's a "gorgeous gift"    
    
    
    @ashleycurry007 @AlanCarr @tourettesaction for Tourette's? Should have told him to fuck off Alan!    
    
    
    @ashleycurry007 @AlanCarr not sure joke would have had same effect then though, good luck with run    
    
    
    @theboyroos course they would, you could go cruising round town like Charlie big potatoes    
    
    
    @theboyroos belle vue and mariners    
    
    
    @LHBmargate what's your capacity Si?    
    
    
    @LHBmargate yeah, party in winter    
    
    
    You have to love a @johnlewisretail Christmas ad!    
    
    
    @Lord_Sugar not trending though Ma Lud    
    
    
    She 16?! If I were 20 years younger! #XFactor    
    
    
    @NewlySingleMan I would retweet that but if lose followers!    
    
    
    @lilyallen nice to hear your dulcet tones again    
    
    
    I have burning desire to own and run a #micropub but if it's so stressful it drives you to murder, I'll give it a miss (as if I was anyway)    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye me? Never! Part of the tweet was true!    
    
    
    On the @Heartfm news they got 2 news stories completely wrong,  unless there is 2 Marlowe academies in Kent? And 2 serious assaults at 0330?    
    
    
    @gbPizzaCo well done, only small thing, you are cheaper than£21 pp surely? Everyone can go!    
    
    
    @gbPizzaCo is it in order of preference? You are not 130 or something? (Hope not!)    
    
    
    @gbPizzaCo fair point!!    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/VQ0sGDV1ZO    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches you are marrying a vicar? Really    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches I think in 2013 a vicar will go anywhere for a bit of bunce!    
    
    
    @jurassiccoastin @MissSeaPeaches and the patience of a saint clearly    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches I'll do the wedding if you want? I did a funeral once, (true) pretty much the same thing id imagine?    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks well done, a genuine achievement    
    
    
    I just didnt want to lick the fish!    
    
    
    @kent_police the link on the website isn't working either    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/events/181369908734389/ …    
    
    
    @BritishGasHelp come to this, brighten your day https://www.facebook.com/events/181369908734389/ …    
    
    
    @Adem you are in @_DionneWarwick ? And that is all?!    
    
    
    @RamsgateMH @SandsHotelMarga    
    
    
    You have a "Nice Uzbund!" I bet you don't #999whatsyouremergency    
    
    
    @peterdav2000 black and brown every week    
    
    
    @MrsTaraPlumbing @ThanetStar you could squash it a bit    
    
    
    FOR SALE: nineteen (19) odd socks, tuppence Ono.    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks did you tell him to fuck off?    
    
    
    @posiekins no, that behaviour is not to be encouraged    
    
    
    @artistsmakers @ThanetCouncil only allowed to get the red spade out on a Tuesday, before 6am ideally    
    
    
    Lovely to see @dean_itfc today bless him, he's a beautiful boy    
    
    
    @qprrforme there is Guinness nuts, not sure they are manufactured from Guinness or merely flavoured    
    
    
    @DawniesKitchen you can keep that one    
    
    
    @dean_itfc I am looking good deany looking good    
    
    
    @artistsmakers @ThanetCouncil this is getting silly, they only cleared that yesterday, it must be the council doing it for job creation    
    
    
    #Siri you little beauty, you have just saved me a fortune! pic.twitter.com/83KJ9ZIqXl    
    
    
    “@DSMpromotions: We are looking for an MC for the 7th December £80 in Margate. Please email "@shortbloke1971 ? One of the best!    
    
    
    Why move to such an anti gay country?! http://m.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-kent-24932948 …    
    
    
    Just watched #homesunderthehammer and it's outrageous @ThanetCouncil ever gave planning for flats in the @SandsHotelMarga what were they on?    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa rubbish jokes my arse! You need to have a word with that child!    
    
    
    @ThanetStar specifically?    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa she is a bloody disgrace!    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc unfollowed    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa tell her I never liked her nor her muvva! Auntie @ginger_nats is lovely though    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa @ginger_nats of all the kids you could've adopted and you picked the cheeky one    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa @ginger_nats uuurrrrrrgggghhh!!    
    
    
    @ginger_nats @kathlaaaa I blame the parents    
    
    
    That's the 3 bins sorted, only exercise I get these days    
    
    
    My tour, 16th Nov, London, 19th Nov, Staines, 3rd Dec, Riegate, 4-5th Dec Leeds, dec 15th, London, 16th Dec, Orpington.    
    
    
    @posiekins mainly dull office blocks    
    
    
    @robbeckettcomic @johnlewisretail @JLcustserv you can take the boy out of Lewisham......    
    
    
    Just wrote down the wifi password for the sitter in crayon!! #ivechanged    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc is it Tesco value blue stripe zebra? Or just your standard zebra?    
    
    
    Worse job ever! Working in a children's hospice #ChildrenInNeed2013    
    
    
    Oh dido! I would give you the best day of your life! Disclaimer: probably not    
    
    
    @artistsmakers is it just a wreck? I used to do a dreamland gag in my stand up, happy to be proven wrong!    
    
    
    @kjbailes @freelanceliz bloody gypos!    
    
    
    @thecomedycow jeeez that's a coop    
    
    
    @thecomedycow is that the right word?!    
    
    
    @dean_itfc you found the rest of your tablet??    
    
    
    Jeez £31m?! Well done, but presumably with that kind of money there will no longer be any #childreninneed so what next year?    
    
    
    There's a girl on this train, I suspect she goes to St Lawrence College, I also suspect if she does not pipe down soon she will not see Xmas    
    
    
    Apologies for using the Xmas abbreviation    
    
    
    She has got off and taken her 2 lap doggy homies with her, blud    
    
    
    Just been mugged in broad daylight on a busy Canterbury street @buildabear be safe people!    
    
    
    @theboyroos @ThanetCouncil good luck with getting that sorted!!    
    
    
    Imagine dropping your silver food waste caddy all over the kitchen floor with devastating effect. Imagine.    
    
    
    @posiekins the lid came off!    
    
    
    Hello, @GaryBarlow here, wouldn't it be terrific if they sing my song, I'll tell them they are shite and then I will sing a song #XFactor    
    
    
    We are having interesting conversation, is there a plural to "pus" as in "2 pus filled spots" I DO NOT reccommend googling it! Is it a word?    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks thanks, I have leant a lot this evening!    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks I had pus lentils once, no, that was puy    
    
    
    Carlton has popped on the old suet! #imacelebrity    
    
    
    @antanddec by mad you mean twat?    
    
    
    @Uxeditor unbelievable queues!    
    
    
    I could literally not do this #imacelebrity    
    
    
    Eating turkey testicles? We've all had nights like that! #imacelebrity    
    
    
    @antanddec @ThatGirlDoes same thing pretty much    
    
    
    @IwagerIan @theJeremyVine does she follow you on twitter?!    
    
    
    If I went in the jungle I would make sure it was my time of the month #imacelebrity    
    
    
    @stefking1989 cos then you get excluded from being buried for "medical reasons"    
    
    
    @themichaelowen you are big in china!    
    
    
    I really am appalling at job interviews.    
    
    
    I don't think you should mess with #ghurkas    
    
    
    Steve Davies will win this #imacelebrity    
    
    
    @davepoflynn I can see you getting on like a house on fire at 4am after 28mins sleep!    
    
    
    @davepoflynn she don't look very pregnant?    
    
    
    I once had a girlfriend with a beef garland #iceland #imacelebrity    
    
    
    @davepoflynn can't say I'd noticed?    
    
    
    @davepoflynn I think she undermines the female race! (I would give her a right undermining!)    
    
    
    @davepoflynn oh, the old "hang (out the back of me) glider from hell" trial. A particular favourite.    
    
    
    @paulfuller what happened?    
    
    
    @paulfuller oh, did they miss it?    
    
    
    Mental illness is truly fascinating #Bedlam    
    
    
    @Kent_999s @_George_Cook Jesus! @LHBmargate all ok?    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches what's in a trio of sausages?    
    
    
    Hey @Liquor_Lounge , you look like a delightful venue! #bouncers    
    
    
    @theboyroos "there's been a rape up there!" No, dunno yet    
    
    
    @theboyroos him on the left looks likely    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches venison? I bet that was deer?    
    
    
    @DSMpromotions @cwordcomedy you coming?    
    
    
    @FofEPRamsgate voted    
    
    
    "Unique club night to launch at the Royal in Ramsgate with Christmas party http://bit.ly/Il6WUa ” that's every night in The Royal surely?    
    
    
    @ThanetGazette you have been to the Royal?! This is nothing new!    
    
    
    Of the 3.5 million #lostprophets albums sold, how many are on eBay tonight?    
    
    
    @CT11RAG @razdaz66 that's not new news, they have missed my road loads over the years!    
    
    
    @CT11RAG @razdaz66 no, they always just come back a few days later, normally whether you complain or not    
    
    
    @LauraSandysMP is stepping down? She will be missed after everything she has done. Oh.    
    
    
    @FofEPRamsgate excellent, well done, I'm sure my 2 votes swung it!    
    
    
    I would like Rudimentals record for Christmas however I disagree with the advert "A perfect gift for Christmas" not really specific that    
    
    
    @dean_itfc yay! #teamdean    
    
    
    My greatest fear in life is that the little compostible bag in the food caddy rips open on its final journey to the outside.    
    
    
    That Zoe on @bbcsoutheast was a right sort, I'd like to fraud her!    
    
    
    Anyone in #Thanet got any spare rubbish they don't want? My bins have never been emptied so often, I want to stack a bit up!    
    
    
    Happy Friday to all my black friends. #BlackFriday    
    
    
    @MoneySavingExp do. Not. Be. Ridiculous.    
    
    
    Eh, no, it's a card, and no, it does not. pic.twitter.com/2kBPc0t4Js    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 real tree?    
    
    
    @willscobie who's performing? I would have been up for that    
    
    
    @willscobie good acts, I've gigged with Tim Clark before. I'll look out for next one    
    
    
    Bought the tree today, it's a beaut! It's too early though so it's in the garden.    
    
    
    Jesus Cilla, let it go #surprisesurprise    
    
    
    Anyone been to the Reindeer Centre at Ashford? Any good?    
    
    
    @The_Glass_Jar whoa, whoa, whoa, what's this??! Sounds interesting!    
    
    
    @chrismccausland awesome indeed!    
    
    
    @TonyCowards I did that joke a year ago, did I nick it off you? Thought it was better than my usual!    
    
    
    #TomDaley is gay? Never!    
    
    
    @ConMend surely that puts you off your stroke?    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches think I need to work for nhs!!    
    
    
    @qprrforme guilty as charged m'lud    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches to celebrate the engagement trip? Bloody disgrace!    
    
    
    @asda are selling DAB radios for £19??!    
    
    
    Don't think I've ever actually noticed what #amywillerton looks like! #imacelebrity    
    
    
    @antanddec @ChelseaBear in the bloody jungle? A critter might eat them!!    
    
    
    @posiekins id be amazed if they had any left!    
    
    
    @ConMend @TheRealJackDee that's proper cool!    
    
    
    I hate you #ashford    
    
    
    @DanielSheppard5 it's a proper tune though! I'm listening to it now. Alone. Naked. Erect.    
    
    
    In Leeds, just going go for me tea!    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks had a meeting earlier, it were 2 while 5!    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 yes thank you    
    
    
    Leeds is bloody miles!!    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches @TravelodgeUK you in the Deluxe room?    
    
    
    @TheBroadie who takes a wardrobe to the beach?!    
    
    
    @dean_itfc yay! I am late and on call #broken    
    
    
    Imagine if you bought a Christmas tree too big for your house? Imagine.    
    
    
    I am not sure if this actually happened but I think I saw Father Christmas walking along grange road #ramsgate earlier! Maybe I imagined it!    
    
    
    My tree's bigger than your tree.    
    
    
    @theboyroos I wouldn't be sure, I have been married six and a half years!    
    
    
    @theboyroos @Adem like Ian's testicles in many ways    
    
    
    Is there any GOOD gift websites?    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc sorry, thought that said "dogging"    
    
    
    So the great British public like boy bands and camp pensioners? #imacelebrity    
    
    
    @daffyrock name one    
    
    
    @daffyrock how long did that take to google?    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches I would have complained and asked to go back!    
    
    
    And the winner of the Award for Ramdomnly Named and Slightly Disturbing Children's Book of the year 2013 goes to ... pic.twitter.com/BlthSLMJo9    
    
    
    This arrived today, where's it from? pic.twitter.com/77s5PSrJIY    
    
    
    @DawniesKitchen maybe, do Selfridges sell fridges?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sam Dick from #stonewall ? Who makes this stuff up?!    
    
    
    So, what's the etiquette with kids Christmas cards?! Do I have to give EVERYONE in the class one?!    
    
    
    @GoonerMan2 valid point. Sorry "Ollie" it's just not your year!    
    
    
    @heineken_UKCorp @rockgod1970 I believe Dave deserves a years (months??) free supply for his help righting the wrong!    
    
    
    @topsecretcomedy bet it's Jack bloody Whitehall?!    
    
    
    #kavos looks toss    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa he hasn't a clue    
    
    
    @TonyCowards could be worse, could be a strip club!!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa everyday babes    
    
    
    @AnthBlakemore @RealMattLucas it's a squid an hour to park there!    
    
    
    @topsecretcomedy I give up?    
    
    
    @topsecretcomedy just seen it. Jesus! Excellent    
    
    
    @lloydhollett there must be SOME tickets left? Any tips?    
    
    
    We want to go to a Panto, oh yes we do! We don't want it to shit, oh no we don't! Any local recommendations?    
    
    
    @theboyroos no    
    
    
    @theboyroos you should    
    
    
    @elliegoulding I most definately would. @LukeFriendMusic i most definitely would not. Xfactor    
    
    
    Forgot the old hash tag on the last tweet, an error typical of 2009    
    
    
    "ideally located in the popular residential area on the West Side of Ramsgate within easy reach of St Lawrence village"    
    
    
    Are we human? Or are we dancers?    
    
    
    @ginger_nats that's proper cool!    
    
    
    @Adem @pinkgypsy1 not before I've bought a cheap handbag!    
    
    
    @davidvitty I would say it depends on the shop and it's advertised opening hours and indeed what you wished to purchase    
    
    
    I am driving into central London. At Christmas. I don't care me.    
    
    
    @davepoflynn I wish you twitter farewell!    
    
    
    @davepoflynn no, you will be within a week, woe betide the new dad caught tweeting!    
    
    
    @razdaz66 I'll save you a space!!    
    
    
    @davepoflynn excellent. Be sure to remind her "you wanted a bloody kid"    
    
    
    @razdaz66 is that pre booked?    
    
    
    @razdaz66 excellent tip! Do you know postcode?    
    
    
    @razdaz66 north Greenwich station?    
    
    
    @razdaz66 appreciate the tip!    
    
    
    @lilyallen not @Heartfm you ain't, number 4 I think    
    
    
    @Baggerz_14 @DevlinOfficial bit harsh?    
    
    
    I have had a simply brilliant day in our fair capital town.    
    
    
    @Gemma_Blythe @thrylmargate was it good?    
    
    
    I still rate AVB, I now rate @avb too!    
    
    
    @No1ninjanaruto Martin jol?    
    
    
    @Gemma_Blythe @thrylmargate excellent. Booked!    
    
    
        
    
    
    See, I told you from the start she was too old to win! I should be psychic bloody Sally! Oh. #xfactor    
    
    
    Good lord. @radioleary just said "Hun"    
    
    
    And again!    
    
    
    @RebekkaMary yes, but he is shit!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa tell http://child.she.is  its bedtime!    
    
    
    @MartinSLewis @SamBaileyREAL @itvthismorning forget all that you saved me £8 in Strada today, can I have a photo?!    
    
    
    #AVBin    
    
    
    Andy Murray has won "Personality of the Year" really??!    
    
    
    @SpursOfficial you have absolutely cocked this up!! Stability is key!    
    
    
    @GaryLineker .won 53.7% of his league games in charge, which is the highest of any Spurs manager since the Premier League era began in 1992.    
    
    
    @ThanetGazette again??!    
    
    
    @GaryLineker @LewisWiltshire if you got it what would the MOTD running order be?    
    
    
    @TopBoobs @davepoflynn I'll give you that Flynn    
    
    
    I'd like to work at @LibertyLondon if I was a bit younger, camper and better looking    
    
    
    You know that massively experienced European coach who has won every trophy going? Tim Sherwood? #AVB #Tottenham    
    
    
    @faithlucy that should be DM surely?!    
    
    
    #sherwoodout    
    
    
    @davepoflynn this is my 7,892nd!    
    
    
    29 years inside is far from ideal! #Lostprophets    
    
    
    #avb would have won that    
    
    
    @BudgensBroadway where you not open at the time?!    
    
    
    @paulfuller did you want to buy your mum candy crush?    
    
    
    @EastKentTom @The_Glass_Jar well done, excellent news, you are living my dream!    
    
    
    @The_Glass_Jar will do, I am looking forward to popping in!    
    
    
    So another exciting, massive improvement to #margate . Welcome @The_Glass_Jar look forward to checking you out!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches about bloody time! Stop milking it!    
    
    
    @kentpoliceroads @kent_police if I was wanted (I am not) there's no way I would get stopped drink driving!!    
    
    
    @rioferdy5 @McInTweet is that ulrika ka ka ka ka?    
    
    
    @davepoflynn unfortunately it is, but you won't be the first to notice! Good luck with it all!    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc creature comforts in harold road, cliftonville, free delivery too    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc @kentprivateeye give them James Beloved, that's a cool name!    
    
    
    Good evening twitter, are you allowed a pet owl? As in a 2 foot high wild bird of prey? Disclaimer: I don't want a pet owl    
    
    
    @Natures_Voice hi, are you allowed to have a pet owl?! Particularly a large one in a small flat?    
    
    
    @davepoflynn fuck all else to do!    
    
    
    It would appear any plans @Ianhwatkins had to be pedophile have been somewhat scuppered by bad journalism! (Not saying he did of course!)    
    
    
    @davepoflynn any "movement"    
    
    
    After day I have 5 days off!! I have not had 5 days off over Christmas for about 18 years!    
    
    
    @Natures_Voice can they? Indoors?! That's bloody ridiculous, what's the world coming twit twoo!    
    
    
    I have noticed I have started tucking my teeshirt into my trousers. I feel I have come of age.    
    
    
    @The_Glass_Jar @EastKentTom I swung past today, looking good. Good luck!    
    
    
        
    
    
    A bloody owl!    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye @4candlespub blimey? You must be a detective or summat?!    
    
    
    @dean_itfc #youveonlydoneabout9daysallyeardealwithitx    
    
    
    @shedseven I would have proper loved to have been there!    
    
    
    It's 1205 therefore drinking Guinness is fine.    
    
    
    I am in the Belgian Bar #Ramsgate. Having an All Day Breakfast. So called because it literally takes all day to arrive!    
    
    
    @LHBmargate when is it?    
    
    
    @ThanetMotorCen that's a beaut!!    
    
    
    @DavidJesudason a murder is for life not just for Christmas    
    
    
    It's Saturday night telly like tonight's that has created the alcohol problems in this country! #brokenbritain    
    
    
    @theboyroos kids films!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa Jesus, pull yourself together!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa It's a soul companion
You can feel it everywhere Lift your hands and voices Free your mind and join us You can feel it in the air    
    
    
    @posiekins hmmm    
    
    
    @theboyroos @posiekins Harry potter    
    
    
    @Lord_Sugar a load of tarts prancing about    
    
    
    @ConMend I bet that think you are a Gaya    
    
    
    @SteveSnooker @robbeckettcomic @BluebellWoodCH no @antanddec ? Bastards.    
    
    
    Has anyone ever used 3G on @o2 in anywhere ever?    
    
    
    @Birdybigbutt45 @The_Glass_Jar you sound full of enthusiasm for another new venture!    
    
    
    @Gemma_Blythe @PRTuk that'll learn 'em    
    
    
    Got to love a traditional "Monday before Christmas Sausage Sandwich"    
    
    
    @posiekins technically    
    
    
    @O2 it's not great, I work in the field and it's generally the case across east Kent regardless of what the postcode checker says.    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks revellers? Thats not very working class yorkshire! London has changed you!    
    
    
    @robbeckettcomic presumably legally?    
    
    
    @ThanetGazette a door fire? A door? Fire?    
    
    
    @peterdav2000 @ZoeMurphyDesign how will you dry the pans if its frames?    
    
    
    @Adem think of all that money you have saved not buying anything at winter wonderland!    
    
    
    Damn you @waitrose with your festive delights! I'm sure it's not that busy every Monday?!    
    
    
    @artistsmakers @RRRamsgate @RamsgateTown I think all these pictures are rubbish!    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye @KentHighways a real good citizen would have shinned up there and made it safe!    
    
    
    @Kent_999s happy Christmas girls!    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye on newington road, spare a thought for lamposts this time of year. Street furniture needs love too. pic.twitter.com/RWDmTZYuS8    
    
    
    @OSLioness @waitrose at 12-13.00 it was utter carnage and not a choc in site!    
    
    
    Gotta love a traditional "1750 on Monday before Christmas beer" an annual delight in our house    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches it was "rammo in the main room" earlier    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ScottWilkins2 @Kent_999s no, a repair truck    
    
    
    This weather is much worse than the "bad weather" a few weeks back!    
    
    
    @DavidThanet course, no credit required! UK Power Networks and Kent Highways were on site if it helps?    
    
    
    @DavidThanet also I didn't ACTUALLY see it blown down!    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches The Streets, Blinded by The Lights    
    
    
    @RealTimVine is an absolute comedy genius!    
    
    
    @SpursOfficial is Daniel Levy actually proper mental?!    
    
    
    @jonawils @davepoflynn seems ludicrous!! AVB was a far safer prospect!    
    
    
    @Huddz8 really?!    
    
    
    @Birdybigbutt45 @The_Glass_Jar  why not pop in and find out?    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 last night was a proper storm too!!    
    
    
    @SkySportsNews oh? I didn't dream that?    
    
    
    @ThanetGazette has to be better than flats!    
    
    
    I just googled "new spurs manager" and up popped @Ianhwatkins , he gets blamed for everything!    
    
    
    Worse job in the world today? Being a @UKPowerNetworks engineer!    
    
    
    I have a child. It does not eat. At all. In 8 days, maybe 2 slices of bread, 1/4 tin of spag, handful carrots, an orange. How do I fix it?    
    
    
    #timsherwood once said pic.twitter.com/Hr5iRV0nbg    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 she must be hungry! She has not eaten! She would easily eat a chocolate bar though!    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 she isn't eating though, yesterday she had half s small tin of spag and a satsuma but that's it, nothing today so far    
    
    
    @GoodDeedLaura thanks, I am convinced its behavioural rather than anything else, frustrating though!    
    
    
    @RRRamsgate I guess there is fruit in it?    
    
    
    @ConMend it's in the last place you will look so look there first    
    
    
    @ConMend where else have you looked since? See I was right!    
    
    
    @thrylmargate any top secret parking spaces I need to know about? We are on our way!    
    
    
    @Adem how do you do that photo thing? How was the footy?    
    
    
    @Fearnecotton looks like the cleaner is having the day off    
    
    
    I do love a proper theatre pic.twitter.com/TcnuBgMggp    
    
    
    @theboyroos oh yes it is    
    
    
    @theboyroos I am going to one day, it will be just as tame as Cinderella    
    
    
    @UKPowerNetworks even the tweets are on hold?! #UKStorm    
    
    
    @ChrisPhilpot @UKPowerNetworks your also probably not the only village?    
    
    
    @ChrisPhilpot fair comment, I have power, I would be the same if not, id let you borrow mine if I could!    
    
    
    I hate the phrase "you and yours" thanks    
    
    
    @ReadingHydro @BritishGasHelp  such a twat http://www.ovoenergy.com/smart-meter-faq/ …    
    
    
    @ReadingHydro they will do!    
    
    
    @rockgod1970  Here is a dog with an arse that looks like Jesus.

Merry Christmas Dave

pic.twitter.com/fBW2TgtEkP”    
    
    
    @SimonBurbage  is this a bizarre social experiment or are you really THAT disorganised?!    
    
    
    @SimonBurbage well I wish you good luck! Update us all!    
    
    
    Luckily we are out for dinner tomorrow, my wife is currently boiling giblets! Why would she do that?    
    
    
    @SimonBurbage good, hope it's a incident free journey! Happy Christmas!    
    
    
    @domisatwit you are on holby!    
    
    
    I've been! pic.twitter.com/0vdlcmIOrx    
    
    
    @dean_itfc  On my Similar To.. Feature on twitter I have discovered you follow @Ginofantastico ? Goodness gracious me    
    
    
    I am sure this is not right? pic.twitter.com/0jGxNKGlrH    
    
    
    When I started out in comedy my inspiration was @rhodgilbertshow he is absolutely different class!    
    
    
    @theboyroos we got him a gram of crack too    
    
    
    @danielswann87 @jaynevenables  not that it helps at all (sorry) elec is "delivered" on 3 phases, you are on different phase to neighbours    
    
    
    @Obonjo it's the only day of the year I do!    
    
    
    @danielswann87 @jaynevenables I work for an energy co and UKP networks are renowned for being shite! (Sorry) hope it's all sorted soon    
    
    
    Everybody should have a child like mine, 0734, still asleep, nice    
    
    
    Bored now!    
    
    
    @Adem that's a bit of a coup! (Also pretty cool) happy Christmas Djemils!    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/2QFvTtF0CA    
    
    
    This is my favourite Christmas present (not my present i hasten to add) but best I've seen pic.twitter.com/UBn5wDLXae    
    
    
    @EastKentTom fuck knows, I am pretty sure it's snide!    
    
    
    @EastKentTom as if D&G ever sat down and said " we need a home range!" It's shit!    
    
    
    Where's ken Barlow? He should be embracing his family at this special time? #Corrie    
    
    
    @shaggystroker @EmMatthews1980 we are here all week!! pic.twitter.com/RLjE2ZN0Dg    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 first your Hev, now your Hayley? I feel your pain x    
    
    
    Will this finish with "Phil Mitchell, YOURE A MUG!!!" @MrDDyer ?    
    
    
    Well that was fun! Hi ho hi ho    
    
    
    @amazon customer service at 0830 on Boxing Day morning is incredible. thank you    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 corrie #asifyoudidntknow    
    
    
    @ThanetCouncil it clearly is!!    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 racist    
    
    
    Boxing Day, the day you feel like a champion in new pants and socks!    
    
    
    @paulfuller least they emailed rather than leave you at station, it's going to rain tonight there won't be trains till March!    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc sorry to hear your news,hope they get them    
    
    
    Anyone know of and ideally recommend a cheap, online kitchen co.?
Loads of people have said order online but no one has said where!!    
    
    
    @RRRamsgate how bizarre!! Just on that site, is it straight forward, ordering etc? Did you design it?    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc the kitchen itself, probably go to AO for appliances    
    
    
    @RRRamsgate ta, I'll look into    
    
    
    @RRRamsgate that's what we have done!    
    
    
    @RRRamsgate nah, we have had them do it twice! They should be about £5000 cheaper then we would buy off them!    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc I think wren are quite expensive, they are opening up Westwood soon, trying to avoid big companies    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc ta, I'll have a look    
    
    
    @LeapFrog is so typically American and so typically over complicated to get working!!    
    
    
    @ThanetCouncil emptying my bins?    
    
    
    @LeapFrog hi, I spoke to someone in UK earlier but no joy, the connect app just doesn't open on windows 8, going to try another machine    
    
    
    @LHBmargate and @The_Glass_Jar both appear to be having a "my burger's better than your burger" contest right here on my timeline?    
    
    
    @ThanetCouncil welcome to Ramsgate in 2013, rubbish overflowing and no street lights. Is there a war on?    
    
    
    @LeapFrog sorted! Took over 2,hours! Installed, uninstalled, reinstalled, error 65, restarted, run as admin, but Connect is now working!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa you snob!    
    
    
    Really, I ask you, is there really any need? pic.twitter.com/IcQbSXUZ5o    
    
    
    @posiekins Christ knows    
    
    
    @theboyroos @posiekins poison!    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 that's even quicker than us!!    
    
    
    @thecomedycow July, the shops are much quieter then    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 we won't get you a wedding present, it'll be in the bin by the Sunday!    
    
    
    How come Shirley has never quipped "oh yeah, my brother is @MrDDyer " you would have thought she'd mention it?    
    
    
    @Adem that'll be a 3 piece box!    
    
    
    @Adem @posiekins plus once the batteries wear out the novelty wears off    
    
    
    @Adem "Emma soon started to regret the chicken coop plan"    
    
    
    @Adem good on you, also can @chrisroos not help out with some chooks? From @gofreerange ?    
    
    
    @amyeee what's that?! Do I need one? Sorry to have missed you (again!!)    
    
    
    @SpursOfficial not that amazing, we conceded 4 against reading!    
    
    
    Just seen a chap quite literally licking a window. In Dover.    
    
    
    @Andrewq1978 it was a special bus    
    
    
    Yeah! I built that! pic.twitter.com/Q5mOYtChj3    
    
    
    @The_Glass_Jar 11? On nye?    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc do you live in @LHBmargate ? Who knew    
    
    
    @NevWilshire_SBM can I have a job? I can't sell anything though!    
    
    
    Tonight is nye in my house, worked all weekend, working NY Day and no sitter (standard) for the real thing tomorrow! Lets drink beer!    
    
    
    Prince William is gonna be a student for 10 weeks? Even I was at Uni longer than that!    
    
    
    @theboyroos will she be only hyper 4 yr old there? and I wouldn't want her being there when @pinkgypsy1 takes her top off!    
    
    
    @davep78 @BritishGasHelp that's a shock, I expect yours is the only tweet they recieved? I can't understand why they didn't reply in 4 mins!    
    
    
    @davep78 @BritishGas ask for a smart meter. Fixed.    
    
    
    @davep78 "butt out"    
    
    
    Tina or no Tina, there's no way Peter Barlow would be ready to go again so quickly!! #corrie    
    
    
    @The_Glass_Jar look like right cox    
    
    
    "Quick, get in the bedroom!" Jeez, he's off again #corrie    
    
    
    @theboyroos @pinkgypsy1 who's that?    
    
    
    Ken won't be happy when he gets home. Oh. #Corrie    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 @theboyroos fuck them off, they can sit for us, we are much beyter    
    
    
    Just realised I was tweeting about #Corrie on my version of NYE! Rock, and indeed roll!    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 pot kettle    
    
    
    Got the wife tickets to see @ChasnHodges (n Dave) @RoyalAlbertHall in April for Christmas, literally cannot wait (gift was for me really!)    
    
    
    @theboyroos @ChasnHodges @RoyalAlbertHall it's going to be the best!!    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 @ChasnHodges @RoyalAlbertHall come, you will love it!    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 @ChasnHodges @RoyalAlbertHall margate?    
    
    
    @ChrisBComedian what will you replace everything you have quit with?    
    
    
    @pinkgypsy1 got a tweet off Chas from Chas n Dave! I'm well jel!    
    
    
    @theboyroos @pinkgypsy1 yup! I am legend    
    
    
    @Adem @theboyroos @pinkgypsy1 @Specsavers no, that doesn't count at all    
    
    
    @thrylmargate visting @thrylmargate    
    
    
    Did @dryathlon last year, what will this years challenge be?    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 @dryathlon challenge??    
    
    
    @dryathlon nah, last year getting sponsorship was literally like getting blood out of a stone, much less stress to drink!    
    
    
    Thanks @HarveysHQ for getting sofas fixed, good luck with the 2014 year long sale!    
    
    
    @HarveysHQ I suspect there will only be 8 days of the year  you DON'T have a sale!    
    
    
    I built that pic.twitter.com/efSr8q1EHy    
    
    
    @qprrforme as if I would look up the instructions online? What do you take me for?!    
    
    
    @theboyroos really is ok, but @pinkgypsy1 ? She's just the greatest!    
    
    
    We are playing a brilliant game, this is one of the cards! pic.twitter.com/fuHgOodOkQ    
    
    
    @Adem we were just talking about you, and how you've changed x    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Adem sorry?!    
    
    
    @SydneyFun @peterdav2000 London totally pissed on them!    
    
    
    Probably. Best. NYE. Ever. X    
    
    
    I may as well do @dryathlon again this year, it's 0903 and I've not had a drink yet! #willpower #easy    
    
    
    @BritishGasHelp blimey joe, you are putting the hours in recently!    
    
    
    We had 2 men round yesterday to quote to repair our roof, the quotes were £420 and £60!    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks a while back we had a quote for £600, it's just random numbers out of a hat!    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 oddly, but more sensibly, the £420 one    
    
    
    @BritishGasHelp you and me both! If anyone asks you about their broken meter in east Kent tell them the engineer is busy, thanks!    
    
    
    @MadgeHooks I don't think you are taking this very seriously!    
    
    
    Oh, let me die where I lie, beneath the curse of my lovers eyes    
    
    
    @marlowetheatre I think it's terrible you employ a murderess as "Good Fairy" I must inform the authorities (unless I can have 3 free tix?!)    
    
    
    How can Ole Gunnar Solksjaer be @CardiffCityFC manager? He is about 7! #solskjaer    
    
    
    Bloody idiots on @BBCRadio2 earlier moaning about @MPSinthesky grrrr!!    
    
    
    Had a weak moment earlier , went into @Tesco , 1st time in months, left my mars bar on till, miserable cow wouldn't give me replacement!!    
    
    
    @Tesco that's 60p you owe me Tesco!!    
    
    
    @posiekins @BBCRadio2 @MPSinthesky saying they should not take pictures out of the helicopter as they are paid by taxpayers    
    
    
    @Tesco I know! I only had a mars  cos were no snickers left! Terrible! It was Manston and the stroppy cow on self serve said not handed in!    
    
    
    @Tesco there's a lot the store can do, 1) try smiling, she really must hate her job!    
    
    
    @Tesco  2) does she really think I am going to try and con Tesco out of 60p?    
    
    
    @Tesco 3)does she really think I would walk across a car park in the bloody rain? For a mars bar?   Unless I'd paid for it? Receipt in hand?    
    
    
    @Tesco manston, Ramsgate    
    
    
    @Tesco I'm not asking you to do anything beyond understanding the principles of common courtesy and the basics of good customer service?    
    
    
    @Adem and you a chicken lover? Terrible!    
    
    
    @Adem @amyeee it was alive once. Chickens have feelings too!    
    
    
    @ConMend I think you should have stood a bit further away to take picture    
    
    
    Who the bloody hell,is Gemma Collins?    
    
    
    @emilyeavis @GlastoFest can I get tickets by post or by calling in person please?    
    
    
    @Adem @Andrewq1978 neither big nor clever    
    
    
    @ginger_nats I don't know what TOWIE is no matter how big you say it?    
    
    
    @theboyroos @Adem @Andrewq1978 have you ever actually been to Liverpool? Do you know where Liverpool is?    
    
    
    I was on the London Underground today, "the Tube" if you're a local. Someone aboard had Jesus as her iPhone screensaver, underground!!    
    
    
    @peterdav2000 what's it about?    
    
    
    @peterdav2000 @CarltonCinema it's brilliant!    
    
    
    @peterdav2000 you are welcome, obviously never seen my stand up!!    
    
    
    @peterdav2000 oh.    
    
    
    Ah, Dolly was a dolly #takemeout    
    
    
    @razdaz66 been to the special car park again today, I'm now a regular!    
    
    
    @dean_itfc Have you been saving all you tweets up for one onslaught?    
    
    
    I have joined @LinkedIn not sure what, how or why, is anyone on there "Shelf Filler at Asda"? Rather than "Head of Replenishment at Asda"?    
    
    
    @kentprivateeye @posiekins @LinkedIn oh, "deletes"    
    
    
    @Gemma_Blythe brilliant oicture    
    
    
    @ThanetGazette @ShepherdNeame it's well over due!! It's looking very shabby    
    
    
    @MPSinthesky if you didnt take that picture I would have to go through life having never seen that and that would be bad! Well done!    
    
    
    @The_Glass_Jar time for a price review?!    
    
    
    I have probably updated my facebook status more times this year then for all of 2013, not good    
    
    
    @alfiemoore everyone knows even the dr can't fix the gays!    
    
    
    @BudgensBroadway what about @TomThumbTheatre ?    
    
    
    @The_Glass_Jar no, but I hope to rectify this soon, hope it's going well?    
    
    
    I went to a really nice hotel today, it was in sittingbourne!! #thingsyouneverthoughtyoudsee    
    
    
    @SkintLondon @tubbsmcguire what if he's married? I am guessing he won't be for much longer!    
    
    
    @RamsgateMH LA to Ramsgate? Wow    
    
    
    I am not shocked by #benefitsstreet one little bit.  This is real life, I meet similar people every single day. (Most are nob heads!)    
    
    
    Fun Guy looks a right bundle of laughs! #benefitsstreet    
    
    
    @smellynat82 it's real life my love!    
    
    
    @smellynat82 there's areas I go where you would be seen as the disgrace!    
    
    
        
    
    
    No, no, no, this is not right at all #livingdolls    
    
    
    Feck my actual luck! The http://femskin.com  website is down! #livingdolls    
    
    
    It's got a beautiful face? Oh, no in comparison to your missus, I'll give you that one #livingdolls    
    
    
    @RoyalBarkBisc sssh, I'm trying to watch!    
    
    
    @posiekins then you'll never know    
    
    
    @JasonManford Southend has a season?!    
    
    
    @MarkSimmonsHaHa @St_StoneStudios does work in progress mean it may be shit?    
    
    
    I hope to launch a little business this year, can't be hard can it?    
    
    
    @Adem I've not entirely thought it out but it will need a web presence!!    
    
    
    @posiekins lend us a quid then    
    
    
    @posiekins booze!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @posiekins retail, unless I can muster up £20,000 then pub    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches I thought you was building up to a big announcement (again!!)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jurassiccoastin @MissSeaPeaches Lucy!! You could have bloody told him, that's a bit wrong!!    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches @jurassiccoastin ooo touchy, must be the hormones    
    
    
    @theboyroos @posiekins I'm crap at home brew! And you can't sell it!!    
    
    
    @posiekins is it cheap?    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches a date and a venue? That's it done surely?    
    
    
    @theboyroos UNDATEABLES IS BACK TOMORROW!!!!    
    
    
    Good news! “@BoycottTesco: Tesco struggling to get back on track as sales fall 2.4pc | via @Telegraph http://fw.to/q1wnxyT "    
    
    
    Quiet please the #Undateables is on    
    
    
    @GoonerMan2 definately not that one!    
    
    
    @theboyroos yup! Got in from call out with 10mins spare! Forgot the milk! Twat!    
    
    
    Hayley's sister is hot #Undateables    
    
    
        
    
    
    As well as #undateables the @jowhiley show on @BBCRadio2 is totally incredible tonight!    
    
    
    @ChrisBComedian I think Holly would like Trevor    
    
    
    @theboyroos will you fancy me?    
    
    
    @theboyroos @MissSeaPeaches @pinkgypsy1 was your first date like this? Look at you now!    
    
    
    It was all going well with Hayley and Chris until she made the fatal error of letting him meet her very tasty little sister #Undateables    
    
    
    Easy, jet! #Undateables    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 you would be all over it!    
    
    
    Eh?? Where's #kavos gone?!    
    
    
    My new favourite thing like ever pic.twitter.com/ca0cD9ddrf    
    
    
    @Adem how many played?    
    
    
    @BowsKitchen you open tomorrow??    
    
    
    @BowsKitchen 745? For 4?    
    
    
    @BowsKitchen excellent! I literally cannot wait!!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa how's business?    
    
    
    Do you #shoplocal ? Had a knackered dyson, took it to this fella in #margate and it's fixed! Good as new, £20!! pic.twitter.com/PH9S9v89MN    
    
    
    @Adem is that a starvation diet?!    
    
    
    What did dads do at dance schools before the Internet?    
    
    
    @SpursOfficial why does the game not get postponed? Surely a better idea?    
    
    
    @LHBmargate are you open to commoners tonight? Should have time to say hello!    
    
    
    @GaryLineker is there more than one in Canada?    
    
    
    Hair of the dog? pic.twitter.com/W26tOeE8yF    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa are you a former smoker?    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa no because it is filthy dirty scummy! But I am genuinely impressed! Well done! Bet B&H goes bust now!    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa if I send you a daily tweet knocking you down and saying you'll never do it, will it help?    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa I'LL GIVE YOU A WEEK!! How has Hayley taken the news??!    
    
    
    A most delightful evening had by all with brilliant food @BowsKitchen and delicious ale @aleandcider , as good as it gets    
    
    
        
    
    
    @robbeckettcomic @lionsdencomedy touché    
    
    
    @robbeckettcomic there's always a slot for you at Christchurch SU (CT10 campus)    
    
    
    Sash my loves #benefitsstreet is on    
    
    
    I will forever be grateful to White Dee for my most successful tweet to date #benefitsstreet    
    
    
    Woah! Surely you can't live with a 15.5 yr old wife in UK even if legal in your own country? #benefitsstreet    
    
    
    focussing on  wrong people on #benefitsstreet , the hard workers living in fear of their lives or the actual scrounging scum?    
    
    
    My job takes me to all the best places, said me at no time ever    
    
    
    I do suspect if I was a celeb in the 60s and 70s I would have been in court today #operationyewtree    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 you've been in hiding since 1998!    
    
    
    There's a Chinese takeaway in St Mary's Bay and it's proudly displaying its 3/5 food hygiene rating in its window, this makes me queasy!    
    
    
    @amyeee hello The Girl, can you ask The Boy if a thing for listening to iPod whilst swimming is a good thing? What's the thing called?    
    
    
    @theboyroos @amyeee alright don't go overboard!! Was it good? Why did she get rid?    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa still an ox? Will power alone or crystal meth?    
    
    
    @kathlaaaa well done! After a week it's easy, just ask Pete Doherty    
    
    
    Sonia has done alright for herself.  Martin must be kicking himself.    
    
    
    @MissSeaPeaches I went to loads!! Was dragged! Hop farm one is good if back home or detling    
    
    
        
    
    
    Not sure i can watch #findingmumanddad I'm out!    
    
    
    @PeppaPigUK is getting her very special package!    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/6C7GRJejSw    
    
    
    I like eyes #TheUndateables    
    
    
        
    
    
    “@GaryLineker: Over 2 hours to a call centre. My personal best. Thrilled! Thanks BT.” Wonder what @BTCare would say?    
    
    
    He's gone ever so pale! #TheUndateables    
    
    
    They'll be married by the time the profiteroles come out #TheUndateables    
    
    
    Not sure if this year we will make the normal trip to @CenterParcsUK , I think we will give #sunnybeach a try instead    
    
    
    @posiekins I assume that's a joke?!    
    
    
    @posiekins you should go to sunny beach, right up your street    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kathlaaaa I know! The C!    
    
    
    44 years after Ken Barlow squeezed your tits you stand up in court and talk about it? 44 years? Please! #freetheweatherfieldone    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 you are safe for 30 years at least!    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 it will be called Operation Thorley    
    
    
    @msjenniferjames I'm not even starting with this    
    
    
    #freetheweatherfieldone    
    
    
    @SkyNewsBreak one of the first places I would have looked!!    
    
    
    @posiekins @Andrewq1978 @SkyNewsBreak we see the obvious without going round the houses?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @posiekins @Andrewq1978 they must of, that's why it took 3 days to find him, they knew he was there but wanted to be sure    
    
    
    @dean_itfc Simon has one in his van!    
    
    
    @dean_itfc the love juice of Ken Barlow. Probably.    
    
    
    @Adem course it does you are King Djemil of the DIY People!    
    
    
    @christchurchsu https://www.facebook.com/events/487588791352635/ …    
    
    
    @WOBroadstairs https://www.facebook.com/events/487588791352635/ …    
    
    
    @WOMargate https://www.facebook.com/events/487588791352635/ …    
    
    
    @WORamsgate https://www.facebook.com/events/487588791352635/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kathlaaaa and he stormed it?    
    
    
    @christchurchsu someone had a good night!    
    
    
    @rockgod1970 @ThanetGazette @Nigel_Farage is that you in the onsie?    
    
    
    #margate let itself down with the @Nigel_Farage protest today, most of them goons probably didnt even know what they were protesting about!    
    
    
    Parenting skills have nothing to do with being on benefits! They are due to intelligence and common sense #benefitsstreet    
    
    
    @theboyroos I've got loads, shall I pop some round?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Gemma_Blythe what? Everything was 49.5p? Bargain!    
    
    
    "A period of real hardship" feck off! #restorationman    
    
    
    @JasonManford shall I bother saving up for this? pic.twitter.com/KiDjj8Lr7P    
    
    
    