Deleting old domains and sub-domains I haven't used in over 4 years    
    
    
    Who knows when the domains I haven't use for three years may come in useful!    
    
    
    @ashley_brown its a shame you never shared an office with @mishra_alok, you could have complained to each other about the temperature allday    
    
    
    Fired up the EEE PC today for the first time in 6 months. Couldn't remember the password or how to open the terminal.    
    
    
    http://bighugelabs.com/onblack.php?id=3880287244&size=large … For thoughs who miss magic eye    
    
    
    On OS X, if I've got a folder of 1000 images named n.png, what's the easiest way to glue them into a movie with each image shown for 1/10s?    
    
    
    If you ported SETI@home to JS posting results back to SETI via JSONP, people would unknowingly search for ET while viewing your pages    
    
    
    ...if Facebook did it we'd be chatting with the Soup Dragon by lunch time    
    
    
    To keep up with each new open source project in a different language -- my next project will be in bash    
    
    
    Strange day at work discussing legal vs moral, portrayal vs intention, right vs wrong. Plus problems with Capitalism and Britain cc @blahpro    
    
    
    @blahpro #ceowithphilosophydegree /cc @ashley_brown    
    
    
    @zacharyvoase You'll want to add item semantics (maybe user as well) to work with small enough samples to attract smaller clients    
    
    
    @blahpro what about the mouse ;-)    
    
    
    @ashley_brown Hal?    
    
    
    My adventures with Infographic CVs: http://numenore.co.uk/wiki/cv     
    
    
    @blahpro A pigeon has a longer call than a dove's coo (will demonstrate in the office)    
    
    
    I'm sure the "expert" on the today program just said there were 100,000 milliseconds in a second    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly I secretly buy 3, surreptitiously eat the first, then share "one each" with my wife    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly I love cupcakes because I can eat a whole cake (or two!) without feeling guilty #nationalcupcakeweek    
    
    
    For anyone confused by paralympic codes: http://bit.ly/qDO2rN     
    
    
    @duncanr2 Sadly I bought @jancyoverell one as an anniversary present    
    
    
    How I spent my day: http://bit.ly/pvH2XS  http://youtu.be/rOFFD4Fmfis  -- it's been a silly day    
    
    
    @peerindex Any chance of a periodic release of the top tweeters by PI like the Alexa 1M download http://bit.ly/WXWD /cc @azeem    
    
    
    @shadchnev If it's important, Google will stick it in my priority inbox    
    
    
    This is me: http://xkcd.com/606/  /cc @blahpro    
    
    
    Our wedding singer is supporting @DaveGorman on tour! Go see them both /cc @jayforeman    
    
    
    @shadchnev Clearly you are a bad person #2020hindsight    
    
    
    Surely this means we're less than 10 years away from time-travel: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-15017484 …    
    
    
    @blahpro just the one?    
    
    
    Just designed a chair -- time to order wood    
    
    
    Watching the @kahnacademy requirements for @aiclass    
    
    
    @milkroundabout How do we go about getting http://spider.io  involved in #milkroundabout?    
    
    
    @andykent @teabass Good work with the #lnug meetup -- very interesting talks    
    
    
    @shadchnev Invisible Hand is plugged on XKCD (almost) http://xkcd.org/958/     
    
    
    Deciding whether to defend my "best pumpkin decorated by an adult" trophy #pirtonpumpkins    
    
    
    @ashley_brown I can only assume you don't have a trophy to defend    
    
    
    First spider.io Blog Post: How To Catch A Bot http://spider.io/2011/09/how-to-catch-a-bot/ …    
    
    
    Just updated my publications page: http://bit.ly/mT38UT . For people that like pictures: http://bit.ly/qwodhq     
    
    
    Quora iPhone app is very snazzy    
    
    
    iPhone Assistant/Siri looks pretty amazing - keen to see the habits and trend analysis that powers the personalisation reverse engineered    
    
    
    It's not the winning, it's the taking part that counts...    
    
    
    Highly remmend listening to Will Self's monologue on prisons currently available on the BBC and only 10 minutes long    
    
    
    Looking forward to tomorrow's #TWTC1 with @aleksk -- heading back to my old home: @imperialcollege    
    
    
    @crowquine keep plugging @milkroundabout #TWTC1    
    
    
    Q for the panel: do we need to teach what the Internet is and how content is created as well as how code is created? #TWTC1    
    
    
    Q for Emma & Jeff: how young should CS be taught and form should this take? #TWTC1    
    
    
    @shadchnev Isn't that what Google's for?    
    
    
    Being a responsible adult is rubbish    
    
    
    Overly excited by my 4 seconds of fame on @guardiantw with @aleksk @crowquine @hubmum et. al http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/blog/audio/2011/oct/12/tech-weekly-tech-city-skills-education-audio … plus spider.io name check    
    
    
    Truly stunned at the legal battle between @acton and @ladygaga. Does no one have a sense of humor anymore? http://www.guardian.co.uk/music/2011/oct/13/lady-gaga-injunction-lady-goo-goo …    
    
    
    @richardprice100 isn't that the idea of Google+ hangouts?    
    
    
    Cavity wall insulation for @littledudes now finished!    
    
    
    Am halfway through building a somewhat unconventional chair -- a few more week-ends to go.    
    
    
    Stumbled across Apache Stanbol for the first time: http://incubator.apache.org/stanbol/     
    
    
    Of the people I know who signed up for @aiclass, only @duncanr2 remains committed -- good work!    
    
    
    Looking forward to @milkroundabout - Send any devs who want to have fun scaling a massive real time system over to the spider.io stand #SMR    
    
    
    Sums up @ScienceWeekly aptly: http://static.guim.co.uk/sys-images/Guardian/Pix/pictures/2011/9/30/1317394560539/Stephen-Collins-Vague-sci-002.jpg …    
    
    
    @mashable Am convinced Microsoft's takeover of Y! is inevitable -- the question is when and for how much --> http://on.mash.to/qwIHCZ     
    
    
    Siri as an entry point for apps seems inevitable -- will be very interesting to see how apple handle this    
    
    
    "Wikipedia Real-Time Challenge" This could lead to something amazing - wish I had time to participate http://www.mediawiki.org/wiki/October_2011_Coding_Challenge/Real-Time …    
    
    
    Our latest blog post: "The Problem With Client-Side Analytics" http://spider.io/blog/2011/10/the-problem-with-client-side-analytics/ …    
    
    
    Made me smile: http://thedailywtf.com/Articles/Rock-amp8216n-Bowl-Champion.aspx#Pic2 …    
    
    
    X-Factor Tracker -- Genius -- http://xfactortracker.com/about/     
    
    
    @PhilipTromans has just snatched the lead from @chrisdarby89 in the spider.io challenge. #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    Surely someone can get more than 10 clues in the spider.io challenge. #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    @steve_barham glad to see you make it onto the leader board. Keep digging for more codes and clues. #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    @steve_barham one more code and you'll be top of the leader board! #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    Is @alol going to take the top spot from @steve_barham in the spider.io challenge? #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    @alol Fantastic! If you're at @milkroundabout, come and say hello to us.    
    
    
    @grisch, @alol and @steve_barham can stand tall today as spider champions. The rest of you: Can you hack it? #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    At #twtc2    
    
    
    #twtc2 Startups primarily need cheap serviced office space -- waiting 6 weeks for a broadband connection as open reach dictate causes pain    
    
    
    #twtc2 Q Eric: Startups are solving their own problems re recruitment & office space.We can't solve OpenReach's broadband monopoly-comment?    
    
    
    #twtc2 we (@spider_io) will also be at @milkroundabout    
    
    
    #twtc2 "Eric Pickles" we can take a pick axe to the strand and lay are own broadband    
    
    
    Have bitched directly to Eric Pickles about the fiasco of the Open Reach monopoly. Weight, shoulders, lifted. #twtc2    
    
    
    @PhilipTromans & @Peterspider both in spitting distance of completing the spider.io challenge - final push? #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    Top work by @Edgemaster in the #spider_io challenge. If your at @milkroundabout on Sunday come over and say hi!    
    
    
    A thing of beauty: http://thedailywtf.com/Articles/The-Query-of-Despair.aspx …    
    
    
    @aiclass is still down :-(    
    
    
    Fun from the Internet: http://www.newlaunches.com/entry_images/0911/14/webchicks.php …    
    
    
    I hate in @aiclass when he says "This is a none trivial question that may take you a while"    
    
    
    @rpstac What is this "outside of London" place you talk about?    
    
    
    On my way to the first #spider_io hackday! /cc @blahpro @edds @Vegard_uk @ashley_brown @chmod755_d    
    
    
    Heading to @milkroundabout tomorrow? Come over to the @spider_io stand, and try http://challenge.spider.io     
    
    
    Logistics! On my way to meet a van driver and a Viking to move epic amounts of stuff to @milkroundabout    
    
    
    Great day recruiting at @milkroundabout. Lots of enthusiasm from people wanting to solve hard engineering problems! Time for sleep now #smr    
    
    
    Startup life: spend your Sunday with the whole company at a recruitment fair in a gazebo. It's hard work but I love it /cc @spider_io    
    
    
    @GoSquared good to meet you at @milkroundabout. Keen on your thoughts on my recent blog post: http://spider.io/blog/2011/10/the-problem-with-client-side-analytics/ … /cc @spider_io    
    
    
    One I'm sure @bengoldacre will appreciate: http://xkcd.org/     
    
    
    Over 50 people on the #spider_io challenge leaderboard http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    @willdangerfield Not far to go! #spider_io challenge    
    
    
    Can anyone recommend a good statistics reference book? Must have standard tables,tests,assumptions and rationales-fed up googling everything    
    
    
    @aiclass When are the next modules and the reading list going to be put up?    
    
    
    @willdangerfield Great work! Have you checked out our careers page? http://spider.io/careers/     
    
    
    @darkip Keep digging, you're nearly there! #spider_io    
    
    
    Does anyone out there understand http://batch.com/  ? Looks like facebook photo sharing for hipsters.    
    
    
    @duncanr2 We have a white board to get rid of if you can transport it from London    
    
    
    @duncanr2 we've painted the office in whiteboard paint :-) #spider_io    
    
    
    A series of AI/NLP web services have just been released by Complexity Intelligence (http://www.complexityintelligence.com/en/homepage ): http://intellexere.com/en/homepage     
    
    
    Have booked tickets to see Red Hot Chili Peppers at Knebworth next year :-)    
    
    
    @beth_tk Sentiment analysis as a service seems to be a hot topic, that's the third service I've seen in as many weeks.    
    
    
    Exciting new geo database: http://georama-project.labs.exalead.com/gazetiki.htm  (for GIR fun)    
    
    
    Sunday 8th July 2012 the Olympic Torch will be carried from Letchworth to Stevenage    
    
    
    For those that missed @milkroundabout: http://youtu.be/upvDMiZRzgU     
    
    
    Too cross to use the internet    
    
    
    Still too cross to use the Internet    
    
    
    @ashley_brown This is more than indirectly your fault :-) http://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/duty_calls.png …    
    
    
    Glad to see @ag1122496850 (nee @anthonygraham1) has stopped lying on his linked in profile http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=68580618 … /cc @aston_carter    
    
    
    If your job was to provide the highest quality of water, would you urinate in the reservoir? /cc @ag1122496850 (nee @anthonygraham1)    
    
    
    @Skaffen We've seen recruiters we use with false details on linked-in profiles to gain people's confidence. This makes them harder to trust.    
    
    
    Spider Towers is in the middle of a Student Process -- Just locked the door    
    
    
    Over 400 people have taken the #spider_io challenge http://challenge.spider.io/  -- can you hack it?    
    
    
    @Nick_Franklin That's a pretty bad CPM    
    
    
    Feeling very smug with myself having fixed our central heating    
    
    
    Feeling 5 years out of touch. Busy playing Portal and Rick Rolling.    
    
    
    @aiclass Are any institutions certifying the course in the UK?    
    
    
    @aiclass is there only one unit this week?    
    
    
    #THappcircus I clearly don't "get" eeve. On the other hand I'm sold on echoecho.    
    
    
    Slickflick is another one  I don't get - I must be getting old #THappcircus    
    
    
    Siine Writer -- the Optimus Keyboard didn't take off, will personalised keyboards work as an app? #THappcircus    
    
    
    Will "Find My Friends" kill "Echo Echo" out of the find my friends apps    
    
    
    I just donated to #Wikipedia, if use and value the service, and can afford it, you should to.    
    
    
    @shadchnev worth every penny. I'm surprised my corporates don't donate. #Wikipedia    
    
    
    I can't imagine this site ever being used for copyright infringement: http://uberzet.com/     
    
    
    Over halfway through @aiclass and still on 100%    
    
    
    I'm increasingly convinced "Men are from mars, women are from Venus"-esque gender differences are a product of society rather than biology    
    
    
    I've asked the same question on Quora, Linkedin and Academia -- we'll see who gives the highest quality answers.    
    
    
    Live opposite me: http://bit.ly/tSCdwu     
    
    
    @teabass doesn't this make it trivially easy for someone to spoof your AB testing?    
    
    
    @teabass If you do everything server side, the fact that you're even doing AB testing is concealed.    
    
    
    Was served notice by a squatter today #startuplife    
    
    
    Very disappointed with @PhotoBox cutting off the sides of my print :-(    
    
    
    @duncanr2 Your mission for the next 7 days is to find as many uses as possible for you found-thing-a-mi-jig    
    
    
    Only a h-index of 7, more writing needed! http://scholar.google.com.au/citations?user=dGTxOQcAAAAJ …    
    
    
    Keen to get "to dog-food" recognised as a verb. e.g. That <company> need to dog-food more. Are you dog-fooding?    
    
    
    It means use your own product.    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet If you don't dog-food the dog food, how can improve the User eXperience? Metrics (e.g. tale velocity) are not enough.    
    
    
    Epic failure from @blahpro and @chmod755_d on assembling a cardboard desk in 3 minutes    
    
    
    @shadchnev I'm sure you dog-food @InvisibleHandHQ #newverbinaction    
    
    
    Realised this morning I haven't shaved for almost a month    
    
    
    You know you're a Computer Scientist if when queueing you worry more about complexity and queueing theory than what you're queueing for.    
    
    
    Thinking for too much about the complexity and optimal organisation of cloakrooms    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet sleeping well? Everything as you left it, in it's rightful place? #yulelads    
    
    
    Cleaning up my linked in profile (or making it messier depending on your point of view)    
    
    
    Spend the last few weeks trying to work through the maths behind a HMM -- worth the effort for anyone interested in Baysian statistics    
    
    
    Clearly it's not Christmas yet as no sign of @unixspiders christmas tree e-mail.    
    
    
    I imagine it went a bit Kissmetrics at the GoDaddy office this week    
    
    
    What did the Internet look like today? http://youtu.be/a9SnO-ACOI4  Merry Christmas    
    
    
    My new years resolution (via Facebook UX) "Data informed, not data driven"    
    
    
    571 out of the top 1,000 web sites set cookies -- the ICO has a lot of work to do by May    
    
    
    Of the top 1,000 web sites @nydnnews and @mashable are the worst offenders when it comes to tags, web bugs, pixels and beacons    
    
    
    Working from home between Christmas and New Year: http://www.ddiy.co/wp-content/uploads/Work-from-home-considerations.png …    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet is that your creation?    
    
    
    Writing a website from scratch(ish) for the first time in nearly two years. Will shortly be updating my homepage for the first time in 4.    
    
    
    11 chinese lanterns over #hitchin, must be #2012    
    
    
    @blahpro on manlab they sent a videocamera into space for under £1k outside Cambridge - #hackday? http://bit.ly/yXd9az     
    
    
    Just updated my website. Post me any thoughts: http://numenore.co.uk/stuff  http://numenore.co.uk/publications     
    
    
    Just written a simple portfolio CMS to power my updated website, will post to GitHub after a little more tidying.    
    
    
    Making snappy Ajaxy sites gracefully degrade where not supported use to be for older browsers and now seems for Search Engines    
    
    
    @beth_tk Many thanks for the feedback -- now fixed!    
    
    
    Have just realised while SEO people keep bothering me on twitter #facepalm    
    
    
    Why aren't you following @the90slife?    
    
    
    @richardprice100 Surely it's in Big G's interest to overstate their proportion causing you to concentrate effort on them #cynical    
    
    
    RT: @mashable This Swiss Army Knife Comes With a 1 TB USB Flash Drive - http://on.mash.to/zNOu6w  <-- A USB drive you can't take in hand luggage    
    
    
    Map reduce over MTurk. All of TED in 6 words: http://www.ted.com/talks/sebastian_wernicke_1000_tedtalks_6_words.html …    
    
    
    Prediction for 2012: Microsoft will ramp up their acquisition strategy online with some big spending    
    
    
    Best bookshops in #London: UCL Waterstones and Wellcome Trust Bookshop    
    
    
    Have added an easter egg to my site leading to a series of challenges    
    
    
    Just signed up for this: http://www.theblenheimtriathlon.com/     
    
    
    Aiming to read at least 3 books a month in 2012 after last years poor showing of one book in 5 months    
    
    
    Google's #SOPA protest page links to Vint Cerf's Wikipedia page, which is blacked out due to #SOPA protest    
    
    
    @rpstac t-shirts!?!    
    
    
    htaccess is a bitch to debug (but worth it when it works smoothly)    
    
    
    @beth_tk as an undergraduate, when we had mice, we set 3 traps with different bait and placed bets on what the mouse would go for    
    
    
    After a talk on Alan Turing at the BCS last week I went to the pub with 3 colleagues, this is what we spoke about: http://bit.ly/zWAuGI     
    
    
    Wittgenstein should get more credit as a founder of Computer Science    
    
    
    @01factory Surely Wittgenstein's Tractatus is the foundation for programming languages and logic used in day to day Software Developement?    
    
    
    Watched the start of Star Wars Uncut: Director's Cut: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ezeYJUz-84 … Great fun!    
    
    
    @O2 sends your phone number to every website you visit. If they don't fix this in the next 48hours I'll be changing carrier.    
    
    
    @O2 I expect you're going to be getting a phone call from the ICO shortly. If one of you has visited their site they have you number.    
    
    
    Today is probably a bad day to be working at @O2 http://conversation.which.co.uk/technology/o2-sharing-mobile-phone-number-network-provider/ … #shitmeetfan    
    
    
    @O2 can I assume you will make a public announcement of the data breach (as reqd by the ICO) and tell users what you've leaked and to whom?    
    
    
    @charlesarthur Surely a mobile number is PII as you just need to phone it to identify the person.    
    
    
    Glad I'm not the Information Officer at @O2, @ICOnews are about to give them a call #privacywhatprivacy    
    
    
    @charlesarthur Someone rings claiming to be @O2, they know your phone no., model and the last site you visited. Could easily gain PII info.    
    
    
    Learn how to build the next Google: http://www.udacity.com/     
    
    
    Have sent something a bit like a philosophy paper to something a bit like peer review /cc  @01factory @duncanr2    
    
    
    They don't make music videos like this anymore: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aFd5Cci_pE4 …    
    
    
    @beth_tk The relationship of Mundanity to Happiness - I'm looking for feedback before I stick it on my website (a private beta). Interested?    
    
    
    Aiming for 3 books a month in 2012. One month almost down and so far so good: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#books     
    
    
    Google+ have hit 100M users but how many of those are active users? I'd like to see some FB vs G+ engagement stats    
    
    
    @duncanr2 Next you need "just f***ing #evi it" which takes you to the app with prefilled search if installed, otherwise the iTunes store    
    
    
    The best thing about owning a house: no one stops you spray painting the stairs :-)    
    
    
    Spray painting our stairs: http://on.fb.me/yyEFlc     
    
    
    Just fixed the graceful degradation and search engine friendly links on my website    
    
    
    Best mobile portal I've seen: http://everything.me/     
    
    
    From the public's perspective the major result of patents is to keep monopolistic pricing in a competitive market #brokensystem    
    
    
    The "C" in "CSV" stands for comma, if your data is TAB separated, its a "TSV", the clue is in the name.    
    
    
    Any startup experiencing technical growing pains should read this and realise the journey they're starting: http://highscalability.com/blog/2012/2/13/tumblr-architecture-15-billion-page-views-a-month-and-harder.html …    
    
    
    Google expanding it's AI offering (and squeezing some value out of the Freebase aquisition): http://mashable.com/2012/02/13/google-knowledge-graph-change-search/ …    
    
    
    @KieranO James Dyson's autobiography is well worth a read.    
    
    
    A summary of what I think is wrong with the patent system: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#patentsystem …    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet As a patent author yourself, what are your views on the swapping disclosure for protection?    
    
    
    Updated my thoughts on patents based on @borkurdotnet's follow up: http://bit.ly/wQa1Yg  http://bit.ly/wLgttT     
    
    
    @richardprice100 Congratulations!    
    
    
    Surely "Top Gear" is just a bad remake of "Last of the Summer Wine"    
    
    
    Fixed back button support on my website (Ajax fun for a Sunday afternoon) /cc @chmod755_d    
    
    
    Two vertical social networks hit a 1m members within 2 weeks of each other: http://bit.ly/yqNKCc  http://bit.ly/Ax6kNa  @academia @playfire    
    
    
    Have swapped from the Tweetdeck to Twitter desktop and Facebook menubar -- much happier    
    
    
    Can anyone recommend a Garden Contractor new  #Hitchin to help remove a treestump /cc @Hitchinites @louiseyexley @hitchinlife @AdvertiserSue    
    
    
    @louiseyexley Fantastic! I'll call them for a quote shortly.    
    
    
    My ramblings on Ebooks: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#ebooks     
    
    
    Playing with 3D graphics for the first time since my undergrad days. This time with three.js rather than OpenGL.    
    
    
    A late #FF @StartupLJackson @DEVOPS_BORAT and @UXYoda    
    
    
    The specific gravity of my soon-to-be beer is 1.011 -- a little while until it'll be ready    
    
    
    On Deal Or No Deal: "The Gambling Commission does not seem to think that there is any skill element to the show." #noshit    
    
    
    Data Scientists are the new Quantitative Analysts #blackisthenewblack    
    
    
    Thank @FirstCapitalConnect for locking me captive on a train, only to miss the next one from Kings X.    
    
    
    @JofArnold Joining Lemmings and Tetris & Sudoku --> "Super Mario is NP-complete. http://www.newscientist.com/article/mg21328565.100-mario-is-hard-and-thats-mathematically-official.html …"    
    
    
    There are currently three copies of @ericries' book in our office. Presumably the #leanerstartups only have one.    
    
    
    There needs to be a campaign to answer "#Spartacus" when asked your name at @starbucks    
    
    
    @danversbaillieu Congratulations on the startup move, you seem to have cemented your position as startup scene celebrity :-)    
    
    
    When did £4 a pint become acceptable in pubs? (I appreciate its been standard in rip off music venues and clubs for some time)    
    
    
    @beth_tk BT kindly left us without Internet for 6 weeks after our last office move :-(    
    
    
    @easyjet Our Luton-Lisbon flight is V delayed and you've txtd me offering us refreshments - there is no information desk, who do I speak to?    
    
    
    Plane delayed. Keeping myself amused: http://bit.ly/HhV8Aj     
    
    
    @richardprice100 I'd have thought with a combination of location and time, it'd be pretty straight forward    
    
    
    @LetchworthCtre I'm very disappointed in your support of homeopathy and hope you appreciate how bad the supporting evidence is.    
    
    
    How recruiters look at your resume http://flowingdata.com/2012/04/11/how-recruiters-look-at-your-resume/ … via @flowingdata    
    
    
    I want an app that uses my current GPS coordinates to work out what train I'm on, how delayed it is, and when/where it stops.    
    
    
    @richardprice100 If someone did it as a kickstarter, I reckon they'd comfortably get support    
    
    
    @drbsg Presumably you'd start with a web-app as proof of concept and use GPS via JS. If you got traction you would build an iPhone app.    
    
    
    Some rare #FF's from me: @flowingdata @CompSciFact and @StatFact    
    
    
    Amazon Cloud search looks very interesting, will people move over from Elastic Search?    
    
    
    @drbsg iPhone :-)    
    
    
    Has anyone successfully used the GitHub for Mac client with git repository not hosted on GitHub?    
    
    
    Chrome OS is looking increasingly like the Debian for the EEE in Easy Mode http://googlesystem.blogspot.co.uk/2012/04/new-window-manager-for-chrome-os.html …    
    
    
    @PookyH I use LinkedIn extensively for managing contacts, as an online CV and to look up extended CVs of candidates I interview    
    
    
    Does anyone use Opera (the web browser) for anything besides checking sites work in Opera?    
    
    
    Learning R, any recommended reading? Starting with "Vizualize This"    
    
    
    If you're an app developer, and you're not currently thinking about applications for the Pebble, then you're missing a trick    
    
    
    @mishra_alok The mobile browser space is clearly very different from desktop. UC Browser and Dolphin are much more popular than I realised.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie who's index do they sit on top of? Or have they done their own? #millionshort    
    
    
    @raemond @vanessa_murdock Congrats! My empirical research showed SIGIR only sent rejection letters ;-)    
    
    
    @cantinacarnitas @siegeworksart If I were in #Hitchin today, I'd come down and buy 35 Burritos    
    
    
    Predictions for the next 9 months: Explossion in Pebble compatible Apps and Stream Processing as a Service from AWS.    
    
    
    @hubmum The alpha model: http://bit.ly/J2y0jw     
    
    
    Should have shorted facebook shares -- reckon it'll bottom out at $20    
    
    
    Why don't estate agents put personalised QR codes on For Sale signs? For details just point your phone at the house - better than a phone no    
    
    
    I'm porting everything to this: http://esolangs.org/wiki/Emoticon     
    
    
    @shadchnev Congratulations! Roadtrip?    
    
    
    @raemond @CharlotteHase A friend of a friend of mine created ETA, example programs worth a look: http://www.miketaylor.org.uk/tech/eta/doc/index.html …    
    
    
    It's so meta it has to work: http://xkcd.com/1060/     
    
    
    @CharlotteHase I refuse to buy a scale at all -- what does that make me?    
    
    
    Some thoughts on Mundanity: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#mundanity … /cc @beth_tk @01factory @duncanr2    
    
    
    Nearly half way through the year and my three books a month aim is still going strong: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#books     
    
    
    Sometimes the most appropriate visualisation method, is not Matplotlib, Gnuplot or ggplot, or even D3, occasionally it's ascii.    
    
    
    @LinkedIn why did you store passwords in plain text? Isn't storage of salted hashed passwords standard practice?    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly can you use a Royal seal now?    
    
    
    It seems Leap Seconds are the new Millennium Bug    
    
    
    @shadchnev Looks good :-)    
    
    
    @richardprice100 People have been working on this for a while: http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?doid=1148170.1148270 …    
    
    
    Can someone do an opening ceremony spotify play list?    
    
    
    Anyone used Java-ML? Have been looking at the API and looks straight forward, keen to hear of anyone's experiences.    
    
    
    Really looking forward to mentoring #YRS2012 tomorrow    
    
    
    Anyone know how to listen again to local radio on the iplayer iOS app? I can only work out how to do it from the website.    
    
    
    If there was a standard markup for infographics, Google could index them and people could search them #JustSayin    
    
    
    @phazonoverload would wrapping the text area in a form submitting as a GET and triggering the submit action on the form work? #yrshelp    
    
    
    @richardprice100 the twitter API offers streaming from a search term    
    
    
    @nathandunn97 How about the Yahoo Finance API? http://www.gummy-stuff.org/Yahoo-data.htm  http://code.google.com/p/yahoo-finance-managed/wiki/YahooFinanceAPIs … #YRSHELP #YRS2012    
    
    
    @jackwilsdon QCN have plans to release data, probably worth mailing: http://qcn.stanford.edu/research/data-downloads … #YRSHELP #YRS2012    
    
    
    @BenTatman1 How about the CrunchBase API? e.g. http://api.crunchbase.com/v/1/search.js?query=facebook.com … Contains links to logo images in JSON #YRSHELP    
    
    
    @Ruirize Check the coords are the right way around (long=Vert,lat=Horiz) and check the projection (e.g. http://xkcd.com/977/ ) #yrshelp    
    
    
    @AndyBursh The IF statement is your friend: SELECT IF(A>B,-1,IF(A=B,0,1)) FROM table; #yrshelp #yrs2012    
    
    
    Hirst-esque fun with spots -- http://numenore.co.uk/stuff#spots     
    
    
    In years to come Harry we be considered the rakish prince and held in similar affection that the Duke of Edinburgh is now.    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly http://www.iheartchaos.com/post/22228565802/youve-been-eating-cupcakes-wrong-your-whole-life …    
    
    
    Finally finished my Spot pictures: http://numenore.co.uk/stuff#spots  http://numenore.co.uk/store/images/spots.html … https://github.com/seo01/SpotPics     
    
    
    @richardprice100 looks very similar (although neater implementation) to Echo Echo    
    
    
    @shadchnev @jure If you consider only people who set their own PIN (I expect this is surprisingly high), is it a fair representation?    
    
    
    Wrote an essay for http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts  over the past few days but @jancyoverell suggested it's a little too caustic for publication    
    
    
    Interview: Douglas de Jager, CEO of spider.io, Explains Ad Viewability and Its Impact on the Online Ad Industry http://bit.ly/Rl9yzn     
    
    
    Planning to start an Etsy/Folksy shop    
    
    
    FYI: linked in endorsements -- you can endorse people for anything...    
    
    
    @shadchnev you are limited to linkedin's auto complete -- trust me, this is wide ranging enough not to limit humour or offence ;-)    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet Unfortunately you're limited to linkedin's vocabulary of skills. This is more of a challenge than a limitation :-)    
    
    
    @fhr You are limited to the skills linkedin offer... the list is a mix of genuine skills and total oddities -- rife for amusement    
    
    
    Raw materials have all arrived to make my "stuff" to sell in my Etsy/Folksy shop -- If I'm successful I might break even    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly don't sell out before we get there!    
    
    
    Swimming, gardening, DIY -- smells like Sunday    
    
    
    Remember there's no-one as Irish as Barack O'bama: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HplZ_taHXLM …    
    
    
    Over 10 months in and 3 books a month still going strong: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#books     
    
    
    @JofArnold if you find an alternative let me know!    
    
    
    @edds does it tell you how to make the title blink?    
    
    
    @duncanr2 I assume you have reasonable excuse for this discovery?    
    
    
    @NHC_Matt Any chance of NHC offering a part time bicycle maintenance course?    
    
    
    The future of billboard advertising is RTB #IMHO: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#sneakytracking …    
    
    
    Was introduced to this today by @jancyoverell: http://minifigs.me/     
    
    
    My twitter followers and linked in connections count have overtaken my facebook friends. I'm sure this significant, but I don't know why.    
    
    
    Planning home improvements with Pinterest... I seem to be planning a shed in a forest with a New York loft above it.    
    
    
    You have to watch Wilfred -- this is my favourite show! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mEH-TRwJwf4 …    
    
    
    The current discussion between the Conservatives and UKIP wouldn't be necessary if Cameron hadn't apposed the single transferable vote.    
    
    
    IAB’s SafeFrames Review by Dr Douglas de Jager, Founder & CEO & Dr Simon Overell, Chief Scientist of spider.io | http://www.exchangewire.com/blog/2012/12/05/iabs-safeframe-review-by-dr-douglas-de-jager-founder-ceo-dr-simon-overell-chief-scientist-of-spider-io/ …    
    
    
    @ashley_brown you have a talent for hair loss    
    
    
    @charlesarthur we've found a MASSIVE data leak in Internet Explorer -- a story of interest?    
    
    
    Best amazon review ever: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00520BKM0/?tag=093-20 …    
    
    
    Trying to decide what to get my dad for Christmas. I don't think one second hand book is going to cut it.    
    
    
    Apparently listing reasons the Olympics is better than Christmas is not "getting into the spirit" #barhumbug    
    
    
    I hope everyone has a close eye on their sheep /cc @borkurdotnet #yulelads    
    
    
    Play the NEW #spider_io challenge -- A worrying IE security leak turned into a "fun" game. http://iedataleak.spider.io/     
    
    
    @blueotterwines What's your e-mail address -- we want to buy some wine    
    
    
    @IE Data leakage of mouse data is doing the rounds: http://zd.net/SPFtKw  http://spider.io/blog/2012/12/internet-explorer-data-leakage/ …    
    
    
    comScore sued over 'sinister' data collection methods http://www.theregister.co.uk/2011/08/24/comscore_privacy_lawsuit/ … via @regvulture    
    
    
    "There is only one thing in life worse than being talked about, and that is not being talked about."    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet A assume you mean the night of the 22nd? Sure! @littledudes have been asking after you.    
    
    
    @alan_patterson It appears to have gone viral, hundreds of articles in over a dozen languages    
    
    
    Hoping the IE Mouse Data leak will make @guardiantw news /cc @aleksk @charlesarthur    
    
    
    Am I the only one in the world not using Bootstrap and still using 960.css? And Prototype? Everyone else is using JQuery. :-(    
    
    
    @richardprice100 There is an interesting discussion on academic paper analytics on this weeks Guardian Science Weekly Podcast wrt eJournals    
    
    
    Anyone else stuck in Kings X :-(    
    
    
    At #hitchin station with a couple of hundred unhappy commuters    
    
    
    @bensummers if it is, it won't catch on    
    
    
    @richardprice100 but you only just passed 1m! Clearly going well!    
    
    
    @ashley_brown #sleep #work #sleep #work #sleep #work #sleep #work #sleep #work    
    
    
    @ashley_brown this is a 4 Square intervention. Admit you have a problem.    
    
    
    @richardprice100 it will come for audio books first (smaller step from music, less collateral damage if it fails)    
    
    
    Writing xeyes for @IE 9    
    
    
    Nearly finished xeyes for Internet Explorer: http://numenore.co.uk/xeyes/     
    
    
    Just released xeyes for @IE on GitHub https://github.com/seo01/xeyes-for-ie … http://numenore.co.uk/xeyes/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Find out if I achieved my 2012 resolution of reading 3 books a month: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#books     
    
    
    @robberwick Glad you liked it. Just written the accompanying post: http://numenore.co.uk/stuff#xeyes-for-ie …    
    
    
    Finally finished eyes for @IE: http://numenore.co.uk/stuff#xeyes-for-ie …
http://numenore.co.uk/xeyes/     
    
    
    Migrating to evernote and pinterest for keeping track of notes and bookmarks    
    
    
    Just this on my CD shelf and ripping it to iTunes -- retro? http://www.amazon.co.uk/Club-Mix-Ibiza-Biggest-Anthems/dp/B00005N6RM …    
    
    
    My resolution for 2013: watch four new films a month… http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#films     
    
    
    @raemond what are you building first?    
    
    
    @raemond let me know when there is an app I can set your microwave from    
    
    
    There seem to be a log of articles and posts about how Big Data/Data Science will explode in the next 2-5 years. It's nosql all over again.    
    
    
    Duck tape is dead to me now. I've discovered denso tape!    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase you know you can endorse people for almost anything. Being creative with endorsements is great fun    
    
    
    #FF @WestEndLunch    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase An example is winging its way to you via linked in -- there is a controlled vocabulary which forces creativity    
    
    
    Epic playlist from 6 Music: http://www.bbc.co.uk/6music/vote/100-greatest-hits/ …    
    
    
    @edds you appear to have a passport next to your TV and cup of tea with pictures of bikes on the background #observations    
    
    
    Saw this in the National Portrait Gallery a couple of weeks ago. Best video installation I've seen: http://www.capguncollective.com/3038/3038/     
    
    
    Great argument against killing the term "Big Data" http://techcrunch.com/2013/01/05/why-we-need-to-kill-big-data/?goback=.gde_4449177_member_203926617 …    
    
    
    Just switched from @giffgaff to @TMobileUK - same price, same product, better customer service    
    
    
    @clubclasstravel I purchased from "Neil" in an EE shop. I can phone or visit him personally about problems. @giffgaff don't offer this.    
    
    
    I hope someone is getting a picture of Hertfordshire's black squirrels in white frosty trees    
    
    
    Roads are like sheets of ice in Hitchin -- #mwoorgwitpwease    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly Fun practicing plumbing: http://instagram.com/p/U9EfHvuqpQ/     
    
    
    I've been practicing my plumbing for our steam punk bathroom: http://instagram.com/p/U9EfHvuqpQ/     
    
    
    @ashley_brown what do you think of my Rules for Recruiters? http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#recruiters …    
    
    
    Join DropWines and get £10 off! http://www.dropwines.com?utm_source=ref_5B7C4BF414C0E93488E90A7FF92EE74Fdropwines.com/?utm_source=re … #wine via @dropwines    
    
    
    @NHC_Matt you need to post a picture of the @cantinacarnitas trailer!    
    
    
    @bensummers We used these extensively and have had no problems -- where are you having trouble?    
    
    
    @bensummers Just checked and I used zipeg to extract mine http://www.zipeg.com/     
    
    
    @bensummers I'm going to blame apple on this one, their [de]compression tools are poor (case in point: http://www.47ronin.com/zcat-broken-on-mac-os-x-feature-or-bug/26 …).    
    
    
    @bensummers it does give the impression Microsoft neglected to test a tool built for testing    
    
    
    Why don't people poke anymore?    
    
    
    @duncanr2 Tea comes in bags because it's infused. You make Machu tea from a powder (like coffee) because it's dissolved (like coffee).    
    
    
    @alan_patterson the scary world of internet advertising    
    
    
    The Bloomberg Billionaires Index is a daily ranking of the world's richest people. http://www.bloomberg.com/billionaires/2013-02-09/aaa/adjaa …    
    
    
    Prediction for 2015-2020: the phrase "Retail 2.0" is coined - a strong brand with complementary online/high street presence.    
    
    
    Having fun with cmx.io http://yfrog.com/hsdagpp     
    
    
    @voltdb Kudos to whoever came up with the name for your e-mail newsletter    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly Dr Seuss clearly didn't have to find a new source of cup cakes! Best of luck on your next endeavour.    
    
    
    Maintain as little code as possible: don't reinvent the wheel, use open source, reusable patterns and a concise language #makersacademy    
    
    
    Impressive, but surely using a font to represent a map shows a string of bad design decisions: http://intridea.github.com/stately/     
    
    
    90% of the time I try to use the reduce operator with a lambda in python it turns out not to be powerful enough    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet Having used a standing desk, what do you make of a walking desk? http://techcrunch.com/2013/03/03/why-every-office-should-switch-to-walking-desks/ …    
    
    
    @JofArnold Where do coins go?    
    
    
    I have strong suspicions that "del" in python does release memory as swiftly as one may expect    
    
    
    @drbsg Scheme is one of the languages that pops up in conversation every 6 months or so (like coffee script or R) - is it worth learning?    
    
    
    @robertcambridge @jofarnold I'm very tempted but don't know what to do with coins. Also as £20 notes are 1.5cm bigger than $s will they fit?    
    
    
    @JofArnold @robertcambridge Admit it, you are a guerrilla salesman! I may be forced to buy one.    
    
    
    @shadchnev that would be inherently gamable and unfair. What would you use as a feedback mechanism?    
    
    
    I just backed ME, FAKEGRIMLOCK: THE BOOK OF AWESOME on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/12vvi60     
    
    
    There seems to be a leak in our bathroom.It's intermittent and is yet to happen while I'm in the house.Does plumbing suffer race conditions?    
    
    
    Best XKCD in some time: http://xkcd.com/1185/     
    
    
    Does anyone know a HTML to JSON converter? Wondering if you can write a viable crawler in Bash using tools to cURL and JQ    
    
    
    @jayforeman at least they didn't say "Harry Potter"    
    
    
    Meet the Most Suspect Publishers on the Web http://adweek.it/16FRzNM     
    
    
    Today we won! (Via @FAKEGRIMLOCK) pic.twitter.com/UAzaVC1Pmv    
    
    
    @jayforeman how does "no woman no cry" or "three little birds" for in?    
    
    
    @robberwick I highly recommend jq, I use it almost everyday    
    
    
    Who Is Behind Chameleon Botnet Tricking Marketers? via @BloombergTV http://bloom.bg/16Og7UF     
    
    
    Thinking of buying a reconditioned Nokia 7110 instead of an iPhone 5 -- am I mad?    
    
    
    @JofArnold I have never been described as a hipster before. I don't even have an 8-bit twitter avatar.    
    
    
    I promise I won't make a habit of tweeting cat gifs. But...
http://24.media.tumblr.com/fe0c67dd3b7e5fe6d0fe4226fc71d126/tumblr_mhvliyb1F51s410g9o1_500.gif …    
    
    
    Have now seen @pottedpotter 3 times (spread over 6 years). I understand that we get pie from @ActorJeff /cc @Daniel_Veronica    
    
    
    @OnScroll Fancy coming to @spider_io towers for a beer sometime to discuss all things viewability? http://www.spider.io/blog/2012/07/join-us-for-a-tipple-at-spider-towers/ …    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase Are you entering?    
    
    
    Does anyone else quietly say "total eclipse" after finishing a Jaffa Cake?    
    
    
    @HANDcreative Minimum Viable Personality from @FAKEGRIMLOCK sums it up: http://www.slideshare.net/asocialme/boring-9519224 …    
    
    
    50% of the time I phone my bank I fail the security checks :-(    
    
    
    Can someone explain to me what QR codes are good for, besides being robust barcode replacements?    
    
    
    @JofArnold I think as way of conveying URLs via print, they are a total failure. Especially given their size and style.    
    
    
    @robberwick #BlinkStick looks very cool -- much more accessible than arduino    
    
    
    @shadchnev Is that the book you recommended to me the last time we had a beer?    
    
    
    @duncanr2 just because a freedom exits, does not mean it needs to be used. Hence norms.    
    
    
    Thinking of buying a #blinkstick and building something Good-Night-Lamp-esque http://blinkstick.com  http://goodnightlamp.com     
    
    
    Came across the notion of "Kantian Fairness" today, and associated problems. Sounds like the British condition.    
    
    
    Is there an extrapolation logical fallacy? Or is it Reductio ad absurdum / Slippery Slope? http://www.theskepticsguide.org/resources/logicalfallacies.aspx … http://xkcd.org/1204/     
    
    
    @PookyH Lyra Says is the best thing on tumblr ATM    
    
    
    Designing an MVP for a 4sq alternative sharing less information to less people in fewer clicks (I appreciate none, noone, 0 is the extreme)    
    
    
    @PookyH WTF? How do people like that exist?    
    
    
    Regrets: http://www.uploadlibrary.com/pushmerchandising/draft_lens4458812module31611932photo_1241584818trooper-regrets.jpg …    
    
    
    @Debsalini thanks for reminding me! #vote    
    
    
    @JofArnold You need a bigger data set.    
    
    
    Parkham WI embarrassed by dressing as pirates for talk by former Somali pirate hostage http://www.thisisnorthdevon.co.uk/Parkham-WI-embarrassed-dressing-pirates-talk/story-18871181-detail/story.html …    
    
    
    Just ordered a #blinkstick -- first project planned on paper -- now I need to clear some time to code! http://blinkstick.com/     
    
    
    @richardprice100 Have you read Wikinomics? Describes sharing data in verticals. If you can become a cross-discipline hub it would be great.    
    
    
    Planning to find out what happens at @HackHitchin tonight /cc @arvydev    
    
    
    This is me: http://www.thedailymash.co.uk/news/society/middle-class-man-convinced-builders-like-him-2013041265450 … /via @dcollis    
    
    
    Have written a simple (and unconventional) scraper for Google Real Time Analytics to solve this problem: http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13839430/real-time-visitors-from-google-analytics-how-to-get-it …    
    
    
    If you think the sale of tumblr/instagram/yammer/summly has any relevance on your own app/dashboard/platform/network you are deeply mistaken    
    
    
    @NunoCardoso Do you plan to build anything on it?    
    
    
    @kirbywinfield viewability measurement in nested cross domain iframes, now accredited for all major desktop browsers: http://spider.io/mrc-viewability     
    
    
    "Microsoft advertise for jobs in optional TCP headers" http://mashable.com/2013/05/28/flickr-jobs/ …    
    
    
    If you don't go to the off licence on the way home from the gym, you're doing it wrong    
    
    
    Having used it for Apache for 10 years, decided I should learn how the apache configs work -- OS X makes life difficult    
    
    
    Oldie but goodie: If PHP were British http://www.addedbytes.com/blog/if-php-were-british/ …    
    
    
    I love Wikipedia: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Portal:Portal …    
    
    
    Love this: http://techcrunch.com/2013/06/18/onion-pi/ …    
    
    
    Has reliable screen sharing over WIFI killed the use-case for a KVM switch?    
    
    
    @bensummers I've noticed a substantial price increase over 5 years. I assumed due to drop in demand. Screen sharing "just works" now.    
    
    
    @robberwick Increased specialisation explains the price hike I've seen.The target is no longer home/office users with a couple of boxes (me)    
    
    
    A startup having multiple revenue streams is code for "we don't know what the business model will be"    
    
    
    @bensummers Are you using a http://modern.ie  VM?    
    
    
    @rdcowley everything    
    
    
    One for all the QR code fans out there: http://xkcd.com/1237/     
    
    
    The more I switch between writing Python and Java, the better my Python gets and the worse my Java gets    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase @cathal The amount of waste that will be reduced when manufacturing on demand hits mainstream is staggering    
    
    
    Common sense comment on Facebook: http://www.bitbanter.com/wara/dutxh4CmQufe2qwqs …    
    
    
    My guide to data science: http://memegenerator.co/instance/39737392 …    
    
    
    Wish I was attending this: http://www.geo.uzh.ch/~rsp/gir13/     
    
    
    Is @TheTileApp genius, creepy or just a gimmick?    
    
    
    @shadchnev @TheTileApp The fact it only lasts a year makes me think the same    
    
    
    MySQL docs are so much better than Postgresql. Both are leaps and bounds ahead of HIVE.    
    
    
    @thistlesandwich so small!    
    
    
    Can someone remind me what a day off feels like...    
    
    
    The proliferation of browser-engine backed crawlers in the past 4 years continues to amaze me    
    
    
    @blahpro If that's a euphemism, I assume you're off to A&E.    
    
    
    @arvydev @1and1_UK Easy solution -- Change your password to "D0ntAsk4ForMyPa$$wordOnTheF0ne!"    
    
    
    Made my day: http://devopsreactions.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    Why is Top Loader's "Dancing in the Moonlight" in the top 40 after 13 years?    
    
    
    @robberwick because it's great!    
    
    
    @NHC_Matt 79% :-)    
    
    
    We made the BBC! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23696805 …    
    
    
    @paulcuth They were running with a 30min delay and 50% cancellation at 7:15 :-(    
    
    
    If I were a teacher, I would do this: http://flowingdata.com/2013/08/02/teacher-forces-student-to-do-math-to-unlock-phone/ …    
    
    
    Creating a mural inspired by Banksy, Invader and Hirst. My house smells of spray paint.    
    
    
    @robberwick @rdcowley Currently it's a work in progress - but you get the idea. pic.twitter.com/vPUDzwWEi2    
    
    
    @rdcowley @robberwick I think I have more in common with "Handy Andy"    
    
    
    @alan_patterson keep up the good work :-)    
    
    
    @robberwick @rdcowley Please tell me you dressed as all three nephews.    
    
    
    @rdcowley What time you meeting? We're heading to this in the Vic at 7:30 https://twitter.com/Poorlybee/status/378477809900859393 …    
    
    
    @rdcowley We may come and join you after the godless filth ;-) We'll see how the evening goes.    
    
    
    @makersacademy Strongly disagree! Interview code tests are not to test code quality. They test approach to problems & grasp of key concepts.    
    
    
    @shadchnev I think this is a very possible view of the future. :-(    
    
    
    First draft of my post on QR-Codes: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#qrcodes …    
    
    
    "@cdixon: "On the phenomenon of bullshit jobs" http://www.strikemag.org/bullshit-jobs/ " sounds like Douglas Adams' 'B' Ark    
    
    
    "@ZenProverbs: Nothing ever exists entirely alone; everything is in relation to everything else." Surprisingly relevant in AI & data science    
    
    
    @shadchnev https://github.com/seo01/SimplePortfolio … ;-)    
    
    
    @shadchnev 1. PHP hosting is cheap & ubiquitous. 2. It's future proof, designed for when mobile resolution matches current desktops :-P    
    
    
    "@StatFact: Simpson's paradox http://ow.ly/pbFNI " <- Keep reading this until you understand it    
    
    
    @shadchnev Getting nostalgic in your old age.    
    
    
    Attempting to write a solr app. It's come on along way in the last 5 years. Documentation is still poor.    
    
    
    @JofArnold @afternoon I've a 1980's Eagle that would qualify :-)    
    
    
    Apple's space ship campus looks like a panopticon to me -- a circular prison of designers.    
    
    
    @MarkMellors presumably the lasers aren't printed. Looks a lot like a future Dr Who villain.    
    
    
    @paulcuth That is pretty unbelievable    
    
    
    @robberwick @paulcuth if this catches on, surely it won't end with electric cars :-(    
    
    
    @robberwick @paulcuth I reckon there is a patent troll opportunity here: pair the term DRM with anything used day-to-day, e.g. DRMed Water    
    
    
    @arvydev @robberwick surely we're going to move the other way - it's only a matter of time until we have a kinetic/solar powered smart watch    
    
    
    "Clap clap tap-tap-tap, clap my cup, clap off the wall, switch my cup..."    
    
    
    @jayforeman only python    
    
    
    @paulcuth As a fan of awesome cats, this Leopardus should be up your street: http://www.bbc.co.uk/nature/25086721     
    
    
    @thistlesandwich they make you look a little like a Doctor Who villain    
    
    
    @TheKrishes Wolfgang?    
    
    
    @TheKrishes Even better!    
    
    
    http://runningahackerspace.tumblr.com/  #cc @HackHitchin @paulcuth @robberwick @rdcowley @arvydev @MarkMellors    
    
    
    PHD Comics: Science News Cycle http://www.phdcomics.com/comics.php?f=1174 … via @phdcomics    
    
    
    @jancyoverell clearly only a padawan rabbit whisperer; Vladimir @littledudes still prefers me.    
    
    
    Finished v0.1 of my ngram tweet generator -- much refactoring required plus more text processing and probabilistic goodness before release    
    
    
    All the business plans on the #Apprentice were disappointing, I'd have fired all of them    
    
    
    Hunting programmers and designers -- if you see any point them at http://spider.io    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly tweet more pics of delicious cakes and all spamming will be forgiven    
    
    
    For those interested in the legalities of hiring and firing visit this months @bootlaw    
    
    
    My automated tweet generator based on ngrams works equally well generating fantastic prose with LOTR as the training data    
    
    
    ... "Sam sat silent for some time arrived to supplement the dwarves night"    
    
    
    @resumevu any chance of a beta invite?    
    
    
    Sadly this made me laugh out loud: http://mashable.com/2011/08/03/best-wi-fi-names/ …    
    
    
    Should blogs be preserved forever or should they have an expiration date? http://blogforever.eu/     
    
    
    @bootlaw Any chance of an article offering a legal perspective on @kissmetrics current sticky situation (and how others can avoid)?    
    
    
    First usable version of my ngram document generator committed: http://bit.ly/pDQvyf    
    
    
    Heatmap of UK property values http://bit.ly/qQ7SLU via @Zoopla, @shadchnev /cc @mishra_alok    
    
    
    @mishra_alok It looks identical to the map you demo'd to me 5 years ago :-)    
    
    
    Deleting old domains and sub-domains I haven't used in over 4 years    
    
    
    Who knows when the domains I haven't use for three years may come in useful!    
    
    
    @ashley_brown its a shame you never shared an office with @mishra_alok, you could have complained to each other about the temperature allday    
    
    
    Fired up the EEE PC today for the first time in 6 months. Couldn't remember the password or how to open the terminal.    
    
    
    http://bighugelabs.com/onblack.php?id=3880287244&size=large … For thoughs who miss magic eye    
    
    
    On OS X, if I've got a folder of 1000 images named n.png, what's the easiest way to glue them into a movie with each image shown for 1/10s?    
    
    
    If you ported SETI@home to JS posting results back to SETI via JSONP, people would unknowingly search for ET while viewing your pages    
    
    
    ...if Facebook did it we'd be chatting with the Soup Dragon by lunch time    
    
    
    To keep up with each new open source project in a different language -- my next project will be in bash    
    
    
    Strange day at work discussing legal vs moral, portrayal vs intention, right vs wrong. Plus problems with Capitalism and Britain cc @blahpro    
    
    
    @blahpro #ceowithphilosophydegree /cc @ashley_brown    
    
    
    @zacharyvoase You'll want to add item semantics (maybe user as well) to work with small enough samples to attract smaller clients    
    
    
    @blahpro what about the mouse ;-)    
    
    
    @ashley_brown Hal?    
    
    
    My adventures with Infographic CVs: http://numenore.co.uk/wiki/cv     
    
    
    @blahpro A pigeon has a longer call than a dove's coo (will demonstrate in the office)    
    
    
    I'm sure the "expert" on the today program just said there were 100,000 milliseconds in a second    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly I secretly buy 3, surreptitiously eat the first, then share "one each" with my wife    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly I love cupcakes because I can eat a whole cake (or two!) without feeling guilty #nationalcupcakeweek    
    
    
    For anyone confused by paralympic codes: http://bit.ly/qDO2rN     
    
    
    @duncanr2 Sadly I bought @jancyoverell one as an anniversary present    
    
    
    How I spent my day: http://bit.ly/pvH2XS  http://youtu.be/rOFFD4Fmfis  -- it's been a silly day    
    
    
    @peerindex Any chance of a periodic release of the top tweeters by PI like the Alexa 1M download http://bit.ly/WXWD /cc @azeem    
    
    
    @shadchnev If it's important, Google will stick it in my priority inbox    
    
    
    This is me: http://xkcd.com/606/  /cc @blahpro    
    
    
    Our wedding singer is supporting @DaveGorman on tour! Go see them both /cc @jayforeman    
    
    
    @shadchnev Clearly you are a bad person #2020hindsight    
    
    
    Surely this means we're less than 10 years away from time-travel: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-15017484 …    
    
    
    @blahpro just the one?    
    
    
    Just designed a chair -- time to order wood    
    
    
    Watching the @kahnacademy requirements for @aiclass    
    
    
    @milkroundabout How do we go about getting http://spider.io  involved in #milkroundabout?    
    
    
    @andykent @teabass Good work with the #lnug meetup -- very interesting talks    
    
    
    @shadchnev Invisible Hand is plugged on XKCD (almost) http://xkcd.org/958/     
    
    
    Deciding whether to defend my "best pumpkin decorated by an adult" trophy #pirtonpumpkins    
    
    
    @ashley_brown I can only assume you don't have a trophy to defend    
    
    
    First spider.io Blog Post: How To Catch A Bot http://spider.io/2011/09/how-to-catch-a-bot/ …    
    
    
    Just updated my publications page: http://bit.ly/mT38UT . For people that like pictures: http://bit.ly/qwodhq     
    
    
    Quora iPhone app is very snazzy    
    
    
    iPhone Assistant/Siri looks pretty amazing - keen to see the habits and trend analysis that powers the personalisation reverse engineered    
    
    
    It's not the winning, it's the taking part that counts...    
    
    
    Highly remmend listening to Will Self's monologue on prisons currently available on the BBC and only 10 minutes long    
    
    
    Looking forward to tomorrow's #TWTC1 with @aleksk -- heading back to my old home: @imperialcollege    
    
    
    @crowquine keep plugging @milkroundabout #TWTC1    
    
    
    Q for the panel: do we need to teach what the Internet is and how content is created as well as how code is created? #TWTC1    
    
    
    Q for Emma & Jeff: how young should CS be taught and form should this take? #TWTC1    
    
    
    @shadchnev Isn't that what Google's for?    
    
    
    Being a responsible adult is rubbish    
    
    
    Overly excited by my 4 seconds of fame on @guardiantw with @aleksk @crowquine @hubmum et. al http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/blog/audio/2011/oct/12/tech-weekly-tech-city-skills-education-audio … plus spider.io name check    
    
    
    Truly stunned at the legal battle between @acton and @ladygaga. Does no one have a sense of humor anymore? http://www.guardian.co.uk/music/2011/oct/13/lady-gaga-injunction-lady-goo-goo …    
    
    
    @richardprice100 isn't that the idea of Google+ hangouts?    
    
    
    Cavity wall insulation for @littledudes now finished!    
    
    
    Am halfway through building a somewhat unconventional chair -- a few more week-ends to go.    
    
    
    Stumbled across Apache Stanbol for the first time: http://incubator.apache.org/stanbol/     
    
    
    Of the people I know who signed up for @aiclass, only @duncanr2 remains committed -- good work!    
    
    
    Looking forward to @milkroundabout - Send any devs who want to have fun scaling a massive real time system over to the spider.io stand #SMR    
    
    
    Sums up @ScienceWeekly aptly: http://static.guim.co.uk/sys-images/Guardian/Pix/pictures/2011/9/30/1317394560539/Stephen-Collins-Vague-sci-002.jpg …    
    
    
    @mashable Am convinced Microsoft's takeover of Y! is inevitable -- the question is when and for how much --> http://on.mash.to/qwIHCZ     
    
    
    Siri as an entry point for apps seems inevitable -- will be very interesting to see how apple handle this    
    
    
    "Wikipedia Real-Time Challenge" This could lead to something amazing - wish I had time to participate http://www.mediawiki.org/wiki/October_2011_Coding_Challenge/Real-Time …    
    
    
    Our latest blog post: "The Problem With Client-Side Analytics" http://spider.io/blog/2011/10/the-problem-with-client-side-analytics/ …    
    
    
    Made me smile: http://thedailywtf.com/Articles/Rock-amp8216n-Bowl-Champion.aspx#Pic2 …    
    
    
    X-Factor Tracker -- Genius -- http://xfactortracker.com/about/     
    
    
    @PhilipTromans has just snatched the lead from @chrisdarby89 in the spider.io challenge. #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    Surely someone can get more than 10 clues in the spider.io challenge. #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    @steve_barham glad to see you make it onto the leader board. Keep digging for more codes and clues. #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    @steve_barham one more code and you'll be top of the leader board! #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    Is @alol going to take the top spot from @steve_barham in the spider.io challenge? #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    @alol Fantastic! If you're at @milkroundabout, come and say hello to us.    
    
    
    @grisch, @alol and @steve_barham can stand tall today as spider champions. The rest of you: Can you hack it? #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    At #twtc2    
    
    
    #twtc2 Startups primarily need cheap serviced office space -- waiting 6 weeks for a broadband connection as open reach dictate causes pain    
    
    
    #twtc2 Q Eric: Startups are solving their own problems re recruitment & office space.We can't solve OpenReach's broadband monopoly-comment?    
    
    
    #twtc2 we (@spider_io) will also be at @milkroundabout    
    
    
    #twtc2 "Eric Pickles" we can take a pick axe to the strand and lay are own broadband    
    
    
    Have bitched directly to Eric Pickles about the fiasco of the Open Reach monopoly. Weight, shoulders, lifted. #twtc2    
    
    
    @PhilipTromans & @Peterspider both in spitting distance of completing the spider.io challenge - final push? #spider_io http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    Top work by @Edgemaster in the #spider_io challenge. If your at @milkroundabout on Sunday come over and say hi!    
    
    
    A thing of beauty: http://thedailywtf.com/Articles/The-Query-of-Despair.aspx …    
    
    
    @aiclass is still down :-(    
    
    
    Fun from the Internet: http://www.newlaunches.com/entry_images/0911/14/webchicks.php …    
    
    
    I hate in @aiclass when he says "This is a none trivial question that may take you a while"    
    
    
    @rpstac What is this "outside of London" place you talk about?    
    
    
    On my way to the first #spider_io hackday! /cc @blahpro @edds @Vegard_uk @ashley_brown @chmod755_d    
    
    
    Heading to @milkroundabout tomorrow? Come over to the @spider_io stand, and try http://challenge.spider.io     
    
    
    Logistics! On my way to meet a van driver and a Viking to move epic amounts of stuff to @milkroundabout    
    
    
    Great day recruiting at @milkroundabout. Lots of enthusiasm from people wanting to solve hard engineering problems! Time for sleep now #smr    
    
    
    Startup life: spend your Sunday with the whole company at a recruitment fair in a gazebo. It's hard work but I love it /cc @spider_io    
    
    
    @GoSquared good to meet you at @milkroundabout. Keen on your thoughts on my recent blog post: http://spider.io/blog/2011/10/the-problem-with-client-side-analytics/ … /cc @spider_io    
    
    
    One I'm sure @bengoldacre will appreciate: http://xkcd.org/     
    
    
    Over 50 people on the #spider_io challenge leaderboard http://challenge.spider.io/     
    
    
    @willdangerfield Not far to go! #spider_io challenge    
    
    
    Can anyone recommend a good statistics reference book? Must have standard tables,tests,assumptions and rationales-fed up googling everything    
    
    
    @aiclass When are the next modules and the reading list going to be put up?    
    
    
    @willdangerfield Great work! Have you checked out our careers page? http://spider.io/careers/     
    
    
    @darkip Keep digging, you're nearly there! #spider_io    
    
    
    Does anyone out there understand http://batch.com/  ? Looks like facebook photo sharing for hipsters.    
    
    
    @duncanr2 We have a white board to get rid of if you can transport it from London    
    
    
    @duncanr2 we've painted the office in whiteboard paint :-) #spider_io    
    
    
    A series of AI/NLP web services have just been released by Complexity Intelligence (http://www.complexityintelligence.com/en/homepage ): http://intellexere.com/en/homepage     
    
    
    Have booked tickets to see Red Hot Chili Peppers at Knebworth next year :-)    
    
    
    @beth_tk Sentiment analysis as a service seems to be a hot topic, that's the third service I've seen in as many weeks.    
    
    
    Exciting new geo database: http://georama-project.labs.exalead.com/gazetiki.htm  (for GIR fun)    
    
    
    Sunday 8th July 2012 the Olympic Torch will be carried from Letchworth to Stevenage    
    
    
    For those that missed @milkroundabout: http://youtu.be/upvDMiZRzgU     
    
    
    Too cross to use the internet    
    
    
    Still too cross to use the Internet    
    
    
    @ashley_brown This is more than indirectly your fault :-) http://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/duty_calls.png …    
    
    
    Glad to see @ag1122496850 (nee @anthonygraham1) has stopped lying on his linked in profile http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=68580618 … /cc @aston_carter    
    
    
    If your job was to provide the highest quality of water, would you urinate in the reservoir? /cc @ag1122496850 (nee @anthonygraham1)    
    
    
    @Skaffen We've seen recruiters we use with false details on linked-in profiles to gain people's confidence. This makes them harder to trust.    
    
    
    Spider Towers is in the middle of a Student Process -- Just locked the door    
    
    
    Over 400 people have taken the #spider_io challenge http://challenge.spider.io/  -- can you hack it?    
    
    
    @Nick_Franklin That's a pretty bad CPM    
    
    
    Feeling very smug with myself having fixed our central heating    
    
    
    Feeling 5 years out of touch. Busy playing Portal and Rick Rolling.    
    
    
    @aiclass Are any institutions certifying the course in the UK?    
    
    
    @aiclass is there only one unit this week?    
    
    
    #THappcircus I clearly don't "get" eeve. On the other hand I'm sold on echoecho.    
    
    
    Slickflick is another one  I don't get - I must be getting old #THappcircus    
    
    
    Siine Writer -- the Optimus Keyboard didn't take off, will personalised keyboards work as an app? #THappcircus    
    
    
    Will "Find My Friends" kill "Echo Echo" out of the find my friends apps    
    
    
    I just donated to #Wikipedia, if use and value the service, and can afford it, you should to.    
    
    
    @shadchnev worth every penny. I'm surprised my corporates don't donate. #Wikipedia    
    
    
    I can't imagine this site ever being used for copyright infringement: http://uberzet.com/     
    
    
    Over halfway through @aiclass and still on 100%    
    
    
    I'm increasingly convinced "Men are from mars, women are from Venus"-esque gender differences are a product of society rather than biology    
    
    
    I've asked the same question on Quora, Linkedin and Academia -- we'll see who gives the highest quality answers.    
    
    
    Live opposite me: http://bit.ly/tSCdwu     
    
    
    @teabass doesn't this make it trivially easy for someone to spoof your AB testing?    
    
    
    @teabass If you do everything server side, the fact that you're even doing AB testing is concealed.    
    
    
    Was served notice by a squatter today #startuplife    
    
    
    Very disappointed with @PhotoBox cutting off the sides of my print :-(    
    
    
    @duncanr2 Your mission for the next 7 days is to find as many uses as possible for you found-thing-a-mi-jig    
    
    
    Only a h-index of 7, more writing needed! http://scholar.google.com.au/citations?user=dGTxOQcAAAAJ …    
    
    
    Keen to get "to dog-food" recognised as a verb. e.g. That <company> need to dog-food more. Are you dog-fooding?    
    
    
    It means use your own product.    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet If you don't dog-food the dog food, how can improve the User eXperience? Metrics (e.g. tale velocity) are not enough.    
    
    
    Epic failure from @blahpro and @chmod755_d on assembling a cardboard desk in 3 minutes    
    
    
    @shadchnev I'm sure you dog-food @InvisibleHandHQ #newverbinaction    
    
    
    Realised this morning I haven't shaved for almost a month    
    
    
    You know you're a Computer Scientist if when queueing you worry more about complexity and queueing theory than what you're queueing for.    
    
    
    Thinking for too much about the complexity and optimal organisation of cloakrooms    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet sleeping well? Everything as you left it, in it's rightful place? #yulelads    
    
    
    Cleaning up my linked in profile (or making it messier depending on your point of view)    
    
    
    Spend the last few weeks trying to work through the maths behind a HMM -- worth the effort for anyone interested in Baysian statistics    
    
    
    Clearly it's not Christmas yet as no sign of @unixspiders christmas tree e-mail.    
    
    
    I imagine it went a bit Kissmetrics at the GoDaddy office this week    
    
    
    What did the Internet look like today? http://youtu.be/a9SnO-ACOI4  Merry Christmas    
    
    
    My new years resolution (via Facebook UX) "Data informed, not data driven"    
    
    
    571 out of the top 1,000 web sites set cookies -- the ICO has a lot of work to do by May    
    
    
    Of the top 1,000 web sites @nydnnews and @mashable are the worst offenders when it comes to tags, web bugs, pixels and beacons    
    
    
    Working from home between Christmas and New Year: http://www.ddiy.co/wp-content/uploads/Work-from-home-considerations.png …    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet is that your creation?    
    
    
    Writing a website from scratch(ish) for the first time in nearly two years. Will shortly be updating my homepage for the first time in 4.    
    
    
    11 chinese lanterns over #hitchin, must be #2012    
    
    
    @blahpro on manlab they sent a videocamera into space for under £1k outside Cambridge - #hackday? http://bit.ly/yXd9az     
    
    
    Just updated my website. Post me any thoughts: http://numenore.co.uk/stuff  http://numenore.co.uk/publications     
    
    
    Just written a simple portfolio CMS to power my updated website, will post to GitHub after a little more tidying.    
    
    
    Making snappy Ajaxy sites gracefully degrade where not supported use to be for older browsers and now seems for Search Engines    
    
    
    @beth_tk Many thanks for the feedback -- now fixed!    
    
    
    Have just realised while SEO people keep bothering me on twitter #facepalm    
    
    
    Why aren't you following @the90slife?    
    
    
    @richardprice100 Surely it's in Big G's interest to overstate their proportion causing you to concentrate effort on them #cynical    
    
    
    RT: @mashable This Swiss Army Knife Comes With a 1 TB USB Flash Drive - http://on.mash.to/zNOu6w  <-- A USB drive you can't take in hand luggage    
    
    
    Map reduce over MTurk. All of TED in 6 words: http://www.ted.com/talks/sebastian_wernicke_1000_tedtalks_6_words.html …    
    
    
    Prediction for 2012: Microsoft will ramp up their acquisition strategy online with some big spending    
    
    
    Best bookshops in #London: UCL Waterstones and Wellcome Trust Bookshop    
    
    
    Have added an easter egg to my site leading to a series of challenges    
    
    
    Just signed up for this: http://www.theblenheimtriathlon.com/     
    
    
    Aiming to read at least 3 books a month in 2012 after last years poor showing of one book in 5 months    
    
    
    Google's #SOPA protest page links to Vint Cerf's Wikipedia page, which is blacked out due to #SOPA protest    
    
    
    @rpstac t-shirts!?!    
    
    
    htaccess is a bitch to debug (but worth it when it works smoothly)    
    
    
    @beth_tk as an undergraduate, when we had mice, we set 3 traps with different bait and placed bets on what the mouse would go for    
    
    
    After a talk on Alan Turing at the BCS last week I went to the pub with 3 colleagues, this is what we spoke about: http://bit.ly/zWAuGI     
    
    
    Wittgenstein should get more credit as a founder of Computer Science    
    
    
    @01factory Surely Wittgenstein's Tractatus is the foundation for programming languages and logic used in day to day Software Developement?    
    
    
    Watched the start of Star Wars Uncut: Director's Cut: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ezeYJUz-84 … Great fun!    
    
    
    @O2 sends your phone number to every website you visit. If they don't fix this in the next 48hours I'll be changing carrier.    
    
    
    @O2 I expect you're going to be getting a phone call from the ICO shortly. If one of you has visited their site they have you number.    
    
    
    Today is probably a bad day to be working at @O2 http://conversation.which.co.uk/technology/o2-sharing-mobile-phone-number-network-provider/ … #shitmeetfan    
    
    
    @O2 can I assume you will make a public announcement of the data breach (as reqd by the ICO) and tell users what you've leaked and to whom?    
    
    
    @charlesarthur Surely a mobile number is PII as you just need to phone it to identify the person.    
    
    
    Glad I'm not the Information Officer at @O2, @ICOnews are about to give them a call #privacywhatprivacy    
    
    
    @charlesarthur Someone rings claiming to be @O2, they know your phone no., model and the last site you visited. Could easily gain PII info.    
    
    
    Learn how to build the next Google: http://www.udacity.com/     
    
    
    Have sent something a bit like a philosophy paper to something a bit like peer review /cc  @01factory @duncanr2    
    
    
    They don't make music videos like this anymore: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aFd5Cci_pE4 …    
    
    
    @beth_tk The relationship of Mundanity to Happiness - I'm looking for feedback before I stick it on my website (a private beta). Interested?    
    
    
    Aiming for 3 books a month in 2012. One month almost down and so far so good: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#books     
    
    
    Google+ have hit 100M users but how many of those are active users? I'd like to see some FB vs G+ engagement stats    
    
    
    @duncanr2 Next you need "just f***ing #evi it" which takes you to the app with prefilled search if installed, otherwise the iTunes store    
    
    
    The best thing about owning a house: no one stops you spray painting the stairs :-)    
    
    
    Spray painting our stairs: http://on.fb.me/yyEFlc     
    
    
    Just fixed the graceful degradation and search engine friendly links on my website    
    
    
    Best mobile portal I've seen: http://everything.me/     
    
    
    From the public's perspective the major result of patents is to keep monopolistic pricing in a competitive market #brokensystem    
    
    
    The "C" in "CSV" stands for comma, if your data is TAB separated, its a "TSV", the clue is in the name.    
    
    
    Any startup experiencing technical growing pains should read this and realise the journey they're starting: http://highscalability.com/blog/2012/2/13/tumblr-architecture-15-billion-page-views-a-month-and-harder.html …    
    
    
    Google expanding it's AI offering (and squeezing some value out of the Freebase aquisition): http://mashable.com/2012/02/13/google-knowledge-graph-change-search/ …    
    
    
    @KieranO James Dyson's autobiography is well worth a read.    
    
    
    A summary of what I think is wrong with the patent system: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#patentsystem …    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet As a patent author yourself, what are your views on the swapping disclosure for protection?    
    
    
    Updated my thoughts on patents based on @borkurdotnet's follow up: http://bit.ly/wQa1Yg  http://bit.ly/wLgttT     
    
    
    @richardprice100 Congratulations!    
    
    
    Surely "Top Gear" is just a bad remake of "Last of the Summer Wine"    
    
    
    Fixed back button support on my website (Ajax fun for a Sunday afternoon) /cc @chmod755_d    
    
    
    Two vertical social networks hit a 1m members within 2 weeks of each other: http://bit.ly/yqNKCc  http://bit.ly/Ax6kNa  @academia @playfire    
    
    
    Have swapped from the Tweetdeck to Twitter desktop and Facebook menubar -- much happier    
    
    
    Can anyone recommend a Garden Contractor new  #Hitchin to help remove a treestump /cc @Hitchinites @louiseyexley @hitchinlife @AdvertiserSue    
    
    
    @louiseyexley Fantastic! I'll call them for a quote shortly.    
    
    
    My ramblings on Ebooks: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#ebooks     
    
    
    Playing with 3D graphics for the first time since my undergrad days. This time with three.js rather than OpenGL.    
    
    
    A late #FF @StartupLJackson @DEVOPS_BORAT and @UXYoda    
    
    
    The specific gravity of my soon-to-be beer is 1.011 -- a little while until it'll be ready    
    
    
    On Deal Or No Deal: "The Gambling Commission does not seem to think that there is any skill element to the show." #noshit    
    
    
    Data Scientists are the new Quantitative Analysts #blackisthenewblack    
    
    
    Thank @FirstCapitalConnect for locking me captive on a train, only to miss the next one from Kings X.    
    
    
    @JofArnold Joining Lemmings and Tetris & Sudoku --> "Super Mario is NP-complete. http://www.newscientist.com/article/mg21328565.100-mario-is-hard-and-thats-mathematically-official.html …"    
    
    
    There are currently three copies of @ericries' book in our office. Presumably the #leanerstartups only have one.    
    
    
    There needs to be a campaign to answer "#Spartacus" when asked your name at @starbucks    
    
    
    @danversbaillieu Congratulations on the startup move, you seem to have cemented your position as startup scene celebrity :-)    
    
    
    When did £4 a pint become acceptable in pubs? (I appreciate its been standard in rip off music venues and clubs for some time)    
    
    
    @beth_tk BT kindly left us without Internet for 6 weeks after our last office move :-(    
    
    
    @easyjet Our Luton-Lisbon flight is V delayed and you've txtd me offering us refreshments - there is no information desk, who do I speak to?    
    
    
    Plane delayed. Keeping myself amused: http://bit.ly/HhV8Aj     
    
    
    @richardprice100 I'd have thought with a combination of location and time, it'd be pretty straight forward    
    
    
    @LetchworthCtre I'm very disappointed in your support of homeopathy and hope you appreciate how bad the supporting evidence is.    
    
    
    How recruiters look at your resume http://flowingdata.com/2012/04/11/how-recruiters-look-at-your-resume/ … via @flowingdata    
    
    
    I want an app that uses my current GPS coordinates to work out what train I'm on, how delayed it is, and when/where it stops.    
    
    
    @richardprice100 If someone did it as a kickstarter, I reckon they'd comfortably get support    
    
    
    @drbsg Presumably you'd start with a web-app as proof of concept and use GPS via JS. If you got traction you would build an iPhone app.    
    
    
    Some rare #FF's from me: @flowingdata @CompSciFact and @StatFact    
    
    
    Amazon Cloud search looks very interesting, will people move over from Elastic Search?    
    
    
    @drbsg iPhone :-)    
    
    
    Has anyone successfully used the GitHub for Mac client with git repository not hosted on GitHub?    
    
    
    Chrome OS is looking increasingly like the Debian for the EEE in Easy Mode http://googlesystem.blogspot.co.uk/2012/04/new-window-manager-for-chrome-os.html …    
    
    
    @PookyH I use LinkedIn extensively for managing contacts, as an online CV and to look up extended CVs of candidates I interview    
    
    
    Does anyone use Opera (the web browser) for anything besides checking sites work in Opera?    
    
    
    Learning R, any recommended reading? Starting with "Vizualize This"    
    
    
    If you're an app developer, and you're not currently thinking about applications for the Pebble, then you're missing a trick    
    
    
    @mishra_alok The mobile browser space is clearly very different from desktop. UC Browser and Dolphin are much more popular than I realised.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie who's index do they sit on top of? Or have they done their own? #millionshort    
    
    
    @raemond @vanessa_murdock Congrats! My empirical research showed SIGIR only sent rejection letters ;-)    
    
    
    @cantinacarnitas @siegeworksart If I were in #Hitchin today, I'd come down and buy 35 Burritos    
    
    
    Predictions for the next 9 months: Explossion in Pebble compatible Apps and Stream Processing as a Service from AWS.    
    
    
    @hubmum The alpha model: http://bit.ly/J2y0jw     
    
    
    Should have shorted facebook shares -- reckon it'll bottom out at $20    
    
    
    Why don't estate agents put personalised QR codes on For Sale signs? For details just point your phone at the house - better than a phone no    
    
    
    I'm porting everything to this: http://esolangs.org/wiki/Emoticon     
    
    
    @shadchnev Congratulations! Roadtrip?    
    
    
    @raemond @CharlotteHase A friend of a friend of mine created ETA, example programs worth a look: http://www.miketaylor.org.uk/tech/eta/doc/index.html …    
    
    
    It's so meta it has to work: http://xkcd.com/1060/     
    
    
    @CharlotteHase I refuse to buy a scale at all -- what does that make me?    
    
    
    Some thoughts on Mundanity: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#mundanity … /cc @beth_tk @01factory @duncanr2    
    
    
    Nearly half way through the year and my three books a month aim is still going strong: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#books     
    
    
    Sometimes the most appropriate visualisation method, is not Matplotlib, Gnuplot or ggplot, or even D3, occasionally it's ascii.    
    
    
    @LinkedIn why did you store passwords in plain text? Isn't storage of salted hashed passwords standard practice?    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly can you use a Royal seal now?    
    
    
    It seems Leap Seconds are the new Millennium Bug    
    
    
    @shadchnev Looks good :-)    
    
    
    @richardprice100 People have been working on this for a while: http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?doid=1148170.1148270 …    
    
    
    Can someone do an opening ceremony spotify play list?    
    
    
    Anyone used Java-ML? Have been looking at the API and looks straight forward, keen to hear of anyone's experiences.    
    
    
    Really looking forward to mentoring #YRS2012 tomorrow    
    
    
    Anyone know how to listen again to local radio on the iplayer iOS app? I can only work out how to do it from the website.    
    
    
    If there was a standard markup for infographics, Google could index them and people could search them #JustSayin    
    
    
    @phazonoverload would wrapping the text area in a form submitting as a GET and triggering the submit action on the form work? #yrshelp    
    
    
    @richardprice100 the twitter API offers streaming from a search term    
    
    
    @nathandunn97 How about the Yahoo Finance API? http://www.gummy-stuff.org/Yahoo-data.htm  http://code.google.com/p/yahoo-finance-managed/wiki/YahooFinanceAPIs … #YRSHELP #YRS2012    
    
    
    @jackwilsdon QCN have plans to release data, probably worth mailing: http://qcn.stanford.edu/research/data-downloads … #YRSHELP #YRS2012    
    
    
    @BenTatman1 How about the CrunchBase API? e.g. http://api.crunchbase.com/v/1/search.js?query=facebook.com … Contains links to logo images in JSON #YRSHELP    
    
    
    @Ruirize Check the coords are the right way around (long=Vert,lat=Horiz) and check the projection (e.g. http://xkcd.com/977/ ) #yrshelp    
    
    
    @AndyBursh The IF statement is your friend: SELECT IF(A>B,-1,IF(A=B,0,1)) FROM table; #yrshelp #yrs2012    
    
    
    Hirst-esque fun with spots -- http://numenore.co.uk/stuff#spots     
    
    
    In years to come Harry we be considered the rakish prince and held in similar affection that the Duke of Edinburgh is now.    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly http://www.iheartchaos.com/post/22228565802/youve-been-eating-cupcakes-wrong-your-whole-life …    
    
    
    Finally finished my Spot pictures: http://numenore.co.uk/stuff#spots  http://numenore.co.uk/store/images/spots.html … https://github.com/seo01/SpotPics     
    
    
    @richardprice100 looks very similar (although neater implementation) to Echo Echo    
    
    
    @shadchnev @jure If you consider only people who set their own PIN (I expect this is surprisingly high), is it a fair representation?    
    
    
    Wrote an essay for http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts  over the past few days but @jancyoverell suggested it's a little too caustic for publication    
    
    
    Interview: Douglas de Jager, CEO of spider.io, Explains Ad Viewability and Its Impact on the Online Ad Industry http://bit.ly/Rl9yzn     
    
    
    Planning to start an Etsy/Folksy shop    
    
    
    FYI: linked in endorsements -- you can endorse people for anything...    
    
    
    @shadchnev you are limited to linkedin's auto complete -- trust me, this is wide ranging enough not to limit humour or offence ;-)    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet Unfortunately you're limited to linkedin's vocabulary of skills. This is more of a challenge than a limitation :-)    
    
    
    @fhr You are limited to the skills linkedin offer... the list is a mix of genuine skills and total oddities -- rife for amusement    
    
    
    Raw materials have all arrived to make my "stuff" to sell in my Etsy/Folksy shop -- If I'm successful I might break even    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly don't sell out before we get there!    
    
    
    Swimming, gardening, DIY -- smells like Sunday    
    
    
    Remember there's no-one as Irish as Barack O'bama: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HplZ_taHXLM …    
    
    
    Over 10 months in and 3 books a month still going strong: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#books     
    
    
    @JofArnold if you find an alternative let me know!    
    
    
    @edds does it tell you how to make the title blink?    
    
    
    @duncanr2 I assume you have reasonable excuse for this discovery?    
    
    
    @NHC_Matt Any chance of NHC offering a part time bicycle maintenance course?    
    
    
    The future of billboard advertising is RTB #IMHO: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#sneakytracking …    
    
    
    Was introduced to this today by @jancyoverell: http://minifigs.me/     
    
    
    My twitter followers and linked in connections count have overtaken my facebook friends. I'm sure this significant, but I don't know why.    
    
    
    Planning home improvements with Pinterest... I seem to be planning a shed in a forest with a New York loft above it.    
    
    
    You have to watch Wilfred -- this is my favourite show! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mEH-TRwJwf4 …    
    
    
    The current discussion between the Conservatives and UKIP wouldn't be necessary if Cameron hadn't apposed the single transferable vote.    
    
    
    IAB’s SafeFrames Review by Dr Douglas de Jager, Founder & CEO & Dr Simon Overell, Chief Scientist of spider.io | http://www.exchangewire.com/blog/2012/12/05/iabs-safeframe-review-by-dr-douglas-de-jager-founder-ceo-dr-simon-overell-chief-scientist-of-spider-io/ …    
    
    
    @ashley_brown you have a talent for hair loss    
    
    
    @charlesarthur we've found a MASSIVE data leak in Internet Explorer -- a story of interest?    
    
    
    Best amazon review ever: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00520BKM0/?tag=093-20 …    
    
    
    Trying to decide what to get my dad for Christmas. I don't think one second hand book is going to cut it.    
    
    
    Apparently listing reasons the Olympics is better than Christmas is not "getting into the spirit" #barhumbug    
    
    
    I hope everyone has a close eye on their sheep /cc @borkurdotnet #yulelads    
    
    
    Play the NEW #spider_io challenge -- A worrying IE security leak turned into a "fun" game. http://iedataleak.spider.io/     
    
    
    @blueotterwines What's your e-mail address -- we want to buy some wine    
    
    
    @IE Data leakage of mouse data is doing the rounds: http://zd.net/SPFtKw  http://spider.io/blog/2012/12/internet-explorer-data-leakage/ …    
    
    
    comScore sued over 'sinister' data collection methods http://www.theregister.co.uk/2011/08/24/comscore_privacy_lawsuit/ … via @regvulture    
    
    
    "There is only one thing in life worse than being talked about, and that is not being talked about."    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet A assume you mean the night of the 22nd? Sure! @littledudes have been asking after you.    
    
    
    @alan_patterson It appears to have gone viral, hundreds of articles in over a dozen languages    
    
    
    Hoping the IE Mouse Data leak will make @guardiantw news /cc @aleksk @charlesarthur    
    
    
    Am I the only one in the world not using Bootstrap and still using 960.css? And Prototype? Everyone else is using JQuery. :-(    
    
    
    @richardprice100 There is an interesting discussion on academic paper analytics on this weeks Guardian Science Weekly Podcast wrt eJournals    
    
    
    Anyone else stuck in Kings X :-(    
    
    
    At #hitchin station with a couple of hundred unhappy commuters    
    
    
    @bensummers if it is, it won't catch on    
    
    
    @richardprice100 but you only just passed 1m! Clearly going well!    
    
    
    @ashley_brown #sleep #work #sleep #work #sleep #work #sleep #work #sleep #work    
    
    
    @ashley_brown this is a 4 Square intervention. Admit you have a problem.    
    
    
    @richardprice100 it will come for audio books first (smaller step from music, less collateral damage if it fails)    
    
    
    Writing xeyes for @IE 9    
    
    
    Nearly finished xeyes for Internet Explorer: http://numenore.co.uk/xeyes/     
    
    
    Just released xeyes for @IE on GitHub https://github.com/seo01/xeyes-for-ie … http://numenore.co.uk/xeyes/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Find out if I achieved my 2012 resolution of reading 3 books a month: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#books     
    
    
    @robberwick Glad you liked it. Just written the accompanying post: http://numenore.co.uk/stuff#xeyes-for-ie …    
    
    
    Finally finished eyes for @IE: http://numenore.co.uk/stuff#xeyes-for-ie …
http://numenore.co.uk/xeyes/     
    
    
    Migrating to evernote and pinterest for keeping track of notes and bookmarks    
    
    
    Just this on my CD shelf and ripping it to iTunes -- retro? http://www.amazon.co.uk/Club-Mix-Ibiza-Biggest-Anthems/dp/B00005N6RM …    
    
    
    My resolution for 2013: watch four new films a month… http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#films     
    
    
    @raemond what are you building first?    
    
    
    @raemond let me know when there is an app I can set your microwave from    
    
    
    There seem to be a log of articles and posts about how Big Data/Data Science will explode in the next 2-5 years. It's nosql all over again.    
    
    
    Duck tape is dead to me now. I've discovered denso tape!    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase you know you can endorse people for almost anything. Being creative with endorsements is great fun    
    
    
    #FF @WestEndLunch    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase An example is winging its way to you via linked in -- there is a controlled vocabulary which forces creativity    
    
    
    Epic playlist from 6 Music: http://www.bbc.co.uk/6music/vote/100-greatest-hits/ …    
    
    
    @edds you appear to have a passport next to your TV and cup of tea with pictures of bikes on the background #observations    
    
    
    Saw this in the National Portrait Gallery a couple of weeks ago. Best video installation I've seen: http://www.capguncollective.com/3038/3038/     
    
    
    Great argument against killing the term "Big Data" http://techcrunch.com/2013/01/05/why-we-need-to-kill-big-data/?goback=.gde_4449177_member_203926617 …    
    
    
    Just switched from @giffgaff to @TMobileUK - same price, same product, better customer service    
    
    
    @clubclasstravel I purchased from "Neil" in an EE shop. I can phone or visit him personally about problems. @giffgaff don't offer this.    
    
    
    I hope someone is getting a picture of Hertfordshire's black squirrels in white frosty trees    
    
    
    Roads are like sheets of ice in Hitchin -- #mwoorgwitpwease    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly Fun practicing plumbing: http://instagram.com/p/U9EfHvuqpQ/     
    
    
    I've been practicing my plumbing for our steam punk bathroom: http://instagram.com/p/U9EfHvuqpQ/     
    
    
    @ashley_brown what do you think of my Rules for Recruiters? http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#recruiters …    
    
    
    Join DropWines and get £10 off! http://www.dropwines.com?utm_source=ref_5B7C4BF414C0E93488E90A7FF92EE74Fdropwines.com/?utm_source=re … #wine via @dropwines    
    
    
    @NHC_Matt you need to post a picture of the @cantinacarnitas trailer!    
    
    
    @bensummers We used these extensively and have had no problems -- where are you having trouble?    
    
    
    @bensummers Just checked and I used zipeg to extract mine http://www.zipeg.com/     
    
    
    @bensummers I'm going to blame apple on this one, their [de]compression tools are poor (case in point: http://www.47ronin.com/zcat-broken-on-mac-os-x-feature-or-bug/26 …).    
    
    
    @bensummers it does give the impression Microsoft neglected to test a tool built for testing    
    
    
    Why don't people poke anymore?    
    
    
    @duncanr2 Tea comes in bags because it's infused. You make Machu tea from a powder (like coffee) because it's dissolved (like coffee).    
    
    
    @alan_patterson the scary world of internet advertising    
    
    
    The Bloomberg Billionaires Index is a daily ranking of the world's richest people. http://www.bloomberg.com/billionaires/2013-02-09/aaa/adjaa …    
    
    
    Prediction for 2015-2020: the phrase "Retail 2.0" is coined - a strong brand with complementary online/high street presence.    
    
    
    Having fun with cmx.io http://yfrog.com/hsdagpp     
    
    
    @voltdb Kudos to whoever came up with the name for your e-mail newsletter    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly Dr Seuss clearly didn't have to find a new source of cup cakes! Best of luck on your next endeavour.    
    
    
    Maintain as little code as possible: don't reinvent the wheel, use open source, reusable patterns and a concise language #makersacademy    
    
    
    Impressive, but surely using a font to represent a map shows a string of bad design decisions: http://intridea.github.com/stately/     
    
    
    90% of the time I try to use the reduce operator with a lambda in python it turns out not to be powerful enough    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet Having used a standing desk, what do you make of a walking desk? http://techcrunch.com/2013/03/03/why-every-office-should-switch-to-walking-desks/ …    
    
    
    @JofArnold Where do coins go?    
    
    
    I have strong suspicions that "del" in python does release memory as swiftly as one may expect    
    
    
    @drbsg Scheme is one of the languages that pops up in conversation every 6 months or so (like coffee script or R) - is it worth learning?    
    
    
    @robertcambridge @jofarnold I'm very tempted but don't know what to do with coins. Also as £20 notes are 1.5cm bigger than $s will they fit?    
    
    
    @JofArnold @robertcambridge Admit it, you are a guerrilla salesman! I may be forced to buy one.    
    
    
    @shadchnev that would be inherently gamable and unfair. What would you use as a feedback mechanism?    
    
    
    I just backed ME, FAKEGRIMLOCK: THE BOOK OF AWESOME on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/12vvi60     
    
    
    There seems to be a leak in our bathroom.It's intermittent and is yet to happen while I'm in the house.Does plumbing suffer race conditions?    
    
    
    Best XKCD in some time: http://xkcd.com/1185/     
    
    
    Does anyone know a HTML to JSON converter? Wondering if you can write a viable crawler in Bash using tools to cURL and JQ    
    
    
    @jayforeman at least they didn't say "Harry Potter"    
    
    
    Meet the Most Suspect Publishers on the Web http://adweek.it/16FRzNM     
    
    
    Today we won! (Via @FAKEGRIMLOCK) pic.twitter.com/UAzaVC1Pmv    
    
    
    @jayforeman how does "no woman no cry" or "three little birds" for in?    
    
    
    @robberwick I highly recommend jq, I use it almost everyday    
    
    
    Who Is Behind Chameleon Botnet Tricking Marketers? via @BloombergTV http://bloom.bg/16Og7UF     
    
    
    Thinking of buying a reconditioned Nokia 7110 instead of an iPhone 5 -- am I mad?    
    
    
    @JofArnold I have never been described as a hipster before. I don't even have an 8-bit twitter avatar.    
    
    
    I promise I won't make a habit of tweeting cat gifs. But...
http://24.media.tumblr.com/fe0c67dd3b7e5fe6d0fe4226fc71d126/tumblr_mhvliyb1F51s410g9o1_500.gif …    
    
    
    Have now seen @pottedpotter 3 times (spread over 6 years). I understand that we get pie from @ActorJeff /cc @Daniel_Veronica    
    
    
    @OnScroll Fancy coming to @spider_io towers for a beer sometime to discuss all things viewability? http://www.spider.io/blog/2012/07/join-us-for-a-tipple-at-spider-towers/ …    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase Are you entering?    
    
    
    Does anyone else quietly say "total eclipse" after finishing a Jaffa Cake?    
    
    
    @HANDcreative Minimum Viable Personality from @FAKEGRIMLOCK sums it up: http://www.slideshare.net/asocialme/boring-9519224 …    
    
    
    50% of the time I phone my bank I fail the security checks :-(    
    
    
    Can someone explain to me what QR codes are good for, besides being robust barcode replacements?    
    
    
    @JofArnold I think as way of conveying URLs via print, they are a total failure. Especially given their size and style.    
    
    
    @robberwick #BlinkStick looks very cool -- much more accessible than arduino    
    
    
    @shadchnev Is that the book you recommended to me the last time we had a beer?    
    
    
    @duncanr2 just because a freedom exits, does not mean it needs to be used. Hence norms.    
    
    
    Thinking of buying a #blinkstick and building something Good-Night-Lamp-esque http://blinkstick.com  http://goodnightlamp.com     
    
    
    Came across the notion of "Kantian Fairness" today, and associated problems. Sounds like the British condition.    
    
    
    Is there an extrapolation logical fallacy? Or is it Reductio ad absurdum / Slippery Slope? http://www.theskepticsguide.org/resources/logicalfallacies.aspx … http://xkcd.org/1204/     
    
    
    @PookyH Lyra Says is the best thing on tumblr ATM    
    
    
    Designing an MVP for a 4sq alternative sharing less information to less people in fewer clicks (I appreciate none, noone, 0 is the extreme)    
    
    
    @PookyH WTF? How do people like that exist?    
    
    
    Regrets: http://www.uploadlibrary.com/pushmerchandising/draft_lens4458812module31611932photo_1241584818trooper-regrets.jpg …    
    
    
    @Debsalini thanks for reminding me! #vote    
    
    
    @JofArnold You need a bigger data set.    
    
    
    Parkham WI embarrassed by dressing as pirates for talk by former Somali pirate hostage http://www.thisisnorthdevon.co.uk/Parkham-WI-embarrassed-dressing-pirates-talk/story-18871181-detail/story.html …    
    
    
    Just ordered a #blinkstick -- first project planned on paper -- now I need to clear some time to code! http://blinkstick.com/     
    
    
    @richardprice100 Have you read Wikinomics? Describes sharing data in verticals. If you can become a cross-discipline hub it would be great.    
    
    
    Planning to find out what happens at @HackHitchin tonight /cc @arvydev    
    
    
    This is me: http://www.thedailymash.co.uk/news/society/middle-class-man-convinced-builders-like-him-2013041265450 … /via @dcollis    
    
    
    Have written a simple (and unconventional) scraper for Google Real Time Analytics to solve this problem: http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13839430/real-time-visitors-from-google-analytics-how-to-get-it …    
    
    
    If you think the sale of tumblr/instagram/yammer/summly has any relevance on your own app/dashboard/platform/network you are deeply mistaken    
    
    
    @NunoCardoso Do you plan to build anything on it?    
    
    
    @kirbywinfield viewability measurement in nested cross domain iframes, now accredited for all major desktop browsers: http://spider.io/mrc-viewability     
    
    
    "Microsoft advertise for jobs in optional TCP headers" http://mashable.com/2013/05/28/flickr-jobs/ …    
    
    
    If you don't go to the off licence on the way home from the gym, you're doing it wrong    
    
    
    Having used it for Apache for 10 years, decided I should learn how the apache configs work -- OS X makes life difficult    
    
    
    Oldie but goodie: If PHP were British http://www.addedbytes.com/blog/if-php-were-british/ …    
    
    
    I love Wikipedia: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Portal:Portal …    
    
    
    Love this: http://techcrunch.com/2013/06/18/onion-pi/ …    
    
    
    Has reliable screen sharing over WIFI killed the use-case for a KVM switch?    
    
    
    @bensummers I've noticed a substantial price increase over 5 years. I assumed due to drop in demand. Screen sharing "just works" now.    
    
    
    @robberwick Increased specialisation explains the price hike I've seen.The target is no longer home/office users with a couple of boxes (me)    
    
    
    A startup having multiple revenue streams is code for "we don't know what the business model will be"    
    
    
    @bensummers Are you using a http://modern.ie  VM?    
    
    
    @rdcowley everything    
    
    
    One for all the QR code fans out there: http://xkcd.com/1237/     
    
    
    The more I switch between writing Python and Java, the better my Python gets and the worse my Java gets    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase @cathal The amount of waste that will be reduced when manufacturing on demand hits mainstream is staggering    
    
    
    Common sense comment on Facebook: http://www.bitbanter.com/wara/dutxh4CmQufe2qwqs …    
    
    
    My guide to data science: http://memegenerator.co/instance/39737392 …    
    
    
    Wish I was attending this: http://www.geo.uzh.ch/~rsp/gir13/     
    
    
    Is @TheTileApp genius, creepy or just a gimmick?    
    
    
    @shadchnev @TheTileApp The fact it only lasts a year makes me think the same    
    
    
    MySQL docs are so much better than Postgresql. Both are leaps and bounds ahead of HIVE.    
    
    
    @thistlesandwich so small!    
    
    
    Can someone remind me what a day off feels like...    
    
    
    The proliferation of browser-engine backed crawlers in the past 4 years continues to amaze me    
    
    
    @blahpro If that's a euphemism, I assume you're off to A&E.    
    
    
    @arvydev @1and1_UK Easy solution -- Change your password to "D0ntAsk4ForMyPa$$wordOnTheF0ne!"    
    
    
    Made my day: http://devopsreactions.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    Why is Top Loader's "Dancing in the Moonlight" in the top 40 after 13 years?    
    
    
    @robberwick because it's great!    
    
    
    @NHC_Matt 79% :-)    
    
    
    We made the BBC! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-23696805 …    
    
    
    @paulcuth They were running with a 30min delay and 50% cancellation at 7:15 :-(    
    
    
    If I were a teacher, I would do this: http://flowingdata.com/2013/08/02/teacher-forces-student-to-do-math-to-unlock-phone/ …    
    
    
    Creating a mural inspired by Banksy, Invader and Hirst. My house smells of spray paint.    
    
    
    @robberwick @rdcowley Currently it's a work in progress - but you get the idea. pic.twitter.com/vPUDzwWEi2    
    
    
    @rdcowley @robberwick I think I have more in common with "Handy Andy"    
    
    
    @alan_patterson keep up the good work :-)    
    
    
    @robberwick @rdcowley Please tell me you dressed as all three nephews.    
    
    
    @rdcowley What time you meeting? We're heading to this in the Vic at 7:30 https://twitter.com/Poorlybee/status/378477809900859393 …    
    
    
    @rdcowley We may come and join you after the godless filth ;-) We'll see how the evening goes.    
    
    
    @makersacademy Strongly disagree! Interview code tests are not to test code quality. They test approach to problems & grasp of key concepts.    
    
    
    @shadchnev I think this is a very possible view of the future. :-(    
    
    
    First draft of my post on QR-Codes: http://numenore.co.uk/thoughts#qrcodes …    
    
    
    "@cdixon: "On the phenomenon of bullshit jobs" http://www.strikemag.org/bullshit-jobs/ " sounds like Douglas Adams' 'B' Ark    
    
    
    "@ZenProverbs: Nothing ever exists entirely alone; everything is in relation to everything else." Surprisingly relevant in AI & data science    
    
    
    @shadchnev https://github.com/seo01/SimplePortfolio … ;-)    
    
    
    @shadchnev 1. PHP hosting is cheap & ubiquitous. 2. It's future proof, designed for when mobile resolution matches current desktops :-P    
    
    
    "@StatFact: Simpson's paradox http://ow.ly/pbFNI " <- Keep reading this until you understand it    
    
    
    @shadchnev Getting nostalgic in your old age.    
    
    
    Attempting to write a solr app. It's come on along way in the last 5 years. Documentation is still poor.    
    
    
    @JofArnold @afternoon I've a 1980's Eagle that would qualify :-)    
    
    
    Apple's space ship campus looks like a panopticon to me -- a circular prison of designers.    
    
    
    @MarkMellors presumably the lasers aren't printed. Looks a lot like a future Dr Who villain.    
    
    
    @paulcuth That is pretty unbelievable    
    
    
    @robberwick @paulcuth if this catches on, surely it won't end with electric cars :-(    
    
    
    @robberwick @paulcuth I reckon there is a patent troll opportunity here: pair the term DRM with anything used day-to-day, e.g. DRMed Water    
    
    
    @arvydev @robberwick surely we're going to move the other way - it's only a matter of time until we have a kinetic/solar powered smart watch    
    
    
    "Clap clap tap-tap-tap, clap my cup, clap off the wall, switch my cup..."    
    
    
    @jayforeman only python    
    
    
    @paulcuth As a fan of awesome cats, this Leopardus should be up your street: http://www.bbc.co.uk/nature/25086721     
    
    
    @thistlesandwich they make you look a little like a Doctor Who villain    
    
    
    @TheKrishes Wolfgang?    
    
    
    @TheKrishes Even better!    
    
    
    http://runningahackerspace.tumblr.com/  #cc @HackHitchin @paulcuth @robberwick @rdcowley @arvydev @MarkMellors    
    
    
    PHD Comics: Science News Cycle http://www.phdcomics.com/comics.php?f=1174 … via @phdcomics    
    
    
    @jancyoverell clearly only a padawan rabbit whisperer; Vladimir @littledudes still prefers me.    
    
    
    Finished v0.1 of my ngram tweet generator -- much refactoring required plus more text processing and probabilistic goodness before release    
    
    
    All the business plans on the #Apprentice were disappointing, I'd have fired all of them    
    
    
    Hunting programmers and designers -- if you see any point them at http://spider.io    
    
    
    @CrumblyWumbly tweet more pics of delicious cakes and all spamming will be forgiven    
    
    
    For those interested in the legalities of hiring and firing visit this months @bootlaw    
    
    
    My automated tweet generator based on ngrams works equally well generating fantastic prose with LOTR as the training data    
    
    
    ... "Sam sat silent for some time arrived to supplement the dwarves night"    
    
    
    @resumevu any chance of a beta invite?    
    
    
    Sadly this made me laugh out loud: http://mashable.com/2011/08/03/best-wi-fi-names/ …    
    
    
    Should blogs be preserved forever or should they have an expiration date? http://blogforever.eu/     
    
    
    @bootlaw Any chance of an article offering a legal perspective on @kissmetrics current sticky situation (and how others can avoid)?    
    
    
    First usable version of my ngram document generator committed: http://bit.ly/pDQvyf    
    
    
    