@tinyFey just send me an email with your resume and any other pertinent information -- thanks!    
    
    
    @lintool @abdur does twitter even have product that does event detection? trending topics != events.    
    
    
    i used to think the limit (as t -> infinity) of unread emails in my inbox was convergent, but recent evidence refutes that hypothesis.    
    
    
    dear @KAYAK, please stop with the horrible "personalized" contextual ads about beijing travel deals. i've already gone there and returned.    
    
    
    @jerepick I suppose businessmen exhibit travel destination burstiness. However, my travel destination distribution is much more uniform :)    
    
    
    @jerepick (with respect to international travel, that is... domestic is a completely different story)    
    
    
    google's "algorithm" for demoting bad sites: if(badsites.contains(url)) { url.score -= 100; } (http://goo.gl/qVQ4o)    
    
    
    today's deadlines: #wsdm2012 papers and TREC microblog track runs.    
    
    
    just submitted our @trecmicroblog runs. i look forward to seeing what approaches other groups took. #trec2011    
    
    
    WSDM submissions flat year-over-year -- 290 for #wsdm2010, 381 for #wsdm2011, and 367 for #wsdm2012    
    
    
    @iadh Last year may have also attracted more papers from Asia. I wonder if SIGIR will see a similar trend from this year to next.    
    
    
    @jteevan The number I quoted was from the "Reviewer Instructions" email sent by the 2011 PC chairs. Prob a few papers dropped during review.    
    
    
    @web_miner i'd personally like a set of knobs that let me trade off personal relevance, network relevance, and recency (cc @twittersearch)    
    
    
    i'm thrilled to join david blei, @kevinrose, and @aplusk as an advisor to @chomp (app search startup) -- http://bit.ly/pThl8F     
    
    
    1st Southern California Workshop on Machine Learning @ UC Irvine on September 9th (free registration) -- http://bit.ly/nGeXqu     
    
    
    trying to get ahead on my reviewing obligations. AIRS done. next up: WSDM and a bunch of journal articles (TOIS, TKDE, TIST, and IRJ).    
    
    
    giving a talk on Mavuno (a scalable distributional similarity engine) at the #kdd2011 LDMTA workshop on sunday. paper: http://bit.ly/o3WsrC     
    
    
    .@JeffD mavuno isn't available yet, but will be soon. i'm looking for some folks to test the install process and run some tests earlier, tho    
    
    
    my #kdd2011 LDMTA workshop slides for "Mavuno: A Scalable and Effective Hadoop-Based Paraphrase Acquisition System" : http://bit.ly/q19kDX     
    
    
    @nimatwtr every time i feel down, i just read your tweet stream, and it makes me feel a lot better.    
    
    
    i noticed a variable number of spam bots follow me each time i tweet. i wonder if it's random or has to do w/ specific keywords. let's test.    
    
    
    seo, sem, search engines, marketing, analytics, optimization, ads, advertising, ranking, web site, services, google, yahoo, bing, first page    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff you're right. that strangely netted me 3 legit followers and just 2 spam bots. weird. maybe not the right set of topic words.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff maybe something like "where can i buy twitter and facebook followers and grow my network ?" will be more effective.    
    
    
    @diazf_y feel much shaking there?    
    
    
    @diazf_y that's clearly the only plausible explanation for this quake and the one in CO last night.    
    
    
    @BenCarterette was that your warm welcome home from Russia?    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson that's a great title for an IR book (or a SIGIR tutorial...)    
    
    
    dumb question: what's the correct usage of "toward" vs "towards"? the copy edits for a manuscript i'm preparing suggest i have no idea.    
    
    
    @jerepick they changed all of my "towards" to "toward". maybe they just wanted to save ink to lower costs.    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson Interesting! Perhaps it's a regional (NW PA) thing. I was raised to say other bizarre things like "what do you taste for?"    
    
    
    @delsweil "toward" just sounds funny to me. i guess i'm more british than i knew :)    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson Yeah. That's another one I never realized was weird until I told someone "my car needs washed".    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff unlike you, i can't even construct an s-less tweet. i look forward to your s-less SIGIR paper next year.    
    
    
    another well-executed LA machine learning meetup today. kudos to @petricek and @zaxtax    
    
    
    now that the initial google+ buzz has died down, my stream is more like a slow drip only worth checking once or twice a week, at most.    
    
    
    @XplusOne good question! i was trying to determine what types of keywords are most targeted by spambots.    
    
    
    .@davidandrzej interesting work! will definitely read the paper. (fwiw, i would strongly recommend to never use the indri "#not" operator)    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries i was responsible for L8 and L15. unfortunately, i haven't seen anyone actually use these in any papers.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries btw, if you have a particular data need, you can always ping someone in y! and they can try to get it released for you.    
    
    
    elevators should require a special "i'm unable to climb stairs" access card for all rides between floors n and n+1 (or n-1).    
    
    
    4.2 earthquake in the san fernando valley. very light shaking here in marina del rey.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG i'm guessing a small %. most are likely random junk, strange misspellings, and bizarre long queries.    
    
    
    i'm co-chairing the #ictir2011 best paper award committee. we have a strong, diverse pool of candidates to choose from.    
    
    
    not too surprised by the bartz news. she was one of the factors that caused me to leave yahoo!    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff you mean, other than government red tape?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff 10 years at NIST?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff that's a nice milestone, btw. only 40 more years until the coveted CD-534.    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson awesome. thanks for the pointer!    
    
    
    attending the southern california machine learning workshop at UC irvine    
    
    
    my socal machine learning workshop slides: http://bit.ly/q5QAN4  . asks what's more important for learning to rank - features or models?    
    
    
    it's only 10am and i already don't want to eat any more mooncake this year.    
    
    
    @lintool that was exactly my argument. no need for incremental modeling improvements when you have lots of data and strong features.    
    
    
    @jerepick yes, excellent point! if the language is expressive enough then the distinction begins to blur such that query = features + model    
    
    
    @lintool that's exactly what i thought... at least it's a step in the right direction.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @trecmicroblog did i miss something or has there been some sort of delay?    
    
    
    it's a longshot, but... does anyone in los angeles know if book royalties necessitate a business tax registration certificate? #la #dtla    
    
    
    mostly happy with our @trecmicroblog results. we kept it simple and combined a number of proven techniques w/ domain-specific adaptations.    
    
    
    @milesEfron i look forward to reading your notebook paper! i wish we had found the time to do something a bit more risky ourselves.    
    
    
    my first patent was recently granted (US 8,005,845). basic idea: "intent-adaptive machine learned query-biased summarization"    
    
    
    twitter started randomly(?) dropping posts made by my followers from my timeline. i've missed a few "important" messages as a result.    
    
    
    @web_miner yes, but when combined they gives rise to a very specific (yet broadly defined) "invention" (that yahoo now has little use for.)    
    
    
    #twitter segmentation #fail... trending topic "Ask Don" as in... "don't ASK, DON't tell".    
    
    
    http://www.businessinsider.com/yahoo-board-not-looking-for-ceo-2011-9 … ... Yahoo! Research => News Corp Research? Doesn't have quite the same ring to it.    
    
    
    i'm not a fan of facebook's redesign, but i do like their new open graph features. nice, simple way to add basic semantics to web content    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries you can add the tags to any web page. e.g., you can appify your publications page with "+Read It" buttons if you so choose    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries @diazf_y i wouldnt actually use this myself, but will gladly scrape other's "open graph" content as a rich source of evidence    
    
    
    another Twitter trending topic gem (for Los Angeles): "Tomorrow is Friday" (trending on Friday, go figure)    
    
    
    do any search toolkits support per-tag weighting? i want to have <tag wt="3">...</tag> in the text and use 3 during ranking. @TerrierTeam ?    
    
    
    @pbrane thanks! low-level custom code isn't a problem. better than the complexities of implementing new index data structures myself.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald thanks, craig. indri supports the same. the problem with that solution is variable # of tags per doc (think anchor text)    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald if terrier implemented that, then you might make a convert out of me, afterall ;)    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald unfortunately, no. weights will be arbitrary real-values in no way connected to the TF (or IDF) of the span's text.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries nope, the weights are static and computed prior to indexing.    
    
    
    do any cities have a "smart grid" of traffic signals? LA could seriously use some more sensors + intelligence to improve system-wide flow.    
    
    
    @CathyE nice -- thanks for the pointer!    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG my pet peeve: when dozens of cars end up waiting at a red light for > 3 minutes, while zero cars pass through the green light    
    
    
    @jelsas depends on how you define "open". most publishers (ACM, Elsevier) allow posting to personal web sites. WWW used to put PDFs on web    
    
    
    there's a fine line between being too busy and being utterly incompetent    
    
    
    @julian_urbano successful procrastination is an art :)    
    
    
    @diazf_y @twittersearch furthermore, [can] should not match [can't].    
    
    
    my interest in a given seminar is inversely proportional to the number of reminder emails i receive about it    
    
    
    @julian_urbano i wonder if they would accept a scanned hand-written PDF.    
    
    
    when using NER annotator w/ latest @stanfordnlp, set ner.useSUTime prop to false to avoid endless exceptions/warnings for docs w/o date tags    
    
    
    @stanfordnlp It is useful for docs w/ timestamps. BTW, not all msgs are just "logging". I got a NullPointerException @ SUTime.java:1707.    
    
    
    Mavuno is now available! Open source. Scalable (Hadoop). Modular. Supports large-scale #nlproc and text mining. Get it: http://bit.ly/nQS2dn     
    
    
    apparently exceeding github's free account "soft limit" of 300MB only becomes an issue if/when you hit 1GB, according to their tech support.    
    
    
    coffee from breakfast spilled on my shirt? check. tomato soup from lunch spilled on my shirt? check. meetings this afternoon? check.    
    
    
    kudos to @yandex for their continued outreach to the research community via (anonymized) data sharing. http://imat-relpred.yandex.ru/en     
    
    
    "A Feature-Centric View of Information Retrieval" (Springer IR Series) is now available - http://bit.ly/nsvXZO     
    
    
    CA homeowners -- did you get any specific earthquake-related inspections done (beyond the minimal ones required by state law) when buying?    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson yeah, probably will end up getting a geologist. have some concerns about liquefaction potential and/or landslides.    
    
    
    i'd be more tempted to try out iamResearcher if they didn't have such a grammatically incorrect name.    
    
    
    does #pandora serve anyone else geo-targeted ads for completely random midwestern cities that nobody's ever heard of? or is it just me?    
    
    
    @diazf_y i did spend four years in terre haute, indiana. i'm thankfully avoided picking up a taste for ICP (or PCP, for that matter.)    
    
    
    @i_am_researcher i was of course only joking. i hope to give it a try when i have a few free minutes.    
    
    
    not to be rude, but the #lucene "DefaultSimilarity" scoring function is an abomination. are users satisfied with its ranking quality?    
    
    
    if anyone's going to take down Google, it's going to be MC Hammer. http://www.cnn.com/2011/10/20/tech/web/mc-hammer-search-engine/index.html?hpt=hp_t2 …    
    
    
    @lintool google, the least "open" of all industrial research labs, is leading the charge towards openness? huh?    
    
    
    finally getting around to writing our TREC microblog track notebook paper.    
    
    
    The Yahoo Circus (Animation) http://techcrunch.com/2011/10/24/the-yahoo-circus-animation/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    i hope everyone enjoys #cikm2011. now the conference is here, i won't be sending you all spam (er, "publicity materials") anymore :)    
    
    
    sad that @congxing left us to work for google, but happy to inherit his apple 30" cinema HD display    
    
    
    metareviews should summarize the strengths/weaknesses raised by the reviewers. writing "reject based on reviews" is just phoning it in.    
    
    
    @bemikelive @doridayan smh    
    
    
    @SethGrimes Sentence boundary detection for Web docs = hard. Adding sentence boundary info to search index = expensive. Demand = little.    
    
    
    a plagiarized version of our SIGIR '10 "Learning to Efficiently Rank" paper found its way into a Materials Science journal, of all places...    
    
    
    @vitroc another researcher told us about it. i have no idea how they discovered it.    
    
    
    @julian_urbano http://www.scientific.net/AMR.268-270.1773 …    
    
    
    USC/ISI now has an (alleged) quantum computer (http://dailytrojan.com/2011/10/30/usc-receives-first-quantum-computer/ …) - time to put quantum IR theories to the test?    
    
    
    @julian_urbano didn't report yet, but will. fake authors? never thought of that. what's their agenda? citation factories?    
    
    
    @kohlschuetter thanks for the support! i'm guessing nothing will ever come of it, but it's certainly worth trying to get resolved.    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson @SebastianThrun key metrics: intelligence vs. propensity to cheat in both populations. too many unknowns to say for sure.    
    
    
    today google rolled out better support for implicitly year qualified queries, wh/ we studied in a YRL '09 tech report: http://www.isi.edu/~metzler/papers/2009-002_Metzler.pdf …    
    
    
    not a huge fan of the #ecir2012 conference management system (ConfTool)    
    
    
    our #trec2011 @trecmicroblog track notebook paper is now available at http://bit.ly/v7DUr4     
    
    
    i finally looked up how to say "wrong number" in spanish -- "número equivocado". that will come in handy.    
    
    
    coding rawcomparators for complex user-defined writable objects in hadoop is well worth the effort (and kind of fun).    
    
    
    @kunegis thanks!    
    
    
    @kohlschuetter @diazf_y regarding the "+" operator issue. google rolled out "verbatim search" today (http://insidesearch.blogspot.com/2011/11/search-using-your-terms-verbatim.html …)    
    
    
    @diazf_y i'd be interested in your findings, as well. don't know of too many IR-specific query languages, really, or user-facing studies.    
    
    
    @diazf_y google should adopt an indri-style query language. #verbatim(inquery stopword list)    
    
    
    @cherhan @julian_urbano @iadh unfortunately not at TREC. like this idea. perhaps tie w/ news feed (eg "predicting tomorrow's headlines")    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries no, you're absolutely correct. the inquery folks deserve all the credit!    
    
    
    only at USC: "... suspect approached him and stated he had a weapon (none seen) demanding complainant's lunch". strong armed lunch robbery.    
    
    
    who honestly thought it would be a good idea to have two NLP paper deadlines following peak vacation time? (NAACL-HLT: Jan 6, ACL: Jan 15).    
    
    
    upcoming conference paper deadline gauntlet: NAACL-HLT: 1/6, ACL: 1/15, ICWSM: 1/18, AAAI: 1/24, KDD: 2/10, SIGIR: 2/13.    
    
    
    @vanessa_murdock i tried in vain to find the deadline. do you know when it is?    
    
    
    @vanessa_murdock thanks!    
    
    
    #www2012 "Appification of the Web" workshop : https://sites.google.com/site/appweb2012/ …    
    
    
    you just know an email starting with "Dear Research Assistant Professor in Computer Science Donald Metzler," is going to be good...    
    
    
    @textminor @bemikelive not so much the sampling, but rather the "analysis".    
    
    
    curious to see how the ongoing yahoo saga will resolve    
    
    
    are there any good, reputable, non-sketchy local residential moving companies in los angeles that anyone can recommend? #dtla    
    
    
    @vgoklani @DataJunkie we have that data, but can't share (ToS issues). the only legit archive (AFAIK) is at the LoC (http://www.forbes.com/sites/oreillymedia/2011/06/13/the-library-of-congress-twitter-archive-one-year-later/ …)    
    
    
    solved a system of equations (3x3) by hand for the first time in over 10 years. math was more fun before i learned Matlab, Maple, and R    
    
    
    @movingpro thank you very much for the information!    
    
    
    looking forward to actually *walking* somewhere for once -- tomorrow's LA machine learning meetup is in downtown (http://www.meetup.com/LA-Machine-Learning/events/41675362/ …)    
    
    
    "new and improved" klout topics are horrible. i'm apparently influential about "email", "notebook", and "models" (the half-naked kind)    
    
    
    the ICTIR 2013 call for bids is heavily Euro-centric. perhaps the "I" should be replaced with an "E".    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries none of the above :) although not explicitly stated, it appears as though non-European bids won't be considered.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries specifically "The location should be easily accessible for people attending from across Europe and elsewhere."    
    
    
    @BenCarterette the *BCS* IRSG mailing list (haven't seen it on SIG-IRlist yet).    
    
    
    @cherhan I've compiled a reading list that should get you started: https://bitly.com/bundles/metzlerd/2 …. Let me know if you have any additional questions!    
    
    
    @cherhan also, sorry for the slow response!    
    
    
    Using Markov Random Fields for Information Retrieval Reading List - https://bitly.com/bundles/metzlerd/2 …    
    
    
    @DataJunkie If you haven't read this paper, then I highly recommend it: http://www.soi.city.ac.uk/~ser/idfpapers/Robertson_idf_JDoc.pdf …    
    
    
    a 10 page paper in ACM format turns into a 16 page paper in ACL/NAACL format. yikes.    
    
    
    @cegme i couldn't agree more. over half of the things they claim are "breaking news" are anything but.    
    
    
    despite the fact i only tweet about geek-laden topics, twitter insists on suggesting i follow chris brown, snoop dogg, and trey songz    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff that strategy seems to have moved me from the space of NBA players to R&B singers. it'll be interesting to see what's next.    
    
    
    @lintool is this subtle foreshadowing?    
    
    
    "who to follow" #fail continues. after nba players and r&b singers, i now get actors (sheen, hill) and something called "tap pet hotel"    
    
    
    @DataJunkie i'm not sure if this is bad matching, bad CF, bad personalization, incognito "promoted" suggestions, or something else entirely.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG i hadn't thought of that. uh oh.    
    
    
    amusing excerpt from the "Hosting SIGIR" web page: "SIGIR has no plans to include Antarctica in the [geographical] rotation."    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl for models w/ few params, coordinate ascent works amazingly well: http://www.cs.umass.edu/~mccallum/papers/direct-metzler05.pdf …    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl What a small world, indeed! You find yourself in excellent company. They are both awesome, top-notch engineers. Tell them hi.    
    
    
    i no longer get carded when buying alcohol, but still manage to get "can i see your student ID?" at campus eateries.    
    
    
    @iadh i totally agree. it's horrible. i've heard the same feedback from several other people, too.    
    
    
    #naacl reviewing load: 1 paper.    
    
    
    @JeffD money > relevance    
    
    
    just about any semi-interesting word i include in my tweet attracts spammers. asbestos.    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson more likely than not, some sort of spambot.    
    
    
    sorry @cnnbrk, you've distracted me with far too many non-breaking news events. i'm unfollowing you and removing you from my phone.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl if you want to see George's face turn red, and his blood begin to boil, talk to him about Pig bugs/errors/documentation    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG i went through my tweet history a few days ago hoping to answer you, but couldn't seem to find anything. i'll look again now.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG are you talking about these? https://twitter.com/?iid=am-70781558913269219505079903&nid=4+sender&uid=17773969&utm_content=profile#!/metzlerd/status/113277861586153472 … https://twitter.com/?iid=am-70781558913269219505079903&nid=4+sender&uid=17773969&utm_content=profile#!/jerepick/status/113360063879581696 …    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl it sounds like you are well on your way (if not already there) to having Pig war stories of your own :)    
    
    
    negative okapi idfs + max_score query optimization = fail    
    
    
    wow, the LA office of finance tax and permit division is so horribly incompetent. makes me want to flee LA even more.    
    
    
    i tend to overuse the word "very". is there a psycholinguistic theory/explanation/name for this very annoying habit?    
    
    
    @lintool very interesting! then perhaps it's something i subconsciously picked up from my wife and/or chinese colleagues    
    
    
    @DataJunkie thanks for the free advertising!    
    
    
    @sgouws very cool! it even correctly detected my horribly scripted \xi    
    
    
    udacity using search engines as CS101 is a brilliant marketing ploy. to actually learn about search, read an information retrieval book.    
    
    
    just deleted my @klout account. it's scoring was seemingly arbitrary, it's topics were horrible, and the perks were lame.    
    
    
    thanks to @lintool for pointing out gh-pages to me. handy way to host web sites associated w/ github projects    
    
    
    in about a month, i'll once again "bleed purple".    
    
    
    @fabreetseo Yeah, I'm flip-flopping between acadmia and industry. Perhaps I am better suited as a politician :)    
    
    
    hey @TWCable_LA -- if you wake me up one more time on the weekend, or call me during dinner again, this new customer will be an ex-customer.    
    
    
    "The Future of IR" paper selections from the upcoming SWIRL workshop: http://www.cs.rmit.edu.au/swirl12/discussion.php …    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald "The position is available as part of the SMART project" - is the name in homage to Cornell's SMART system?    
    
    
    paper w/ @bemikelive (http://bit.ly/zXpB6r ) received the best search paper "runner-up" award at #wsdm2012    
    
    
    contrary to popular belief, information retrieval is, in fact, more than just vector space models, TF.IDF, and PageRank    
    
    
    @aria42 that has yet to make its way into any of the naive characterizations of the field that i've heard    
    
    
    was surprised (and somewhat embarrassed) to find one of my tweets featured in the keynote by @hmason at #wsdm2012    
    
    
    does anyone know of any studies or articles on (reverse) age discrimination in academia?    
    
    
    @aria42 i finally gave into your relentless PR campaign and signed up for prismatic.    
    
    
    what are some creative things that one can do with 480 unused business cards?    
    
    
    @sgouws i also highly recommend 30 yo tawny porto at 30.    
    
    
    tried out @prismatic today and was pleasantly surprised to find so many relevant story recommendations    
    
    
    Google buys what’s left of defunct search startup Cuil http://venturebeat.com/2012/02/20/google-buys-cuil-patents/ …  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @julian_urbano NTCIREVAL - http://research.nii.ac.jp/ntcir/tools/ntcireval-en.html …. ERR not included in trec_eval, last time i checked (/cc @ian_soboroff)    
    
    
    attending Google LA's inaugural Speaker Series' talk by @theamitsinghal on  Monday. should be interesting.    
    
    
    facebook insists on recommending that I friend someone who sadly passed away recently. i guess death is hard to algorithmically model.    
    
    
    my recent work w/ @lintool, @nimapp, et al. has embraced this. paper experiments = Ivory unit tests http://arstechnica.com/science/news/2012/02/science-code-should-be-open-source-according-to-editorial.ars …  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @lintool my vacation is still young! :)    
    
    
    thanks for the follow @TRECWithUs, but I don't TREC like *that*    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl I'll actually be in the Bay Area March 5--16. It would be great to meet and also catch up w/ George and Lance.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG i'll have limited availability during the days. if you, @ChrisDiehl, + others want to get together some evening that'd be great    
    
    
    1) find cool data set 2) compute elementary statistics 3) post tag cloud or map viz to your blog 4) declare yourself a "data scientist"    
    
    
    @elunca @HCIR_GeneG @ChrisDiehl any day after 6pm that week works for me. mt view (or anywhere on light rail would be most convenient)    
    
    
    @zaxtax i'll be in the bay area for the next couple of weeks, too. let me know if you find some folks who want to get together    
    
    
    Tomorrow's my first day back at Yahoo. I sure picked an interesting time to rejoin.    
    
    
    worst. timing. ever.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @elunca sounds good. what day next week would work best for you guys? any day except friday is ok with me    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @elunca ok, tuesday it is, then! i'm impartial. do either of you have any preferences?    
    
    
    @JeffD thanks for the free advertisement, Jeff!    
    
    
    @stanfordnlp i strategically managed to open source mavuno before i left, so i plan to continue maintaining/developing it.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG pretty easy. the quality would depend on the NLP stack's "compatibility" with ur data. do u have newswire? web? something else?    
    
    
    like the author of this article, i was also pleasantly surprised by the number of tech startups in LA http://www.forbes.com/sites/tarabrown/2012/03/06/why-los-angeles-will-outpace-silicon-valley-as-the-tech-startup-capital/ …  via @prismatic    
    
    
    How Twitter is doing its part to democratize big data http://gigaom.com/cloud/how-twitter-is-doing-its-part-to-democratize-big-data/ …  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @zaxtax @ogrisel ditto. it was nice bumping into you guys. hope you enjoyed the conference.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG it currently doesn't perform any text cleansing. garbage chars would throw the NLP tools off. lines breaks are less problematic.    
    
    
    i've relocated my web site to http://bit.ly/wuiejt  (hint: you can find my latest CV there)    
    
    
    @sodaontheside from the web interface you can click "open" and then "details" to get the URL of a specific tweet    
    
    
    @faultlinebrew your web site is borked.    
    
    
    @faultlinebrew no problem. luckily, that won't stop me from stopping by tonight :)    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @elunca hey guys, i woke up with a bad fever this morning, so i'm going to have to postpone. if i'm better, thu would work    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @elunca thanks, guys. i'll let you know. i've done the warm whiskey home remedy several times before, and it really does work!    
    
    
    when pitching your startup, please try harder than "our co-founders are ex-Googlers".    
    
    
    @techmilind it's not every day you learn the identity of those pesky blind reviewers ;) thanks for the mavuno mention!    
    
    
    Nice intro article on how search engines rewrite your queries http://prsm.tc/251p5X  via @prismatic    
    
    
    our (long) paper titled "Structured Event Retrieval over Microblog Archives" was accepted at NAACL-HLT    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG nope. much more interesting than that :) we retrieve structured representations of events in response to ad hoc search queries    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG technically, it can be as few as 1, but realistically you want enough to generate a good summary of the event    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson of course. but since this is an academic paper you have to make it sound overly fancy / general :)    
    
    
    @francesco1986_ yep. event query => burst detection => temporal query expansion => tweet retrieval => generate "structured" results    
    
    
    @francesco1986_ @PFCdgayo i'll make a preprint available in the next week or two. thanks for the interest!    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries thanks. preprint will be available soon.    
    
    
    Nice to see @lintool 's "Data-Intensive Text Processing with MapReduce" show up in my Prismatic feed - http://prsm.tc/4YCCHg  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Looking for an excellent systems-oriented Search Engines book? Check out: http://www.amazon.com/Information-Retrieval-Implementing-Evaluating-Engines/dp/0262026511 …    
    
    
    Will Twitter put the U.N. out of the disaster business? http://prsm.tc/aif9yv  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @ian_soboroff that's along the lines of what i was also going to say...    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff i always thought that "Divergence from Randomness" would make for a great band name.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @ian_soboroff @tetsuyasakai I personally like "Rank Fusion" the best. I would totally buy that album.    
    
    
    @diazf_y i ultimately decided that nothing of great significance would arise any time soon, so i punted on it.    
    
    
    @JeffD small magnitude gains can also be substantive. even tiny (e.g., tenths of a %) gains in DCG in commercial search => lots of $$.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG yes, very good point!    
    
    
    Super expensive, but could be interesting - Mining Text Data (Aggarwal & Zhai) : http://prsm.tc/m1F6R8  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Microsoft Expands Hadoop/Azure Preview http://prsm.tc/2zJUmT  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Do I Need SQL or Hadoop? A Flowchart http://prsm.tc/p7FQfs  via @prismatic    
    
    
    anyone know who won the Karen Sparck Jones award this year? thought the winner was supposed to give a keynote #ecir2012 ?    
    
    
    .@wavii is great at surfacing random facts about topics, while @prismatic finds content i'm actually interested in.    
    
    
    preprint of our #naacl2012 paper "Structured Event Retrieval over Microblog Archives" : http://bit.ly/ICIQfC     
    
    
    2 USC Students Murdered During Attempted Carjacking Near Campus « CBS Los Angeles http://cbsloc.al/I2ZdET     
    
    
    @zaxtax factual is trying to become this    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @IR_oldie that's where i'll also be headed in the not-so-distant future.    
    
    
    Watch SNL Call Out Angelenos For Their Obsession With the 10 http://curbed.cc/J6zSuZ  via @CurbedLA    
    
    
    yahoo: "refocusing our R&D on O&O properties and stopping development of … theoretical science … outside of our core" http://ow.ly/alD6J     
    
    
    SNL skit "The Californians" - http://www.hulu.com/watch/350669/saturday-night-live-the-californians … - I prefer to take the 90 into Marina del Rey, myself :)    
    
    
    oren kurland and i will be giving a half day tutorial titled "Experimental Methods for Information Retrieval" at #sigir2012    
    
    
    @julian_urbano thanks, we thought so, too. and yes, we plan to make all of the slides publicly available after the tutorial.    
    
    
    Sign up for @Prismatic right now, and get in within 24 hours http://getprismatic.com/inviteportal?ref=metzlerd …    
    
    
    @francesco1986_ we'll post the slides after the tutorial.    
    
    
    This post contains some interesting details about the Inktomi ranking function - http://prsm.tc/M5F9Dm  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @semanticpc very interesting! did you implement it yourself?    
    
    
    CIKM 2011 Call for Workshops -- http://www.cikm2011.org/callforworkshops    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr hope you're enjoying your first day!    
    
    
    @dtunkelang is there a way to report that a linkedin member is deceased? several keep appearing in my "people you may know" list.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff perks: increased awareness of exciting government processes you probably never knew about (e.g., continuing resolutions).    
    
    
    @djoerd that's exactly what i first thought. but, alas, no: https://twitter.com/iadh/status/168036055344365569 …    
    
    
    @sgouws how long will you be in LA?    
    
    
    @sgouws yeah, i'll be around the whole time. you should stop by for lunch w/ me and @congxing.    
    
    
    there are many interesting #sigir2012 tutorials, but the one you should register for is "Experimental Methods for IR": http://bit.ly/LjzNX4     
    
    
    i'm serving as a program chair for OAIR (the conference formerly known as RIAO) 2013. i look forward to some good submissions!    
    
    
    @aria42 here's a good place to start: http://www.cs.rmit.edu.au/swirl12/discussion.php …    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase i don't think so, as things are just now coming together. i'll be sure to circulate the web site + CFP when they're available    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase as an aside, the "Psychedelic Experience Open Air 2013" event does indeed sound interesting.    
    
    
    #oair2013 (formerly RIAO) web site - http://oair2013.org/home/     
    
    
    Semi-interesting popular press article about deep learning applied at scale. http://prsm.tc/wpapPU  via @prismatic    
    
    
    SIGIR 2012 Workshop on Open Source Information Retrieval http://prsm.tc/hnM0w3  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Twitter Tweaks Tweet Search -http://prsm.tc/2R6JEF via @prismatic    
    
    
    Is Data Is, or Is Data Ain’t, a Plural? http://prsm.tc/shQ37U  via @prismatic    
    
    
    One of the last papers I worked on while I was at USC/ISI: http://bit.ly/M6f3m9  (using data integration to help prevent sex trafficking).    
    
    
    @DataJunkie *had* and likely never will have again.    
    
    
    did the #sigir2012 tutorial you registered for get cancelled? then check out the "Empirical Methods for IR" tutorial: http://bit.ly/LjzNX4     
    
    
    slides for #sigir2012 tutorial "experimental methods for IR" available here: http://bit.ly/R5Glgz     
    
    
    (#sigir2012 spoiler alert) ... the conference booklet seems to reveal that Norbert Fuhr is this year's salton award winner    
    
    
    Having chaired a session in the #sigir2012 "batcave", I can say it was the single worst presentation venue I ever experienced.    
    
    
    @milesEfron I believe it was part of an underground parking garage that was fitted with portable curtains and a low quality sound system.    
    
    
    @xuexb i noticed that your tweet frequency drastically increased. no tweets == no bonus? ;)    
    
    
    @brendan642 stemming/spell-correction typically done contextually (at the word and/or char level). many possible implementations.    
    
    
    @brendan642 feel free to email me (see web site for contact info). would be happy to explain in more detail.    
    
    
    @gilelbaz i saw you at the google office last week w/ tom. was going to say hi, but didn't want to interrupt. hope you enjoyed your visit.    
    
    
    CIKM 2012 Industry Event - http://prsm.tc/lmU0BO  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Why Los Angeles Is Emerging As The Next Silicon Valley - Forbes http://onforb.es/SNW55N     
    
    
    A Brief Tour of Factual’s Machine Learning Pipeline http://prsm.tc/M5JJc5  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase You should check out "Information Retrieval: Implementing and Evaluating Search Engines" by Buettcher, Clarke, and Cormack.    
    
    
    Anecdotal science http://prsm.tc/54UXbk  via @prismatic    
    
    
    On Stanford's use of "flipped" classrooms to teach IR (and other CS courses): http://prsm.tc/wopOtU  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Did Blowing into Nintendo Cartridges Really Help? http://prsm.tc/LypIiT  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @n0v0id @HCIR_GeneG But if you're from Cuba, Iran, Sudan, or Syria then "more information will be requested."    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG great plotline -- enemies of the state infiltrate IR community, get internship at NIST w/ @ian_soboroff, take over gov't    
    
    
    @zaxtax fast coreference is an oxymoron.    
    
    
    I'm surprised how many people fail to realize this happened *last year* - Dennis Ritchie Passes Away http://prsm.tc/vBnJKG  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @peter_c_william Yeah, it almost certainly has to be the result of blind retweeting.    
    
    
    Tech Titans Buy Homes in Los Angeles http://prsm.tc/J7WEot  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @bradfordcross yeah, that was a particularly bad couple of weeks. i think that ritchie's passing was largely overshadowed by jobs' death.    
    
    
    @bradfordcross @peter_c_william reminds me of academics citing papers they've never read, and may have never existed (http://blog.codalism.com/?p=773 )    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr @tetsuyasakai sounds interesting!    
    
    
    I guess now's as good time as ever to start using Twitter...    
    
    
    space shuttle endeavor is parked about a mile from my house, between a krispy kreme and a walmart. doesn't get much more american than that.    
    
    
    IBM's Watson is (partially) powered by Indri... (see AI Magazine article -- http://bit.ly/h1AKIm)    
    
    
    #www2011 relevance and ranking track had a solid set of papers submitted this year. track acceptance rate=19% (vs. 12% overall accept rate)    
    
    
    @KushalDave depends on score distributions. 0-1 normalization and z-normalization tend to work well in practice.    
    
    
    @KushalDave here's a relevant paper: http://www.iicm.tugraz.at/thesis/cguetl_diss/literatur/Kapitel07/References/Montague_et_al._2001/p427-montague.pdf …    
    
    
    Shootings in Hollywood and on USC campus tonight. This is why I !(love) LA.    
    
    
    @bemikelive I'm surprised it took them this long to do this. It's all about tracking, err, "analytics".    
    
    
    @lintool and the jobtracker runs out of memory in 3, 2, 1...    
    
    
    Gave a talk today at UC Irvine's AI/ML seminar titled "Learning to Effectively and Efficiently Rank" (slides: http://bit.ly/d7Of9E).    
    
    
    i'm waiting for godot (aka sentence breaking, pos tagging, chunking, and parsing 140GB of text).    
    
    
    "Please Click On Our Website's Banner Ads" (The Onion) -http://www.theonion.com/articles/please-click-on-our-websites-banner-ads,30513/ …    
    
    
    @jelsas mine, too! my mandelbrot code doesnt seem to work anymore, but i found my zoomable newton's method fractal app: http://bit.ly/aDwcwR    
    
    
    UIUC is recruiting (senior) Computational Advertising faculty - http://cs.illinois.edu/csillinois/employment/CS-tenure-track-faculty-positions …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I don't think that SEO + AdSense revenue counts as a valid form of research funding.    
    
    
    @lintool i was having the same exact problem today.. my supposed stochastic matrix was not-even-close-to-stochastic    
    
    
    @bemikelive the question is as ignorant as the contestants. i'd say the country's name officially starts with U, not A.    
    
    
    If you're in LA and interested in machine learning, this talk by Yan Liu should be good - http://www.meetup.com/LA-Machine-Learning/events/95951242/?a=ea1_grp&rv=ea1 …    
    
    
    Don't forget that #www2011 papers are due at *6PM* Pacific time.    
    
    
    #www2010 relevance and ranking track only received 45 submissions, compared to 77 last year    
    
    
    #naacl2013 reviews done. lots of good ideas, but so many bad evaluations. doing IR experiments? check this out: http://bit.ly/R5Glgz     
    
    
    @blekko is a step in the right direction in terms of more expressive, powerful query languages. it also has some fun IR geek tools (/rank)    
    
    
    tracking the flu using twitter? that's so 2010: http://arxiv.org/abs/1007.4748     
    
    
    For the first time in 9 years, I'm not preparing a paper for #sigir2013. In other words, I had a very stress-free December and January.    
    
    
    @jcmayfield the tweeter's dilemma: to actually make sense or to make sure your tweet is discoverable? i obviously chose the latter.    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr yes, of course. there's writing papers, and then there's making magic.    
    
    
    @julian_urbano @HCIR_GeneG i've always wanted to try procrastinating, but never got around to it.    
    
    
    passagifiable -- the ability to split a document into passages.    
    
    
    note to self: do not accidentally click buttons in confmaster minutes before a paper deadline, especially when you are very tired    
    
    
    @hintikka sounds fascinating. i look forward to seeing the slides!    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries nothing actually happened, but i came close to accidentally withdrawing a paper    
    
    
    over the past year, the word that is most likely to co-trend with "layoffs" on Twitter is "yahoo" (i'm not joking).    
    
    
    I apparently have one of the top 1% most viewed @LinkedIn profiles for 2012. However, 1% of 200M = really not that impressive.    
    
    
    @hintikka That's probably it. And the fact that probably 75% of those 200M people have probably only logged in once and have empty profiles.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai i find it amazing some japanese tweets characterize a 5.7 magnitude as a "small tremor". your preparedness is most impressive.    
    
    
    @peter_r_bailey what a great set of tips! you should retweet these before next year's deadline.    
    
    
    I will serve as PC co-chair for @ictir2013 alongside Oren Kurland. For more details about the conference check out: http://bit.ly/ZZQVpz     
    
    
    "Data Science for Social Good" (U of Chicago) program looking for lots of ML/data mining grad students this summer - http://www.ci.uchicago.edu/datasciencefellowship/application.html …    
    
    
    ICTIR 2013 deadlines are about a month away - see http://bit.ly/X8RujK  for CfP and newly added guidelines on experimentation for papers    
    
    
    i look forward to serving as program co-chair of #wsdm2014 w/ @ChaToX    
    
    
    @DataJunkie the neon paint is probably a belated celebration of the indian Holi festival    
    
    
    a friendly reminder that the deadline for #ictir2013 full papers is April 22nd. for full details see: http://www.ictir2013.org/cfp.html     
    
    
    @DataJunkie i think about this problem often, esp. when sitting at a red light w/ 20 other cars for 5 mins, while 0 cars pass thru the green    
    
    
    this "Bing is cheating" argument is nothing more than a negative PR attack, in my opinion    
    
    
    MS has been heavily publishing about their use of toolbar data for ranking for the past 5 years. so how is this surprising?    
    
    
    @jelsas yeah, i agree with you there. they certainly could've done a better job at making it less obvious    
    
    
    The deadline for #ictir2013 papers (and tutorials) has been extended to May 1st. Posters now due May 3rd.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald @HCIR_GeneG @lintool Thanks for pointing this out, Craig, and for reporting it to Springer, Gene!    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff you should expect an angry mob of teenage girls waiting for you after work.    
    
    
    @RojaBandari congratulations! and thanks again for all the help w/ the RIPS team this summer. best of luck in the future.    
    
    
    reasons why I reject your IR paper: poor evaluation (70%), lack of novelty (10%), flawed methodology (10%), bad motivation (5%), other (5%)    
    
    
    looking for a MS or PhD student who has experience (or interest) in topic models for an internship at Google Los Angeles. DM me for details.    
    
    
    @amurphy_ email me -- you can find me on google :)    
    
    
    @cpsievert thanks for the reply -- send me an email and we can discuss more    
    
    
    today i visited @factual (www.factual.com), a LA-based startup that's working on some pretty cool things in the realm of open data...    
    
    
    trying to wrap my head around git(hub), the soon-to-be new home of ivory (ivory.cc)    
    
    
    "export LC_ALL=C" <-- incredibly useful, especially if you do a lot of sorting and don't want any weird surprises    
    
    
    @jelsas are you trying to modify indri or just run it "out of the box"?    
    
    
    @jelsas ah, that's not the most well-tested code, i don't think. do you really need to merge? most indri cmds allow multiple index locations    
    
    
    Call for Tutorials - CIKM 2011 - http://www.cikm2011.org/callfortutorials #cikm2011    
    
    
    i was amused (and impressed) to see that google's spell checker can correct "dawnuld metslur" (via phonetic similarity, i presume?)    
    
    
    @Jeffye it would be even more impressive if it worked for americans' horrible spellings of foreign (esp. chinese) names/words (eg "buydo")    
    
    
    our #sigir2011 workshop on search and data mining in social media was accepted (w/ fernando diaz, ed hovy, irwin king, and jie tang)    
    
    
    attending a talk by ibm's chris welty titled "inside the mind of watson" -- should be interesting    
    
    
    going crazy w/ horrible mturk documentation and useless error messages...    
    
    
    @natala it may take a bit more than 140 chars, but i'll try :)    
    
    
    @natala 1) soft 404s in documentation, 2) CLT errors uninformative, 3) inability to design qual tests + attach to HITS in RUI    
    
    
    @bemikelive Congratulations, Michael!    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff A certain nameless gov't agency is particularly fond of sticking everything in Excel. Agenda.xls? Huh?    
    
    
    -XX:+UseCompressedOops JVM flag rescued my mem hungry #hadoop text mining job (see http://bit.ly/f58XGa) -XX:+UseCompressedStrings also good    
    
    
    #sigir2011 Workshop on Social Web Search & Mining: Analysis of User Generated Content Under Crisis http://bit.ly/gBnEbe (#www2011 #SoME2011)    
    
    
    @sgouws 3y3 bee phollowin' u.    
    
    
    CIKM 2011 Industry Event - http://www.cikm2011.org/industryevent    
    
    
    Three #sigir2011 papers accepted (2 w/ @lintool and 1 w/ @bemikelive).    
    
    
    @diazf_y i find it much more of an honor to be the recipient of your first tweet than to have the papers accepted :) did you have any luck?    
    
    
    @iadh are there any good comprehensive (e.g., survey) papers covering the latest and greatest advances in blog-related search tasks?    
    
    
    @lintool I was semi-expecting you to announce that you were leaving for good. I was close :) What does this mean for your grants+students?    
    
    
    #LosAngeles ML & IR folks -- i'm giving a talk on ranking at the LA #MachineLearning meetup at eHarmony on 4/28 (http://bit.ly/fXmGt6)    
    
    
    @iadh exactly what i was looking for -- thanks for the pointer!    
    
    
    #sigir2011 Workshop on Social Web Search & Mining: Analysis of User Generated Content Under Crisis http://bit.ly/gBnEbe (cc: #ecir2011)    
    
    
    experimenting with #hadoop 0.22 alpha...    
    
    
    @lintool ... and then starts blinking at 100Hz?    
    
    
    Yahoo Mulls Spinoff for Hadoop Software Unit - http://on.wsj.com/g4ozXG    
    
    
    looking forward to my talk and meeting everyone at the #LosAngeles #MachineLearning meetup tomorrow (12pm @ eHarmony) http://bit.ly/fXmGt6    
    
    
    #sigir2011 Workshop on Social Web Search and Mining Under Crisis - DEADLINE EXTENSION (May 15th) + also accepting SHORT PAPERS (<= 4 pages)    
    
    
    Loose use of loose and lose makes me lose my mind.    
    
    
    @lintool isn't that just a corollary to murphy's law?    
    
    
    jack ma: 1, yhoo: -7.3%    
    
    
    fun paper w/ (@sgouws and @congxing) on Twitter vocab usage : http://bit.ly/jgmPcc (to appear at the ACL Language in Social Media Workshop)    
    
    
    friendly reminder: papers to the #sigir2011 Workshop on Social Web Search and Mining Under Crisis (http://bit.ly/gBnEbe) are due in 3 days    
    
    
    steve ballmer will speak at USC's commencement ceremony today    
    
    
    *@ian_soboroff i always thought the dot was informal, user-defined syntax. is it functionally any different than the syntax i used here?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @arjenpdevries my guess: if tweet[0] == '@' then msg only appears in timeline of mutual followers, else it appears to everyone    
    
    
    @allthingshadoop fwiw, i think it's actually "grayskull" (i've been watching way too many he-man and she-ra reruns lately)...    
    
    
    http://on.wsj.com/k01Lfe  - At LinkedIn's Valuation, Apple Would Be Worth $3 Trillion    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff will the trec microblog assessors be ex-intelligence analysts or be more demographically aligned w/ actual microblog users?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff i ask because i want to know whether or not to highly upweight mentions of bieber, or highly downweight them :)    
    
    
    sean combs - a "vocabulary mismatch" disaster (http://marquee.blogs.cnn.com/2011/05/20/sean-diddy-combs-changes-his-name-again/ …)    
    
    
    #sigir2011 paper (w/ @bemikelive + croft) "Parameterized Concept Weighting in Verbose Queries" now available at http://bit.ly/kj8ZbD    
    
    
    #sigir2011 paper (w/ wang + @lintool) "A Cascade Ranking Model for Efficient Ranked Retrieval" now available at http://bit.ly/kMWe1b    
    
    
    #sigir2011 paper (w/ @nimatwtr, @lintool, elsayed) "Pseudo Test Collections for Learning Web Search Ranking Functions" http://bit.ly/iYr7HB    
    
    
    @bemikelive glad to see that you survived the tornado?    
    
    
    @nimatwtr you just learned tech industry rule #1: never show up before 10am. the other option is to show up just in time for lunch.    
    
    
    maybe it's because i'm getting older, or lamer, but it's going to take a lot more than having an "in-house kegerator" to join your startup.    
    
    
    my outgoing email server apparently has a "bad reputation", which results in my outgoing emails being marked as spam or being bounced. fun.    
    
    
    @jelsas amen to that.    
    
    
    back from #acl2011, where we presented our short paraphrase eval paper (http://bit.ly/jsdUiy ) & our twitter vocab paper (http://bit.ly/jgmPcc )    
    
    
    #mturk paraphrase evaluation data collected for our #acl2011 paper is now available for download at http://bit.ly/iVfkr6     
    
    
    our matchmaking paper from sigir '10 was invited to a special cross-conference session at #icml2011. @diazf_y will present it on thursday    
    
    
    @nimatwtr napa (for wine), brentwood (for fresh produce), muir woods (for nature), santa cruz / monterrey / hwy 1 (for scenery), or sleep.    
    
    
    @petricek nope, i'm not attending the conference. my co-author @diazf_y will present the paper. you two should definitely chat.    
    
    
    i'll fortunately be leaving LA just in time to miss #carmageddon    
    
    
    if( attending( #sigir2011 ) && interestedIn( social media ) ) { visit( http://bit.ly/gBnEbe  ); registerFor( SWSM ); } else { RT( this ); }    
    
    
    @jelsas i may have accidentally pocket emailed you. i just got a new phone and apparently haven't mastered locking it yet. if so, sorry!    
    
    
    @nimatwtr it sounds like you chose a neighborhood with a healthy amount of "character". i just hope you're paying next to nothing in rent.    
    
    
    obligatory tweet about google+    
    
    
    the microsoft partner conference is in town this week. no wonder why there is an abundance of (car) crashes, erratic behavior, and gridlock.    
    
    
    "Unsupervised Mining of Lexical Variants from Noisy Text," EMNLP Workshop on Unsupervised Learning in NLP (w/ @sgouws): http://bit.ly/pVwIxf     
    
    
    i just realized that the @trecmicroblog runs are (in)conveniently due on the same day of the #wsdm2012 paper deadline    
    
    
    bing's y/y volume growth is impressive, but will likely saturate soon, just like google has started to. how long before y! sees y/y losses?    
    
    
    @diazf_y comscore report for june. summary stats: http://techcrunch.com/2011/07/13/binghoo-gains-search-share/ …    
    
    
    @diazf_y i'm not sure. it says it's "total explicit searches (excluding the effects of slideshows, contextual search, and Google Instant)"    
    
    
    qi lu gave an interesting keynote today at #sigir2011, despite the fact that it was heavy on "our [msft] vision" and light on "my vision"    
    
    
    honorable mention award at #sigir2011 for "Parameterized Concept Weighting in Verbose Queries" (w/ @bemikelive & Croft): http://bit.ly/kj8ZbD     
    
    
    catching up on two weeks' worth of emails...    
    
    
    @lucasjosh if you're ever in downtown LA some weekend (or evening) then drop me a line. it'd be great to meet/chat about search stuff.    
    
    
    to avoid doing actual work i created my google scholar profile: http://scholar.google.com/citations?user=bmXpOd8AAAAJ …    
    
    
    @diazf_y sorry, no. i visited scholar while logged into my google acct, clicked "my citations" and then just fiddled around a lot    
    
    
    yhoo hit a 52 week low today. ouch. upside: excellent stock option pricing for new hires    
    
    
    i hope @MercuryIns is more attentive to their own customers' needs, because they're a massive #fail when dealing with my claim against them    
    
    
    @bemikelive i find it amusing that klout thinks you're highly influential for the topic "philadelphia eagles"    
    
    
    @pbrane done! 189, 189, 189.    
    
    
    @rusillini congratulations! it was nice to meet you at sigir.    
    
    
    we're looking for a talented research programmer to join us in the USC/ISI natural language group. relocation available. contact me for info    
    
    
    @tinyFey just send me an email with your resume and any other pertinent information -- thanks!    
    
    
    @lintool @abdur does twitter even have product that does event detection? trending topics != events.    
    
    
    i used to think the limit (as t -> infinity) of unread emails in my inbox was convergent, but recent evidence refutes that hypothesis.    
    
    
    dear @KAYAK, please stop with the horrible "personalized" contextual ads about beijing travel deals. i've already gone there and returned.    
    
    
    @jerepick I suppose businessmen exhibit travel destination burstiness. However, my travel destination distribution is much more uniform :)    
    
    
    @jerepick (with respect to international travel, that is... domestic is a completely different story)    
    
    
    google's "algorithm" for demoting bad sites: if(badsites.contains(url)) { url.score -= 100; } (http://goo.gl/qVQ4o)    
    
    
    today's deadlines: #wsdm2012 papers and TREC microblog track runs.    
    
    
    just submitted our @trecmicroblog runs. i look forward to seeing what approaches other groups took. #trec2011    
    
    
    WSDM submissions flat year-over-year -- 290 for #wsdm2010, 381 for #wsdm2011, and 367 for #wsdm2012    
    
    
    @iadh Last year may have also attracted more papers from Asia. I wonder if SIGIR will see a similar trend from this year to next.    
    
    
    @jteevan The number I quoted was from the "Reviewer Instructions" email sent by the 2011 PC chairs. Prob a few papers dropped during review.    
    
    
    @web_miner i'd personally like a set of knobs that let me trade off personal relevance, network relevance, and recency (cc @twittersearch)    
    
    
    i'm thrilled to join david blei, @kevinrose, and @aplusk as an advisor to @chomp (app search startup) -- http://bit.ly/pThl8F     
    
    
    1st Southern California Workshop on Machine Learning @ UC Irvine on September 9th (free registration) -- http://bit.ly/nGeXqu     
    
    
    trying to get ahead on my reviewing obligations. AIRS done. next up: WSDM and a bunch of journal articles (TOIS, TKDE, TIST, and IRJ).    
    
    
    giving a talk on Mavuno (a scalable distributional similarity engine) at the #kdd2011 LDMTA workshop on sunday. paper: http://bit.ly/o3WsrC     
    
    
    .@JeffD mavuno isn't available yet, but will be soon. i'm looking for some folks to test the install process and run some tests earlier, tho    
    
    
    my #kdd2011 LDMTA workshop slides for "Mavuno: A Scalable and Effective Hadoop-Based Paraphrase Acquisition System" : http://bit.ly/q19kDX     
    
    
    @nimatwtr every time i feel down, i just read your tweet stream, and it makes me feel a lot better.    
    
    
    i noticed a variable number of spam bots follow me each time i tweet. i wonder if it's random or has to do w/ specific keywords. let's test.    
    
    
    seo, sem, search engines, marketing, analytics, optimization, ads, advertising, ranking, web site, services, google, yahoo, bing, first page    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff you're right. that strangely netted me 3 legit followers and just 2 spam bots. weird. maybe not the right set of topic words.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff maybe something like "where can i buy twitter and facebook followers and grow my network ?" will be more effective.    
    
    
    @diazf_y feel much shaking there?    
    
    
    @diazf_y that's clearly the only plausible explanation for this quake and the one in CO last night.    
    
    
    @BenCarterette was that your warm welcome home from Russia?    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson that's a great title for an IR book (or a SIGIR tutorial...)    
    
    
    dumb question: what's the correct usage of "toward" vs "towards"? the copy edits for a manuscript i'm preparing suggest i have no idea.    
    
    
    @jerepick they changed all of my "towards" to "toward". maybe they just wanted to save ink to lower costs.    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson Interesting! Perhaps it's a regional (NW PA) thing. I was raised to say other bizarre things like "what do you taste for?"    
    
    
    @delsweil "toward" just sounds funny to me. i guess i'm more british than i knew :)    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson Yeah. That's another one I never realized was weird until I told someone "my car needs washed".    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff unlike you, i can't even construct an s-less tweet. i look forward to your s-less SIGIR paper next year.    
    
    
    another well-executed LA machine learning meetup today. kudos to @petricek and @zaxtax    
    
    
    now that the initial google+ buzz has died down, my stream is more like a slow drip only worth checking once or twice a week, at most.    
    
    
    @XplusOne good question! i was trying to determine what types of keywords are most targeted by spambots.    
    
    
    .@davidandrzej interesting work! will definitely read the paper. (fwiw, i would strongly recommend to never use the indri "#not" operator)    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries i was responsible for L8 and L15. unfortunately, i haven't seen anyone actually use these in any papers.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries btw, if you have a particular data need, you can always ping someone in y! and they can try to get it released for you.    
    
    
    elevators should require a special "i'm unable to climb stairs" access card for all rides between floors n and n+1 (or n-1).    
    
    
    4.2 earthquake in the san fernando valley. very light shaking here in marina del rey.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG i'm guessing a small %. most are likely random junk, strange misspellings, and bizarre long queries.    
    
    
    i'm co-chairing the #ictir2011 best paper award committee. we have a strong, diverse pool of candidates to choose from.    
    
    
    not too surprised by the bartz news. she was one of the factors that caused me to leave yahoo!    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff you mean, other than government red tape?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff 10 years at NIST?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff that's a nice milestone, btw. only 40 more years until the coveted CD-534.    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson awesome. thanks for the pointer!    
    
    
    attending the southern california machine learning workshop at UC irvine    
    
    
    my socal machine learning workshop slides: http://bit.ly/q5QAN4  . asks what's more important for learning to rank - features or models?    
    
    
    it's only 10am and i already don't want to eat any more mooncake this year.    
    
    
    @lintool that was exactly my argument. no need for incremental modeling improvements when you have lots of data and strong features.    
    
    
    @jerepick yes, excellent point! if the language is expressive enough then the distinction begins to blur such that query = features + model    
    
    
    @lintool that's exactly what i thought... at least it's a step in the right direction.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @trecmicroblog did i miss something or has there been some sort of delay?    
    
    
    it's a longshot, but... does anyone in los angeles know if book royalties necessitate a business tax registration certificate? #la #dtla    
    
    
    mostly happy with our @trecmicroblog results. we kept it simple and combined a number of proven techniques w/ domain-specific adaptations.    
    
    
    @milesEfron i look forward to reading your notebook paper! i wish we had found the time to do something a bit more risky ourselves.    
    
    
    my first patent was recently granted (US 8,005,845). basic idea: "intent-adaptive machine learned query-biased summarization"    
    
    
    twitter started randomly(?) dropping posts made by my followers from my timeline. i've missed a few "important" messages as a result.    
    
    
    @web_miner yes, but when combined they gives rise to a very specific (yet broadly defined) "invention" (that yahoo now has little use for.)    
    
    
    #twitter segmentation #fail... trending topic "Ask Don" as in... "don't ASK, DON't tell".    
    
    
    http://www.businessinsider.com/yahoo-board-not-looking-for-ceo-2011-9 … ... Yahoo! Research => News Corp Research? Doesn't have quite the same ring to it.    
    
    
    i'm not a fan of facebook's redesign, but i do like their new open graph features. nice, simple way to add basic semantics to web content    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries you can add the tags to any web page. e.g., you can appify your publications page with "+Read It" buttons if you so choose    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries @diazf_y i wouldnt actually use this myself, but will gladly scrape other's "open graph" content as a rich source of evidence    
    
    
    another Twitter trending topic gem (for Los Angeles): "Tomorrow is Friday" (trending on Friday, go figure)    
    
    
    do any search toolkits support per-tag weighting? i want to have <tag wt="3">...</tag> in the text and use 3 during ranking. @TerrierTeam ?    
    
    
    @pbrane thanks! low-level custom code isn't a problem. better than the complexities of implementing new index data structures myself.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald thanks, craig. indri supports the same. the problem with that solution is variable # of tags per doc (think anchor text)    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald if terrier implemented that, then you might make a convert out of me, afterall ;)    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald unfortunately, no. weights will be arbitrary real-values in no way connected to the TF (or IDF) of the span's text.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries nope, the weights are static and computed prior to indexing.    
    
    
    do any cities have a "smart grid" of traffic signals? LA could seriously use some more sensors + intelligence to improve system-wide flow.    
    
    
    @CathyE nice -- thanks for the pointer!    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG my pet peeve: when dozens of cars end up waiting at a red light for > 3 minutes, while zero cars pass through the green light    
    
    
    @jelsas depends on how you define "open". most publishers (ACM, Elsevier) allow posting to personal web sites. WWW used to put PDFs on web    
    
    
    there's a fine line between being too busy and being utterly incompetent    
    
    
    @julian_urbano successful procrastination is an art :)    
    
    
    @diazf_y @twittersearch furthermore, [can] should not match [can't].    
    
    
    my interest in a given seminar is inversely proportional to the number of reminder emails i receive about it    
    
    
    @julian_urbano i wonder if they would accept a scanned hand-written PDF.    
    
    
    when using NER annotator w/ latest @stanfordnlp, set ner.useSUTime prop to false to avoid endless exceptions/warnings for docs w/o date tags    
    
    
    @stanfordnlp It is useful for docs w/ timestamps. BTW, not all msgs are just "logging". I got a NullPointerException @ SUTime.java:1707.    
    
    
    Mavuno is now available! Open source. Scalable (Hadoop). Modular. Supports large-scale #nlproc and text mining. Get it: http://bit.ly/nQS2dn     
    
    
    apparently exceeding github's free account "soft limit" of 300MB only becomes an issue if/when you hit 1GB, according to their tech support.    
    
    
    coffee from breakfast spilled on my shirt? check. tomato soup from lunch spilled on my shirt? check. meetings this afternoon? check.    
    
    
    kudos to @yandex for their continued outreach to the research community via (anonymized) data sharing. http://imat-relpred.yandex.ru/en     
    
    
    "A Feature-Centric View of Information Retrieval" (Springer IR Series) is now available - http://bit.ly/nsvXZO     
    
    
    CA homeowners -- did you get any specific earthquake-related inspections done (beyond the minimal ones required by state law) when buying?    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson yeah, probably will end up getting a geologist. have some concerns about liquefaction potential and/or landslides.    
    
    
    i'd be more tempted to try out iamResearcher if they didn't have such a grammatically incorrect name.    
    
    
    does #pandora serve anyone else geo-targeted ads for completely random midwestern cities that nobody's ever heard of? or is it just me?    
    
    
    @diazf_y i did spend four years in terre haute, indiana. i'm thankfully avoided picking up a taste for ICP (or PCP, for that matter.)    
    
    
    @i_am_researcher i was of course only joking. i hope to give it a try when i have a few free minutes.    
    
    
    not to be rude, but the #lucene "DefaultSimilarity" scoring function is an abomination. are users satisfied with its ranking quality?    
    
    
    if anyone's going to take down Google, it's going to be MC Hammer. http://www.cnn.com/2011/10/20/tech/web/mc-hammer-search-engine/index.html?hpt=hp_t2 …    
    
    
    @lintool google, the least "open" of all industrial research labs, is leading the charge towards openness? huh?    
    
    
    finally getting around to writing our TREC microblog track notebook paper.    
    
    
    The Yahoo Circus (Animation) http://techcrunch.com/2011/10/24/the-yahoo-circus-animation/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    i hope everyone enjoys #cikm2011. now the conference is here, i won't be sending you all spam (er, "publicity materials") anymore :)    
    
    
    sad that @congxing left us to work for google, but happy to inherit his apple 30" cinema HD display    
    
    
    metareviews should summarize the strengths/weaknesses raised by the reviewers. writing "reject based on reviews" is just phoning it in.    
    
    
    @bemikelive @doridayan smh    
    
    
    @SethGrimes Sentence boundary detection for Web docs = hard. Adding sentence boundary info to search index = expensive. Demand = little.    
    
    
    a plagiarized version of our SIGIR '10 "Learning to Efficiently Rank" paper found its way into a Materials Science journal, of all places...    
    
    
    @vitroc another researcher told us about it. i have no idea how they discovered it.    
    
    
    @julian_urbano http://www.scientific.net/AMR.268-270.1773 …    
    
    
    USC/ISI now has an (alleged) quantum computer (http://dailytrojan.com/2011/10/30/usc-receives-first-quantum-computer/ …) - time to put quantum IR theories to the test?    
    
    
    @julian_urbano didn't report yet, but will. fake authors? never thought of that. what's their agenda? citation factories?    
    
    
    @kohlschuetter thanks for the support! i'm guessing nothing will ever come of it, but it's certainly worth trying to get resolved.    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson @SebastianThrun key metrics: intelligence vs. propensity to cheat in both populations. too many unknowns to say for sure.    
    
    
    today google rolled out better support for implicitly year qualified queries, wh/ we studied in a YRL '09 tech report: http://www.isi.edu/~metzler/papers/2009-002_Metzler.pdf …    
    
    
    not a huge fan of the #ecir2012 conference management system (ConfTool)    
    
    
    our #trec2011 @trecmicroblog track notebook paper is now available at http://bit.ly/v7DUr4     
    
    
    i finally looked up how to say "wrong number" in spanish -- "número equivocado". that will come in handy.    
    
    
    coding rawcomparators for complex user-defined writable objects in hadoop is well worth the effort (and kind of fun).    
    
    
    @kunegis thanks!    
    
    
    @kohlschuetter @diazf_y regarding the "+" operator issue. google rolled out "verbatim search" today (http://insidesearch.blogspot.com/2011/11/search-using-your-terms-verbatim.html …)    
    
    
    @diazf_y i'd be interested in your findings, as well. don't know of too many IR-specific query languages, really, or user-facing studies.    
    
    
    @diazf_y google should adopt an indri-style query language. #verbatim(inquery stopword list)    
    
    
    @cherhan @julian_urbano @iadh unfortunately not at TREC. like this idea. perhaps tie w/ news feed (eg "predicting tomorrow's headlines")    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries no, you're absolutely correct. the inquery folks deserve all the credit!    
    
    
    only at USC: "... suspect approached him and stated he had a weapon (none seen) demanding complainant's lunch". strong armed lunch robbery.    
    
    
    who honestly thought it would be a good idea to have two NLP paper deadlines following peak vacation time? (NAACL-HLT: Jan 6, ACL: Jan 15).    
    
    
    upcoming conference paper deadline gauntlet: NAACL-HLT: 1/6, ACL: 1/15, ICWSM: 1/18, AAAI: 1/24, KDD: 2/10, SIGIR: 2/13.    
    
    
    @vanessa_murdock i tried in vain to find the deadline. do you know when it is?    
    
    
    @vanessa_murdock thanks!    
    
    
    #www2012 "Appification of the Web" workshop : https://sites.google.com/site/appweb2012/ …    
    
    
    you just know an email starting with "Dear Research Assistant Professor in Computer Science Donald Metzler," is going to be good...    
    
    
    @textminor @bemikelive not so much the sampling, but rather the "analysis".    
    
    
    curious to see how the ongoing yahoo saga will resolve    
    
    
    are there any good, reputable, non-sketchy local residential moving companies in los angeles that anyone can recommend? #dtla    
    
    
    @vgoklani @DataJunkie we have that data, but can't share (ToS issues). the only legit archive (AFAIK) is at the LoC (http://www.forbes.com/sites/oreillymedia/2011/06/13/the-library-of-congress-twitter-archive-one-year-later/ …)    
    
    
    solved a system of equations (3x3) by hand for the first time in over 10 years. math was more fun before i learned Matlab, Maple, and R    
    
    
    @movingpro thank you very much for the information!    
    
    
    looking forward to actually *walking* somewhere for once -- tomorrow's LA machine learning meetup is in downtown (http://www.meetup.com/LA-Machine-Learning/events/41675362/ …)    
    
    
    "new and improved" klout topics are horrible. i'm apparently influential about "email", "notebook", and "models" (the half-naked kind)    
    
    
    the ICTIR 2013 call for bids is heavily Euro-centric. perhaps the "I" should be replaced with an "E".    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries none of the above :) although not explicitly stated, it appears as though non-European bids won't be considered.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries specifically "The location should be easily accessible for people attending from across Europe and elsewhere."    
    
    
    @BenCarterette the *BCS* IRSG mailing list (haven't seen it on SIG-IRlist yet).    
    
    
    @cherhan I've compiled a reading list that should get you started: https://bitly.com/bundles/metzlerd/2 …. Let me know if you have any additional questions!    
    
    
    @cherhan also, sorry for the slow response!    
    
    
    Using Markov Random Fields for Information Retrieval Reading List - https://bitly.com/bundles/metzlerd/2 …    
    
    
    @DataJunkie If you haven't read this paper, then I highly recommend it: http://www.soi.city.ac.uk/~ser/idfpapers/Robertson_idf_JDoc.pdf …    
    
    
    a 10 page paper in ACM format turns into a 16 page paper in ACL/NAACL format. yikes.    
    
    
    @cegme i couldn't agree more. over half of the things they claim are "breaking news" are anything but.    
    
    
    despite the fact i only tweet about geek-laden topics, twitter insists on suggesting i follow chris brown, snoop dogg, and trey songz    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff that strategy seems to have moved me from the space of NBA players to R&B singers. it'll be interesting to see what's next.    
    
    
    @lintool is this subtle foreshadowing?    
    
    
    "who to follow" #fail continues. after nba players and r&b singers, i now get actors (sheen, hill) and something called "tap pet hotel"    
    
    
    @DataJunkie i'm not sure if this is bad matching, bad CF, bad personalization, incognito "promoted" suggestions, or something else entirely.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG i hadn't thought of that. uh oh.    
    
    
    amusing excerpt from the "Hosting SIGIR" web page: "SIGIR has no plans to include Antarctica in the [geographical] rotation."    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl for models w/ few params, coordinate ascent works amazingly well: http://www.cs.umass.edu/~mccallum/papers/direct-metzler05.pdf …    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl What a small world, indeed! You find yourself in excellent company. They are both awesome, top-notch engineers. Tell them hi.    
    
    
    i no longer get carded when buying alcohol, but still manage to get "can i see your student ID?" at campus eateries.    
    
    
    @iadh i totally agree. it's horrible. i've heard the same feedback from several other people, too.    
    
    
    #naacl reviewing load: 1 paper.    
    
    
    @JeffD money > relevance    
    
    
    just about any semi-interesting word i include in my tweet attracts spammers. asbestos.    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson more likely than not, some sort of spambot.    
    
    
    sorry @cnnbrk, you've distracted me with far too many non-breaking news events. i'm unfollowing you and removing you from my phone.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl if you want to see George's face turn red, and his blood begin to boil, talk to him about Pig bugs/errors/documentation    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG i went through my tweet history a few days ago hoping to answer you, but couldn't seem to find anything. i'll look again now.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG are you talking about these? https://twitter.com/?iid=am-70781558913269219505079903&nid=4+sender&uid=17773969&utm_content=profile#!/metzlerd/status/113277861586153472 … https://twitter.com/?iid=am-70781558913269219505079903&nid=4+sender&uid=17773969&utm_content=profile#!/jerepick/status/113360063879581696 …    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl it sounds like you are well on your way (if not already there) to having Pig war stories of your own :)    
    
    
    negative okapi idfs + max_score query optimization = fail    
    
    
    wow, the LA office of finance tax and permit division is so horribly incompetent. makes me want to flee LA even more.    
    
    
    i tend to overuse the word "very". is there a psycholinguistic theory/explanation/name for this very annoying habit?    
    
    
    @lintool very interesting! then perhaps it's something i subconsciously picked up from my wife and/or chinese colleagues    
    
    
    @DataJunkie thanks for the free advertising!    
    
    
    @sgouws very cool! it even correctly detected my horribly scripted \xi    
    
    
    udacity using search engines as CS101 is a brilliant marketing ploy. to actually learn about search, read an information retrieval book.    
    
    
    just deleted my @klout account. it's scoring was seemingly arbitrary, it's topics were horrible, and the perks were lame.    
    
    
    thanks to @lintool for pointing out gh-pages to me. handy way to host web sites associated w/ github projects    
    
    
    in about a month, i'll once again "bleed purple".    
    
    
    @fabreetseo Yeah, I'm flip-flopping between acadmia and industry. Perhaps I am better suited as a politician :)    
    
    
    hey @TWCable_LA -- if you wake me up one more time on the weekend, or call me during dinner again, this new customer will be an ex-customer.    
    
    
    "The Future of IR" paper selections from the upcoming SWIRL workshop: http://www.cs.rmit.edu.au/swirl12/discussion.php …    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald "The position is available as part of the SMART project" - is the name in homage to Cornell's SMART system?    
    
    
    paper w/ @bemikelive (http://bit.ly/zXpB6r ) received the best search paper "runner-up" award at #wsdm2012    
    
    
    contrary to popular belief, information retrieval is, in fact, more than just vector space models, TF.IDF, and PageRank    
    
    
    @aria42 that has yet to make its way into any of the naive characterizations of the field that i've heard    
    
    
    was surprised (and somewhat embarrassed) to find one of my tweets featured in the keynote by @hmason at #wsdm2012    
    
    
    does anyone know of any studies or articles on (reverse) age discrimination in academia?    
    
    
    @aria42 i finally gave into your relentless PR campaign and signed up for prismatic.    
    
    
    what are some creative things that one can do with 480 unused business cards?    
    
    
    @sgouws i also highly recommend 30 yo tawny porto at 30.    
    
    
    tried out @prismatic today and was pleasantly surprised to find so many relevant story recommendations    
    
    
    Google buys what’s left of defunct search startup Cuil http://venturebeat.com/2012/02/20/google-buys-cuil-patents/ …  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @julian_urbano NTCIREVAL - http://research.nii.ac.jp/ntcir/tools/ntcireval-en.html …. ERR not included in trec_eval, last time i checked (/cc @ian_soboroff)    
    
    
    attending Google LA's inaugural Speaker Series' talk by @theamitsinghal on  Monday. should be interesting.    
    
    
    facebook insists on recommending that I friend someone who sadly passed away recently. i guess death is hard to algorithmically model.    
    
    
    my recent work w/ @lintool, @nimapp, et al. has embraced this. paper experiments = Ivory unit tests http://arstechnica.com/science/news/2012/02/science-code-should-be-open-source-according-to-editorial.ars …  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @lintool my vacation is still young! :)    
    
    
    thanks for the follow @TRECWithUs, but I don't TREC like *that*    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl I'll actually be in the Bay Area March 5--16. It would be great to meet and also catch up w/ George and Lance.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG i'll have limited availability during the days. if you, @ChrisDiehl, + others want to get together some evening that'd be great    
    
    
    1) find cool data set 2) compute elementary statistics 3) post tag cloud or map viz to your blog 4) declare yourself a "data scientist"    
    
    
    @elunca @HCIR_GeneG @ChrisDiehl any day after 6pm that week works for me. mt view (or anywhere on light rail would be most convenient)    
    
    
    @zaxtax i'll be in the bay area for the next couple of weeks, too. let me know if you find some folks who want to get together    
    
    
    Tomorrow's my first day back at Yahoo. I sure picked an interesting time to rejoin.    
    
    
    worst. timing. ever.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @elunca sounds good. what day next week would work best for you guys? any day except friday is ok with me    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @elunca ok, tuesday it is, then! i'm impartial. do either of you have any preferences?    
    
    
    @JeffD thanks for the free advertisement, Jeff!    
    
    
    @stanfordnlp i strategically managed to open source mavuno before i left, so i plan to continue maintaining/developing it.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG pretty easy. the quality would depend on the NLP stack's "compatibility" with ur data. do u have newswire? web? something else?    
    
    
    like the author of this article, i was also pleasantly surprised by the number of tech startups in LA http://www.forbes.com/sites/tarabrown/2012/03/06/why-los-angeles-will-outpace-silicon-valley-as-the-tech-startup-capital/ …  via @prismatic    
    
    
    How Twitter is doing its part to democratize big data http://gigaom.com/cloud/how-twitter-is-doing-its-part-to-democratize-big-data/ …  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @zaxtax @ogrisel ditto. it was nice bumping into you guys. hope you enjoyed the conference.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG it currently doesn't perform any text cleansing. garbage chars would throw the NLP tools off. lines breaks are less problematic.    
    
    
    i've relocated my web site to http://bit.ly/wuiejt  (hint: you can find my latest CV there)    
    
    
    @sodaontheside from the web interface you can click "open" and then "details" to get the URL of a specific tweet    
    
    
    @faultlinebrew your web site is borked.    
    
    
    @faultlinebrew no problem. luckily, that won't stop me from stopping by tonight :)    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @elunca hey guys, i woke up with a bad fever this morning, so i'm going to have to postpone. if i'm better, thu would work    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @elunca thanks, guys. i'll let you know. i've done the warm whiskey home remedy several times before, and it really does work!    
    
    
    when pitching your startup, please try harder than "our co-founders are ex-Googlers".    
    
    
    @techmilind it's not every day you learn the identity of those pesky blind reviewers ;) thanks for the mavuno mention!    
    
    
    Nice intro article on how search engines rewrite your queries http://prsm.tc/251p5X  via @prismatic    
    
    
    our (long) paper titled "Structured Event Retrieval over Microblog Archives" was accepted at NAACL-HLT    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG nope. much more interesting than that :) we retrieve structured representations of events in response to ad hoc search queries    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG technically, it can be as few as 1, but realistically you want enough to generate a good summary of the event    
    
    
    @stuartrobinson of course. but since this is an academic paper you have to make it sound overly fancy / general :)    
    
    
    @francesco1986_ yep. event query => burst detection => temporal query expansion => tweet retrieval => generate "structured" results    
    
    
    @francesco1986_ @PFCdgayo i'll make a preprint available in the next week or two. thanks for the interest!    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries thanks. preprint will be available soon.    
    
    
    Nice to see @lintool 's "Data-Intensive Text Processing with MapReduce" show up in my Prismatic feed - http://prsm.tc/4YCCHg  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Looking for an excellent systems-oriented Search Engines book? Check out: http://www.amazon.com/Information-Retrieval-Implementing-Evaluating-Engines/dp/0262026511 …    
    
    
    Will Twitter put the U.N. out of the disaster business? http://prsm.tc/aif9yv  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @ian_soboroff that's along the lines of what i was also going to say...    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff i always thought that "Divergence from Randomness" would make for a great band name.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @ian_soboroff @tetsuyasakai I personally like "Rank Fusion" the best. I would totally buy that album.    
    
    
    @diazf_y i ultimately decided that nothing of great significance would arise any time soon, so i punted on it.    
    
    
    @JeffD small magnitude gains can also be substantive. even tiny (e.g., tenths of a %) gains in DCG in commercial search => lots of $$.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG yes, very good point!    
    
    
    Super expensive, but could be interesting - Mining Text Data (Aggarwal & Zhai) : http://prsm.tc/m1F6R8  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Microsoft Expands Hadoop/Azure Preview http://prsm.tc/2zJUmT  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Do I Need SQL or Hadoop? A Flowchart http://prsm.tc/p7FQfs  via @prismatic    
    
    
    anyone know who won the Karen Sparck Jones award this year? thought the winner was supposed to give a keynote #ecir2012 ?    
    
    
    .@wavii is great at surfacing random facts about topics, while @prismatic finds content i'm actually interested in.    
    
    
    preprint of our #naacl2012 paper "Structured Event Retrieval over Microblog Archives" : http://bit.ly/ICIQfC     
    
    
    2 USC Students Murdered During Attempted Carjacking Near Campus « CBS Los Angeles http://cbsloc.al/I2ZdET     
    
    
    @zaxtax factual is trying to become this    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @IR_oldie that's where i'll also be headed in the not-so-distant future.    
    
    
    Watch SNL Call Out Angelenos For Their Obsession With the 10 http://curbed.cc/J6zSuZ  via @CurbedLA    
    
    
    yahoo: "refocusing our R&D on O&O properties and stopping development of … theoretical science … outside of our core" http://ow.ly/alD6J     
    
    
    SNL skit "The Californians" - http://www.hulu.com/watch/350669/saturday-night-live-the-californians … - I prefer to take the 90 into Marina del Rey, myself :)    
    
    
    oren kurland and i will be giving a half day tutorial titled "Experimental Methods for Information Retrieval" at #sigir2012    
    
    
    @julian_urbano thanks, we thought so, too. and yes, we plan to make all of the slides publicly available after the tutorial.    
    
    
    Sign up for @Prismatic right now, and get in within 24 hours http://getprismatic.com/inviteportal?ref=metzlerd …    
    
    
    @francesco1986_ we'll post the slides after the tutorial.    
    
    
    This post contains some interesting details about the Inktomi ranking function - http://prsm.tc/M5F9Dm  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @semanticpc very interesting! did you implement it yourself?    
    
    
    CIKM 2011 Call for Workshops -- http://www.cikm2011.org/callforworkshops    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr hope you're enjoying your first day!    
    
    
    @dtunkelang is there a way to report that a linkedin member is deceased? several keep appearing in my "people you may know" list.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff perks: increased awareness of exciting government processes you probably never knew about (e.g., continuing resolutions).    
    
    
    @djoerd that's exactly what i first thought. but, alas, no: https://twitter.com/iadh/status/168036055344365569 …    
    
    
    @sgouws how long will you be in LA?    
    
    
    @sgouws yeah, i'll be around the whole time. you should stop by for lunch w/ me and @congxing.    
    
    
    there are many interesting #sigir2012 tutorials, but the one you should register for is "Experimental Methods for IR": http://bit.ly/LjzNX4     
    
    
    i'm serving as a program chair for OAIR (the conference formerly known as RIAO) 2013. i look forward to some good submissions!    
    
    
    @aria42 here's a good place to start: http://www.cs.rmit.edu.au/swirl12/discussion.php …    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase i don't think so, as things are just now coming together. i'll be sure to circulate the web site + CFP when they're available    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase as an aside, the "Psychedelic Experience Open Air 2013" event does indeed sound interesting.    
    
    
    #oair2013 (formerly RIAO) web site - http://oair2013.org/home/     
    
    
    Semi-interesting popular press article about deep learning applied at scale. http://prsm.tc/wpapPU  via @prismatic    
    
    
    SIGIR 2012 Workshop on Open Source Information Retrieval http://prsm.tc/hnM0w3  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Twitter Tweaks Tweet Search -http://prsm.tc/2R6JEF via @prismatic    
    
    
    Is Data Is, or Is Data Ain’t, a Plural? http://prsm.tc/shQ37U  via @prismatic    
    
    
    One of the last papers I worked on while I was at USC/ISI: http://bit.ly/M6f3m9  (using data integration to help prevent sex trafficking).    
    
    
    @DataJunkie *had* and likely never will have again.    
    
    
    did the #sigir2012 tutorial you registered for get cancelled? then check out the "Empirical Methods for IR" tutorial: http://bit.ly/LjzNX4     
    
    
    slides for #sigir2012 tutorial "experimental methods for IR" available here: http://bit.ly/R5Glgz     
    
    
    (#sigir2012 spoiler alert) ... the conference booklet seems to reveal that Norbert Fuhr is this year's salton award winner    
    
    
    Having chaired a session in the #sigir2012 "batcave", I can say it was the single worst presentation venue I ever experienced.    
    
    
    @milesEfron I believe it was part of an underground parking garage that was fitted with portable curtains and a low quality sound system.    
    
    
    @xuexb i noticed that your tweet frequency drastically increased. no tweets == no bonus? ;)    
    
    
    @brendan642 stemming/spell-correction typically done contextually (at the word and/or char level). many possible implementations.    
    
    
    @brendan642 feel free to email me (see web site for contact info). would be happy to explain in more detail.    
    
    
    @gilelbaz i saw you at the google office last week w/ tom. was going to say hi, but didn't want to interrupt. hope you enjoyed your visit.    
    
    
    CIKM 2012 Industry Event - http://prsm.tc/lmU0BO  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Why Los Angeles Is Emerging As The Next Silicon Valley - Forbes http://onforb.es/SNW55N     
    
    
    A Brief Tour of Factual’s Machine Learning Pipeline http://prsm.tc/M5JJc5  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase You should check out "Information Retrieval: Implementing and Evaluating Search Engines" by Buettcher, Clarke, and Cormack.    
    
    
    Anecdotal science http://prsm.tc/54UXbk  via @prismatic    
    
    
    On Stanford's use of "flipped" classrooms to teach IR (and other CS courses): http://prsm.tc/wopOtU  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Did Blowing into Nintendo Cartridges Really Help? http://prsm.tc/LypIiT  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @n0v0id @HCIR_GeneG But if you're from Cuba, Iran, Sudan, or Syria then "more information will be requested."    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG great plotline -- enemies of the state infiltrate IR community, get internship at NIST w/ @ian_soboroff, take over gov't    
    
    
    @zaxtax fast coreference is an oxymoron.    
    
    
    I'm surprised how many people fail to realize this happened *last year* - Dennis Ritchie Passes Away http://prsm.tc/vBnJKG  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @peter_c_william Yeah, it almost certainly has to be the result of blind retweeting.    
    
    
    Tech Titans Buy Homes in Los Angeles http://prsm.tc/J7WEot  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @bradfordcross yeah, that was a particularly bad couple of weeks. i think that ritchie's passing was largely overshadowed by jobs' death.    
    
    
    @bradfordcross @peter_c_william reminds me of academics citing papers they've never read, and may have never existed (http://blog.codalism.com/?p=773 )    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr @tetsuyasakai sounds interesting!    
    
    
    I guess now's as good time as ever to start using Twitter...    
    
    
    space shuttle endeavor is parked about a mile from my house, between a krispy kreme and a walmart. doesn't get much more american than that.    
    
    
    IBM's Watson is (partially) powered by Indri... (see AI Magazine article -- http://bit.ly/h1AKIm)    
    
    
    #www2011 relevance and ranking track had a solid set of papers submitted this year. track acceptance rate=19% (vs. 12% overall accept rate)    
    
    
    @KushalDave depends on score distributions. 0-1 normalization and z-normalization tend to work well in practice.    
    
    
    @KushalDave here's a relevant paper: http://www.iicm.tugraz.at/thesis/cguetl_diss/literatur/Kapitel07/References/Montague_et_al._2001/p427-montague.pdf …    
    
    
    Shootings in Hollywood and on USC campus tonight. This is why I !(love) LA.    
    
    
    @bemikelive I'm surprised it took them this long to do this. It's all about tracking, err, "analytics".    
    
    
    @lintool and the jobtracker runs out of memory in 3, 2, 1...    
    
    
    Gave a talk today at UC Irvine's AI/ML seminar titled "Learning to Effectively and Efficiently Rank" (slides: http://bit.ly/d7Of9E).    
    
    
    i'm waiting for godot (aka sentence breaking, pos tagging, chunking, and parsing 140GB of text).    
    
    
    "Please Click On Our Website's Banner Ads" (The Onion) -http://www.theonion.com/articles/please-click-on-our-websites-banner-ads,30513/ …    
    
    
    @jelsas mine, too! my mandelbrot code doesnt seem to work anymore, but i found my zoomable newton's method fractal app: http://bit.ly/aDwcwR    
    
    
    UIUC is recruiting (senior) Computational Advertising faculty - http://cs.illinois.edu/csillinois/employment/CS-tenure-track-faculty-positions …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I don't think that SEO + AdSense revenue counts as a valid form of research funding.    
    
    
    @lintool i was having the same exact problem today.. my supposed stochastic matrix was not-even-close-to-stochastic    
    
    
    @bemikelive the question is as ignorant as the contestants. i'd say the country's name officially starts with U, not A.    
    
    
    If you're in LA and interested in machine learning, this talk by Yan Liu should be good - http://www.meetup.com/LA-Machine-Learning/events/95951242/?a=ea1_grp&rv=ea1 …    
    
    
    Don't forget that #www2011 papers are due at *6PM* Pacific time.    
    
    
    #www2010 relevance and ranking track only received 45 submissions, compared to 77 last year    
    
    
    #naacl2013 reviews done. lots of good ideas, but so many bad evaluations. doing IR experiments? check this out: http://bit.ly/R5Glgz     
    
    
    @blekko is a step in the right direction in terms of more expressive, powerful query languages. it also has some fun IR geek tools (/rank)    
    
    
    tracking the flu using twitter? that's so 2010: http://arxiv.org/abs/1007.4748     
    
    
    For the first time in 9 years, I'm not preparing a paper for #sigir2013. In other words, I had a very stress-free December and January.    
    
    
    @jcmayfield the tweeter's dilemma: to actually make sense or to make sure your tweet is discoverable? i obviously chose the latter.    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr yes, of course. there's writing papers, and then there's making magic.    
    
    
    @julian_urbano @HCIR_GeneG i've always wanted to try procrastinating, but never got around to it.    
    
    
    passagifiable -- the ability to split a document into passages.    
    
    
    note to self: do not accidentally click buttons in confmaster minutes before a paper deadline, especially when you are very tired    
    
    
    @hintikka sounds fascinating. i look forward to seeing the slides!    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries nothing actually happened, but i came close to accidentally withdrawing a paper    
    
    
    over the past year, the word that is most likely to co-trend with "layoffs" on Twitter is "yahoo" (i'm not joking).    
    
    
    I apparently have one of the top 1% most viewed @LinkedIn profiles for 2012. However, 1% of 200M = really not that impressive.    
    
    
    @hintikka That's probably it. And the fact that probably 75% of those 200M people have probably only logged in once and have empty profiles.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai i find it amazing some japanese tweets characterize a 5.7 magnitude as a "small tremor". your preparedness is most impressive.    
    
    
    @peter_r_bailey what a great set of tips! you should retweet these before next year's deadline.    
    
    
    I will serve as PC co-chair for @ictir2013 alongside Oren Kurland. For more details about the conference check out: http://bit.ly/ZZQVpz     
    
    
    "Data Science for Social Good" (U of Chicago) program looking for lots of ML/data mining grad students this summer - http://www.ci.uchicago.edu/datasciencefellowship/application.html …    
    
    
    ICTIR 2013 deadlines are about a month away - see http://bit.ly/X8RujK  for CfP and newly added guidelines on experimentation for papers    
    
    
    i look forward to serving as program co-chair of #wsdm2014 w/ @ChaToX    
    
    
    @DataJunkie the neon paint is probably a belated celebration of the indian Holi festival    
    
    
    a friendly reminder that the deadline for #ictir2013 full papers is April 22nd. for full details see: http://www.ictir2013.org/cfp.html     
    
    
    @DataJunkie i think about this problem often, esp. when sitting at a red light w/ 20 other cars for 5 mins, while 0 cars pass thru the green    
    
    
    this "Bing is cheating" argument is nothing more than a negative PR attack, in my opinion    
    
    
    MS has been heavily publishing about their use of toolbar data for ranking for the past 5 years. so how is this surprising?    
    
    
    @jelsas yeah, i agree with you there. they certainly could've done a better job at making it less obvious    
    
    
    The deadline for #ictir2013 papers (and tutorials) has been extended to May 1st. Posters now due May 3rd.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald @HCIR_GeneG @lintool Thanks for pointing this out, Craig, and for reporting it to Springer, Gene!    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff you should expect an angry mob of teenage girls waiting for you after work.    
    
    
    @RojaBandari congratulations! and thanks again for all the help w/ the RIPS team this summer. best of luck in the future.    
    
    
    reasons why I reject your IR paper: poor evaluation (70%), lack of novelty (10%), flawed methodology (10%), bad motivation (5%), other (5%)    
    
    
    looking for a MS or PhD student who has experience (or interest) in topic models for an internship at Google Los Angeles. DM me for details.    
    
    
    @amurphy_ email me -- you can find me on google :)    
    
    
    @cpsievert thanks for the reply -- send me an email and we can discuss more    
    
    
    today i visited @factual (www.factual.com), a LA-based startup that's working on some pretty cool things in the realm of open data...    
    
    
    trying to wrap my head around git(hub), the soon-to-be new home of ivory (ivory.cc)    
    
    
    "export LC_ALL=C" <-- incredibly useful, especially if you do a lot of sorting and don't want any weird surprises    
    
    
    @jelsas are you trying to modify indri or just run it "out of the box"?    
    
    
    @jelsas ah, that's not the most well-tested code, i don't think. do you really need to merge? most indri cmds allow multiple index locations    
    
    
    Call for Tutorials - CIKM 2011 - http://www.cikm2011.org/callfortutorials #cikm2011    
    
    
    i was amused (and impressed) to see that google's spell checker can correct "dawnuld metslur" (via phonetic similarity, i presume?)    
    
    
    @Jeffye it would be even more impressive if it worked for americans' horrible spellings of foreign (esp. chinese) names/words (eg "buydo")    
    
    
    our #sigir2011 workshop on search and data mining in social media was accepted (w/ fernando diaz, ed hovy, irwin king, and jie tang)    
    
    
    attending a talk by ibm's chris welty titled "inside the mind of watson" -- should be interesting    
    
    
    going crazy w/ horrible mturk documentation and useless error messages...    
    
    
    @natala it may take a bit more than 140 chars, but i'll try :)    
    
    
    @natala 1) soft 404s in documentation, 2) CLT errors uninformative, 3) inability to design qual tests + attach to HITS in RUI    
    
    
    @bemikelive Congratulations, Michael!    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff A certain nameless gov't agency is particularly fond of sticking everything in Excel. Agenda.xls? Huh?    
    
    
    -XX:+UseCompressedOops JVM flag rescued my mem hungry #hadoop text mining job (see http://bit.ly/f58XGa) -XX:+UseCompressedStrings also good    
    
    
    #sigir2011 Workshop on Social Web Search & Mining: Analysis of User Generated Content Under Crisis http://bit.ly/gBnEbe (#www2011 #SoME2011)    
    
    
    @sgouws 3y3 bee phollowin' u.    
    
    
    CIKM 2011 Industry Event - http://www.cikm2011.org/industryevent    
    
    
    Three #sigir2011 papers accepted (2 w/ @lintool and 1 w/ @bemikelive).    
    
    
    @diazf_y i find it much more of an honor to be the recipient of your first tweet than to have the papers accepted :) did you have any luck?    
    
    
    @iadh are there any good comprehensive (e.g., survey) papers covering the latest and greatest advances in blog-related search tasks?    
    
    
    @lintool I was semi-expecting you to announce that you were leaving for good. I was close :) What does this mean for your grants+students?    
    
    
    #LosAngeles ML & IR folks -- i'm giving a talk on ranking at the LA #MachineLearning meetup at eHarmony on 4/28 (http://bit.ly/fXmGt6)    
    
    
    @iadh exactly what i was looking for -- thanks for the pointer!    
    
    
    #sigir2011 Workshop on Social Web Search & Mining: Analysis of User Generated Content Under Crisis http://bit.ly/gBnEbe (cc: #ecir2011)    
    
    
    experimenting with #hadoop 0.22 alpha...    
    
    
    @lintool ... and then starts blinking at 100Hz?    
    
    
    Yahoo Mulls Spinoff for Hadoop Software Unit - http://on.wsj.com/g4ozXG    
    
    
    looking forward to my talk and meeting everyone at the #LosAngeles #MachineLearning meetup tomorrow (12pm @ eHarmony) http://bit.ly/fXmGt6    
    
    
    #sigir2011 Workshop on Social Web Search and Mining Under Crisis - DEADLINE EXTENSION (May 15th) + also accepting SHORT PAPERS (<= 4 pages)    
    
    
    Loose use of loose and lose makes me lose my mind.    
    
    
    @lintool isn't that just a corollary to murphy's law?    
    
    
    jack ma: 1, yhoo: -7.3%    
    
    
    fun paper w/ (@sgouws and @congxing) on Twitter vocab usage : http://bit.ly/jgmPcc (to appear at the ACL Language in Social Media Workshop)    
    
    
    friendly reminder: papers to the #sigir2011 Workshop on Social Web Search and Mining Under Crisis (http://bit.ly/gBnEbe) are due in 3 days    
    
    
    steve ballmer will speak at USC's commencement ceremony today    
    
    
    *@ian_soboroff i always thought the dot was informal, user-defined syntax. is it functionally any different than the syntax i used here?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @arjenpdevries my guess: if tweet[0] == '@' then msg only appears in timeline of mutual followers, else it appears to everyone    
    
    
    @allthingshadoop fwiw, i think it's actually "grayskull" (i've been watching way too many he-man and she-ra reruns lately)...    
    
    
    http://on.wsj.com/k01Lfe  - At LinkedIn's Valuation, Apple Would Be Worth $3 Trillion    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff will the trec microblog assessors be ex-intelligence analysts or be more demographically aligned w/ actual microblog users?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff i ask because i want to know whether or not to highly upweight mentions of bieber, or highly downweight them :)    
    
    
    sean combs - a "vocabulary mismatch" disaster (http://marquee.blogs.cnn.com/2011/05/20/sean-diddy-combs-changes-his-name-again/ …)    
    
    
    #sigir2011 paper (w/ @bemikelive + croft) "Parameterized Concept Weighting in Verbose Queries" now available at http://bit.ly/kj8ZbD    
    
    
    #sigir2011 paper (w/ wang + @lintool) "A Cascade Ranking Model for Efficient Ranked Retrieval" now available at http://bit.ly/kMWe1b    
    
    
    #sigir2011 paper (w/ @nimatwtr, @lintool, elsayed) "Pseudo Test Collections for Learning Web Search Ranking Functions" http://bit.ly/iYr7HB    
    
    
    @bemikelive glad to see that you survived the tornado?    
    
    
    @nimatwtr you just learned tech industry rule #1: never show up before 10am. the other option is to show up just in time for lunch.    
    
    
    maybe it's because i'm getting older, or lamer, but it's going to take a lot more than having an "in-house kegerator" to join your startup.    
    
    
    my outgoing email server apparently has a "bad reputation", which results in my outgoing emails being marked as spam or being bounced. fun.    
    
    
    @jelsas amen to that.    
    
    
    back from #acl2011, where we presented our short paraphrase eval paper (http://bit.ly/jsdUiy ) & our twitter vocab paper (http://bit.ly/jgmPcc )    
    
    
    #mturk paraphrase evaluation data collected for our #acl2011 paper is now available for download at http://bit.ly/iVfkr6     
    
    
    our matchmaking paper from sigir '10 was invited to a special cross-conference session at #icml2011. @diazf_y will present it on thursday    
    
    
    @nimatwtr napa (for wine), brentwood (for fresh produce), muir woods (for nature), santa cruz / monterrey / hwy 1 (for scenery), or sleep.    
    
    
    @petricek nope, i'm not attending the conference. my co-author @diazf_y will present the paper. you two should definitely chat.    
    
    
    i'll fortunately be leaving LA just in time to miss #carmageddon    
    
    
    if( attending( #sigir2011 ) && interestedIn( social media ) ) { visit( http://bit.ly/gBnEbe  ); registerFor( SWSM ); } else { RT( this ); }    
    
    
    @jelsas i may have accidentally pocket emailed you. i just got a new phone and apparently haven't mastered locking it yet. if so, sorry!    
    
    
    @nimatwtr it sounds like you chose a neighborhood with a healthy amount of "character". i just hope you're paying next to nothing in rent.    
    
    
    obligatory tweet about google+    
    
    
    the microsoft partner conference is in town this week. no wonder why there is an abundance of (car) crashes, erratic behavior, and gridlock.    
    
    
    "Unsupervised Mining of Lexical Variants from Noisy Text," EMNLP Workshop on Unsupervised Learning in NLP (w/ @sgouws): http://bit.ly/pVwIxf     
    
    
    i just realized that the @trecmicroblog runs are (in)conveniently due on the same day of the #wsdm2012 paper deadline    
    
    
    bing's y/y volume growth is impressive, but will likely saturate soon, just like google has started to. how long before y! sees y/y losses?    
    
    
    @diazf_y comscore report for june. summary stats: http://techcrunch.com/2011/07/13/binghoo-gains-search-share/ …    
    
    
    @diazf_y i'm not sure. it says it's "total explicit searches (excluding the effects of slideshows, contextual search, and Google Instant)"    
    
    
    qi lu gave an interesting keynote today at #sigir2011, despite the fact that it was heavy on "our [msft] vision" and light on "my vision"    
    
    
    honorable mention award at #sigir2011 for "Parameterized Concept Weighting in Verbose Queries" (w/ @bemikelive & Croft): http://bit.ly/kj8ZbD     
    
    
    catching up on two weeks' worth of emails...    
    
    
    @lucasjosh if you're ever in downtown LA some weekend (or evening) then drop me a line. it'd be great to meet/chat about search stuff.    
    
    
    to avoid doing actual work i created my google scholar profile: http://scholar.google.com/citations?user=bmXpOd8AAAAJ …    
    
    
    @diazf_y sorry, no. i visited scholar while logged into my google acct, clicked "my citations" and then just fiddled around a lot    
    
    
    yhoo hit a 52 week low today. ouch. upside: excellent stock option pricing for new hires    
    
    
    i hope @MercuryIns is more attentive to their own customers' needs, because they're a massive #fail when dealing with my claim against them    
    
    
    @bemikelive i find it amusing that klout thinks you're highly influential for the topic "philadelphia eagles"    
    
    
    @pbrane done! 189, 189, 189.    
    
    
    @rusillini congratulations! it was nice to meet you at sigir.    
    
    
    we're looking for a talented research programmer to join us in the USC/ISI natural language group. relocation available. contact me for info    
    
    
    