@TweeteRR Thank you :-)    
    
    
    Great news! Elsevier withdraws support for the Research Works Act: http://www.elsevier.com/wps/find/intro.cws_home/newmessagerwa …    
    
    
    @LiamPomfret @kayirowling Though all data is open under a Creative Commons license: http://dev.mendeley.com  :-)    
    
    
    @subcide @mrgunn @openscience @f1000research Indeed a  two million grant for semantic annotations. Wish it was 80 million :-)    
    
    
    Best endorsement ever! :-) RT @HeyItsDaijoubu: @TrevorDikes Mendeley is the bomb for academic gangsters looking to blow it up all raw like    
    
    
    Great fun yesterday at Oxford U panel on the Future of Academic Publishing with Tim Gowers, @CameronNeylon, and others pic.twitter.com/RCxuYjI3    
    
    
    @neuromusic very sorry! maybe @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @pilarcubas Sorry about that! That's not supposed to happen. Can you let @mendeleysupport more, so we can investigate? Thanks!    
    
    
    Mendeley is now available in @hojoki! Retweet this to win one of 10 t-shirts with the awesome Hojoki-Mendeley robot: http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-features/mendeley-now-available-in-hojoki/ …    
    
    
    @subcide @hojoki I want one, too!    
    
    
    Mendeley friends: Please vote for us at the People's Choice Award of the London Web Summit! http://www.websummit.net/nominee/vote/     
    
    
    @swiftj Your wish is fulfilled - check out @KinSyncApp / http://www.kinsync.com/  :-)    
    
    
    @pixievondust Very sorry - we're still experiencing server issues. We're on it.    
    
    
    @InvasiveNotes Sorry about that. We're experiencing server issues - should be back in a few minutes.    
    
    
    Young Mendeleyans - check out the the Young Researchers in Life Sciences congress in Paris: http://yrls.fr  (via @suvidu @YRLS2012)    
    
    
    "Why I am leaving Goldman Sachs": http://www.nytimes.com/2012/03/14/opinion/why-i-am-leaving-goldman-sachs.html?pagewanted=1&_r=2 …; "Why I am leaving The Empire, by Darth Vader": http://www.thedailymash.co.uk/news/society/why-i-am-leaving-the-empire,-by-darth-vader-201203145007/ …    
    
    
    @theronkelso Sorry, there isn't right now - but it could be built by anyone, by using our API: http://dev.mendeley.com     
    
    
    JISC Report (incl. Mendeley): Text mining promises huge economic/research benefit, but copyright law is limiting it: http://www.jisc.ac.uk/publications/reports/2012/value-and-benefits-of-text-mining.aspx …    
    
    
    "Open Science and the Future of Publishing" - a recording of the Oxford U panel I participated in three weeks ago: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yELZ3kbFj1w&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Just made this slide for a presentation & thought I'd share: Mendeley user love! All tweets are from the last 6 weeks: pic.twitter.com/f5eDdzHn    
    
    
    Team Mendeley at London Web Summit today! pic.twitter.com/h8W0zDOD    
    
    
    @TheNeuroNetwork @mendeleytips Seen this? :-) https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=10150641568343611&set=a.10150156999648611.291608.42920143610&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    @TheNeuroNetwork Thanks! This might also be of interest: http://www.google.com/trends/?q=mendeley,+researchgate,+academia.edu …    
    
    
    @hojoki Your t-shirts arrived today - thanks guys! They're proving very popular, so if you could send some more, we'd wear them proudly :-)    
    
    
    Hell yeah! RT @tpoi: I'm a @mendeley_com advisor now, and I'll advise the sh*t out of my university!    
    
    
    @GianninaRossini Too smug? ;-) I'll blame the wine they gave us before the panel!    
    
    
    @adinalav Very sorry - what kind of messages are they? Messages from other users, or from Mendeley?    
    
    
    @adinalav Apologies - that sounds like a bug. Could you forward one of them to support@mendeley.com, so we can look into it? Thanks!    
    
    
    @SayBeano Mendeley can auto-generate BibTeX entries from your document library, so it works great with LaTeX :-)    
    
    
    @trentyarwood Check out @droideley and #scholarley - both native Android apps for Mendeley!    
    
    
    Ha! Last paper of my PhD thesis was accepted for publication today - 3 years after first submission. Didn't see that one coming!    
    
    
    @briankelly Apologies! We're working on a "flag this user" feature and also have internal alerts, so @mendeleysupport should be on the case!    
    
    
    @MattWatermeyer Very sorry! Can you send more info to @mendeleysupport, so we can help? Thanks!    
    
    
    @grace_baynes Thanks! Glad you liked it! #stm2012    
    
    
    @ScottAtSpringer I agree! #STM2012    
    
    
    Great review of Mendeley/PLoS Binary Battle winner OpenSNP: http://www.genomesunzipped.org/2012/05/a-review-of-opensnp-a-platform-to-share-genetic-data.php …    
    
    
    Disgusting. Groupon now sells doctorate degrees: http://www.groupon.de/deals/online-deal/doktortitel-kaufende/5740776?nlp&CID=DE_CRM_1_0_0_135&a=1655 …    
    
    
    @easternblot Apologetics!    
    
    
    @tpoi Apologies! Can you please send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can try to fix this? Thanks!    
    
    
    @ZachTocchi Could you please send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can try to help? Thanks!    
    
    
    @awaisathar Social networking is a subset of our functionality. We're primarily about research workflow management and collaboration :-)    
    
    
    Open Access gets an €80 billion boost from EU: http://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/story.asp?storycode=419949 …    
    
    
    Welcome aboard! RT @omphe: Thrilled to announce that today I joined the Mendeley team as VP of Product. http://www.mendeley.com/  #fb    
    
    
    Yeah, why? - Eric Schmidt's talk at Science Museum about to start! pic.twitter.com/i1LRTMnu    
    
    
    Cool! Eric Schmidt just gave a shout-out to Mendeley as one of the tools that are making research more social! pic.twitter.com/WNWDGUSb    
    
    
    Our friends at @Symplectic_UK are announcing the forthcoming Mendeley module for Symplectic Elements: http://www.symplectic.co.uk/news-events/2012/05/16/dura-project-with-mendeley-and-caret/ …    
    
    
    @knodeinc Cool - let me know more!    
    
    
    Another interesting study from York University linking Mendeley readership stats to citation counts: http://yfile.news.yorku.ca/2012/06/06/business-librarian-validates-altmetrics-for-research-impact-evaluation/ …    
    
    
    800000 #fishfight supporters are watching you @RichardBenyonMP! Restore fish stocks & end discards @hughsfishfight @ClientEarth    
    
    
    EU Commissioner Neelie Kroes: Let's make science open - https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=6sJbi2eaPXc …    
    
    
    Visiting friends in Ireland; they have a photo in their kitchen which accidentally contains the Mendeley NY office: pic.twitter.com/X1Iwbru5    
    
    
    In Montpellier for ABES library event. Presenting the Mendeley Institutional Edition later! pic.twitter.com/0PSS0pUz    
    
    
    @sasbongo Very sorry to hear that! What went wrong? Can @mendeleysupport help?    
    
    
    The future of transportation looks awesome: http://www.litmotors.com  (it comes with a Joy Division soundtrack, always a winner). / @LitMotors    
    
    
    @IanMulvany Congrats!! If we had baby-sized Mendeley t-shirts, you'd get one :-)    
    
    
    @xtaldave Sorry, no official Android app, but there are a number of third-party Android apps for Mendeley (e.g. Scholarley and Droideley).    
    
    
    Since @stylistpick moved out of our office yesterday, a few Mendeleyans are making somewhat excessive use of the space http://campl.us/kCnG     
    
    
    @heatonjb We are indeed! Drop me a line at victor dot henning at mendeley dot com.    
    
    
    Just spoke at #findbetterproblems - good fun! http://instagram.com/p/M80SI7vl3x/     
    
    
    CODE research grant meeting in our office today! Goal: crowdsourcing zebras (and science) http://campl.us/kJEU     
    
    
    @cwaring @sleepio @johannakoll @brownsdon @underwoodemily @joescarboro Thanks all!    
    
    
    That belongs in here http://www.mendeley.com/groups/536621/creatively-named-research-papers/papers … MT @jenvalentino Jay-Z's "99 Problems" provides lessons on the 4th Amendment: http://bit.ly/LEKeTq     
    
    
    @jaleh_f There are number of third-party apps for Mendeley, though - check out Droideley or Scholarley!    
    
    
    Great article by @iansample in The Guardian: http://www.guardian.co.uk/science/2012/jul/15/free-access-british-scientific-research …. This is huge news, also for our 3rd-party research app developers!    
    
    
    @mikebutcher Great news - and thanks for the shout-out!    
    
    
    Cool interview with @scienceexchange on our blog: http://blog.mendeley.com/mendeley-use-case/another-science-startup-thats-changing-how-research-is-done-an-interview-with-elizabeth-iorns-of-science-exchange/ …    
    
    
    @Thomas_Gutjahr Sorry about that. Major update in the works!    
    
    
    @CameronNeylon Coming up next: Peer reviews to decide whether Mendeley Desktop will accept an article into your document library!    
    
    
    @astefanowitsch @coffee001 Mendeley hat auch eine Zotero-Sync-Funktion: Alles was man in Z. speichert, wird direkt auch in M. übernommen.    
    
    
    @MattB_UK @magpie @debbiefuco @greenjenniferb Sorry, that must be a misunderstanding - Zotero and Mendeley are separate entities.    
    
    
    @eileentso How about dragging scientific research/data kicking and screaming into a future-y webby future :-)    
    
    
    New t-shirt / underpant slogan! RT @subcide "Mendeley, the future-y webby future of research" <- I like it. (cc: @eileentso)    
    
    
    @jesperht Careful! Looks like someone licked that burger bun!    
    
    
    @barrywellman @dirkvl @Amanda_Lenhart Trust is good, desktop app with local backups plus Open APIs are better: http://dev.mendeley.com  :-)    
    
    
    @dirkvl Yes, it is! Schönen Abend gleichfalls :-)    
    
    
    @peyron @NextScientist Thanks for the nice write-up!    
    
    
    Stanford University Libraries announce campus-wide rollout of Mendeley: http://librarypreview.stanford.edu/news/2012/08/join-us-road-mendeley-workshop-library-staff …    
    
    
    University of Pittsburgh adopts Mendeley campus licence, replacing RefWorks: http://www.hsls.pitt.edu/news/mendeley     
    
    
    @erikmstp Go to main folder "Radiography Lit.", click the "Edit Settings" button in middle pane, tick "Download attached files from group"    
    
    
    @erikmstp You're welcome! :-)    
    
    
    @friendly_rock http://librarypreview.stanford.edu/news/2012/08/join-us-road-mendeley-workshop-library-staff … :-)    
    
    
    Rat Overlords! MT @TomChivers: Petri-dish-grown culture of rat brain cells can fly a simulated F-22 fighter jet http://news.discovery.com/tech/brain-dish-flies-plane-041022.html …    
    
    
    Mendeley featured in the Lifehacker Student Edition for Windows (http://ow.ly/cX6J8 ) and Mac (http://ow.ly/cX6Kh )!    
    
    
    @Melissa_Loy Thank you! Happy to hear
that Mendeley was helpful!    
    
    
    With today's update, Mendeley Desktop now supports 2,728 citation styles, up from 1,600! Also, WYSIWYG citation style editor coming soon...    
    
    
    @sjcockell Personally, I wish we wouldn't have to support thousands of citation styles - but as long as journals keep demanding them..    
    
    
    @MKTitsworth It's a server-side update. Should be available in your Mendeley Desktop right now!    
    
    
    P.S. On now supporting 2,728 citation styles: http://xkcd.com/927/     
    
    
    @samusb Thank you! :-) More cool news coming up in the near future.    
    
    
    @geoffwatts That's weird. We had the same awful kerosene / diesel smell over in Primrose Hill at that time!    
    
    
    @phylogenomics Apologies! You can change which actions trigger tweets under My Account > Sharing / Importing.    
    
    
    @phylogenomics Oh - you changed the settings but it still tweeted? If so, would you mind sending more info to support@mendeley.com?    
    
    
    @phylogenomics Ok, thanks. Sorry again for the hassle!    
    
    
    @bobbiejohnson @majohns I'll be there! Spoke at a previous Future Human event about science; really loved it.    
    
    
    @bobbiejohnson: Thank you! Really appreciate it.    
    
    
    At the #futurehuman Smash Publishing event. People in the picture: This is what you look like from behind. pic.twitter.com/2m93LJ6V    
    
    
    Yes, I did! And thanks :-) RT @Stephen_Curry: @mendeley_com Such a great THE story… ;-) Also seen this? http://occamstypewriter.org/scurry/2012/08/13/sick-of-impact-factors/ …    
    
    
    Goodbye Neil! http://ow.ly/i/SE3y     
    
    
    Mendeley news on Times Square, NY:  http://ow.ly/i/TgDs     
    
    
    Insightful: "The unsuccessful self-treatment of a case of writer's block", Journal of Applied Behavioral Analysis: http://ow.ly/dsmFw     
    
    
    @yukop That is amazing!! I'd love to add it to our official press photos (http://www.flickr.com/photos/mendeley/sets/72157630652171616/ …), with credit to you - would that be ok?    
    
    
    I think we have a new slogan: "Mendeley - like caffeine for your research!" Awesome #geeklatte photo by @yukop: http://ow.ly/i/UwUU     
    
    
    Guardian guest post by @mrgunn & myself: "Impact factor: researchers should define the metrics that matter to them" http://www.guardian.co.uk/higher-education-network/blog/2012/sep/06/mendeley-altmetrics-open-access-publishing …    
    
    
    @JacobShiach @Stephen_Curry Thanks!    
    
    
    @kimberlyhogg Thanks! Enjoyed it!    
    
    
    Gave a talk at the Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology today. Check out the banner! http://ow.ly/i/VpfB     
    
    
    Team @OxfordJournals, Team @Tandfonline, and Team Mendeley discussing publishing over beer and soju! pic.twitter.com/2eZyhMHD    
    
    
    Financial Times feature on Mendeley - great photo of my co-founder @janerixo: http://ow.ly/1OvtPi     
    
    
    @pelf81 @mattwargent Mendeley is not just web-based: We have desktop software that syncs across Windows, Mac, Linux (and iOS / Android)!    
    
    
    @SQFPinfo We'll take "<3"! Or a simple link to http://www.mendeley.com  :-) Thanks! (cc @mendeleysupport)    
    
    
    Mendeley Advisor Appreciation Day! Advisors from all over the UK visiting Mendeley HQ pic.twitter.com/kQ81Nt2A    
    
    
    Pizza for all at Mendeley Advisor Appreciation Day! pic.twitter.com/Q4SB4kLn    
    
    
    Mendeley Advisor World Map - thank you to all our Advisors for helping us make science more open! pic.twitter.com/uthWqw0D    
    
    
    @adam42smith @fheimburger @laspic Mendeley does have a feature to export your PDFs including annotations to share with non-Mendeley users.    
    
    
    Amazing summary of the Mendeley Advisor Appreciation Day by Andy Tattersall @scharrlib: http://scharrlibrary.blogspot.co.uk/2012/09/mendelely-advisors-appreciation-day.html …. Thanks Andy!    
    
    
    Butterfly under the doorbell of @Whitebearyard pic.twitter.com/vC03IqHN    
    
    
    @SeanALibby I hear you - very soon!    
    
    
    @addy_dren Yes - try http://www.kinsync.com/  (@kinsync)!    
    
    
    @LSmonster You can sign up for a Mendeley profile without using our software :-)    
    
    
    @OC_org @whitebearyard Took the pic with my iPhone 4S, then cropped/edited in Snapseed :-)    
    
    
    @IanMulvany @subcide @omphe @phpeach Sorry, I'm out of town for a conference!    
    
    
    @OC_org @whitebearyard Thanks!!    
    
    
    @suewolff Here are some tweets :-) http://Twitter.com/Mendeley_com/favorites …    
    
    
    My interview @figshare: #Mendeley, Times Square and Number 10 Downing Street http://shar.es/5U2nX  #openscience #openaccess    
    
    
    @erikreinertsen Yes - completely new version coming soon!    
    
    
    @PlanktonMath Very sorry about that. Brand new iPad app coming soon!    
    
    
    @josmel1 @keitabando @planktonmath iPhone and iPad!    
    
    
    View over foggy Westminster at this morning's copyright symposium at Dept for Business, Innovation & Skills pic.twitter.com/1mCEzimA    
    
    
    @BobOHara We all wore party hats    
    
    
    @whatterz Apologies - you should have received a notification! Perhaps @mendeleysupport can help? Sorry again for the inconvenience!    
    
    
    @mika_jo Sorry about that - in which respect? Perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @mika_jo In Mendeley Desktop or Mendeley Web? Could you send an example to @MendeleySupport? Thanks for your feedback, really appreciate it!    
    
    
    @sofiambg Thank you! Appreciate it!    
    
    
    Great Physics Today feature on #OpenAccess by @starbird2005. Mendeley API also gets a mention. http://www.physicstoday.org/resource/1/phtoad/v65/i11/p22_s1?bypassSSO=1 …    
    
    
    @sarcozona New iPad app coming soon!    
    
    
    @benjrooney What about pitches about academic startups? I hear they're good :-) Great article about the Govt's Open Data strategy, btw.    
    
    
    @Richvn The data seems to suggest otherwise - why else would the #papers accessed by researchers be linked to R&D spend so closely? (1/2)    
    
    
    @Richvn I doubt that scholars in developing countries *want* to access fewer papers, so s.th. must be limiting them. What's your take? (2/2)    
    
    
    @Richvn Interesting thought - then who's to blame for the lack of awareness? Libraries? Also, perhaps top journals like Nature have OA (1/2)    
    
    
    @Richvn ..option, but the long tail of journals doesn't? (2/2)    
    
    
    @Richvn Re: R&D spend = lower research activity: Probably true to some extent, but daily activity time much less influenced by R&D spend.    
    
    
    @Richvn Appreciate your thoughts! We don't have the answers either - it was our best stab at interpreting the data. Cheers!    
    
    
    @Kobrako Sure - send me an email! victor.henning@mendeley.com    
    
    
    Mendeley's Global Research Report (http://mnd.ly/VtjPPM ) on Times Square, NY pic.twitter.com/c4U2PlWv    
    
    
    @becky_rtw I can email you the data tables in Excel format in case you're interested!    
    
    
    @becky_rtw Yes, would've liked to include data tables on our microsite (http://www.mendeley.com/global-research-report …), just didn't get around to it :-)    
    
    
    @SarahRHarrison @floraMbartlett @JessieBluebell Very sorry to hear that! Perhaps our community team (@mrgunn, @rvidal) can help?    
    
    
    @floraMbartlett Glad to hear you got it sorted. Let our community team know if you need any further help!    
    
    
    @jeffreycrow Really sorry about that. We're aware of the issue - new iOS app coming soon!    
    
    
    My girlfriend @michelle_phelan (voc) and @TechCrunch's @mikebutcher (drums) together in the track “Little Wolf” http://carosel.bandcamp.com/track/little-wolf …    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall Yes, sure! Please go ahead! :-)    
    
    
    @michelle_phelan @midem @unicum_music Disrupt your own guitar!!!    
    
    
    @ptreadwell Have a look at @hojoki perhaps?    
    
    
    @HiddenPeanuts Actually, the US is our largest userbase - about 18% of users. UK comes second with about 10%.    
    
    
    @IanMulvany @Stew @jasonpriem @figshare Hi all - unfortunately, I can't do either date, but Jan could do the 3rd!    
    
    
    Some cool new videos showcasing the data dashboard of Mendeley Institutional Edition: http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL2B61A6BB62DF9D4A …    
    
    
    In-depth interview with the eLife team on the Mendeley blog: http://blog.mendeley.com/open-access/interview-with-elife-a-new-tech-forward-openaccess-journal/ …    
    
    
    @kristisan What do you feel is missing from Mendeley? Appreciate your feedback - thanks!    
    
    
    @kristisan You can print notes: While viewing a PDF document, go to File > Export PDF with Annotations. Notes will be appended to the (1/2)    
    
    
    @kristisan PDF file, and you can print it from any other PDF viewer. Re: the crashes, very sorry to hear that! Are you running the (2/3)    
    
    
    @kristisan latest version? If you send more info to support@mendeley.com, we can try to figure out what's going on. Thanks! (3/3)    
    
    
    @jemimah_knight Awesome shot!    
    
    
    @kristisan The notes are all appended at the end of the PDF document, so you could only print the last few pages containing the notes.    
    
    
    @iansample @ECspokesScience Europe currently leading the world in access to research papers and daily research time: http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-life/mendeley-has-two-million-users-to-celebrate-were-releasing-the-global-research-report/ …    
    
    
    My Interview on Scientific American blogs by @Hadas_Shema: http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/information-culture/2012/11/23/interview-with-dr-victor-henning-mendeley/ …    
    
    
    @egonwillighagen @ImpactStory @rkiddr Strange! Could you please send the info to support@mendeley.com, so we can investigate? Thanks!    
    
    
    @roxannevarza I would happily speak about big data in academia/science!    
    
    
    @gigaseal Very sorry to hear you're experiencing issues - could you send details to support@mendeley.com so we can try to fix them? Thanks!    
    
    
    Awesome! One of Mendeley's investors (Jaan Tallinn) is now part of a Cambridge Doomwatch team to save the world: http://www.engadget.com/2012/11/26/cambridge-existential-risk/ …    
    
    
    @SianHarris8 Engagdet probably didn't mean that those fields were fringes, but rather that the fringes of those fields would be investigated    
    
    
    @jasonpriem @IanMulvany @Stew @figshare You'll have to go old-school and email Jan with time/date - he's not active on Twitter :-)    
    
    
    @fsayre Yes, people are using it for systematic reviews - particularly using the collaborative PDF annotation function!    
    
    
    @raulpacheco @EndNoteNews Since our latest 1.7 release, Mendeley has a WYSIWYG citation style editor: http://csl.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @pixievondust @TriploidTree @IrishTimes Everybody should get the name of their company added as a first name! Aldous Huxley would approve!    
    
    
    @onekind @stephx You can use both together: Mendeley has a Zotero-sync function (as well as cite-as-you-write in Word/OO and BibTex support)    
    
    
    @mark_carrigan I'm not skeptical at all about expertise - but about identifying it lazily by virtue of their academic position #lseimpact    
    
    
    @commutiny I'm not skeptical at all about expertise - but about identifying it lazily by virtue of their academic position #lseimpact    
    
    
    @cubanba @congabonga Charts may not match your taste, but labels not being gatekeeper to who can distribute music widely = good #lseimpact    
    
    
    @jfurfey Info on semantically linked data set project here: http://code-research.eu/  #lseimpact    
    
    
    @WarrenPearce Quite simple: Premium / team collaboration accounts (http://www.mendeley.com/upgrade/ ), institutional licensing (http://www.swets.com/mendeley-institutional-edition …).    
    
    
    @mark_carrigan Agreed! Hence not all crowdsourced annotations will be treated as equal - there will be markers (e.g. academic status, ..    
    
    
    @mark_carrigan .. research background, impact based on publications/readership). More data = more criteria for people to assign trust.    
    
    
    The three Mendeley founders spreading Christmas cheer in the office - courtesy of @JessReeves1! pic.twitter.com/CPyMrPOz    
    
    
    @mark_carrigan It was a heated discussion :-)    
    
    
    @stochastician New iOS app coming soon!    
    
    
    @DrLabRatOry New iOS app coming soon!    
    
    
    @altmetric @IanMulvany Looking good!    
    
    
    @nulliusinverba @jasonpriem http://code-research.eu     
    
    
    @kesloane @raulpacheco In EndNote, export your library as .xml (not .enl, which is a proprietary format). Mendeley can import EndNote XML.    
    
    
    @lpsavoie Not anymore! We've just released a visual citation style editor: http://csl.mendeley.com/about/     
    
    
    I just added my own publication: 'Interview with Victor' http://mnd.ly/SSRfVO     
    
    
    @subcide Ha, forgot about the auto-tweet! Was just testing something :-)    
    
    
    @whatterz Yes - if you're using Android phones/tablets, we recommend using 3rd-party apps like Droideley or Scholarley.    
    
    
    @whatterz We are considering it for next year. Also, new API methods coming soon will make 3rd-party apps much more powerful.    
    
    
    @Eetezadi Our API will allow annotation/comment syncing early next year!    
    
    
    @RottenCapital Yes, you will be able to retrieve/create your own annotations via our API!    
    
    
    @karlita_dDios Yes, I'm one of the founders of Mendeley - but we are now a team of 40!    
    
    
    @karlita_dDios Thank you!! I'll pass it on to the team :-)    
    
    
    @liljefred Sorry about that - new iPad version coming soon!    
    
    
    @dittlebird Sorry about that. You can change the citation style rules using http://csl.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @Viil Apologies - what bug is it? Perhaps @MendeleySupport can help?    
    
    
    @erikreinertsen New iOS App is already in closed beta testing, will come in January!    
    
    
    @liljefred Yes, it will support sub-folders!    
    
    
    @eagereyes Very sorry - could you send more details to support@mendeley.com, so we can investigate? Thanks for letting us know!    
    
    
    @drlawson Considering it. Are already improving our API so that 3rd party apps (e.g. Scholarley or Droideley) can access notes/highlights.    
    
    
    @KennKnowles Mendeley can automatically generate/update BibTeX files that stay in sync with your document library.    
    
    
    @Jobium Christmas party hangover? Joking aside - sorry about that! Could you send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can check?    
    
    
    @dullhunk @mfenner @nuin @srp Full story: Our Open API is more full-featured & allows two-way sync, unlike the separate API .. (1/2)    
    
    
    @dullhunk @mfenner @nuin @srp .. @CiteULike has been using. We ask everyone to use the Open API so we only need to maintain one. (2/2)    
    
    
    @brinxmat @danbri We're just going to retire the private API @CiteULike are using & asked them to use our (more full-featured) public API.    
    
    
    @rafaelsidi CiteULike sync is using an outdated private API which we'll retire; we've asked them to move to our public Open API instead.    
    
    
    @rmounce @citeulike @rafaelsidi Sorry, should've been clearer. We're retiring private sync methods and APIs for our Desktop and iOS apps..    
    
    
    @rmounce @citeulike @rafaelsidi ..in order to move everything, including our own apps, to our public APIs. This will make it easier for..    
    
    
    @rmounce @citeulike @rafaelsidi ..us to support 3rd party devs and give them the same capabilities as our own apps (2-way sync, notes etc).    
    
    
    Happy New Year, Mendeley community! Wishing you a successful 2013 with all the research results you're hoping for!    
    
    
    @markhawker That day is coming soon :-)    
    
    
    @cdsouthan @egonwillighagen CUL sync relies on outdated private (and 1-way) API; we want to move everything to our Open API (2-way) instead.    
    
    
    @blkmage Sorry about that - new iOS app coming soon!    
    
    
    @DavidScaduto New iOS app already in beta testing and coming soon!    
    
    
    @DrJohnCosgrove @DrPlumEU There are third-party Mendeley plugins for inserting references in Wordpress and Drupal: http://dev.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @carusb @rmounce Mendeley does read PDF XMP metadata, but it's frequently noisy/incorrect, so we check it against other signals.    
    
    
    @ElleCovell Sorry, we're not the developers of Droideley, it's a 3rd-party app! As an alternative, have you tried Scholarley?    
    
    
    @ShintaroSato @mendeleyAPI That's coming soon!    
    
    
    @ToxTalks Yes, we do have a citation plugin for Word on Mac!    
    
    
    @raulpacheco Thanks for the feedback - can you clarify what you mean with the citation output?    
    
    
    @raulpacheco Have you seen our WYSIWYG citation style editor at http://csl.mendeley.com ? It should let you configure this as you wish.    
    
    
    @raulpacheco Thanks - happy we were able to help :-)    
    
    
    @raulpacheco We're working on letting users define their own document types :-)    
    
    
    @O2 Any broadband issues in Primrose Hill (NW1)? My home internet connection has been intermittently disappearing for the past 2-3 days.    
    
    
    @O2 Yes, wireless router. Tried rebooting and resetting. DSL light is flashing - can't seem to get DSL signal. Internet gone completely now.    
    
    
    @jmlaforge Could you send the document to support@mendeley.com, so we can have a look where the highlighting fails? Thanks!    
    
    
    @ythuky Can you please send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can take a closer look? Thanks!    
    
    
    @ythuky I'll ask them to check again.    
    
    
    @ythuky Hi Ythuky, the support team can't find an email from that address or with your name - could you please re-send it? Thank you!    
    
    
    @uhrenbacher Danke für die Weihnachtskarte übrigens :-) Sehen wir uns bei DLD oder The Europas?    
    
    
    Mendeley in the Financial Times today: http://ow.ly/gMM3A     
    
    
    @soniaahhh There is a WYSIWYG CSL editor at http://csl.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @Recher_she Thanks for the reminder - noted :-) New iOS app is already in beta testing, will come soon!    
    
    
    @soniaahhh Yes - as determined by the citation style you choose (and it can also be formatted using the CSL Editor).    
    
    
    @soniaahhh The Nature & IEEE styles have numbered in-text citations - does it not work for you? Also, Mendeley is currently at version 1.7.    
    
    
    Join @mrgunn, @researchremix, @researchtrendy for "The Individual and Scholarly Network" 2-part seminar: http://reedelsevier.reg.meeting-stream.com/researchtrends_elsevierlabs/ … #scholnet12    
    
    
    @darrenmackay @MendeleySupport We feel your pain. Brand-new, rewritten-from-scratch iOS app is coming soon and already in beta testing.    
    
    
    @TheEuropas Whoohoo! Thanks everyone! Gutted we couldn't make it because of the weather!    
    
    
    Whoohoo! RT @TheEuropas: And the winners of Best Startup Founders are Jan Reichelt, Paul Foeckler & Victor Henning of Mendeley! #TheEuropas    
    
    
    Jan, Paul, and I just won the award for Best Startup Founders in Europe at #TheEuropas in Berlin! http://ow.ly/i/1plZV ...    
    
    
    @ewancarr Psychedelic! Could you please send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can have a look? Thanks!    
    
    
    @KrisPorterDPT New Mendeley iOS app, rewritten from scratch, with faster sync and annotations/highlights, coming soon! #bestPTapps    
    
    
    @nickrw I know - was digging through the @Postbox settings to see if I could change them... but GMail web UI is sloooow for me!    
    
    
    @KarenODonoghue @michelle_phelan Thanks :-)    
    
    
    @amyewest You can export PDFs with annotations from Mendeley, so they'll show up in Evernote!    
    
    
    @IanMulvany Ha, me too. Looks like it will be another just-in-time delivery.    
    
    
    @iheartlineart Yes, we do!    
    
    
    @jakubdostal @Patered @matt_j_miller Mendeley actually syncs with Kindle, via 3rd party app http://www.kinsync.com/     
    
    
    @Patered Not sure - I believe notes on Kindle are in proprietary format? Our API does have the ability to sync your Mendeley notes.    
    
    
    @RBrownSalazar @adam42smith The recommendation engine is only available to Mendeley Premium subscribers and Advisors (for now; might change)    
    
    
    @Recher_she Please get in touch with @subcide - he might be able to help :-)    
    
    
    @VenusLeyenda Yes - if you add the notes to a document in a group, the other members in the group can see them.    
    
    
    @Stevancw @timrittman You mean, different colored highlights? That's planned, more info here: http://feedback.mendeley.com/forums/4941-general/suggestions/273284-making-it-possible-to-highlight-text-with-differen#comments …    
    
    
    @Stevancw Interesting thought! I'll share it with our UX team. Thanks!    
    
    
    @CenterSuccess Apologies - we chose today because it's a public holiday in the US. Very sorry that it interfered with your class!    
    
    
    @taavet Us? :-)    
    
    
    The website and syncing will be unavailable for maintenance from 10am GMT tomorrow for around two hours. Sorry for any inconvenience!    
    
    
    @CClements88 Fear not! We shall return in a few minutes, with backend upgrades that have made us stronger!    
    
    
    @prezi Eh.. did your editing toolbar just change? I can't find the freehand drawing tool anymore? pic.twitter.com/hEhB2Q5D    
    
    
    @prezi ..and the ability to turn elements into Library Objects is gone too?    
    
    
    @n0v0id Doch, das geht auf Deinem Mendeley-Profil - siehe z.B. http://www.mendeley.com/profiles/victor-henning/ …    
    
    
    @jmlaforge That's awesome!    
    
    
    @gertsenmsnv6 Brand-new iPad app coming soon! @subcide can tell you whether there are beta testing spots available.    
    
    
    @davidleetalk2me @sofi_nas Went there with @michelle_phelan a couple of weeks ago. Lovely food!    
    
    
    @James_Wheldon Sorry about that. New iPad app with annotations sync coming soon!    
    
    
    @mefunk Thank you - my pleasure :-)    
    
    
    @gendalus Sorry - komplett neu entwickelte iOS App ist schon im Beta-Testing und kommt bald!    
    
    
    @costrike @GlobalEcoGuy @mbeisen For a Mendeley-Kindle integration, try http://www.kinsync.com  :-)    
    
    
    @hossiet @sc_evans Have you tried one of the third-party Android apps, e.g. Scholarley or Droideley? Other users have said good things!    
    
    
    @KinSyncApp You're welcome - we're happy there are apps like KinSync! :-)    
    
    
    @rbizzlesticks Thank you!    
    
    
    @MichaelTsielepi Very sorry to hear you're having problems. Maybe @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    Owl sighting at Mendeley HQ! This owl will run a cancer charity half-marathon, please donate: http://www.justgiving.com/Matthew-Green14  pic.twitter.com/MQ39N9RSSn    
    
    
    @sarahkendrew Yeay! Good luck!    
    
    
    @raulpacheco Yes, absolutely! Photos in our Flickr account are CC-BY by default.    
    
    
    @ariannabetti Sorry, that might be a bug - your group allowances shouldn't have changed. Perhaps community@mendeley.com can help?    
    
    
    @michellehudson Yes - both in Mendeley Desktop and Mendeley Web, you can filter your documents by one or multiple tags (cc @mrgunn).    
    
    
    @michalboo @AndrewOfficer @mrgunn But on Flickr! http://www.flickr.com/photos/mendeley/sets/72157624898905520/ …    
    
    
    Getting ready to speak about "Mendeley and Altmetrics" at University of Granada seminar #giec3 pic.twitter.com/K5b04rFEBU    
    
    
    @jae3goals @gfyar You can easily edit the citation style at http://csl.mendeley.com  - hope that helps!    
    
    
    Loving @davidleetalk2me's hackday project! pic.twitter.com/uuRtQeSYmz    
    
    
    @flipphillips Sorry - we do care! It's just always difficult juggling dev priorities. What exactly is the bibtex issue?    
    
    
    @flipphillips Perhaps you could get in touch with our desktop developers directly, to explain what exactly is needed? desktop@mendeley.com    
    
    
    @flipphillips Thanks, I see - will poke to desktop team to review this!    
    
    
    @ThomasPRoland @robknight_ You can merge authors by dragging & dropping names onto each other in the "Filter by Authors" box (bottom left).    
    
    
    @ThomasPRoland @robknight_ We've started work on that, but I don't yet know when we can roll it out.    
    
    
    @Artandmylife That's awesome! Thank you!    
    
    
    @bgamari Sorry to hear - what was it that didn't work for you?    
    
    
    @bgamari Thanks for the feedback - much appreciated. Sorry to see that the support team couldn't help. Maybe see you again in the future!    
    
    
    @PatParslow Glad to hear that :-)    
    
    
    @Zay_017 Very sorry - perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @neuromusic @mrgunn @ResearchBlogs There are plugins for Wordpress and Drupal already which pull citations from the Mendeley API.    
    
    
    @vickytnz On the contrary - we're doubling the available storage space for free!    
    
    
    @simoncolumbus @mrgunn Will be a boost - great new features that weren't possible before in the pipeline!    
    
    
    @gedankenstuecke @mrgunn Thank you - we won't disappoint :-)    
    
    
    @simoncolumbus Thanks - that's indeed what's planned!    
    
    
    @markhawker Actually, no cleverness intended :-) There currently is a free version, and there always will be - what else could it mean?    
    
    
    @markhawker @amcunningham Just a few weeks away now!    
    
    
    @markhawker @amcunningham From last week :-)    
    
    
    @elizabethiorns Thanks Liz!    
    
    
    @vitauria Thank you! Yes, I'll be there :-)    
    
    
    @Kolvin @orrick @torchpartners Thanks all!    
    
    
    @querolus @jesusmendezzz @versvs Mendeley & our OAPI will remain free and open: Still under a CC-BY license, more/cleaner/richer data.    
    
    
    @querolus @jesusmendezzz @versvs I believe this opens additional opportunities and represents a further step by Elsevier towards openness.    
    
    
    @wilbanks Thanks John. We're still pushing for open data; will use E. data to clean/enrich/complete our API data, still under CC-BY.    
    
    
    @TorchPartners Thank you for helping us see this through from start to finish!    
    
    
    @SianHarris8 I had a ticket for that, too, but something got in the way :-)    
    
    
    @FakeElsevier You gotta admit those hats say YOLO    
    
    
    @futurehumanista Thank you!    
    
    
    @marylgray @phenatypical In my mind, the Open API under a Creative Commons CC-BY license does - and we'll keep expanding it!    
    
    
    @marlenc Thank you - likewise!    
    
    
    @gregladen @mrgunn We won't let you down!    
    
    
    @Elisotope @dambrodebarcola @LabSpaces @mrgunn When we started everyone doubted that 3 PhD students could have influence on the industry :-)    
    
    
    @marylgray We'll move more features from the paid to the free version soon. But hope you understand we also have to pay our staff somehow!    
    
    
    liked:  "Documents added 'The Expression of Emotions in 20th Century Books'" http://mnd.ly/ZMxpKw     
    
    
    @richardewest Sorry, no - I don't say that publishers will become redundant, but talk about where to look for new business opportunities.    
    
    
    @nniiicc Our goal is to create more of those A-HA moments in the future, including bigger/better/more open groups and a follower model.    
    
    
    @davemcclure Thanks Dave - much appreciated :-)    
    
    
    @drdrAatBLC @rvidal I don't see any sharks with laser beams on their head in our office yet!    
    
    
    @zakandrewking I guarantee you we won't - great features and product improvements in the pipeline!    
    
    
    @Karenmca @NazlinBhimani It won't - in fact, we're under less pressure to monetize now, so will provide more features/value for free!    
    
    
    @neuromusic @researchremix @mrgunn Why wouldn't it be objective? We're simply providing aggregate usage data, independent of publisher.    
    
    
    @neuromusic @mrgunn @researchremix I am confident that the overall composition of our userbase won't change - in fact, I believe.. (1/2)    
    
    
    @neuromusic @mrgunn @researchremix .. that the representativeness and richness of our usage data will increase due to larger scale. (2/2)    
    
    
    @ssbittner We do have an iPad app (new release coming soon) + there are Android apps like Droideley or Scholarley. Which OS are you on?    
    
    
    @ssbittner True, though they work very well. We're also currently recruiting mobile developers for an in-house Android app!    
    
    
    @Werner Thank you, much appreciated - #awspowered indeed!    
    
    
    @sennoma No worries, Bill - no offence taken. To be honest, I had to laugh at the picture, too :-)    
    
    
    @trentyarwood I wouldn't put it that way, but yeah, we're now hiring mobile devs to make an Android client :-)    
    
    
    @annacreech @rvidal Our Mendeley Institutional Edition is actually designed to help libraries increase their interaction with researchers.    
    
    
    @gise_pr Jajaja... gracias :-)    
    
    
    @MeninAndrea Thank you - glad we could help, and congrats on the masters!    
    
    
    @hbunke I can assure you that neither is the case. We're optimists and always up for a challenge :-)    
    
    
    @reidpr No, core motivation was (and is) to make researchers' lives easier. Being useful and being a for-profit are not mutually exclusive.    
    
    
    @LymeAction @light_lyme It won't - it will only get better!    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall Hi Andy - thanks! Yes, I'd be happy to. Off to a BBC Radio 4 interview now, but we'll find a time!    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall I'll be live at 4.30pm on BBC's Material World :-) http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01rr7ry …    
    
    
    @jasonpriem @Andy_Tattersall @ImpactStory Amazing how fast that went! Felt like we were only speaking for 5 minutes!    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall Thanks Andy! Off to team bowling event now, and speaking at Oxford Open Sci Conf tomorrow - you won't be there by chance?    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall Email might be easier then - do you have my address? As for bowling: I'm dragging down my team's scores :-)    
    
    
    @flipphillips Thank you, Flip! There are a number of cool things in the pipeline already!    
    
    
    @Tim_Budge Thanks! We'll actually stay very independent - in our own office, same team, same management and founders in charge, same vision.    
    
    
    @DianaJSpencer @thesiswhisperer Intention is to let Mendeley be Mendeley, with more resources (e.g. for Android app) & better content access    
    
    
    @DianaJSpencer @thesiswhisperer Most definitely!    
    
    
    @herrison Thong?! I know my drawing skills need work, but that one was unexpected :-)    
    
    
    At the BBC Radio 4 studio yesterday! http://ow.ly/i/1SsW5     
    
    
    @dirkvl @mrgunn We will!    
    
    
    @dirkvl Thank you, Dirk - much appreciated. Jan and I will do our best to keep it!    
    
    
    @samplereality Sorry - but where are we doing that? We are sad to see any user leave, anytime, and hope they reconsider.. (1/2)    
    
    
    @samplereality ..when they see the results of our joint work in a few months down the line. I apologize if anyone felt otherwise. (2/2)    
    
    
    @rrichard09 @techsoc @rvidal We have always supported import/export in standard formats (XML, RIS, BibTex) and will continue to do so.    
    
    
    @nthmost As per my last tweet - we have always supported import/export in standard formats (XML, RIS, BibTex) and will continue to do so.    
    
    
    @FrederikHjorth I can guarantee you we won't - it'll always be free. We also just doubled everyone's storage space for free; more to come!    
    
    
    @guetto We're not going anywhere, Harry Lime :-) Exciting things on our roadmap - better desktop app, new mobile apps, better content access    
    
    
    @nthmost Yes - it wasn't meant in a snarky way! I was just pointing out that it's already possible and easy :-)    
    
    
    @jdhowgego Not just possible, but very, very likely :-)    
    
    
    @jdhowgego Naturally :-) But looking at our roadmap, I'm very excited.    
    
    
    @klockemd @nlafferty We're not going anywhere - UX improvements, new features, new iOS app, better content access coming soon :-)    
    
    
    @nthmost Agreed :-) Much appreciated!    
    
    
    @AmidstScience Very sorry. Any idea how it happened - sync issue? If you drop support@mendeley.com a line, we'll try to help!    
    
    
    @cyrilleadam iOS app that doesn't suck is coming soon, including note/highlight functionality :-) We'll also start Android app development.    
    
    
    @cyrilleadam We decided to rewrite from scratch to move to our Open API, which also lets 3rd-party devs sync notes/highlights. Will be free!    
    
    
    @cyrilleadam You're welcome :-)    
    
    
    @fso_swe Mendeley has a Zotero-sync feature - you can set it to auto-import everything you capture in Zotero.    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor And I thought I was mainly plugging my girlfriend's food blog!    
    
    
    @Yaamina23 Yes - in the Mendeley PDF Viewer go to "File > Export with Annotations".    
    
    
    @Yaamina23 Ah, sorry, I misunderstood - I thought you wanted to see Mendeley annotations in other PDF viewers, not the other way around!    
    
    
    @Yaamina23 I suppose you would have to save the annotations from Skim/Preview into the PDF somehow - then Mendeley would see them.    
    
    
    @bobbiejohnson Belated, but nonetheless: Congrats!!    
    
    
    @bobbiejohnson I'm in Amsterdam this week :-)    
    
    
    @DennisEckmeier @mrgunn @laxvid @Odysseyblog We're aware the API needs improvement and are working on it - see...    
    
    
    @DennisEckmeier @mrgunn @laxvid @Odysseyblog .. http://ow.ly/1VnIt7  :-) (URL got cut in my last tweet)    
    
    
    @Laserjunge New Mendeley iOS app including annotations&highlights sync already being tested, will be released soon. @subcide knows more :-)    
    
    
    @nicoadams More Star Wars references here: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … :-)    
    
    
    @grahamburdge @surreynourish You can now easily customise citation styles: http://csl.mendeley.com  :-)    
    
    
    @mselibrary I'm answering some of the most frequently asked questions here: http://elsevierconnect.com/what-you-really-want-to-know-about-mendeley-and-elsevier/ … :-)    
    
    
    @lucdall Mendeley reste libre et ouvert. Plus d'info ici: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … and http://blog.mendeley.com/press-release/qa-team-mendeley-joins-elsevier/ …    
    
    
    Press release: @ThomsonReuters / @EndNoteNews brings feather to a pillow fight :-) http://www.marketwatch.com/story/thomson-reuters-ups-ante-for-mendeley-customers-seeking-free-alternative-2013-04-23 …    
    
    
    @Yaamina23 @StephMulrine @PhDForum We have a new iPhone/iPad app with annotations/highlights sync coming soon; Android apps also available!    
    
    
    @bpwned Ich liebe es, wenn ein Plan funktioniert :-)    
    
    
    @DrRachie @botbml That's brilliant! Thank you :-)    
    
    
    Amazing - Mendeley / Linux / Android nail art! RT @hollycassell: @jesperht how'd you like them apples? :) pic.twitter.com/6PrAPg6fZw    
    
    
    @hollycassell This is great! Can we add it to our press photos (http://www.flickr.com/photos/mendeley/sets/72157630652171616/ …)? Do you have a Flickr account we could credit?    
    
    
    @hollycassell Done! http://www.flickr.com/photos/mendeley/8676982369/in/set-72157630652171616 … - thank you! :-)    
    
    
    @JavierCanavate @danjhayden Better iOS with annotations & highlights sync already in testing - will be released soon!    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor @rintzezelle I think it's about 15 different styles (still too many, if you ask me!) mapped to the 1500 journal names.    
    
    
    @rintzezelle @MikeTaylor Sorry, you're right - only 6 different ones, not 15.    
    
    
    @DrRachie On the contrary! Here's some info on our plans and improvements we've already rolled out: http://ow.ly/1VEOp0     
    
    
    @DrRachie Also, another recent interview on the topic: http://bit.ly/10g9KCJ  - let me know if you have more questions!    
    
    
    @ReinerGrundmann @CountCarbon No need to - here's some info on our plans and improvements we've already rolled out: http://ow.ly/1VEOp0     
    
    
    @grolimur @mrgunn For a more in-depth look at how we use & share data via our API, see this: http://ow.ly/1VEOp0     
    
    
    @daviesjs Completely rewritten/redesigned iOS app coming soon - faster, prettier, and with annotations & highlights sync!    
    
    
    @anandamide @willhowells Completely rewritten iOS app with annotations & highlights coming very soon - already in beta testing!    
    
    
    @jesgar On the contrary: We're currently looking into how we can expand collaboration :-)    
    
    
    @Laura_Fortune @Jason_P_Smith Yes, it does :-) We have apps for Win, Mac, Linux, iOS, and there are 3rd-party apps for iOS, Android, Kindle.    
    
    
    @TomReller @jasonpriem Time to capitalise and start a boy band!    
    
    
    @Jason_P_Smith @Laura_Fortune Thank you - much appreciated!    
    
    
    @papershipapp @quesnelm Yes - annotation sync to 3rd-party app will be available soon!    
    
    
    @gendalus @totalreflexion Das ist Sippenhaft :-) Hier Infos, wie wir unseren Nutzern in Zukunft noch mehr bieten: http://ow.ly/kKZrf     
    
    
    @blogkamp @urbaneprofessor @StuartWilksHeeg Yes, Mendeley imports EndNote XML libraries, RIS, BibTex; straight from PDF, & syncs with Zotero    
    
    
    Great Mendeley tutorial video: http://vimeo.com/65511929     
    
    
    @brandontlocke @ScholCommons I see why you would ugh, but here's more context on how it will benefit our users: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ …    
    
    
    @muammar I hope not :-) Here is more info on how it will benefit our users: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … - great stuff in the pipeline!    
    
    
    @SarahHCarl @firegenome Actually, good things are already coming out of it, see http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … and http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-features/mendeley-contributes-2000-citation-styles-to-the-open-citation-style-repository-at-citationstyles-org/ …    
    
    
    @firegenome @SarahHCarl Yes - though I won't really have to, as Elsevier are significantly ramping up their OA publishing efforts already!    
    
    
    @firegenome @SarahHCarl I don't know yet - I'm new on the job :-)    
    
    
    @MatthewJGreene Good question - could you give @mendeleysupport more info, so they can have a look? Thanks!    
    
    
    @jatenas Not quite, our Open API under Creative Commons license is alive & well, see http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … and also http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-features/mendeley-contributes-2000-citation-styles-to-the-open-citation-style-repository-at-citationstyles-org/ …    
    
    
    @f_ferraro More on the Star Wars references here: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … :-)    
    
    
    @gmact I do believe our Word plugin supports that - you could try http://csl.mendeley.com  to edit citation styles as needed!    
    
    
    @m_wall @JimP @neuroconscience @ethanweed New, faster, more stable iOS app with annotations & highlight coming soon!    
    
    
    @MarikaRose @orionedgar @DavidHowey Yes, Mendeley has automatic BibTex export which keeps BibTex files in sync with your document library.    
    
    
    Killer Robot Discussion at Google Big Tent event http://ow.ly/i/2aMhm     
    
    
    Eric Schmidt: Because Cody Wilson thought it was a good idea to put the 3D-printed gun on the web, people will die. http://ow.ly/i/2aS4h     
    
    
    @davidleetalk2me By the way, Eric Schmidt's was another "Fireside Chat" without a fireside anywhere in sight. False labelling! #bigtentuk    
    
    
    @Le_GFII ça me fait plaisir - à la semaine prochaine!    
    
    
    @lgroeni @MiguelJohnson Mendeley also backs up/syncs any documents and files in your library.    
    
    
    @hbunke That's very strange - when you delete your account, all personal info (incl. email address) is deleted. I'll check what's going on!    
    
    
    @jenlrile New iOS app coming soon, with all the features u want :-)    
    
    
    @azeem @pjozefak Nobody's being geocitied. Amazing stuff in the pipeline - watch this space!    
    
    
    @hamilton_ia @jenlrile Yes, sorry about that! We had to make some changes to the underlying architecture to improve notes & highlights sync.    
    
    
    @rvidal A million bucks of product placement well spent!    
    
    
    @eileentso Some of it sounds very familiar!    
    
    
    @teraspawn Dear Beth,

Sorry for that! We tried :-)

Lots of love,
Mendeley

P.S. We're always working on improving the metadata extraction.    
    
    
    @yoavram @MendeleySupport Working on it, and coming soon!    
    
    
    @mattd_hall New, flexible recommender engine that works for any set of papers you select is in the works!    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor @wisealic There were other offers, but Elsevier was the best fit in terms of product fit/platform vision. (1/2)    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor @wisealic Can't disclose who the other offers were from - such stuff is covered by NDAs. (2/2)    
    
    
    @jonfwilkins @mrgunn @openscience Here, have some camomile tea. We're not going anywhere! Ask Open Day attendees what they thought :-)    
    
    
    @algae Apparently you disagree, or why is it bothering you?    
    
    
    @MatthieuRegnier You can use http://www.mendeley.com/import/  to save websites/PDFs for later; you can also sort papers in your library by date added.    
    
    
    @BobRimington Sorry to hear - how so? Any way we can help?    
    
    
    @algae I respectfully disagree. Mendeley is about crowdsourcing/open science; 3D printing is about crowdsourcing/open manufacturing. They..    
    
    
    @algae ..are related trends. I was quoting Eric Schmidt at a conference I was attending. Also, I don't think what he said was inflammatory.    
    
    
    @dasKerst Sorry to hear - perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @rintzezelle Thanks for pointing it out. I've asked the editor of the website to add the link!    
    
    
    @rintzezelle @cparnot Absolutely. I'm sure that the omission of the link was not intentional. It's been added now!    
    
    
    @davidleetalk2me It's like magic! There's a little me in the box where you plug your headphones in!    
    
    
    @MaryLouCowan Sorry about that! Perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @aleciarrb Looks like the icon for "link to PDF broken"! @MendeleySupport can help.    
    
    
    @APAPsycNET As a former APA member (when I was a practicing researcher), that makes me very happy! Thanks! :-)    
    
    
    Team Mendeley plotting research workflow magnificence with Team @Scopus pic.twitter.com/TaAkQtaalR    
    
    
    @subcide @Scopus Chosen intentionally ;-)    
    
    
    @chanamuu Very sorry to hear - perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @smeh In case it helps, here's a blog post addressing some of the questions/concerns people have had: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ …    
    
    
    Giving a talk at the University of Vienna. Always a great photo op n magnificent venues like these! pic.twitter.com/j1LOi4bAtk    
    
    
    @thijsbart @ipoga Yes, the API (and Mendeley itself) will remain free! In the future, we may introduce additional paid metrics/data.    
    
    
    @MeninAndrea Very happy to hear that - thank you!!    
    
    
    @kaankalkan You're welcome, and thank you for the kind words!    
    
    
    Interesting new study on correlation between Mendeley readers vs citations by @ehsanwlv presented at #ISSI13 pic.twitter.com/FlV7Ew3A2Y    
    
    
    Study by @sh2106 et al: @Scopus and Mendeley have higher article coverage than @webofknowledge #ISSI2013 pic.twitter.com/OvfXNf8ISM    
    
    
    Thought-provoking article in The Atlantic: "If PRISM Is Good Policy, Why Stop With Terrorism?" http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2013/07/if-prism-is-good-policy-why-stop-with-terrorism/277531/ …    
    
    
    Talk by Mendeley visiting researcher @PeterKraker, co-authored by our Chief Scientist @_krisjack #ISSI2013 pic.twitter.com/u4cVQ8uDr7    
    
    
    @barbalink @pickleswarlz @cbahlai @carlyziter Mendeley has automatic BibTex export (to keep the .bib files in sync with your PDF library).    
    
    
    @barbalink @cbahlai @carlyziter Sorry to hear! Those glitches may have been fixed; we now have thousands more styles & a WYSIWG style editor    
    
    
    Mendeley hosted a conference on Recommender Engines recently; here's a great @FastCompany write-up including videos: http://www.fastcolabs.com/3014630/open-company/how-to-make-room-for-experts-in-your-app …    
    
    
    Team Mendeley making good use of Google Hangouts and Hangout-provided fake beards during weekly Team Briefing pic.twitter.com/d6Tocp3WM6    
    
    
    @OmarRHosny @idlehans Have you tried http://csl.mendeley.com ? If that doesn't work, perhaps @MendeleySupport can help.    
    
    
    @tertiary Hm, that sounds like a circular reference - perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @_megmkelly_ Apologies! @mendeleysupport will look into it tomorrow.    
    
    
    @jamiedavies Much appreciated :-)    
    
    
    @raulpacheco You can easily edit it here: http://csl.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @AdamGDunn A good starting point to check is here: http://www.sherpa.ac.uk/romeo/     
    
    
    Fantastic video capturing the vibe at Mendeley Open Day 2013 - quote by @scharrlib "I feel like I'm at a Mini-Google" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EwxxdgcQPIg …    
    
    
    @easternblot Good question! Have you updated your academic status in your profile? If so, it seems that Groups don't update after creation..    
    
    
    @Brightblue Very sorry - we don't like Donkey Balls either! What went wrong? Perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @stelfrich We wanted to avoid documents disappearing from your local lib if someone else deleted it in a group. Notes are synced, though.    
    
    
    @stelfrich The best person to ask is @subcide - he's working on future plans for document annotations!    
    
    
    @ph1lk Wo denn zum Beispiel? Gibt's bestimmte Features, die Dir fehlen?    
    
    
    @Recher_she Thanks, will pass it on!    
    
    
    @AdamGDunn @thesiswhisperer 2.5 million users, and nobody has gotten into trouble :-) Seriously: Our job is to make academics' lives easier.    
    
    
    @LynneJ_P @SkyLizzie Try http://csl.mendeley.com  - it's an easy-to-use visual citation style editor!    
    
    
    @JohnNCoupland You're right, our pricing doesn't support the classroom use case very well. We're considering changes (but it'll take time).    
    
    
    @jlynnmuir Completely new iOS app has been submitted to the App Store last week, we're waiting for approval!    
    
    
    @NatashaHodgson Sure - just contact community@mendeley.com!    
    
    
    Congrats to @PeerJ for winning the 2013 ALPSP Innovation Award! pic.twitter.com/zCO5sCh0FG    
    
    
    Congrats to @ThePeerJ for winning the 2013 ALPSP Innovation Award! pic.twitter.com/XwJAv08i2h    
    
    
    @WillTullett Stay strong, brother. I hope it's going well!    
    
    
    @Mohamed_Dayem Unfortunately no Android app in the near future, but our users have had good experiences with Scholarley and Droideley.    
    
    
    @librarychirp Completely new iOS app (faster, prettier, more stable, tons of new features) will be released in the next few days!    
    
    
    @librarychirp Exactly :-)    
    
    
    @trentmkays @_rnbrewer Our users have had good experiences with Scholarley and Droideley - give them a try!    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall I did - just about to respond! Sorry for the delay!    
    
    
    @caseybergman @mrgunn @MikeTaylor Nothing has changed. We have always complied with DMCA takedown requests, as per http://www.mendeley.com/copyright/     
    
    
    @aglet I assume you wore a helmet this time. Stab vest next? Hope you're ok!    
    
    
    @aglet I didn't buy my spreadsheet-proof vest for nothing    
    
    
    @issnruede Super, die kleinen flauschigen Dinger!    
    
    
    @AndreaLiang91 @Lee_Sun08 Thank you - always great to hear nice things about our work :-)    
    
    
    @eb0la Sure - just contact community@mendeley.com!    
    
    
    @jenlrile Should be fixed in the next iOS release - already submitted to the App Store!    
    
    
    @jamaral Sounds like you have to change the citation style from number format to author-date format? cc @mendeleysupport    
    
    
    @jamaral Sorry, meant from author-date format (which is the default) to number format! cc @mendeleysupport    
    
    
    @jamaral Whether the ref is inserted as text or # is determined by the citation style; http://csl.mendeley.com  helps you find the right one    
    
    
    @jamaral @mendeleysupport will have a look on Monday!    
    
    
    @MegMacMichael Sorry to hear, very strange - do you perhaps store your Mendeley library in Dropbox? Can create conflicts. @mendeleysupport    
    
    
    @_PhilMartin @tomjwebb No current plans, but thinking about letting users make their article annotations public. Would be useful, no?    
    
    
    @tomjwebb @_PhilMartin Yes, would be opt-in. Technical barrier is not that high, but roadmap is packed with higher-priority items for now..    
    
    
    @seinecle We have engaged our Klingon battlecruiser cloaking device while we work on big things.    
    
    
    @SauberNick Apologies, very sorry to hear that - perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @ckatzenbach Tut mir Leid zu hören - darf ich fragen, woran es liegt? Was müssen wir besser machen? Danke für das Feedback!    
    
    
    @ckatzenbach Danke, sehr hilfreich. Sind gerade dabei, das Web UI komplett zu überarbeiten. Welche Ausgabeoptionen fehlen Dir?    
    
    
    @ckatzenbach Hilft http://csl.mendeley.com  (WYSIWYG CSL-Editor) eventuell? Ansonsten kann @mendeleysupport helfen, Ausgabestile anzupassen.    
    
    
    @jaimedash @jrossibarra @evolvability @michaelhoffman @Graham_Coop Yep, Mendeley Desktop gives you recommendations based on what you read!    
    
    
    @jaimedash @jrossibarra @evolvability @michaelhoffman @Graham_Coop In fact, you can select any set of papers to receive corresponding recs.    
    
    
    @JonoBone Not just him :-) http://blog.mendeley.com/start-up-life/from-climax-control-gel-to-german-shepherd-dogs-the-top-5-misspellings-of-mendeley/ …    
    
    
    @alicebonasio Always there in spirit!    
    
    
    @Jason_R_Berg @aclerktherwas Mendeley now has a WYSIWYG citation editor (http://csl.mendeley.com ), so perhaps give us another shot :-)    
    
    
    @haikus_by_KN @ShirazHaderach @ckunzelman @10rdBen @dangolding You can! :-) Open PDF in Mendeley, then "File - Export PDF with Annotations"    
    
    
    @haikus_by_KN @ShirazHaderach @ckunzelman @10rdBen @dangolding The last page of the exported PDF contains overview of all annotations    
    
    
    @haikus_by_KN @ShirazHaderach @ckunzelman @10rdBen @dangolding We're also working on making all annotations available via our API    
    
    
    @haikus_by_KN Agreed - should include highlighted text as well! I'll pass it on to the UX/desktop team.    
    
    
    @IanMulvany @aglet Late to this party, but I laughed about the Poland joke    
    
    
    @IanMulvany @aglet P.S. Driving a used Volvo now    
    
    
    @IanMulvany Grand :-) Love Amsterdam, it's a great place to be. But going back to Ireland for Xmas/New Years!    
    
    
    @IanMulvany In Dún Laoghaire? I'll be down in Naas with the in-laws :-)    
    
    
    @McDawg @Villavelius Closer to around 90m uniques now.    
    
    
    @IanMulvany Cool, would love to catch up!    
    
    
    @Villavelius @McDawg I think the 25% is mkt share of articles published annually. Estimate for all articles ever published is ~100m (or so)    
    
    
    @subcide @djhocking @thermalecology Plus, our data is open under a Creative Commons license: http://dev.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @barrywellman @mrgunn We have always provided full, unconditional data portability - via standard data export formats and our API.    
    
    
    @barrywellman @mrgunn @rvidal Sorry, that's not true. Mendeley is still run by the same team, our mission (and behavior) has not changed.    
    
    
    @barrywellman @mrgunn @rvidal And we do have influence on Elsevier's views as well, but change doesn't happen overnight.    
    
    
    @AnalyzerAimee We are hiring Android developers, but it's going to take some time... meanwhile, try Scholarley or Droideley?    
    
    
    @david_colquhoun @DavidPriceUCL It was not, fortunately. In the 5 days after acquisition, 250 people left, and 3,000 more than usual joined.    
    
    
    @melioravit Looks like someone needs to solve that problem! :-)    
    
    
    @alexqgb @zeynep I can confirm that I can't make @mrgunn say what I want :-) He has a long public record of opinion on OA, pre-Mendeley.    
    
    
    @alexqgb @zeynep Mendeley continues to work on making science more open in many ways (API, data access, sharing etc). Keep watching us.    
    
    
    @jimmylovestea @hjpimentel No one's going to fuck off until you point out specifically where we're *not* making science more open. Coz we do    
    
    
    @jimmylovestea Can you point to a single thing that we used to do, but are not doing anymore? Apart from doing it on gold-plated laptops now    
    
    
    @jimmylovestea So, all joking aside, Mendeley hasn't changed. In fact, we've made more Elsevier content openly available than before (1/2)    
    
    
    @jimmylovestea via previews of all articles & via our API. We try to push the company towards more openness, but it won't happen overnight.    
    
    
    @alexqgb @zeynep Mendeley has never been profitable, so I guess that makes us charitable :-) And how do *we* do harm? We push for openness.    
    
    
    @david_colquhoun @DavidPriceUCL I don't think we tried to keep it a secret? By the way, we weren't happy about 250 people leaving either.    
    
    
    @mrgunn @dandrezner Hey @zeynep, I wish you would stop twisting facts and words. It's unbecoming of a scientist.    
    
    
    @zeynep @mrgunn @dandrezner So, are you deliberately misquoting me, then? Big difference between what I said and what you claimed I said.    
    
    
    @zeynep @mrgunn @dandrezner I said "not profitable", you claimed I said "never made money" (thus, "no business model") - twisting my words.    
    
    
    @alexqgb @zeynep Lots of researchers, myself included, would disagree. IMHO copyright has a place, but authors should be free to choose OA.    
    
    
    @zeynep @mrgunn @dandrezner If you don't think there's a difference, I suggest an ECON 101 class. You can make a billion & not be profitable    
    
    
    @alexqgb @lteytelman @zeynep Noone's stopping you from publishing papers with a CC0 license on yr Mendeley profile (I'd be happy if you did)    
    
    
    @zeynep @mrgunn @dandrezner No, we weren't profitable, but on path to be with individual & institutional (MIT, Stanford etc) subscriptions    
    
    
    @Dymaxion @TomReller @zeynep That's a false & unfair accusation. Elsevier is not a monolith with uniform opinions. @mrgunn has always been..    
    
    
    @Dymaxion @TomReller @zeynep an OA advocate. There are plenty OA advocates (& OA journals) in Elsevier/Mendeley who try to push for change.    
    
    
    @Dymaxion @TomReller @zeynep @mrgunn I bid thee farewell.    
    
    
    @alexqgb Self-serving, career-related reasons which are entirely legitimate. Decision where to publish and/or commercialise - and thus (1/2)    
    
    
    @alexqgb which license to choose or whether to waive copyright/IP entirely - has to be the researcher's. Doesn't rule out advancing science.    
    
    
    @alexqgb Agreed. And US universities pull in about $2bn/yr in licensing revenue, so they wouldn't agree with getting rid of copyright either    
    
    
    @fellowsra @edfrenkel @profkeithdevlin It's been 9 months & we've only gotten better. More/cheaper storage space, bigger groups, new/free..    
    
    
    @fellowsra @edfrenkel @profkeithdevlin iOS app, integration with Scopus/ScienceDirect, new/better API still under CC license. More to come!    
    
    
    @pixievondust Working on it! You can also try Scholarley, Droideley, or PubChase.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TweeteRR Thank you :-)    
    
    
    Great news! Elsevier withdraws support for the Research Works Act: http://www.elsevier.com/wps/find/intro.cws_home/newmessagerwa …    
    
    
    @LiamPomfret @kayirowling Though all data is open under a Creative Commons license: http://dev.mendeley.com  :-)    
    
    
    @subcide @mrgunn @openscience @f1000research Indeed a  two million grant for semantic annotations. Wish it was 80 million :-)    
    
    
    Best endorsement ever! :-) RT @HeyItsDaijoubu: @TrevorDikes Mendeley is the bomb for academic gangsters looking to blow it up all raw like    
    
    
    Great fun yesterday at Oxford U panel on the Future of Academic Publishing with Tim Gowers, @CameronNeylon, and others pic.twitter.com/RCxuYjI3    
    
    
    @neuromusic very sorry! maybe @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @pilarcubas Sorry about that! That's not supposed to happen. Can you let @mendeleysupport more, so we can investigate? Thanks!    
    
    
    Mendeley is now available in @hojoki! Retweet this to win one of 10 t-shirts with the awesome Hojoki-Mendeley robot: http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-features/mendeley-now-available-in-hojoki/ …    
    
    
    @subcide @hojoki I want one, too!    
    
    
    Mendeley friends: Please vote for us at the People's Choice Award of the London Web Summit! http://www.websummit.net/nominee/vote/     
    
    
    @swiftj Your wish is fulfilled - check out @KinSyncApp / http://www.kinsync.com/  :-)    
    
    
    @pixievondust Very sorry - we're still experiencing server issues. We're on it.    
    
    
    @InvasiveNotes Sorry about that. We're experiencing server issues - should be back in a few minutes.    
    
    
    Young Mendeleyans - check out the the Young Researchers in Life Sciences congress in Paris: http://yrls.fr  (via @suvidu @YRLS2012)    
    
    
    "Why I am leaving Goldman Sachs": http://www.nytimes.com/2012/03/14/opinion/why-i-am-leaving-goldman-sachs.html?pagewanted=1&_r=2 …; "Why I am leaving The Empire, by Darth Vader": http://www.thedailymash.co.uk/news/society/why-i-am-leaving-the-empire,-by-darth-vader-201203145007/ …    
    
    
    @theronkelso Sorry, there isn't right now - but it could be built by anyone, by using our API: http://dev.mendeley.com     
    
    
    JISC Report (incl. Mendeley): Text mining promises huge economic/research benefit, but copyright law is limiting it: http://www.jisc.ac.uk/publications/reports/2012/value-and-benefits-of-text-mining.aspx …    
    
    
    "Open Science and the Future of Publishing" - a recording of the Oxford U panel I participated in three weeks ago: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yELZ3kbFj1w&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Just made this slide for a presentation & thought I'd share: Mendeley user love! All tweets are from the last 6 weeks: pic.twitter.com/f5eDdzHn    
    
    
    Team Mendeley at London Web Summit today! pic.twitter.com/h8W0zDOD    
    
    
    @TheNeuroNetwork @mendeleytips Seen this? :-) https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=10150641568343611&set=a.10150156999648611.291608.42920143610&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    @TheNeuroNetwork Thanks! This might also be of interest: http://www.google.com/trends/?q=mendeley,+researchgate,+academia.edu …    
    
    
    @hojoki Your t-shirts arrived today - thanks guys! They're proving very popular, so if you could send some more, we'd wear them proudly :-)    
    
    
    Hell yeah! RT @tpoi: I'm a @mendeley_com advisor now, and I'll advise the sh*t out of my university!    
    
    
    @GianninaRossini Too smug? ;-) I'll blame the wine they gave us before the panel!    
    
    
    @adinalav Very sorry - what kind of messages are they? Messages from other users, or from Mendeley?    
    
    
    @adinalav Apologies - that sounds like a bug. Could you forward one of them to support@mendeley.com, so we can look into it? Thanks!    
    
    
    @SayBeano Mendeley can auto-generate BibTeX entries from your document library, so it works great with LaTeX :-)    
    
    
    @trentyarwood Check out @droideley and #scholarley - both native Android apps for Mendeley!    
    
    
    Ha! Last paper of my PhD thesis was accepted for publication today - 3 years after first submission. Didn't see that one coming!    
    
    
    @briankelly Apologies! We're working on a "flag this user" feature and also have internal alerts, so @mendeleysupport should be on the case!    
    
    
    @MattWatermeyer Very sorry! Can you send more info to @mendeleysupport, so we can help? Thanks!    
    
    
    @grace_baynes Thanks! Glad you liked it! #stm2012    
    
    
    @ScottAtSpringer I agree! #STM2012    
    
    
    Great review of Mendeley/PLoS Binary Battle winner OpenSNP: http://www.genomesunzipped.org/2012/05/a-review-of-opensnp-a-platform-to-share-genetic-data.php …    
    
    
    Disgusting. Groupon now sells doctorate degrees: http://www.groupon.de/deals/online-deal/doktortitel-kaufende/5740776?nlp&CID=DE_CRM_1_0_0_135&a=1655 …    
    
    
    @easternblot Apologetics!    
    
    
    @tpoi Apologies! Can you please send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can try to fix this? Thanks!    
    
    
    @ZachTocchi Could you please send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can try to help? Thanks!    
    
    
    @awaisathar Social networking is a subset of our functionality. We're primarily about research workflow management and collaboration :-)    
    
    
    Open Access gets an €80 billion boost from EU: http://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/story.asp?storycode=419949 …    
    
    
    Welcome aboard! RT @omphe: Thrilled to announce that today I joined the Mendeley team as VP of Product. http://www.mendeley.com/  #fb    
    
    
    Yeah, why? - Eric Schmidt's talk at Science Museum about to start! pic.twitter.com/i1LRTMnu    
    
    
    Cool! Eric Schmidt just gave a shout-out to Mendeley as one of the tools that are making research more social! pic.twitter.com/WNWDGUSb    
    
    
    Our friends at @Symplectic_UK are announcing the forthcoming Mendeley module for Symplectic Elements: http://www.symplectic.co.uk/news-events/2012/05/16/dura-project-with-mendeley-and-caret/ …    
    
    
    @knodeinc Cool - let me know more!    
    
    
    Another interesting study from York University linking Mendeley readership stats to citation counts: http://yfile.news.yorku.ca/2012/06/06/business-librarian-validates-altmetrics-for-research-impact-evaluation/ …    
    
    
    800000 #fishfight supporters are watching you @RichardBenyonMP! Restore fish stocks & end discards @hughsfishfight @ClientEarth    
    
    
    EU Commissioner Neelie Kroes: Let's make science open - https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=6sJbi2eaPXc …    
    
    
    Visiting friends in Ireland; they have a photo in their kitchen which accidentally contains the Mendeley NY office: pic.twitter.com/X1Iwbru5    
    
    
    In Montpellier for ABES library event. Presenting the Mendeley Institutional Edition later! pic.twitter.com/0PSS0pUz    
    
    
    @sasbongo Very sorry to hear that! What went wrong? Can @mendeleysupport help?    
    
    
    The future of transportation looks awesome: http://www.litmotors.com  (it comes with a Joy Division soundtrack, always a winner). / @LitMotors    
    
    
    @IanMulvany Congrats!! If we had baby-sized Mendeley t-shirts, you'd get one :-)    
    
    
    @xtaldave Sorry, no official Android app, but there are a number of third-party Android apps for Mendeley (e.g. Scholarley and Droideley).    
    
    
    Since @stylistpick moved out of our office yesterday, a few Mendeleyans are making somewhat excessive use of the space http://campl.us/kCnG     
    
    
    @heatonjb We are indeed! Drop me a line at victor dot henning at mendeley dot com.    
    
    
    Just spoke at #findbetterproblems - good fun! http://instagram.com/p/M80SI7vl3x/     
    
    
    CODE research grant meeting in our office today! Goal: crowdsourcing zebras (and science) http://campl.us/kJEU     
    
    
    @cwaring @sleepio @johannakoll @brownsdon @underwoodemily @joescarboro Thanks all!    
    
    
    That belongs in here http://www.mendeley.com/groups/536621/creatively-named-research-papers/papers … MT @jenvalentino Jay-Z's "99 Problems" provides lessons on the 4th Amendment: http://bit.ly/LEKeTq     
    
    
    @jaleh_f There are number of third-party apps for Mendeley, though - check out Droideley or Scholarley!    
    
    
    Great article by @iansample in The Guardian: http://www.guardian.co.uk/science/2012/jul/15/free-access-british-scientific-research …. This is huge news, also for our 3rd-party research app developers!    
    
    
    @mikebutcher Great news - and thanks for the shout-out!    
    
    
    Cool interview with @scienceexchange on our blog: http://blog.mendeley.com/mendeley-use-case/another-science-startup-thats-changing-how-research-is-done-an-interview-with-elizabeth-iorns-of-science-exchange/ …    
    
    
    @Thomas_Gutjahr Sorry about that. Major update in the works!    
    
    
    @CameronNeylon Coming up next: Peer reviews to decide whether Mendeley Desktop will accept an article into your document library!    
    
    
    @astefanowitsch @coffee001 Mendeley hat auch eine Zotero-Sync-Funktion: Alles was man in Z. speichert, wird direkt auch in M. übernommen.    
    
    
    @MattB_UK @magpie @debbiefuco @greenjenniferb Sorry, that must be a misunderstanding - Zotero and Mendeley are separate entities.    
    
    
    @eileentso How about dragging scientific research/data kicking and screaming into a future-y webby future :-)    
    
    
    New t-shirt / underpant slogan! RT @subcide "Mendeley, the future-y webby future of research" <- I like it. (cc: @eileentso)    
    
    
    @jesperht Careful! Looks like someone licked that burger bun!    
    
    
    @barrywellman @dirkvl @Amanda_Lenhart Trust is good, desktop app with local backups plus Open APIs are better: http://dev.mendeley.com  :-)    
    
    
    @dirkvl Yes, it is! Schönen Abend gleichfalls :-)    
    
    
    @peyron @NextScientist Thanks for the nice write-up!    
    
    
    Stanford University Libraries announce campus-wide rollout of Mendeley: http://librarypreview.stanford.edu/news/2012/08/join-us-road-mendeley-workshop-library-staff …    
    
    
    University of Pittsburgh adopts Mendeley campus licence, replacing RefWorks: http://www.hsls.pitt.edu/news/mendeley     
    
    
    @erikmstp Go to main folder "Radiography Lit.", click the "Edit Settings" button in middle pane, tick "Download attached files from group"    
    
    
    @erikmstp You're welcome! :-)    
    
    
    @friendly_rock http://librarypreview.stanford.edu/news/2012/08/join-us-road-mendeley-workshop-library-staff … :-)    
    
    
    Rat Overlords! MT @TomChivers: Petri-dish-grown culture of rat brain cells can fly a simulated F-22 fighter jet http://news.discovery.com/tech/brain-dish-flies-plane-041022.html …    
    
    
    Mendeley featured in the Lifehacker Student Edition for Windows (http://ow.ly/cX6J8 ) and Mac (http://ow.ly/cX6Kh )!    
    
    
    @Melissa_Loy Thank you! Happy to hear
that Mendeley was helpful!    
    
    
    With today's update, Mendeley Desktop now supports 2,728 citation styles, up from 1,600! Also, WYSIWYG citation style editor coming soon...    
    
    
    @sjcockell Personally, I wish we wouldn't have to support thousands of citation styles - but as long as journals keep demanding them..    
    
    
    @MKTitsworth It's a server-side update. Should be available in your Mendeley Desktop right now!    
    
    
    P.S. On now supporting 2,728 citation styles: http://xkcd.com/927/     
    
    
    @samusb Thank you! :-) More cool news coming up in the near future.    
    
    
    @geoffwatts That's weird. We had the same awful kerosene / diesel smell over in Primrose Hill at that time!    
    
    
    @phylogenomics Apologies! You can change which actions trigger tweets under My Account > Sharing / Importing.    
    
    
    @phylogenomics Oh - you changed the settings but it still tweeted? If so, would you mind sending more info to support@mendeley.com?    
    
    
    @phylogenomics Ok, thanks. Sorry again for the hassle!    
    
    
    @bobbiejohnson @majohns I'll be there! Spoke at a previous Future Human event about science; really loved it.    
    
    
    @bobbiejohnson: Thank you! Really appreciate it.    
    
    
    At the #futurehuman Smash Publishing event. People in the picture: This is what you look like from behind. pic.twitter.com/2m93LJ6V    
    
    
    Yes, I did! And thanks :-) RT @Stephen_Curry: @mendeley_com Such a great THE story… ;-) Also seen this? http://occamstypewriter.org/scurry/2012/08/13/sick-of-impact-factors/ …    
    
    
    Goodbye Neil! http://ow.ly/i/SE3y     
    
    
    Mendeley news on Times Square, NY:  http://ow.ly/i/TgDs     
    
    
    Insightful: "The unsuccessful self-treatment of a case of writer's block", Journal of Applied Behavioral Analysis: http://ow.ly/dsmFw     
    
    
    @yukop That is amazing!! I'd love to add it to our official press photos (http://www.flickr.com/photos/mendeley/sets/72157630652171616/ …), with credit to you - would that be ok?    
    
    
    I think we have a new slogan: "Mendeley - like caffeine for your research!" Awesome #geeklatte photo by @yukop: http://ow.ly/i/UwUU     
    
    
    Guardian guest post by @mrgunn & myself: "Impact factor: researchers should define the metrics that matter to them" http://www.guardian.co.uk/higher-education-network/blog/2012/sep/06/mendeley-altmetrics-open-access-publishing …    
    
    
    @JacobShiach @Stephen_Curry Thanks!    
    
    
    @kimberlyhogg Thanks! Enjoyed it!    
    
    
    Gave a talk at the Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology today. Check out the banner! http://ow.ly/i/VpfB     
    
    
    Team @OxfordJournals, Team @Tandfonline, and Team Mendeley discussing publishing over beer and soju! pic.twitter.com/2eZyhMHD    
    
    
    Financial Times feature on Mendeley - great photo of my co-founder @janerixo: http://ow.ly/1OvtPi     
    
    
    @pelf81 @mattwargent Mendeley is not just web-based: We have desktop software that syncs across Windows, Mac, Linux (and iOS / Android)!    
    
    
    @SQFPinfo We'll take "<3"! Or a simple link to http://www.mendeley.com  :-) Thanks! (cc @mendeleysupport)    
    
    
    Mendeley Advisor Appreciation Day! Advisors from all over the UK visiting Mendeley HQ pic.twitter.com/kQ81Nt2A    
    
    
    Pizza for all at Mendeley Advisor Appreciation Day! pic.twitter.com/Q4SB4kLn    
    
    
    Mendeley Advisor World Map - thank you to all our Advisors for helping us make science more open! pic.twitter.com/uthWqw0D    
    
    
    @adam42smith @fheimburger @laspic Mendeley does have a feature to export your PDFs including annotations to share with non-Mendeley users.    
    
    
    Amazing summary of the Mendeley Advisor Appreciation Day by Andy Tattersall @scharrlib: http://scharrlibrary.blogspot.co.uk/2012/09/mendelely-advisors-appreciation-day.html …. Thanks Andy!    
    
    
    Butterfly under the doorbell of @Whitebearyard pic.twitter.com/vC03IqHN    
    
    
    @SeanALibby I hear you - very soon!    
    
    
    @addy_dren Yes - try http://www.kinsync.com/  (@kinsync)!    
    
    
    @LSmonster You can sign up for a Mendeley profile without using our software :-)    
    
    
    @OC_org @whitebearyard Took the pic with my iPhone 4S, then cropped/edited in Snapseed :-)    
    
    
    @IanMulvany @subcide @omphe @phpeach Sorry, I'm out of town for a conference!    
    
    
    @OC_org @whitebearyard Thanks!!    
    
    
    @suewolff Here are some tweets :-) http://Twitter.com/Mendeley_com/favorites …    
    
    
    My interview @figshare: #Mendeley, Times Square and Number 10 Downing Street http://shar.es/5U2nX  #openscience #openaccess    
    
    
    @erikreinertsen Yes - completely new version coming soon!    
    
    
    @PlanktonMath Very sorry about that. Brand new iPad app coming soon!    
    
    
    @josmel1 @keitabando @planktonmath iPhone and iPad!    
    
    
    View over foggy Westminster at this morning's copyright symposium at Dept for Business, Innovation & Skills pic.twitter.com/1mCEzimA    
    
    
    @BobOHara We all wore party hats    
    
    
    @whatterz Apologies - you should have received a notification! Perhaps @mendeleysupport can help? Sorry again for the inconvenience!    
    
    
    @mika_jo Sorry about that - in which respect? Perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @mika_jo In Mendeley Desktop or Mendeley Web? Could you send an example to @MendeleySupport? Thanks for your feedback, really appreciate it!    
    
    
    @sofiambg Thank you! Appreciate it!    
    
    
    Great Physics Today feature on #OpenAccess by @starbird2005. Mendeley API also gets a mention. http://www.physicstoday.org/resource/1/phtoad/v65/i11/p22_s1?bypassSSO=1 …    
    
    
    @sarcozona New iPad app coming soon!    
    
    
    @benjrooney What about pitches about academic startups? I hear they're good :-) Great article about the Govt's Open Data strategy, btw.    
    
    
    @Richvn The data seems to suggest otherwise - why else would the #papers accessed by researchers be linked to R&D spend so closely? (1/2)    
    
    
    @Richvn I doubt that scholars in developing countries *want* to access fewer papers, so s.th. must be limiting them. What's your take? (2/2)    
    
    
    @Richvn Interesting thought - then who's to blame for the lack of awareness? Libraries? Also, perhaps top journals like Nature have OA (1/2)    
    
    
    @Richvn ..option, but the long tail of journals doesn't? (2/2)    
    
    
    @Richvn Re: R&D spend = lower research activity: Probably true to some extent, but daily activity time much less influenced by R&D spend.    
    
    
    @Richvn Appreciate your thoughts! We don't have the answers either - it was our best stab at interpreting the data. Cheers!    
    
    
    @Kobrako Sure - send me an email! victor.henning@mendeley.com    
    
    
    Mendeley's Global Research Report (http://mnd.ly/VtjPPM ) on Times Square, NY pic.twitter.com/c4U2PlWv    
    
    
    @becky_rtw I can email you the data tables in Excel format in case you're interested!    
    
    
    @becky_rtw Yes, would've liked to include data tables on our microsite (http://www.mendeley.com/global-research-report …), just didn't get around to it :-)    
    
    
    @SarahRHarrison @floraMbartlett @JessieBluebell Very sorry to hear that! Perhaps our community team (@mrgunn, @rvidal) can help?    
    
    
    @floraMbartlett Glad to hear you got it sorted. Let our community team know if you need any further help!    
    
    
    @jeffreycrow Really sorry about that. We're aware of the issue - new iOS app coming soon!    
    
    
    My girlfriend @michelle_phelan (voc) and @TechCrunch's @mikebutcher (drums) together in the track “Little Wolf” http://carosel.bandcamp.com/track/little-wolf …    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall Yes, sure! Please go ahead! :-)    
    
    
    @michelle_phelan @midem @unicum_music Disrupt your own guitar!!!    
    
    
    @ptreadwell Have a look at @hojoki perhaps?    
    
    
    @HiddenPeanuts Actually, the US is our largest userbase - about 18% of users. UK comes second with about 10%.    
    
    
    @IanMulvany @Stew @jasonpriem @figshare Hi all - unfortunately, I can't do either date, but Jan could do the 3rd!    
    
    
    Some cool new videos showcasing the data dashboard of Mendeley Institutional Edition: http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL2B61A6BB62DF9D4A …    
    
    
    In-depth interview with the eLife team on the Mendeley blog: http://blog.mendeley.com/open-access/interview-with-elife-a-new-tech-forward-openaccess-journal/ …    
    
    
    @kristisan What do you feel is missing from Mendeley? Appreciate your feedback - thanks!    
    
    
    @kristisan You can print notes: While viewing a PDF document, go to File > Export PDF with Annotations. Notes will be appended to the (1/2)    
    
    
    @kristisan PDF file, and you can print it from any other PDF viewer. Re: the crashes, very sorry to hear that! Are you running the (2/3)    
    
    
    @kristisan latest version? If you send more info to support@mendeley.com, we can try to figure out what's going on. Thanks! (3/3)    
    
    
    @jemimah_knight Awesome shot!    
    
    
    @kristisan The notes are all appended at the end of the PDF document, so you could only print the last few pages containing the notes.    
    
    
    @iansample @ECspokesScience Europe currently leading the world in access to research papers and daily research time: http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-life/mendeley-has-two-million-users-to-celebrate-were-releasing-the-global-research-report/ …    
    
    
    My Interview on Scientific American blogs by @Hadas_Shema: http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/information-culture/2012/11/23/interview-with-dr-victor-henning-mendeley/ …    
    
    
    @egonwillighagen @ImpactStory @rkiddr Strange! Could you please send the info to support@mendeley.com, so we can investigate? Thanks!    
    
    
    @roxannevarza I would happily speak about big data in academia/science!    
    
    
    @gigaseal Very sorry to hear you're experiencing issues - could you send details to support@mendeley.com so we can try to fix them? Thanks!    
    
    
    Awesome! One of Mendeley's investors (Jaan Tallinn) is now part of a Cambridge Doomwatch team to save the world: http://www.engadget.com/2012/11/26/cambridge-existential-risk/ …    
    
    
    @SianHarris8 Engagdet probably didn't mean that those fields were fringes, but rather that the fringes of those fields would be investigated    
    
    
    @jasonpriem @IanMulvany @Stew @figshare You'll have to go old-school and email Jan with time/date - he's not active on Twitter :-)    
    
    
    @fsayre Yes, people are using it for systematic reviews - particularly using the collaborative PDF annotation function!    
    
    
    @raulpacheco @EndNoteNews Since our latest 1.7 release, Mendeley has a WYSIWYG citation style editor: http://csl.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @pixievondust @TriploidTree @IrishTimes Everybody should get the name of their company added as a first name! Aldous Huxley would approve!    
    
    
    @onekind @stephx You can use both together: Mendeley has a Zotero-sync function (as well as cite-as-you-write in Word/OO and BibTex support)    
    
    
    @mark_carrigan I'm not skeptical at all about expertise - but about identifying it lazily by virtue of their academic position #lseimpact    
    
    
    @commutiny I'm not skeptical at all about expertise - but about identifying it lazily by virtue of their academic position #lseimpact    
    
    
    @cubanba @congabonga Charts may not match your taste, but labels not being gatekeeper to who can distribute music widely = good #lseimpact    
    
    
    @jfurfey Info on semantically linked data set project here: http://code-research.eu/  #lseimpact    
    
    
    @WarrenPearce Quite simple: Premium / team collaboration accounts (http://www.mendeley.com/upgrade/ ), institutional licensing (http://www.swets.com/mendeley-institutional-edition …).    
    
    
    @mark_carrigan Agreed! Hence not all crowdsourced annotations will be treated as equal - there will be markers (e.g. academic status, ..    
    
    
    @mark_carrigan .. research background, impact based on publications/readership). More data = more criteria for people to assign trust.    
    
    
    The three Mendeley founders spreading Christmas cheer in the office - courtesy of @JessReeves1! pic.twitter.com/CPyMrPOz    
    
    
    @mark_carrigan It was a heated discussion :-)    
    
    
    @stochastician New iOS app coming soon!    
    
    
    @DrLabRatOry New iOS app coming soon!    
    
    
    @altmetric @IanMulvany Looking good!    
    
    
    @nulliusinverba @jasonpriem http://code-research.eu     
    
    
    @kesloane @raulpacheco In EndNote, export your library as .xml (not .enl, which is a proprietary format). Mendeley can import EndNote XML.    
    
    
    @lpsavoie Not anymore! We've just released a visual citation style editor: http://csl.mendeley.com/about/     
    
    
    I just added my own publication: 'Interview with Victor' http://mnd.ly/SSRfVO     
    
    
    @subcide Ha, forgot about the auto-tweet! Was just testing something :-)    
    
    
    @whatterz Yes - if you're using Android phones/tablets, we recommend using 3rd-party apps like Droideley or Scholarley.    
    
    
    @whatterz We are considering it for next year. Also, new API methods coming soon will make 3rd-party apps much more powerful.    
    
    
    @Eetezadi Our API will allow annotation/comment syncing early next year!    
    
    
    @RottenCapital Yes, you will be able to retrieve/create your own annotations via our API!    
    
    
    @karlita_dDios Yes, I'm one of the founders of Mendeley - but we are now a team of 40!    
    
    
    @karlita_dDios Thank you!! I'll pass it on to the team :-)    
    
    
    @liljefred Sorry about that - new iPad version coming soon!    
    
    
    @dittlebird Sorry about that. You can change the citation style rules using http://csl.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @Viil Apologies - what bug is it? Perhaps @MendeleySupport can help?    
    
    
    @erikreinertsen New iOS App is already in closed beta testing, will come in January!    
    
    
    @liljefred Yes, it will support sub-folders!    
    
    
    @eagereyes Very sorry - could you send more details to support@mendeley.com, so we can investigate? Thanks for letting us know!    
    
    
    @drlawson Considering it. Are already improving our API so that 3rd party apps (e.g. Scholarley or Droideley) can access notes/highlights.    
    
    
    @KennKnowles Mendeley can automatically generate/update BibTeX files that stay in sync with your document library.    
    
    
    @Jobium Christmas party hangover? Joking aside - sorry about that! Could you send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can check?    
    
    
    @dullhunk @mfenner @nuin @srp Full story: Our Open API is more full-featured & allows two-way sync, unlike the separate API .. (1/2)    
    
    
    @dullhunk @mfenner @nuin @srp .. @CiteULike has been using. We ask everyone to use the Open API so we only need to maintain one. (2/2)    
    
    
    @brinxmat @danbri We're just going to retire the private API @CiteULike are using & asked them to use our (more full-featured) public API.    
    
    
    @rafaelsidi CiteULike sync is using an outdated private API which we'll retire; we've asked them to move to our public Open API instead.    
    
    
    @rmounce @citeulike @rafaelsidi Sorry, should've been clearer. We're retiring private sync methods and APIs for our Desktop and iOS apps..    
    
    
    @rmounce @citeulike @rafaelsidi ..in order to move everything, including our own apps, to our public APIs. This will make it easier for..    
    
    
    @rmounce @citeulike @rafaelsidi ..us to support 3rd party devs and give them the same capabilities as our own apps (2-way sync, notes etc).    
    
    
    Happy New Year, Mendeley community! Wishing you a successful 2013 with all the research results you're hoping for!    
    
    
    @markhawker That day is coming soon :-)    
    
    
    @cdsouthan @egonwillighagen CUL sync relies on outdated private (and 1-way) API; we want to move everything to our Open API (2-way) instead.    
    
    
    @blkmage Sorry about that - new iOS app coming soon!    
    
    
    @DavidScaduto New iOS app already in beta testing and coming soon!    
    
    
    @DrJohnCosgrove @DrPlumEU There are third-party Mendeley plugins for inserting references in Wordpress and Drupal: http://dev.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @carusb @rmounce Mendeley does read PDF XMP metadata, but it's frequently noisy/incorrect, so we check it against other signals.    
    
    
    @ElleCovell Sorry, we're not the developers of Droideley, it's a 3rd-party app! As an alternative, have you tried Scholarley?    
    
    
    @ShintaroSato @mendeleyAPI That's coming soon!    
    
    
    @ToxTalks Yes, we do have a citation plugin for Word on Mac!    
    
    
    @raulpacheco Thanks for the feedback - can you clarify what you mean with the citation output?    
    
    
    @raulpacheco Have you seen our WYSIWYG citation style editor at http://csl.mendeley.com ? It should let you configure this as you wish.    
    
    
    @raulpacheco Thanks - happy we were able to help :-)    
    
    
    @raulpacheco We're working on letting users define their own document types :-)    
    
    
    @O2 Any broadband issues in Primrose Hill (NW1)? My home internet connection has been intermittently disappearing for the past 2-3 days.    
    
    
    @O2 Yes, wireless router. Tried rebooting and resetting. DSL light is flashing - can't seem to get DSL signal. Internet gone completely now.    
    
    
    @jmlaforge Could you send the document to support@mendeley.com, so we can have a look where the highlighting fails? Thanks!    
    
    
    @ythuky Can you please send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can take a closer look? Thanks!    
    
    
    @ythuky I'll ask them to check again.    
    
    
    @ythuky Hi Ythuky, the support team can't find an email from that address or with your name - could you please re-send it? Thank you!    
    
    
    @uhrenbacher Danke für die Weihnachtskarte übrigens :-) Sehen wir uns bei DLD oder The Europas?    
    
    
    Mendeley in the Financial Times today: http://ow.ly/gMM3A     
    
    
    @soniaahhh There is a WYSIWYG CSL editor at http://csl.mendeley.com     
    
    
    @Recher_she Thanks for the reminder - noted :-) New iOS app is already in beta testing, will come soon!    
    
    
    @soniaahhh Yes - as determined by the citation style you choose (and it can also be formatted using the CSL Editor).    
    
    
    @soniaahhh The Nature & IEEE styles have numbered in-text citations - does it not work for you? Also, Mendeley is currently at version 1.7.    
    
    
    Join @mrgunn, @researchremix, @researchtrendy for "The Individual and Scholarly Network" 2-part seminar: http://reedelsevier.reg.meeting-stream.com/researchtrends_elsevierlabs/ … #scholnet12    
    
    
    @darrenmackay @MendeleySupport We feel your pain. Brand-new, rewritten-from-scratch iOS app is coming soon and already in beta testing.    
    
    
    @TheEuropas Whoohoo! Thanks everyone! Gutted we couldn't make it because of the weather!    
    
    
    Whoohoo! RT @TheEuropas: And the winners of Best Startup Founders are Jan Reichelt, Paul Foeckler & Victor Henning of Mendeley! #TheEuropas    
    
    
    Jan, Paul, and I just won the award for Best Startup Founders in Europe at #TheEuropas in Berlin! http://ow.ly/i/1plZV ...    
    
    
    @ewancarr Psychedelic! Could you please send more info to support@mendeley.com, so we can have a look? Thanks!    
    
    
    @KrisPorterDPT New Mendeley iOS app, rewritten from scratch, with faster sync and annotations/highlights, coming soon! #bestPTapps    
    
    
    @nickrw I know - was digging through the @Postbox settings to see if I could change them... but GMail web UI is sloooow for me!    
    
    
    @KarenODonoghue @michelle_phelan Thanks :-)    
    
    
    @amyewest You can export PDFs with annotations from Mendeley, so they'll show up in Evernote!    
    
    
    @IanMulvany Ha, me too. Looks like it will be another just-in-time delivery.    
    
    
    @iheartlineart Yes, we do!    
    
    
    @jakubdostal @Patered @matt_j_miller Mendeley actually syncs with Kindle, via 3rd party app http://www.kinsync.com/     
    
    
    @Patered Not sure - I believe notes on Kindle are in proprietary format? Our API does have the ability to sync your Mendeley notes.    
    
    
    @RBrownSalazar @adam42smith The recommendation engine is only available to Mendeley Premium subscribers and Advisors (for now; might change)    
    
    
    @Recher_she Please get in touch with @subcide - he might be able to help :-)    
    
    
    @VenusLeyenda Yes - if you add the notes to a document in a group, the other members in the group can see them.    
    
    
    @Stevancw @timrittman You mean, different colored highlights? That's planned, more info here: http://feedback.mendeley.com/forums/4941-general/suggestions/273284-making-it-possible-to-highlight-text-with-differen#comments …    
    
    
    @Stevancw Interesting thought! I'll share it with our UX team. Thanks!    
    
    
    @CenterSuccess Apologies - we chose today because it's a public holiday in the US. Very sorry that it interfered with your class!    
    
    
    @taavet Us? :-)    
    
    
    The website and syncing will be unavailable for maintenance from 10am GMT tomorrow for around two hours. Sorry for any inconvenience!    
    
    
    @CClements88 Fear not! We shall return in a few minutes, with backend upgrades that have made us stronger!    
    
    
    @prezi Eh.. did your editing toolbar just change? I can't find the freehand drawing tool anymore? pic.twitter.com/hEhB2Q5D    
    
    
    @prezi ..and the ability to turn elements into Library Objects is gone too?    
    
    
    @n0v0id Doch, das geht auf Deinem Mendeley-Profil - siehe z.B. http://www.mendeley.com/profiles/victor-henning/ …    
    
    
    @jmlaforge That's awesome!    
    
    
    @gertsenmsnv6 Brand-new iPad app coming soon! @subcide can tell you whether there are beta testing spots available.    
    
    
    @davidleetalk2me @sofi_nas Went there with @michelle_phelan a couple of weeks ago. Lovely food!    
    
    
    @James_Wheldon Sorry about that. New iPad app with annotations sync coming soon!    
    
    
    @mefunk Thank you - my pleasure :-)    
    
    
    @gendalus Sorry - komplett neu entwickelte iOS App ist schon im Beta-Testing und kommt bald!    
    
    
    @costrike @GlobalEcoGuy @mbeisen For a Mendeley-Kindle integration, try http://www.kinsync.com  :-)    
    
    
    @hossiet @sc_evans Have you tried one of the third-party Android apps, e.g. Scholarley or Droideley? Other users have said good things!    
    
    
    @KinSyncApp You're welcome - we're happy there are apps like KinSync! :-)    
    
    
    @rbizzlesticks Thank you!    
    
    
    @MichaelTsielepi Very sorry to hear you're having problems. Maybe @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    Owl sighting at Mendeley HQ! This owl will run a cancer charity half-marathon, please donate: http://www.justgiving.com/Matthew-Green14  pic.twitter.com/MQ39N9RSSn    
    
    
    @sarahkendrew Yeay! Good luck!    
    
    
    @raulpacheco Yes, absolutely! Photos in our Flickr account are CC-BY by default.    
    
    
    @ariannabetti Sorry, that might be a bug - your group allowances shouldn't have changed. Perhaps community@mendeley.com can help?    
    
    
    @michellehudson Yes - both in Mendeley Desktop and Mendeley Web, you can filter your documents by one or multiple tags (cc @mrgunn).    
    
    
    @michalboo @AndrewOfficer @mrgunn But on Flickr! http://www.flickr.com/photos/mendeley/sets/72157624898905520/ …    
    
    
    Getting ready to speak about "Mendeley and Altmetrics" at University of Granada seminar #giec3 pic.twitter.com/K5b04rFEBU    
    
    
    @jae3goals @gfyar You can easily edit the citation style at http://csl.mendeley.com  - hope that helps!    
    
    
    Loving @davidleetalk2me's hackday project! pic.twitter.com/uuRtQeSYmz    
    
    
    @flipphillips Sorry - we do care! It's just always difficult juggling dev priorities. What exactly is the bibtex issue?    
    
    
    @flipphillips Perhaps you could get in touch with our desktop developers directly, to explain what exactly is needed? desktop@mendeley.com    
    
    
    @flipphillips Thanks, I see - will poke to desktop team to review this!    
    
    
    @ThomasPRoland @robknight_ You can merge authors by dragging & dropping names onto each other in the "Filter by Authors" box (bottom left).    
    
    
    @ThomasPRoland @robknight_ We've started work on that, but I don't yet know when we can roll it out.    
    
    
    @Artandmylife That's awesome! Thank you!    
    
    
    @bgamari Sorry to hear - what was it that didn't work for you?    
    
    
    @bgamari Thanks for the feedback - much appreciated. Sorry to see that the support team couldn't help. Maybe see you again in the future!    
    
    
    @PatParslow Glad to hear that :-)    
    
    
    @Zay_017 Very sorry - perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @neuromusic @mrgunn @ResearchBlogs There are plugins for Wordpress and Drupal already which pull citations from the Mendeley API.    
    
    
    @vickytnz On the contrary - we're doubling the available storage space for free!    
    
    
    @simoncolumbus @mrgunn Will be a boost - great new features that weren't possible before in the pipeline!    
    
    
    @gedankenstuecke @mrgunn Thank you - we won't disappoint :-)    
    
    
    @simoncolumbus Thanks - that's indeed what's planned!    
    
    
    @markhawker Actually, no cleverness intended :-) There currently is a free version, and there always will be - what else could it mean?    
    
    
    @markhawker @amcunningham Just a few weeks away now!    
    
    
    @markhawker @amcunningham From last week :-)    
    
    
    @elizabethiorns Thanks Liz!    
    
    
    @vitauria Thank you! Yes, I'll be there :-)    
    
    
    @Kolvin @orrick @torchpartners Thanks all!    
    
    
    @querolus @jesusmendezzz @versvs Mendeley & our OAPI will remain free and open: Still under a CC-BY license, more/cleaner/richer data.    
    
    
    @querolus @jesusmendezzz @versvs I believe this opens additional opportunities and represents a further step by Elsevier towards openness.    
    
    
    @wilbanks Thanks John. We're still pushing for open data; will use E. data to clean/enrich/complete our API data, still under CC-BY.    
    
    
    @TorchPartners Thank you for helping us see this through from start to finish!    
    
    
    @SianHarris8 I had a ticket for that, too, but something got in the way :-)    
    
    
    @FakeElsevier You gotta admit those hats say YOLO    
    
    
    @futurehumanista Thank you!    
    
    
    @marylgray @phenatypical In my mind, the Open API under a Creative Commons CC-BY license does - and we'll keep expanding it!    
    
    
    @marlenc Thank you - likewise!    
    
    
    @gregladen @mrgunn We won't let you down!    
    
    
    @Elisotope @dambrodebarcola @LabSpaces @mrgunn When we started everyone doubted that 3 PhD students could have influence on the industry :-)    
    
    
    @marylgray We'll move more features from the paid to the free version soon. But hope you understand we also have to pay our staff somehow!    
    
    
    liked:  "Documents added 'The Expression of Emotions in 20th Century Books'" http://mnd.ly/ZMxpKw     
    
    
    @richardewest Sorry, no - I don't say that publishers will become redundant, but talk about where to look for new business opportunities.    
    
    
    @nniiicc Our goal is to create more of those A-HA moments in the future, including bigger/better/more open groups and a follower model.    
    
    
    @davemcclure Thanks Dave - much appreciated :-)    
    
    
    @drdrAatBLC @rvidal I don't see any sharks with laser beams on their head in our office yet!    
    
    
    @zakandrewking I guarantee you we won't - great features and product improvements in the pipeline!    
    
    
    @Karenmca @NazlinBhimani It won't - in fact, we're under less pressure to monetize now, so will provide more features/value for free!    
    
    
    @neuromusic @researchremix @mrgunn Why wouldn't it be objective? We're simply providing aggregate usage data, independent of publisher.    
    
    
    @neuromusic @mrgunn @researchremix I am confident that the overall composition of our userbase won't change - in fact, I believe.. (1/2)    
    
    
    @neuromusic @mrgunn @researchremix .. that the representativeness and richness of our usage data will increase due to larger scale. (2/2)    
    
    
    @ssbittner We do have an iPad app (new release coming soon) + there are Android apps like Droideley or Scholarley. Which OS are you on?    
    
    
    @ssbittner True, though they work very well. We're also currently recruiting mobile developers for an in-house Android app!    
    
    
    @Werner Thank you, much appreciated - #awspowered indeed!    
    
    
    @sennoma No worries, Bill - no offence taken. To be honest, I had to laugh at the picture, too :-)    
    
    
    @trentyarwood I wouldn't put it that way, but yeah, we're now hiring mobile devs to make an Android client :-)    
    
    
    @annacreech @rvidal Our Mendeley Institutional Edition is actually designed to help libraries increase their interaction with researchers.    
    
    
    @gise_pr Jajaja... gracias :-)    
    
    
    @MeninAndrea Thank you - glad we could help, and congrats on the masters!    
    
    
    @hbunke I can assure you that neither is the case. We're optimists and always up for a challenge :-)    
    
    
    @reidpr No, core motivation was (and is) to make researchers' lives easier. Being useful and being a for-profit are not mutually exclusive.    
    
    
    @LymeAction @light_lyme It won't - it will only get better!    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall Hi Andy - thanks! Yes, I'd be happy to. Off to a BBC Radio 4 interview now, but we'll find a time!    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall I'll be live at 4.30pm on BBC's Material World :-) http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01rr7ry …    
    
    
    @jasonpriem @Andy_Tattersall @ImpactStory Amazing how fast that went! Felt like we were only speaking for 5 minutes!    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall Thanks Andy! Off to team bowling event now, and speaking at Oxford Open Sci Conf tomorrow - you won't be there by chance?    
    
    
    @Andy_Tattersall Email might be easier then - do you have my address? As for bowling: I'm dragging down my team's scores :-)    
    
    
    @flipphillips Thank you, Flip! There are a number of cool things in the pipeline already!    
    
    
    @Tim_Budge Thanks! We'll actually stay very independent - in our own office, same team, same management and founders in charge, same vision.    
    
    
    @DianaJSpencer @thesiswhisperer Intention is to let Mendeley be Mendeley, with more resources (e.g. for Android app) & better content access    
    
    
    @DianaJSpencer @thesiswhisperer Most definitely!    
    
    
    @herrison Thong?! I know my drawing skills need work, but that one was unexpected :-)    
    
    
    At the BBC Radio 4 studio yesterday! http://ow.ly/i/1SsW5     
    
    
    @dirkvl @mrgunn We will!    
    
    
    @dirkvl Thank you, Dirk - much appreciated. Jan and I will do our best to keep it!    
    
    
    @samplereality Sorry - but where are we doing that? We are sad to see any user leave, anytime, and hope they reconsider.. (1/2)    
    
    
    @samplereality ..when they see the results of our joint work in a few months down the line. I apologize if anyone felt otherwise. (2/2)    
    
    
    @rrichard09 @techsoc @rvidal We have always supported import/export in standard formats (XML, RIS, BibTex) and will continue to do so.    
    
    
    @nthmost As per my last tweet - we have always supported import/export in standard formats (XML, RIS, BibTex) and will continue to do so.    
    
    
    @FrederikHjorth I can guarantee you we won't - it'll always be free. We also just doubled everyone's storage space for free; more to come!    
    
    
    @guetto We're not going anywhere, Harry Lime :-) Exciting things on our roadmap - better desktop app, new mobile apps, better content access    
    
    
    @nthmost Yes - it wasn't meant in a snarky way! I was just pointing out that it's already possible and easy :-)    
    
    
    @jdhowgego Not just possible, but very, very likely :-)    
    
    
    @jdhowgego Naturally :-) But looking at our roadmap, I'm very excited.    
    
    
    @klockemd @nlafferty We're not going anywhere - UX improvements, new features, new iOS app, better content access coming soon :-)    
    
    
    @nthmost Agreed :-) Much appreciated!    
    
    
    @AmidstScience Very sorry. Any idea how it happened - sync issue? If you drop support@mendeley.com a line, we'll try to help!    
    
    
    @cyrilleadam iOS app that doesn't suck is coming soon, including note/highlight functionality :-) We'll also start Android app development.    
    
    
    @cyrilleadam We decided to rewrite from scratch to move to our Open API, which also lets 3rd-party devs sync notes/highlights. Will be free!    
    
    
    @cyrilleadam You're welcome :-)    
    
    
    @fso_swe Mendeley has a Zotero-sync feature - you can set it to auto-import everything you capture in Zotero.    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor And I thought I was mainly plugging my girlfriend's food blog!    
    
    
    @Yaamina23 Yes - in the Mendeley PDF Viewer go to "File > Export with Annotations".    
    
    
    @Yaamina23 Ah, sorry, I misunderstood - I thought you wanted to see Mendeley annotations in other PDF viewers, not the other way around!    
    
    
    @Yaamina23 I suppose you would have to save the annotations from Skim/Preview into the PDF somehow - then Mendeley would see them.    
    
    
    @bobbiejohnson Belated, but nonetheless: Congrats!!    
    
    
    @bobbiejohnson I'm in Amsterdam this week :-)    
    
    
    @DennisEckmeier @mrgunn @laxvid @Odysseyblog We're aware the API needs improvement and are working on it - see...    
    
    
    @DennisEckmeier @mrgunn @laxvid @Odysseyblog .. http://ow.ly/1VnIt7  :-) (URL got cut in my last tweet)    
    
    
    @Laserjunge New Mendeley iOS app including annotations&highlights sync already being tested, will be released soon. @subcide knows more :-)    
    
    
    @nicoadams More Star Wars references here: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … :-)    
    
    
    @grahamburdge @surreynourish You can now easily customise citation styles: http://csl.mendeley.com  :-)    
    
    
    @mselibrary I'm answering some of the most frequently asked questions here: http://elsevierconnect.com/what-you-really-want-to-know-about-mendeley-and-elsevier/ … :-)    
    
    
    @lucdall Mendeley reste libre et ouvert. Plus d'info ici: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … and http://blog.mendeley.com/press-release/qa-team-mendeley-joins-elsevier/ …    
    
    
    Press release: @ThomsonReuters / @EndNoteNews brings feather to a pillow fight :-) http://www.marketwatch.com/story/thomson-reuters-ups-ante-for-mendeley-customers-seeking-free-alternative-2013-04-23 …    
    
    
    @Yaamina23 @StephMulrine @PhDForum We have a new iPhone/iPad app with annotations/highlights sync coming soon; Android apps also available!    
    
    
    @bpwned Ich liebe es, wenn ein Plan funktioniert :-)    
    
    
    @DrRachie @botbml That's brilliant! Thank you :-)    
    
    
    Amazing - Mendeley / Linux / Android nail art! RT @hollycassell: @jesperht how'd you like them apples? :) pic.twitter.com/6PrAPg6fZw    
    
    
    @hollycassell This is great! Can we add it to our press photos (http://www.flickr.com/photos/mendeley/sets/72157630652171616/ …)? Do you have a Flickr account we could credit?    
    
    
    @hollycassell Done! http://www.flickr.com/photos/mendeley/8676982369/in/set-72157630652171616 … - thank you! :-)    
    
    
    @JavierCanavate @danjhayden Better iOS with annotations & highlights sync already in testing - will be released soon!    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor @rintzezelle I think it's about 15 different styles (still too many, if you ask me!) mapped to the 1500 journal names.    
    
    
    @rintzezelle @MikeTaylor Sorry, you're right - only 6 different ones, not 15.    
    
    
    @DrRachie On the contrary! Here's some info on our plans and improvements we've already rolled out: http://ow.ly/1VEOp0     
    
    
    @DrRachie Also, another recent interview on the topic: http://bit.ly/10g9KCJ  - let me know if you have more questions!    
    
    
    @ReinerGrundmann @CountCarbon No need to - here's some info on our plans and improvements we've already rolled out: http://ow.ly/1VEOp0     
    
    
    @grolimur @mrgunn For a more in-depth look at how we use & share data via our API, see this: http://ow.ly/1VEOp0     
    
    
    @daviesjs Completely rewritten/redesigned iOS app coming soon - faster, prettier, and with annotations & highlights sync!    
    
    
    @anandamide @willhowells Completely rewritten iOS app with annotations & highlights coming very soon - already in beta testing!    
    
    
    @jesgar On the contrary: We're currently looking into how we can expand collaboration :-)    
    
    
    @Laura_Fortune @Jason_P_Smith Yes, it does :-) We have apps for Win, Mac, Linux, iOS, and there are 3rd-party apps for iOS, Android, Kindle.    
    
    
    @TomReller @jasonpriem Time to capitalise and start a boy band!    
    
    
    @Jason_P_Smith @Laura_Fortune Thank you - much appreciated!    
    
    
    @papershipapp @quesnelm Yes - annotation sync to 3rd-party app will be available soon!    
    
    
    @gendalus @totalreflexion Das ist Sippenhaft :-) Hier Infos, wie wir unseren Nutzern in Zukunft noch mehr bieten: http://ow.ly/kKZrf     
    
    
    @blogkamp @urbaneprofessor @StuartWilksHeeg Yes, Mendeley imports EndNote XML libraries, RIS, BibTex; straight from PDF, & syncs with Zotero    
    
    
    Great Mendeley tutorial video: http://vimeo.com/65511929     
    
    
    @brandontlocke @ScholCommons I see why you would ugh, but here's more context on how it will benefit our users: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ …    
    
    
    @muammar I hope not :-) Here is more info on how it will benefit our users: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … - great stuff in the pipeline!    
    
    
    @SarahHCarl @firegenome Actually, good things are already coming out of it, see http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … and http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-features/mendeley-contributes-2000-citation-styles-to-the-open-citation-style-repository-at-citationstyles-org/ …    
    
    
    @firegenome @SarahHCarl Yes - though I won't really have to, as Elsevier are significantly ramping up their OA publishing efforts already!    
    
    
    @firegenome @SarahHCarl I don't know yet - I'm new on the job :-)    
    
    
    @MatthewJGreene Good question - could you give @mendeleysupport more info, so they can have a look? Thanks!    
    
    
    @jatenas Not quite, our Open API under Creative Commons license is alive & well, see http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … and also http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-features/mendeley-contributes-2000-citation-styles-to-the-open-citation-style-repository-at-citationstyles-org/ …    
    
    
    @f_ferraro More on the Star Wars references here: http://blog.mendeley.com/community-relations/mendeley-and-elsevier-heres-more-info/ … :-)    
    
    
    @gmact I do believe our Word plugin supports that - you could try http://csl.mendeley.com  to edit citation styles as needed!    
    
    
    @m_wall @JimP @neuroconscience @ethanweed New, faster, more stable iOS app with annotations & highlight coming soon!    
    
    
    @MarikaRose @orionedgar @DavidHowey Yes, Mendeley has automatic BibTex export which keeps BibTex files in sync with your document library.    
    
    
    Killer Robot Discussion at Google Big Tent event http://ow.ly/i/2aMhm     
    
    
    Eric Schmidt: Because Cody Wilson thought it was a good idea to put the 3D-printed gun on the web, people will die. http://ow.ly/i/2aS4h     
    
    
    @davidleetalk2me By the way, Eric Schmidt's was another "Fireside Chat" without a fireside anywhere in sight. False labelling! #bigtentuk    
    
    
    @Le_GFII ça me fait plaisir - à la semaine prochaine!    
    
    
    @lgroeni @MiguelJohnson Mendeley also backs up/syncs any documents and files in your library.    
    
    
    @hbunke That's very strange - when you delete your account, all personal info (incl. email address) is deleted. I'll check what's going on!    
    
    
    @jenlrile New iOS app coming soon, with all the features u want :-)    
    
    
    @azeem @pjozefak Nobody's being geocitied. Amazing stuff in the pipeline - watch this space!    
    
    
    @hamilton_ia @jenlrile Yes, sorry about that! We had to make some changes to the underlying architecture to improve notes & highlights sync.    
    
    
    @rvidal A million bucks of product placement well spent!    
    
    
    @eileentso Some of it sounds very familiar!    
    
    
    @teraspawn Dear Beth,

Sorry for that! We tried :-)

Lots of love,
Mendeley

P.S. We're always working on improving the metadata extraction.    
    
    
    @yoavram @MendeleySupport Working on it, and coming soon!    
    
    
    @mattd_hall New, flexible recommender engine that works for any set of papers you select is in the works!    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor @wisealic There were other offers, but Elsevier was the best fit in terms of product fit/platform vision. (1/2)    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor @wisealic Can't disclose who the other offers were from - such stuff is covered by NDAs. (2/2)    
    
    
    @jonfwilkins @mrgunn @openscience Here, have some camomile tea. We're not going anywhere! Ask Open Day attendees what they thought :-)    
    
    
    @algae Apparently you disagree, or why is it bothering you?    
    
    
    @MatthieuRegnier You can use http://www.mendeley.com/import/  to save websites/PDFs for later; you can also sort papers in your library by date added.    
    
    
    @BobRimington Sorry to hear - how so? Any way we can help?    
    
    
    @algae I respectfully disagree. Mendeley is about crowdsourcing/open science; 3D printing is about crowdsourcing/open manufacturing. They..    
    
    
    @algae ..are related trends. I was quoting Eric Schmidt at a conference I was attending. Also, I don't think what he said was inflammatory.    
    
    
    @dasKerst Sorry to hear - perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @rintzezelle Thanks for pointing it out. I've asked the editor of the website to add the link!    
    
    
    @rintzezelle @cparnot Absolutely. I'm sure that the omission of the link was not intentional. It's been added now!    
    
    
    @davidleetalk2me It's like magic! There's a little me in the box where you plug your headphones in!    
    
    
    @MaryLouCowan Sorry about that! Perhaps @mendeleysupport can help?    
    
    
    @aleciarrb Looks like the icon for "link to PDF broken"! @MendeleySupport can help.    
    
    
    