Started QuoteCompiler lets see what today did to my stocks :-(    
    
    
    Lol, there is only one stock in my depot that did well during all the time even today: Reply Deutschland AG, the company I work for.    
    
    
    My copy of "SAP WebClient" http://bit.ly/oBIg5P arrived. Gonna start reading tomorrow after I finish "ABAP - Performance Tuning" #sapcrm    
    
    
    "You've just made the first step to becoming an expert on the subject of SAP Web Client" <- Wonder what I did the the last 5 years.. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Uhh, it is really time consuming to get a hang of Joomla when you see it the first time.    
    
    
    Working on my third post CRM 7 EHP1 upgrade. Always the same problem with enhanced components and inactive services. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Anyone know how to assign a user ID to an employee in SAP CRM 7 EHP1? In WebClient fields are locked. Do not want to use TX BP. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Did Seesmic cut the "Sign in with Twitter" dialog for its Web Client? Need to get an account now... Back to good old Twitter.com client    
    
    
    @esjewett Do not think about it. We are talking about DB here. You even get problems if the ticket is not printed in A4 but A5.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Judging from your tweets it took you 18 hours to get to work on your bike?! Tough times...    
    
    
    Just enhancing PipelinePerformanceManagment views in #sapcrm. I have seen some weird coding the past years, but never sth like that!    
    
    
    If you ever wondered how to not use a dyn search tag and rebuild it on a BSP page have a look at view PPM_DYNSEARCH/Filter.htm. #sapcrm    
    
    
    I really hat this earphone jack on my Acer Iconia to look like the one for power. A USB charger could have been so cool.    
    
    
    Just got a forces logoff from the clients system. Seems I should call it a day.    
    
    
    Btw. Anyone got problems with locks on ServiceRequests in #sapcrm not being removed when creating a followup? Mine stay a whole session.    
    
    
    New York seems a little quite: http://bit.ly/pkpG3h  but still people on the street inspite of hurricane #Irene    
    
    
    Only two more weeks until holiday. Best thing: Afterwards I get rid of my #Volkswagen EOS :-) Finally free of this piece of crap.    
    
    
    Another highlight from #sapcrm Marketing xPress: Getting views by ViewArea number instead of ViewName. Once s/o changes the config --> dump!    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor: Just posted a long comment to @sjohannes blog post about the SAP WebClient book.    
    
    
    Century City in Los Angeles does exactly look like Sim City on Bing: http://binged.it/n73WU3     
    
    
    Wondering if I can access us4368.wdf.sap.corp from our local system. At least CRMCMP_SURVEY/SurveyEdit calls it on the BSP page #sapcrm    
    
    
    @esjewett Maybe they don't care? Maybe they got no QA? Bad thing for SAP: I can see their source. Not able to for other companies...    
    
    
    @pixelbase thanks for the write up. conversation looked interesting, but could not follow it on twitter. it is just the wrong platform ;-)    
    
    
    The #sapcrm Wiki looks like some shiny marketing presentation: http://bit.ly/qpxLSG  Even got contact details to a "Service Manager"    
    
    
    Just a test how many new followers some words bring: #apple #ipod #iphone #ipad    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Yeah, becomes really annoying for document templates in #sapcrm.    
    
    
    Last day at work before a four week holiday. Last day on project after nearly four years. Feeling like leaving a whole chapter of my life.    
    
    
    Just recieved a very nice present from my customer. Really hard leaving here :-/    
    
    
    First life sign from Singapore: We had fantastic first days.Feels just like NY-City just cheaper&cleaner.Tomorrow Universal.Than Malaysia    
    
    
    @geirish I feel with you. Got to be in Düsseldorf at 11am. Usual time would be 8am ;-) Lazy mondays.    
    
    
    Kuala Lumpur really is a nice city. According to our taxi driver the shopping malls are solely occupied by tourists. Next is East Malaysia.    
    
    
    sitting at Jakarta airport. Flight is due in 35 minutes.Finally back in germany tomorrow :-) 15.5h flight. Stops at Kuala Lumpur & Amsterdam    
    
    
    There is nothing as sweet as Jetlag. Waking you up at 3 am, not f***ing able to get back to sleep for 2 hours.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Fraueninsel... sounds delicious. Or is it some kind of shoe shop?    
    
    
    Have to document code inline...Now developer who was here before did not document anything. Am I to document for him as well?    
    
    
    @pixelbase Ask for the uplink  to the Internet. A Gigabit for a whole village probably ;-) Sound like the 21 MBits HSP+ joke    
    
    
    @esjewett Yeah, deleting SAP Consultings #sapcrm Xpress enhancements would be nasty :-)    
    
    
    @sjohannes Is that your desk? Didn't have a treat?    
    
    
    Automated Voice Response systems really freak me out. Spent 10 minutes shouting at my mobile while trying to track a letter. Deutsche Post    
    
    
    My SGS2 synced with google now I got all spammers in my address book and 1000 appointments I do not care about :-(    
    
    
    Does it really make sense to reproduce http://help.sap.com  in the SAP CRM Wiki? http://bit.ly/rZljIm  #sapcrm    
    
    
    #sapcrm EHP 2 hit the "Restricted Availablity" today. Still in ramp up, no unrestricted date shown, yet. Anyone some first impressions?    
    
    
    Sometimes I wonder who invented the #sapcrm status table CRM_JEST. It is such a hassle to select a transaction that does not have a status.    
    
    
    When a consultant asks me in which table he should put his developer key, he is probably no good development consultant...    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Maybe this helps http://bit.ly/s0VQko  @thomas_jung @ivanfemia @juliusbussche    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Or to put it short. It will be one of the C functions in the kernel ,-)    
    
    
    It is quite shocking to see s/o program the SPLIT command in ABAP manually. Ahh, might have been a good practive ;-)    
    
    
    Fascinating: THe fourth part of the Eclipse movies is categorized as Horror. Wonder if that is a mistake or a man who had to watch it :-p    
    
    
    Twitter really is ambient communication. Can not catch up reading the last two days. If I missed you, msg or mention me.    
    
    
    There is fun in SAP - For #sapcrm global attribute tags one of the developers maintained the "Ultimative Answer" with value "42"    
    
    
    New Firmware for my old SGH i900 Omnia. New UI is SPB Shell and Android skin. Super fast and really cool looking. iPhone beware :-p    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvberge @sjohannes @johanvanzil With exclusive lock OK. Though wouldn't do it. BDT issues: tx. BUS7 FMs not called by BOL.    
    
    
    Ok guys. Stop buying faster CPUs, start buying faster hard drives. Just decoding three files. CPUs are at 30%. HDD is running hot.    
    
    
    Just installed Seesmic on my mobile. Anyone suggestions for a twitter&google+ client?    
    
    
    trying to post from spb shell    
    
    
    Samsung has got a patent on smilies?! OMG 8-0    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @tpowlas @sjohannes @roelvberge @johanvanzil We are runnuing #sapcrm itsm here, including incidents, but no solman. Sorry    
    
    
    @thorstenster Why did you choose Ipad 2 over GalaxyTab or Iconia?    
    
    
    Dropped my phone today. Got it in a cover protecting 3 corners and the back. Guess which corner it landed on :-(    
    
    
    Saw Jurassic Park yesterday. Now I'm wondering: Is it a pun that they named the girl "Lex Murphy" = Murphy's Law?    
    
    
    @paphko Layered interfaces and steroscopic output... Sound fancy. But can I still use my phone for calling somebody?    
    
    
    Happy new year everyone. Had a great time yesterday watching fireworks in Düsseldorf.    
    
    
    Interesting: My company just installed a SAP HANA sandbox system. Now I am wondering what to do with it. Any suggestions?    
    
    
    Ran into a problem with RFW in #sapcrm. Searching for STATUS_COMMON and another criteria returns different results depending on MAX HITS.    
    
    
    #sapcrm MAX_HITS = 100 returns 60 results. MAX_HITS = 200 returns 90 results. Bug is in FM CRM_BSP_OIC_1O_SEARCH_FROM_RF. Anyone know this?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor No filter or BAdI implemented.I checked the code. It seems like an error. The results "vanish" in the FM from line 335 onwards.    
    
    
    @se38 Judging from that video it could even be bats in that tree ;-) Anyway I know we got parrots in germany. Seen some in Wiesbaden as well    
    
    
    Found the problem with the sRFW query in #sapcrm today. It is not FM CRM_BSP_OIC_1O_SEARCH_FROM_RF but class CL_CRM_SRQM_SRV_REQ_RUN_BTIL...    
    
    
    ...#sapcrm selects status schema according to process type, this leads to doubled criteria if two transaction typs share the same schema.    
    
    
    @sapcrm I filed the issue in OSS 0000019943/2012. Hope it will get solved soon :-) #sapcrm    
    
    
    Backupping my 2 TB NAS over LAN. Too sad Linux can not handle NTFS drives with good write data rates. FreeFileSync estimates 14h for 380GB    
    
    
    There is nothing more fun than sorting a large pile of files on a saturday evening. Hope the database does not break, ever.    
    
    
    Why does Win XP place a blinking cursor in an input field, but I can not type until I manually click it with the mouse?    
    
    
    @NicholasK71 @applebyj @dakoller Thanks for the input. But my difficulty is to imagine any such scenario. What is #hana good for in #sapcrm    
    
    
    @thorstenster Read the Hitchhikers guide. Otherwise watch Spaceballs.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @PatrickMeurer86 Very good wiki entry! Posted one small suggestion as a comment. Maybe you would want to update your code.    
    
    
    @pixelbase Yes. When writing classes ABAP sometimes messes up the sections. You can "activate anyway" and it works. Better is to repair.    
    
    
    Anyone know which is the preferred framework for customer developments with TREX in #sapcrm: SAF or SES?    
    
    
    Wow, Sheldon hat bei der Big bang theory auf Pro 7 ein total cooles Wascheflatteil.    
    
    
    @NicholasK71 @applebyj @dakoller sounds great. Thanks a lot. Helps me to get some feeling what #hana is good for.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor How is it possible to set up custom search objects with Enterprise Search? Looked at documentation and system today.    
    
    
    @se38 Still present on my #sapcrm system. Got any further information on plans SAP might have? Maybe a new interpreter?    
    
    
    @koljareiss On a note: I have seen people on Bali reserve their sun loungers exactly the same annoying way. Hardly any germans there...    
    
    
    /me hungrig. geht in die Küche. /part . *carkas has left #twitter. <-- Still remember this thing named IRC :-)    
    
    
    @ttrapp @thorstenster Did not one of you write a blog about Android and SUP? Just facing a new challenge: Setup SUP with Android Tablet.    
    
    
    Received a tweet some weeks ago. Was important info. Searching for it, can not find :-( Where can I search tweets I received?    
    
    
    @evabraham Nah, it was not directed to me. Just was a link I found very interesting. Clicked, read the articel and now need it again.    
    
    
    @evabraham Ja... Twitter ist halt echt "ambient communication". Bei ICQ oder IRC hat man wenigstens ne ordentliche History :-(    
    
    
    How would I get the rights to download SAP CRM Sales for Android from the market as described in this note 1664439? #sapcrm    
    
    
    Does anyone have a information about #sapcrm 5.2 Version. Need to compare it to current #sapcrm 7 EHP2. Some high level brochures ;-)    
    
    
    @sapcrm That looks very promising. Thanks a lot! Though it does not feature #sapcrm 5.2 but 6.0 should do as well.    
    
    
    @derphil Happy Birthday!    
    
    
    WTF?! Someone disabled old list view in SE16 for NW Mobile 7.1. Now I can not debug my values into the tables anymore. What to do?    
    
    
    @citoki There is no SE16N in any NetWeaver version. Suppose the note will not help.    
    
    
    @sapcrm Why can I try iPhone/iPad, Windows and Blackberry CRM Sales APPs, but have to buy Android right away? No download from Sap Store?    
    
    
    While digging into the enhancement concept of #sapcrm Sales for Mobile you find code dating back to 2008. Quite a long development.    
    
    
    @thorstenster Yep, same here. My colleagues got two contacts for SUP & CRM Sales. One Sybase one SAP. Both are not responsible :-)    
    
    
    @dakoller @findyourquarter Looks good. Would have needed that a year ago. Flat between work, sports, shopping,no airtraffic,public transport    
    
    
    @thorstenster @dakoller @findyourquarter @rhirsch Monetize: Charge the same as real est. agents,but offer real value throuhg personalization    
    
    
    Is there any free RDP and VNC viewer for Android supporting multiple servers? PocketCloud only supports one.    
    
    
    @se38 Cool. When on a windows machine and click "Install" it displays a different language after click on Sign-In and browser Back, Back.    
    
    
    @se38 Better try that on my Acer Iconia.    
    
    
    Coolest SAP related post recieved today. 1-click SAP Notes:  http://bit.ly/xbWKAo     
    
    
    Just starting to refactor some code that integrates WebClient with WebDynpro. Hope I can port everything to WebClient :-)    
    
    
    Software not working. My task is to port it to #sapcrm webclient and fix it. Would be a lot easier if I'd seen what it does before it broke.    
    
    
    SAPLogon started with 100MB this morning. Now it reserved more than 500MB. Wonder what it does with it. No additional modes opened.    
    
    
    For anybody who wishes to generate guided activity pages in #sapcrm with custom namespace: Implement note 1618875 before you start.    
    
    
    @se38 Das heisst doch "All your base are belong to us" #nda    
    
    
    Worst thing about ABAP method chaining: It works only with functional methods. No IMPORTING supported :-(    
    
    
    @esjewett I suppose returning parameters aren't that bad if you only pass references. Concerning internal tables I am quite unsure.    
    
    
    @esjewett Thouht tables would be handled as references as well and only copied after first change. Read sth like that a while ago.    
    
    
    My favourite dialog of the day: "Marked objects will be deleted. Delete anyway?" Wondering what the designer of this popup thought...    
    
    
    When inside an ABAP class I get another instance of this class, I can access the instances protected variables. Is this correct OO?    
    
    
    Employee in front of me to her colleague: "I had 357 new mails in my inbox. Deleted them all. Can not read them anyway".    
    
    
    #sapcrm displays a message that it doesn't work with FireFox 10. Use about:config with param general.useragent.override to change user agent    
    
    
    @esjewett It blocks with a BSP error: <htmlb:content>: (*) This browser is not supported; for Design2003 the Internet Explorer as of 5.50...    
    
    
    @esjewett The really bad part is the rest that was cut off before: "...and the Mozilla as of 1.75 are supported" <-- I'm on Firefox 10    
    
    
    Anybody problems with OSS today? Anytime I try to open a note I get a "500 - Dispatching Error" #sap    
    
    
    The graphical buying center in #sapcrm crashes about every 5 minutes. Wondering if it got problems with Java 1.6    
    
    
    Wanted to know about HDD encryption performance. #mcafee compares 7200rpm drive with ssd #fail http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=54bpHHmVX-c …    
    
    
    Social Media is not the answer to everything. Stores shut down on facebook:  http://bloom.bg/wzoUxj     
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Did you try to move enhanced #sapcrm components between systems using #SAPLink? Does it work?    
    
    
    Back from holiday. Arrived save and sound in Cologne this morning    
    
    
    Currently reading the Steve Jobs biography. Everything I ever suspected about Apple design seems to be true.    
    
    
    Just listening to an old Captain Jack album. #OMG    
    
    
    Ok, off on the Autobahn. Ready for X-MAS    
    
    
    Note to self: Jogging on a sunny day, good idea. Soaking your mobile with sweat while tracking your run, bad idea.    
    
    
    Does anyone know if note 938591 for SGWI is still valid in #sapcrm ehp1? It is mentioned in help (http://bit.ly/GUoAba  ) but released 2006.    
    
    
    I definitely need to log into SCN soon. Always getting emails that someone is following me.    
    
    
    @sapcrm Sadly that note does not help me as I need integration of Lotus Domino 8.5. sGWI Version 5 is Exchange only :-(    
    
    
    Hmm, new SCN is complicated at a first glance. Where are the forums?    
    
    
    @fredverheul Thanks, finally found the "ABAP community". Is it just me or did the loading times increase significantly?    
    
    
    Damn. I can not even search for "IMAP CLIENT" in the new #SCN. It always alters my search to "IMP" "CLIENT".    
    
    
    day of bad discoverings today. ABAP does not support sockets. Telnet is not installed. No clue if I can put a program into the java stack.    
    
    
    Has anyone tried the "new" #scn with a mobile browser yet? Does it work? Good?    
    
    
    Some of the older blogs look messed up in the new #scn http://bit.ly/HZgGR0     
    
    
    @thorstenster @antichrista Germans do not capitalize english words at random. We got a system: Only nouns.    
    
    
    @thorstenster @antichrista that looks gross. Though I have to admit I do it for titles as well -> Campaign Management . I like camel case.    
    
    
    If I need to get a Adobe Credentials file as described in note 736902 to create Interactive Forms by Adobe, do I have to pay for it?    
    
    
    @johanvanzijl DO you know if I need a license/credential per form or just one for our dev-system?    
    
    
    #TomTom still did not fix the HD Traffic bug. Wunderful three days easter traffic without information. The last #TomTom I have bought.    
    
    
    @sapcrm Did you find any information on server side Groupware Integration? Send you my mail address a while ago, but did not hear anything.    
    
    
    Iron skys cant be for real. Nazis from the dark side of the moon?? is it watchable?    
    
    
    #logitravel just cancelled my hotel booking for tomorrow. The alternative is 37 km away from destination. I hate trade fair weeks!!    
    
    
    Did anyone come up with a good solution to do drag and drop of files to Internet Explorer? Want to upload Images directly from clipboard.    
    
    
    Since I subscribed the new feeds for #scn blogs I get a lot of content that are not blogs in google reader. Anyone else got problems?    
    
    
    Interesting: After Android 4 update my mobile worked for 2 days. Then crashed repetedly. Factory reset did not help. Full wipe did until now    
    
    
    Please please please #sap give me an option to order the entries in SPRO alphabetically.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Just wondering: What is a #MBP?    
    
    
    My SGS2 arrived at samsung repair facility. Hoping for a fast solution to get my mobile back.    
    
    
    I am in a very bad mood. Lost my USB stick with some important data :-(    
    
    
    Looking for a new USB stick. This must be the most expensive stick ever: 8GB for 907,86 EUR.At least shipping is free. http://amzn.to/ekyPUa    
    
    
    Just paid 5% more for my online order,because the other dealer wanted me to create an account first.Lazy me.Hail to Amazon Marketplace    
    
    
    The people who programmed the WebClient part of the Account Factsheet in #sapcrm obviously did not know what they were doing.    
    
    
    5:30 and everybody has left. Kinda lonely in here. At least some cleaning ladies are here as well.    
    
    
    @geirish Ever tried throwing a coin?    
    
    
    @geirish Sounds like you got promoted. Congratulations.    
    
    
    syskoplan AG renewed their Special Expertise Partner status with SAP for 2010/2011: Including #sapcrm (and many others)    
    
    
    Wondering: Has anyone ever tried http://www.onlive.com/ by now? Found it pretty impressing about a year ago when I first heard of.    
    
    
    Just had a meddle around with www.wolframalpha.com . The previously hyped Google killer ;-) Anyone remember?    
    
    
    Logged in again after some weeks of abstinence. Hope I did not miss anything relevant :-)    
    
    
    A little bit later: Happy new year everybody!    
    
    
    Learned this weekend: Windows & Linux passwords are 0 security when you have physical access to the PC and Windows is not in a domain.    
    
    
    Grml... Have to copy whole class because variables are declared private in #sapcrm Office Integration handler. No means of accessing them :(    
    
    
    Tried yesterday for 4 hours to get ActiveSync to work with my mobile. This morning I booted my PC. Everything works fine. Miracles of tech.    
    
    
    Does anyone know how to convert special characters that were encoded to ISO-8859-1 back to UTF-8? ABAP converters won't do :(    
    
    
    Better question: Why do Adobe Forms crash on non-Unicode systems when they get ISO-8859-1 encoded strings that contain special chars?    
    
    
    @yojibee @dakoller told me that you might now about unicode in Adobe Forms. Interested in answering me some questions?    
    
    
    @yojibee I tried that once. Only answer was that I should go looking in the Adobe Forums. Maybe you're right and I should try again.    
    
    
    posted question to the #sap #adobe forums about unicode: https://forums.sdn.sap.com/thread.jspa?threadID=1763058    
    
    
    @yojibee Thanks a lot! Already done the posting part: https://forums.sdn.sap.com/thread.jspa?threadID=1763058    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor what is excel reader?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor nice! Thought about a parser myself for some time after abap2xslx came up. Though it is parsing CRM Configs to Excel and back.    
    
    
    Implemented Facebook like business partner search in #sapcrm today. Quite cool seeing the partners popup while you search.    
    
    
    @yojibee try reading a book. Maybe you can put a nifty sticker on it that says "iRead" ;-)    
    
    
    Once again disappointed by #sap support: We know it does not work. We do not like it either. We will not fix it.    
    
    
    Development system: Does not have data. Test system: Is not configured properly. So... only one system left for troubleshooting. Thrilling.    
    
    
    Differences in customer support: Wrote #TomTom an email 10 days ago. No reaction until I called them. #Amazon needed 40 minutes to respond.    
    
    
    @thomas_jung Any chance to get ahold of this "Encyclopedia WebDynpronica" without attending #sapteched? 203 pages is massive.    
    
    
    Ok... I need 60.000 Lufthansa Miles to get my free flight to Bush Gardens in California. Any ideas except: Fly Lufthansa and earn Miles?    
    
    
    Really enyoning this thread in #sapcrm forum: https://forums.sdn.sap.com/thread.jspa?messageID=9463595&#9463595    
    
    
    Those JavaScript libraries of the #sapcrm WebClient are huge. Does anyone have heard of some documentation about them?    
    
    
    @thomas_jung Your probably right. After looking up "witty banter": http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=witty%20banter    
    
    
    @thomas_jung Do not get it wrong, I just had a laugh how so unrelated meanings can come to one phrase.    
    
    
    I just installed #ZAKE on our server.It updated #ZAKE itself from the SVN.Now the class ZCL_ZAKE_SVN contains errors: ZAKE_HOME is undefined    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor We had a lot of problems with BT126H_MAIL as well. Lots of hardcoded stuff in the view. Check the inbound plugs.    
    
    
    Odysse continues: Finding someone who is actively using #sapcrm server groupware integration with #lotus #notes    
    
    
    Read this article earlier: http://tcrn.ch/aqvc7N Is it true for SAP ABAPers as well? I fear so. Maybe time to move on.    
    
    
    Service from #tomtom makes me wanna puke. They addressed the return parcel wrong and I notified them. Now they want me to fix it. #fail    
    
    
    ABAPs badly documented API just made me program a new method after searching for 30 min. Just finished I find the exact logic one call away.    
    
    
    Well at least I learned a lot about week day computations.    
    
    
    #tomtom service experience: After they send my device to "Stadt,DE", they ask for my address. Quoting my previous mail with my address in it    
    
    
    Anyone know how I can block #foursquare updates? They really get annoying not containing any valueable information.    
    
    
    @yojibee Do not give in. The last time it overwhelmed me a whole 300g chocolate mysteriously disappeared.    
    
    
    Finally finished consolidating customers print templates. Time for weekend.    
    
    
    grml. My #RoundCube installation stopped working two hours ago. After login just sends me back to login screen after a few seconds.    
    
    
    Got mail from @sjohannes "BTW: If you never need moderator assistance...let me know". Suppose I can do that ;-)    
    
    
    been configuring my webspace the whole evening. My guess is: I can not change any php variable at all.    
    
    
    @esjewett You staying at antarctica currently? Or is it just summer sunshine in your display?    
    
    
    @esjewett Oh, thought you ment "dark" literally. Got the shades closed here as well. Damn summer is coming round after all.    
    
    
    The trouble with my hosting provider encouraged me to set up #CrystalWebmail. Bases on #Roundcube, but looks a little bit nicer.Gonna use it    
    
    
    Woke up at 7am this morning, ready to go to work. Took me some minutes to recognize that it is a holiday and I just forgot my alarm clock.    
    
    
    @esjewett Ask them for the protocol they made when you got the car.    
    
    
    Finally #tomtom service send me back my navigation system. Took nearly one month and numerous emails/calls to get a replacement. #fail    
    
    
    Darn, I am tired. Think I am getting ill. Maybe @yojibee spread the desease with her tweets:-p    
    
    
    @Reply_DE Haben wir da was mit #ByOD geplant?    
    
    
    Signed #hilton loyalty program just to avoid spelling out my address every week over and over again for the bill.    
    
    
    You know how it is: Some days just suck - Montags könnt ich kotzen    
    
    
    Saw the first sneak peek of our #syskoplan #reply video. Even it its raw version looks interesting.    
    
    
    @esjewett I believe the first scentence says it all.In my opinion there are people in the forum just to gain points for "reputation"    
    
    
    @esjewett  you Don Not get points. I believe the entry is there to stress that. Bumping threads with "alibi"information is bad style also.    
    
    
    Found a new interesting idea for CRM WebClient on #sap #ideaplace https://ideas.sap.com/ideas/1214    
    
    
    Finally completed the Starcraft 1 - Terran campaign. Took me only like 14 years...    
    
    
    @dakoller Probably... But I am getting bored by the game again. Could take a couple of months for Zerg campaign.    
    
    
    My new satellite reciever just arrived. Cruel world: Sun is shining, got a telephone conference coming up and no time on the weekend :-(    
    
    
    @thorstenster I liked the Wynn while visiting Vegas, though it was mainly because of  their spectacular dinner buffet.Don't know room prices    
    
    
    Am I legally allowed to use a google map layer in my OpenLayers?It's no Google API: http://www.google.com/intl/de-DE_US/help/terms_maps.html    
    
    
    @kojote Ok, mail is on its way. Will write the issue up in more detail.    
    
    
    @pixelbase @thorstenster I thought every iPhone was to big parts manufactured by/with Samsung anyway. Nexus is Google, so same story.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Your #DemoJam contribution looks very promising. Hope I have some spare time to test it out in the future.    
    
    
    Cruel cruel world. Paint and PowerPoint are currently the tools I use most on my job.    
    
    
    Now I got it. The full #Adobe Reader is only available by FTP. HTTP only offers the installer.Too bad if you do not have internet everywhere    
    
    
    That's what I call errecting yourself a statue for lifetime. Even including some advertisement. #sapcrm pic.twitter.com/zcwyINPM    
    
    
    Looking for a job in corporate finance for a friend of mine near Cologne or in NRW. Is: Dipl. Kaufmann, #CFA. Ideas? Message me :-)    
    
    
    is looking for documentation on the TAJAX tag library    
    
    
    Anyone know if there is a kind of API for material configuration in ERP? Some function modules or classes?    
    
    
    My employer #Reply upgraded their facebook page with some videos http://de-de.facebook.com/reply.deutschland/app_264666250248559 … featuring guess who... me. Take a look if you dare.    
    
    
    Wondering if this Note from #sapcrm is for real https://service.sap.com/sap/support/notes/1664070 …    
    
    
    Doing PowerPoints all afternoon long. Oh my gosh, there is absolutely no fun in that.    
    
    
    @jpenninkhof They are waiting for "Nordsee" to open up. Fish is only fresh in the morning ;-)    
    
    
    @sjohannes Either put a slice between the pages or try this: http://www.naturesgardencandles.com/candlemaking-soap-supplies/item/bacon/-BACON-Fragrance-Oil.html …    
    
    
    It really is interesting to watch my #roomba clean the floor. Wondering if I could build this robot.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor The Note does nothing and contains no information. It just points to Note 1642681. #sgwi #sapcrm    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Interesting... why don't they just use the Note with the content directly?    
    
    
    Programming ABAP and JavaScript in parallel is like hell made of . and ;    
    
    
    SAP Note  http://bit.ly/hzV0l4 is linking to a SCN Blog to explain what has to be done. Nice one @sjohannes    
    
    
    Half the department is gone to #DSAG meeting today. Kinda empty here.    
    
    
    OMG, JavaScript is so fricking ugly. Took me an hour to figure out how to call an object function in an mouseover event supplying the event.    
    
    
    Whereas the hard part was to do it in setTimeout and call clearTimeout for the same instance when mouseout.    
    
    
    Anybody got ideas how to directly access views in WebClient components? An URL would be best. Got to display a view in a DIV overlay.#sapcrm    
    
    
    I really would love to hook up with one of the WCUIF developers and get some insight into the PopUp handling.Any ideas? #sap #wcuif #sapcrm    
    
    
    @se38 Started wondering after reading @e_bcorp. Is anyone actually using #twibap in business cases?    
    
    
    @sjohannes 1337658 - Ready/Not Ready radio button gray out and cannot be changed    
    
    
    One day doing support. Damn, how I love development.    
    
    
    woohoo 90 minutes to finally get some coding done :)    
    
    
    Done my deeds for today. Good night!    
    
    
    Heh, looks like some extra time on the editor. "Just this little thing more" costs me hours of sleep    
    
    
    Anybody know where is the difference between a manual mouseclick on a button in CRM WebClient and javascript call: button.click(); ? #sapcrm    
    
    
    posted a question to the CRM forums regarding #WCUIF, Delta Handling and JavaScript http://bit.ly/cJEB0S #sapcrm    
    
    
    @thomas_jung Calling the noConflict() function in jQuery should take care of any conflicts. http://api.jquery.com/jQuery.noConflict/    
    
    
    @thomas_jung I am quite sure you already tried, but does not changing the include sequence of the libs help? Normal case: Last include wins.    
    
    
    Finally! Found the error and solved another of my SDN threads by myself. SAP documentation is worse in some places :(    
    
    
    Wow. I just withdrew from my first contract by chat. Times really change. Handling time < 5 minutes. I am impressed @klarmobilde    
    
    
    @se38 Hmm, sounds I should never publish anything on SCN ;-) Unless they promise me kidneys in exchange.    
    
    
    @se38 Yep. All questions asked on #SCN are for a company. Nobody has a SAP installation at home for private pleasures...    
    
    
    Forgot an FTP password today. Luckily I use #Filezilla that stores them in clear text in an XML file. Now thinking about security :-/    
    
    
    Refresh in Windows: F5. Refresh in SAP: F5 or F8 or SHIFT-CAPS-F6 or SHIFT-F2 or... What went wrong here?    
    
    
    I should start selling HTPC cases on ebay. The prices paid there are around 100 Euro higher than those I pay on Amazon...    
    
    
    Did anyone ever seemlessly integrate a standalone Java application into #SAP GUI? Just like Excel or Word?    
    
    
    How I hate forced rescheduling of my projects... but sometimes it benefits me more than anyone else :-)    
    
    
    Is it possible to use add. settypes (like in products) for order header? The EEWB documentation claims something like this.#sapcrm    
    
    
    Been musing with some colleagues about an older #SAP song. Anyone got a link to this. "S-A-P it is easy as 1-2-3" thing? Can not find it :(    
    
    
    Wanted to play The Witcher, released 2008. Now stuck downloading 2 GB of patches. What happend to games fitting on one 1.44" floppy?    
    
    
    The thing I like most about my notebook in winter: My fingers do not get cold :)    
    
    
    mcafee killed my daemon tools installation. piece of shit.    
    
    
    The TechEd website http://bit.ly/boBHqU can not be running on an SAP server. It is so responsive #sapteched    
    
    
    Learned something new today: In ABAP you can redefine methods as final. Better get a modification key to solve this "feature".    
    
    
    @se38 Nope. I was told that it is used by programmers to make use of the SE80 feature to collapse blocks of code. DO...ENDDO defines a block    
    
    
    My head is spinning. Read too much information today. At work could not do one thing undisturbed. Crazy day.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Thanks for the Video link. Now I managed to see what you did at #innowe10. Looks kinda cool. Got to get an iPhone ;-)    
    
    
    I got 7 days of vacation time left this year. Maybe I should start making use of it...    
    
    
    @yojibee Uhh I envy you. Tampa. Home of Bush Gardens and Tampa Bay Lightnings.    
    
    
    Found the Bat Cave! See maps.google.de with coordinates 26.358298,127.78389 . Only on satellite.    
    
    
    JavaScript is so very dirty. Registering anonymous functions for events is one thing. Deregistering them impossible without another variable    
    
    
    @thorstenster Preparing a workshop on SAP UI strategy. Ours, not SAP's - that would presuppose SAP has one. ;) <-- LOL, Tell me the outcome    
    
    
    @SergioFerrari You might actually like this page: http://www.thonky.com/qr-code-tutorial/part-3-mask-pattern/ … #qrcode    
    
    
    Design Layer in #sapcrm is complete junk. Not even possible to assign them by UI Object AND Subobject Type.    
    
    
    Hmm... Mailserver is configured to send out under any domain and it is highly trusted... Some system admins make me worry.    
    
    
    @yojibee @esjewett @maggiefox Wondering how GitHub and Google do the distribution.    
    
    
    @yojibee @esjewett @maggiefox Then I do prefer GitHub https://help.github.com/articles/github-terms-of-service … section F.1    
    
    
    Wuhu, learned something new today: How to rework generated table maintenance in SAP to do what I want :-)    
    
    
    After moving from Windows Mobile to Android I have problems remembering my SIM cards PIN code. #awkward    
    
    
    Putting a choclate bar next to your notebooks exhaust fan: #badidea    
    
    
    Interesting read about #amazon is letting your account be compromised: http://gizmodo.com/5969981/two+for+one-amazons-socially-engineered-replacement-order-scam …    
    
    
    It is so frustrating to find out that you wasted one hour debugging because the VMC buffered a customizing entry :-/    
    
    
    My laptop battery dies after 90 Minutes while surfing with mobile broadband. Time to get my book out.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor My framed @gapingvoid "Quality isn't Job One - Being totaly frickin' amazing is Job One" @SAPMentors <-- lol    
    
    
    #SAP developers doing a READ .. BINARY ... on an unsorted table in OneOrder search in #sapcrm. Third time we mention this to support :-(    
    
    
    My new Canon MG5450 works like a charm with Windows. Interactive setup, automatic discovery via WIFI.    
    
    
    Seems as if #ABAP does not allow recursive data structures :-( How do I model my folder with subfolders with subfolders... now?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Interesting that India leads every query in regards to SAP. Either people there like SAP or they search a lot.    
    
    
    @harshitkg @carkas @wolf_gregor Is it possible to activate absolute numbers in the Google graph or get them somehow else?    
    
    
    "Where can we find the customizing for BT BOL objects?" <- #sapcrm response in OSS to my error about a hardcoded BOL structure. So sad :-(    
    
    
    @sapcrm You got your post. Though I would have personally preferred to put it in the ranting forum. Feel free to move :-)    
    
    
    Why does PDFCreator always try to install some additional stuff on my PC when updating :-( Do not want PDFArchitect or Browser "Toolbar".    
    
    
    Dear #SAP developer: It is great you use method chaining in your ABAP! But please remember to catch exceptions from all methods.    
    
    
    One video that is really worth watching & considering: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F7pYHN9iC9I …    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge The COMPONENT_LOADING BAdI is the way to go. Queried during runtime and in workbench. Hard to put in 160 chars ;-)    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge Nevertheless I still see the problem in enhancing already enhanced components. Fear modifications are necessary.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge Did look into our #sapcrm system today. Class CL_BSP_WD_COMPONENT_DESCRIPTOR in CONSTRUCTOR. Needs modification.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge I used BAdI BSP_WD_APPL_WD for this task. Implemented both methods so that we get a /SYSKO/ as class prefix.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge Thought you were still in the "I want to create a template case". For new generation it is BAdI CLASS_GENERATION.    
    
    
    Just putting 23 MB/s through a network cable. Wishing wireless would be anywhere near that speed :-/    
    
    
    Wondering if starting Virtual PC with an image from external USB HDD is faster than from encrypted 2,5" internal HDD.    
    
    
    Adding a new field to GenIL component PML is probably going to take me the whole day. Great enhancement concept #sapcrm. No BAdI, no Appends    
    
    
    Using persistent classes as API for a GenIL component... Now even modification of standard will not help. How am I going to set my data?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor It is. In my case it is these Mail Forms that can be used as templates for outbound Emails.Link named "Mail Forms" in Marketing    
    
    
    Made new BOL objects possible in #sapcrm GenIL component PML by massive enhancements in class CL_CRM_PML_IL_MAILFORM.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor From me as well. I wish you a fantastic birthday and a succulent cake.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @tsanstef @roelvdberge Do you have a screen shot? I suspect CSS rendering error. Try a different Style in WebClient. #sapcrm    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @tsanstef @roelvdberge @sjohannes CHTMLB or THTMLB?Check BSP crm_thtmlb_test/multiAreaFrame.htm & BSP_DLC_OVW/OvwViewset.htm    
    
    
    Updating my #LinkedIN profile after 3 years of negligence. Quite confusing, but result looks good :-)    
    
    
    Interesting: #LinkedIn lets me add #XING as other profile on the web. #XING does not accept #LinkedIn.    
    
    
    Big fun: Explaining to SAP support that DELETE LT_ITAB will delete all entries in the table and not only the current line of the LOOP.    
    
    
    Colleagues of mine from forge #Reply are developing a computer game http://www.polygon.com/2013/3/26/4150380/joe-devers-lone-wolf-gamebooks-reborn-as-a-mobile-e-book-rpg-hybrid …
Fascinating where our company moves.    
    
    
    @Nicolas_Busson Yeah. Feels weird when english recruiters call for the first time. Gets annoying the umpteenth time.    
    
    
    Very good April Fools from YouTube: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H542nLTTbu0 …    
    
    
    And one from #Twitter themselves: http://blog.twitter.com/2013/03/annncng-twttr.html …    
    
    
    In for a treasure hunt? Google Maps april fools: http://maps.google.com/treasure . Way better than Google Nose an Gmail Blue.    
    
    
    @sjohannes Do you have a TOC for your #sapcrmtpp book already? Eager to know what is coming.    
    
    
    @sjohannes I am sure I can get sth out of it :-) Always looking for best practices and patterns. Our juniors need to learn too.    
    
    
    Anybody integrated a nice WYSIWYG Editor in #MantisBT ?    
    
    
    Wondering how long it takes before Excel is proposed as our bug tracking tool...    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @sjohannes You might be lucky with BAdI COM_PRODUCT_SE otherwise it is classes. Altered the product search a long time ago.    
    
    
    After upgrade to #sapcrm 712 it is migration to the #hana database tonight. *CrossingFingers*    
    
    
    First time logged on to our new #sapcrm 702 sandbox. Feels kind of awkward being the first user to create anything.    
    
    
    Born on the 31st of March? Not in #sapcrm. pic.twitter.com/YUe7TnqCbO    
    
    
    Space, the final frontier. Help me get there:
http://space.klm.com/place/2fad00bcb8c4e4a1574b98795b7abb92e18ad2c98d6de908e2dea7bbb036e276 … #KLMspace    
    
    
    @harshitkg @sjohannes @wolf_gregor @VishnAndr Wow, did draw some attention. Our systems are quite up to date #SAPCRM 701 SP 09 and 702 SP 06    
    
    
    @harshitkg @sjohannes @wolf_gregor @VishnAndr pic.twitter.com/3R9jpFKOpQ    
    
    
    @harshitkg @sjohannes @wolf_gregor @VishnAndr pic.twitter.com/AocDvIw8cu    
    
    
    Our #sapcrm after 712 upgrade and #HANA migration disconnects every hour from the database... Happy developing :-(    
    
    
    #ZoneAlarm Free setup features one really useful checkbox: "Skip all offers". One software I stay with for years.    
    
    
    Wondering if the #Amazon #kindle 3G map can be seen as developed areas also: http://client0.cellmaps.com/viewer_de.html     
    
    
    @se38 At least you are not alone. Hamburg can be nasty when it's rainy. Wish all of you a lot of fun @ #sithh.    
    
    
    @thomas_jung All these pictures make me want to go to Orlando again. Though i prefer the Universal Studio parks and Sea World.    
    
    
    @roelvdberge @lvhengel @thomasritter Oh how I wish I could have been there :-/ Any slides from #sithh going to be posted to the Wiki?    
    
    
    Just registered for #openSAP. Now find out what it is all about :-)    
    
    
    @se38 Do not worry.I'm a professional.I already know how to correctly spell HANA ;-) Lets see where it takes me.    
    
    
    @se38 Hmm, the final test for week one in #openSAP for #hana is only ten questions in 60 minutes? Did I miss something?    
    
    
    @roelvdberge @SAPPRESS @sjohannes Is it coming out tomorrow? Sap-press.de writes "end of June".    
    
    
    Testing phase is fun. Error description "Fields are not editable". My solution "Pressing the EDIT button will switch to change mode".    
    
    
    True words from SAP. Who would have guessed... pic.twitter.com/mcJn09bV7Z    
    
    
    @sjohannes @roelvdberge @Nicolas_Busson @harshitkg @wolf_gregor Had problems with AET and BW Datasource, too, manually adjusted the source.    
    
    
    So many people on #SCN writing about things they do not have a clue about: http://scn.sap.com/message/14141663 …    
    
    
    Now up for some more #BadgeVille configuration.    
    
    
    Enjoying Dr .Lorenzo Cavallaro: "That time there was no hotline: "Hey I took over a bot net. What should I do?" https://class.coursera.org/malsoftware-001/lecture/3 …    
    
    
    I am getting impressed really often today #coursera runs on Android in my dolphin browser. This includes videos! Good work guys!    
    
    
    5 minutes to another interesting meeting    
    
    
    When you are convinced the bottom is hit on #scn, someone replys to the thread without having read any of the posts http://scn.sap.com/message/14147155#14147155 …    
    
    
    @jpenninkhof @se38 I've recently been to Cuba. I understand Snowden. Wrong place when you are addicted to the Internet.Would prefer Ecuador.    
    
    
    I have watched 529 episodes of The Simpsons. What a massive amount. But just 9,2 days in 25 years.    
    
    
    @harshitkg Do you mean Audience Discovery&Targeting? Are we going to have the nifty graphics in CRM? http://www.saphana.com/community/learn/solutions/enterprise-applications/customer-intelligence …    
    
    
    #SAPCRM hero of refresh keys. CTRL+SHIFT+F6 - guess which transaction I am in.    
    
    
    The next part of my #roomba fails. Designed to outlife warranty by just two months. The second plastic gear is broken pic.twitter.com/FqfqP640E2    
    
    
    Finally made it back to Bavaria. See if #sapcrm 7.0 is now ready with EHP1... If not it will be a very boring day.    
    
    
    #sapcrm system is still grounded with the upgrade... will be a rather slow day with no development.    
    
    
    @se38 @thomas_jung SAP Press tells me it is available from February 2011... That is now... http://www.sap-press.de/2406    
    
    
    @sapcrm Concerning the #sapcrm EHP1 RampUp?I can't work because the customers system isn't running due to 3 open "very high" OSS messages    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @Nicolas_Busson @sjohannes @harshitkg @roelvdberge I also thought that SmartValuhe helps do the trick http://help.sap.com/saphelp_crm70/helpdata/en/80/d1fe7d1c814eeda259e30923ce3f63/frameset.htm …    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @Nicolas_Busson @sjohannes @harshitkg @roelvdberge SVH is the answer. Table CRMC_SVH_ENTRIES stores 5 values per INPUT field.    
    
    
    @sapcrm I asked for the numbers today. Two of the messages have been resolved meanwhile. The remaining is 93502/2011.    
    
    
    @sapcrm As mentioned I'm just an external consultant and not direclty involved in the upgrade process.I can only relay information. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Is #sap #scn currently down? Can not reach https://scn.sap.com/     
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @Nicolas_Busson @sjohannes @harshitkg @roelvdberge Suppose you have to do that yourself. JS is not there http://pastebin.com/9spHemQD     
    
    
    @se38 Really wondering if this helps in readability of ABAP. Inline DATA declarations... Do you know if ABAPDoc works for SAP GUI as well?    
    
    
    Ever wondered why things behave different in #sapcrm #webclient? Brilliant data interface by #sap pic.twitter.com/4ai1VoKihK    
    
    
    Latest patch on #sap #hana database. Hope it will run smoothly now.    
    
    
    @sjohannes Just reading the first chapters of your book http://www.sap-press.de/katalog/buecher/titel/gp/titelID-3194?GalileoSession=53681149A6-zwhUP72E … Thank you for mentioning me :-) My first time in a book.    
    
    
    The current #daftpunk album somehow reminds me of 8 bit soundtracks of the 80s computer games.    
    
    
    Some weeks ago s/o posted a link about #GMAIL and visualisation of contacts. Anybody still have it? Think article was written by @dahowlett    
    
    
    Ahh, holiday time in germany. My #sapcrm OSS messages have not seen any update during the last 3 weeks. Lucky they are not that important.    
    
    
    wondering if i should by #avm fritz!powerline adapters to tackle the jammed wireless channels in my area. Anybody any experience with this?    
    
    
    Nice! #sapcrm #ehp3 allows deep table enhancements using #aet. Also includes business partner dublicate check on #hana.    
    
    
    Hoped that #amazon would ship my parcel today. Obviously they are affected by the people on strike.    
    
    
    #spotify is the coolest thing ever for listening to video game music interpreted by big orchesters :-) Huge catalog. Just awesome.    
    
    
    Too much vor SAP: "The specified regulöar expression ".*(=0D|=0A|=0A=0D|=0D=0A).*" is too complex." I did not put the 'ö' there ;-)    
    
    
    Cool graphics of the world:
http://twistedsifter.com/2013/08/maps-that-will-help-you-make-sense-of-the-world/ …
I like #12    
    
    
    @Ascara In Deutschlan fehlt Legoland. England (AltonTowers, Thorpe,M&Ds).USA(SeaWorld,2*Universal,Disney-MK,Bush Gardens).Singapur(Universal    
    
    
    I really envy Startrek. An unkown vessel floating in space.First Contact.Then directly interface with their technology.Zero config required.    
    
    
    Spent two wonderful days at #AltonTowers. Have to say again: In my opinion the most scenic park I have ever been to.    
    
    
    Today it is Birmingham. Curry capital of the nation they say.    
    
    
    @pixelbase any recommendations on: indian Restaurant and a good leisure spa/swimming/bath?    
    
    
    On top of birmingham at the new library. Waiting for the elevator to the 9th floor.    
    
    
    "The ink my have run out" <- If the printer does not know for sure how should I? Not really happy with my #canon #5450 printer :-(    
    
    
    Still baffeld by the guard change at #Windsor castle. The band really played the #StarTrek TNG opening theme. #BritishHumor    
    
    
    @se38 @wolf_gregor I like it. The figure perfectly relates to the topic ;-)    
    
    
    Learned a about a new topic today "Social Loafing". Good thing: Teams reach the minimum productivity per person with 20.    
    
    
    Just making my way through campaign qualification of SAPs CRM Marketing eXpress solution for #SAPCRM. Plain horrible. Who developed this?    
    
    
    Worst coding seen today: Someone redefined a method with the remark that only then it calls other redefined methods. (They are not private!)    
    
    
    Wahh, they are using a test message class and only a single message. Writing all text hard into the code in msgv1 in german. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Lets see if I can train Spotify to play only Hip Hop songs for a radio station named "Evanescence"    
    
    
    Just installing #PDFCreator. Why does every program come with AddWare nowadays. And why do they always try to sneak it in. #fail    
    
    
    For #sapcrm developers. User Parameter WCF_POPUP_DBG = X lets the WebClient open PopUps in a normal Browser window. With a maximize button.    
    
    
    When I hear the title track of the film "Hackers" I still get this feeling :-)    
    
    
    Wonderful programming: LOOP AT... next statement is a CHECK. Why do we have LOOP with WHERE conditions again? #ABAP    
    
    
    Still wondering if my token does make any difference between 0 and O. Either I am very lucky or it does not.    
    
    
    Kudos to the the developers of #SAPCRM SavedSearch WebClient component. Best documented SAP code I have seen in years!    
    
    
    Time for the #Mediaportal 1.5 Upgrade. Since installation of 1.4 over 1.3 I had some minor issues. Thus it is time for a clean install.    
    
    
    I hate #samsung for not giving the Galaxy Tab 2 7.0 a USB plug instead of the proprietary connector. Charging is hell.    
    
    
    I have two chargers for all my mobile devices. One for my Samsung Galaxy Tab and one Micro USB fitting everything else.#fail    
    
    
    In top oft the Burji Khalifa in Dubai. Sun is down and still 33 degrees.    
    
    
    Our Italian @Reply_DE @ReplyLivingNet just release #LoneWolf to iOS and Android http://www.reply.eu/en/newsroom/newsitaly/readd/,15037 … Review here http://it.ign.com/recensione/10229/recensione-ipad-iphone-android-joe-dever-lone-wolf …    
    
    
    Excellent piece on #microcopy http://bokardo.com/archives/writing-microcopy/ … Wondering if this would help #sapcrm to be more user friendly.    
    
    
    Wondering if #SAP could do a SSO to alls SAP pages like SCN, MarketPlace, DSAG... without client side certificate.    
    
    
    Damn DHL just drove by without delivering my new display :-(    
    
    
    Ok, UPS passed our house, too. Suppose my display is not coming today.    
    
    
    Interesting "Value Help" seems to be a term coined by #SAP. Wondering why nearly no one else uses it. All "Input Help"?    
    
    
    No new display today either :-( UPS, DHL and DPD already passed."Instant availability" obviously means 4-5 days for http://www.notebooksektor.de     
    
    
    Finally finished my #Avisynth script to turn SBS 3d into line-interleave 3d for #Fujitsu P23T-6 FPR 3 using Media Player classic :-)    
    
    
    My first day enjoying #sapcrm EHP1. All custom fields in Quotation search are gone. Designlayer ate them. Need to be present in DesignObject    
    
    
    So much to do, so little time. Still no dinner. Maybe I should start training to sleep only once every 36 hours.    
    
    
    When computer games come alive: http://youtu.be/bYP4wKD-6J8     
    
    
    @sapcrmtpp @bussonnick @san2787 I would definitively recommend reading, helps you develop functionality that runs in CRM not just IC :-)    
    
    
    @JohannesSchnatz AFAIK it is planned maintenance until tomorrow. Read somthing like this during the week on #SCN.    
    
    
    Just heard that one of SAPs Product Managers was impressed by the product configuration UI I developed for #sapcrm WebClient :-)    
    
    
    Wanted to watch a movie this evening. Forgot it at home. This can still happen in our digital age.    
    
    
    Sometimes I am feeling really sorry for the guys in #sap support :-(    
    
    
    @bussonnick  I love that one =)    
    
    
    Who would have thought that #SAP delivers a solver for linear equations with every installation out of the box!?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @sjohannes @bussonnick Has anyone of you already seen the new "mobile" BSP Tags? The library is "M". See BSP App. CRM_M_FRAME.    
    
    
    @sjohannes @wolf_gregor @bussonnick Ahh thanks. First time I noticed it, but you are correct. Creation is around 2008. Too sad :-(    
    
    
    @bussonnick @sjohannes @wolf_gregor There is a CRM_M_TEST you can execute in SE80. Sadly it is not too impressive either.    
    
    
    @roelvdberge @bussonnick @wolf_gregor @sjohannes @h_neumann @harshitkg Too bad I have to wait until next year before our CRM gets EHP3    
    
    
    Now starting to read up on all the #sap #OpenUI5 stuff that happend today    
    
    
    Kreatives Schreiben - continued http://www.mykasper.net/joomla/index.php/stuff/7-kreatives-schreiben-continued …    
    
    
    Greetings to the @Reply_DE Social Media Command Center ;-)    
    
    
    @smashmouth goes christmas on http://open.spotify.com/album/7FbUjbPGtILUqdWSLIs5Tu …    
    
    
    Never thought #SAP could do such an awesome introduction to a library https://openui5.hana.ondemand.com/#content/Overview.html … #openui5. Kudos!    
    
    
    Everybody seriously thinking about investing in #BitCoins must be of a gambling nature http://bitcoincharts.com/charts/mtgoxUSD#rg360ztgCzm1g10zm2g25zv …    
    
    
    Time to update my Defy+ to Android 4.4.2. Hope everything works well.    
    
    
    Grml, finally got TWRP working after bootmenu in CWM. Now a reboot during CWM 11 flash :-( Phone seems bricked :-(    
    
    
    So much for a quick flash of Android 4.4.2.    
    
    
    OK. Back to Android 2.3.6 now with root.    
    
    
    Funny how much slower Android 2.3.6 is compared to 4.2. Thought it would be other way round.    
    
    
    Update from Stock worked perfectly. Finally my Defy+ is running Android 4.4.2 :-) Time to install the APPs.    
    
    
    Fair enough I can create Excel .XSLX files in XML. Anybody know how to create VBA Makros? They are binary in the .XSLM container.    
    
    
    Some #SCN threads really make my day: http://scn.sap.com/thread/3478474  . I should propably add another reply "We ask, but we do not listen".    
    
    
    When I sat down to write a QR Code generator in #ABAP, I never thought it would be so much work :-/    
    
    
    Sounds like you are having a lot of fun at #replyhackathon. Looking forward to the final presenatitions.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/LckhQ clearly shows why IE is not good. Lacking behind in feature implementation and JavaScript execution speed.    
    
    
    Am I doing something wrong? Customer has got 36 hour week. Everybody leaving about now... Got about 2 h left.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Customizing #sapcrm is never fun. Most of the time it is pain an sorrow.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor The #sap #dkom is only open for SAP employees, correct?    
    
    
    @sapcrm @wolf_gregor Do not get it? What questions? Customizing in SAPGUI being a pain in usability is not a question.    
    
    
    @yojibee You seem out of luck. Maybe you can do the same as @ttrapp and ask nuns to pray for you ;-)    
    
    
    @thorstenster @ttrapp @yojibee Maybe we can even do a iPray App. Afterwards extend it to "FernReiki" - http://bit.ly/clkn3p    
    
    
    Maybe I should do remote consulting. You send me 20 Euro and your problem.I think of you and your problem.If it gets solved I get 20 Euro +    
    
    
    "Sybase - An SAP company" -- Brilliant how some people treat english grammar in their company logos.    
    
    
    @esjewett The use of A and AN in english language: http://bit.ly/gywJ5y    
    
    
    @esjewett But maybe I am mistaken. Some people in the US told me that times are "more bad" recently...    
    
    
    @esjewett @se38 Interesting, that is what happens when you are german. I pronounce SAP like "ZAPP". I hate spelling out single letters ;-)    
    
    
    Woho, just ordered a whole lot of books from SAP Press. CRM WebClient, ABAP Performance, Next Generation ABAP development.    
    
    
    Arrived at Würzburg.Nobody on strike today :-)    
    
    
    Great #sapcrm got additional JS files,with priority.What do they to?!Select with ORDER BY ASCENDING then concatenate the includes DESCENDING    
    
    
    Wuhu. Customer went live with #sapcrm EHP1. System up and running. Still issues with dumps in shared memory. 500 MB just is not enough :(    
    
    
    @thorstenster Someone got the same idea as you had some months ago: https://weblogs.sdn.sap.com/pub/wlg/23714    
    
    
    IMG Starcraft 2 takes up 12 GB on my harddisk. That is a hundred times the capacity of my first hdd in 1994.    
    
    
    starcraft 2 is still installing. downloading a bunch of patches    
    
    
    How can I "teach" IE the nth-child() property of CSS3 ? Fear it is not supported until IE9 and I do need it for 7 and 8.    
    
    
    Android 3 tablets not going to be released soon. If I did not hate apples platform concept so much... naaah! Maybe I should buy Windows    
    
    
    Making my way through Infosets in SQ02. Anybody an idea how I can restrict those JOINs with a WHERE condition? #sapcrm    
    
    
    @paphko Congrats! When is the big party ,-)    
    
    
    @yojibee Ever heard of broadband? It is this new thingy that makes pages load faster than 56k ;-)    
    
    
    Got to take out Adobe Printforms for a ride again this week. Merge different forms to one pdf without page breaks.    
    
    
    Anybody know how to hook a JS function into the Send event of the ActiveX object of Outlook? Sending mail works.Need to do some stuff after.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @sapcrm brilliant! That one freaks me out every time. Fear SAP would have to change every DynPro manually...    
    
    
    Finally arrived in Iphofen. Train had a 60min delay as the one before us damaged the catenary right between Frankfurt & Aschaffenburg.    
    
    
    Gave me time to read the first pages of "Next generation ABAP development V2" by @thomas_jung & Rich Heilman. Well invested time :-)    
    
    
    @sjohannes I count Idiocracy as plausible. It got electrolyts and that is what plants crave. No really, sad as it sounds, it is plausible.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Do not care much bout that. Multiedit to change all "Title" and mode without marking every single line would be great.#sapcrm    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor and probably show more than 10 lines for Overviewpages. For Formviews always show Fielddetails an Available fields. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Customer asked me to transform @wolf_gregor 's ZAPP_INTEGRATOR from BSP to WebService. Quite challenging to get the client side cookie.    
    
    
    Darn, I still need to change my photo. Sitting here with short sleves and my photo got snow on it.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor In the hyperlink. In the HREF you can call JS. I extracted the SSO data there and appended it to the URL as GET parameter.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Not very nice, but didnt find other way. ServerSide cookie does not have the SSO2 info :-( Its only on the client.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Customer wants it as a simple link.This way it integrates smoothly in CRM fields just using GET_P method.No extra window opened    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Problem was: BSP opens a new blank page, then shows a download. Page stays open. Users complain. Solution: Do not us BSP.    
    
    
    @ttrapp Just had a look at the link. Google Refine looks just awesome!    
    
    
    Back from Turkey. Nice weather... sunshine all the time. Ready to start working again on monday.    
    
    
    Definitely need a new profile photo.    
    
    
    Finally managed to change my profile pic to sth without snow. Odd #Seesmic does not offer the functionality to do it?!    
    
    
    Just ordered myself an Acer Iconia 32GB http://amzn.to/jpzAa5 . Just could not refuse the deal ;-)    
    
    
    @thorstenster Security escorted you out while having lunch?! Must be quite an experience seeing you eating :-p    
    
    
    My Acer Iconia is just 10km away from my doorstep. Ordered yesterday. I am always amazed how fast AmazonDE is at processing and delivery.    
    
    
    My Iconia A500 arrived :-) installing updates right now    
    
    
    Recieved answer to one of our #sapcrm OSS messages. Summed up: We know its broke but we are not gonna fix it in CRM 6. Upgrade to CRM 7 EHP1    
    
    
    A new day brings: 2cm of new snow. Cold feet and having to brush my car clean before I could leave for work.    
    
    
    Just wanted to look at #FMDroid. Got to sign the #sap #codeexchange agreement first. Loosing interest.    
    
    
    Train broke today at FFM mainstation could only go at 140 km/h. Lost 20 minutes till Cologne. Wondering how fast the train usually is?    
    
    
    @paphko AldiTalk 15 Euro/Monat und sofort online. Hat mir gut geholfen :-)    
    
    
    "Do not be Apple!" - Just read that phrase as synonym for running a closed device/software policy. Maybe Apple finally made it into language    
    
    
    @esjewett The context clearly stated Acer should not lock the Bootloader of its Iconia.But you're right: iPad got a great user experience    
    
    
    I got numerous USB A->USB B, USB -> mini USB, USB -> micro USB, USB extensions. But not a single cable that fits into the Iconia A500 :-(    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor nice one. Did not get the requirement yet, but it is always good to see such solutions. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Just mention some buzzwords and you get a whole lot of new followers...    
    
    
    My new Zotac Zbox ID36 3d just arrived. Fitting in the components now. The PC looks like one nifty little console.    
    
    
    ok... found first problem... I do not have a keyboard to use with it :-( Darn.    
    
    
    Memory and HDD fit.PC boots up OK."No OS found.Please insert medium into selected boot device AND PRESS ANY KEY" - Off to buy a keyboard now    
    
    
    Got myself a new Logitech wireless keyboard. Local PC Shack not so bad, maybe try them out more often. Now installing Windows 7.    
    
    
    Windows 7 installation complete. Quite easy. Now configuring #XBMC to run on the #ZBOX. Wireless keyboard & mouse were a good investment!    
    
    
    Still installing drivers. Fractal Design Shape is very good choice for remote control! Even can control my mouse with it :-)    
    
    
    @thorstenster Do not forget to mention the cat. Has to be white, sit on the lap and be stroked while threatening or making demands.    
    
    
    Everybody preaches the end of facebook. Should I get an account to see what all the fuzz is about before it is over?    
    
    
    Men in Black - 14 years old and I still like the music. Am I becoming old? Is this a classic? What will my children say.    
    
    
    @yojibee If only one of the persons is orange, it must be a dutch guy ;-) They tend to have an orange touch.    
    
    
    Still got two .de domain names left in my package. Anybody suggestions what to register?    
    
    
    Anyone worked with #sapcrm EHP1 Action Menu using DesignLayer? I am getting actions displayed, but I can not click them.    
    
    
    Still in Bonn.Waiting for 5th train today.This time only 5mins delay.Cross fingers.    
    
    
    Now waiting for train #6 at Frankfurt airport.Last train was quite empty.    
    
    
    Wuhu final train #7!Arrived in Wurzburg, ready for dparture.Usally it is 3 trains.    
    
    
    @sapcrm did that already,it helps configuring,but not troubleshooting.Actions show up,but no events are triggered or rendered. #ehp1 #sapcrm    
    
    
    @sapcrm Thanks, but I already found the solution. SAP note 1575422. Go to get used to the new component CA-WUI-UI no longer CRM.    
    
    
    Just decided that I will never sign the current #SAP #CodeExchange policies.    
    
    
    @se38 Hopefully they change §4b.1 and §6b    
    
    
    @esjewett Thanks. I just hate the thought of contributing my free time and grant SAP the exclusive privilege to sell the communities work.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @se38 #apm Just a thought: Write some COM/OLE classes.They can be used from ABAP as a proxy for web access.Not brilliant,I know    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @sjohannes See note: 1259940. BADI_CRM_BP_UIU_AUTHORITY. Roles: B_BUPA_RLT & CRM_BPROLES & B_BUPA_GRP| Rel. Cat.: B_BUPR_BZT    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @sjohannes SAP note 1129682 mentions why B_BUPA_RLT no longer works in #sapcrm. Do not know if it might help with the problem    
    
    
    OK, off to our syskoplan company summer festival. Though it is raining should be a lot of fun.    
    
    
    Interesting story on #wikileaks an #cablegate on ARD (german television).Sad the documents do not date back to the Rosswell UFO incident :-p    
    
    
    Tried yesterday: Dropped Acer Iconia A500 from 1.5 meters onto stone. Landed on one of the edges. Still working, just missing some paint.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor You don't need a callback class unless for Subobjects.The interface is: IF_BSP_DLC_OBJ_TYPE_CALLBACK.See view: BSPDLCV_OBJ_TYPE    
    
    
    @sjohannes Book looks like the german version, but all authors are different? Wondering if it's different content as well. Is the TOC avail?    
    
    
    @sjohannes http://bit.ly/oGKmFe just answered my question. Content is different than german book by Tim Back, Uwe Reimitz & Michael Füchsle    
    
    
    @marilynpratt Quite an old joke. Edward Tufte told it about five years ago http://bit.ly/fS0fbC    
    
    
    35.000 Paypal accounts closed by now. http://bit.ly/o2JBoy seems to be a desaster for ebay. 1 Billion Stock loss. #oppaypal    
    
    
    "You sucessfully unsubscribed. As confirmation that you will not recieve any further mails from us we will send you a confirmation mail."    
    
    
    Does anyone know a BAdI or the like where I can adjust values of BUT000 when/before a BP is saved? Stop saving would be great, too.#sapcrm    
    
    
    There was a real flood coming down while driving home near Montabaur. Started with 26 °C, arrived with 16 °C. Summer in germany :-)    
    
    
    Starting my new book "ABAP performance tuning" by Hermann Gahm: http://amzn.to/o6gzqL    
    
    
    Just answered some questions in #SCN WebClient forum. Wondering why they are still the same as one year ago... always the same issues.    
    
    
    Can s/o explain what "Direct Sourcing" means in context of attracting new employees?    
    
    
    Google reader is annoying. Just when think you reached the page bottom it loads a couple of more lines. It is defacto endless scrolling.    
    
    
    Updated my XING and SDN profiles with information about my new/old employer http://www.reply.de    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Make sure they are written to tab AUSP.Do they show in TX BP?Got auth?GenIL class is CL_CRM_BUIL_MKT_ATTRIB. @sjohannes    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @sjohannes I would take a peek at the GenIL class CL_CRM_BUIL_MKT_ATTRIB first. It got the code to add mkt attribues correctly.    
    
    
    I am really shocked at what has been implemented in this CRM system. Why are fields added by EEWB if you can customize them? #sapcrm    
    
    
    @johanvanzijl It is marketing campaigns. Additional dates can be added in customizing, but new fields on campaign head were created instead.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Did you already read the german WebClient book? Are there enough differences to justify a buy?    
    
    
    @geirish I would guess a "showman"    
    
    
    OK, as no one seems to have heard about CL_BSP_WD_CONTEXT_NODE_TV2 I will dig into it today. I want this ALV. #sapcrm    
    
    
    @sapcrm You port the #AET to CRM 2007 and I will gladly use it :-) Anyway it was not me who modified using EEWB where customizing was due.    
    
    
    Started QuoteCompiler lets see what today did to my stocks :-(    
    
    
    Lol, there is only one stock in my depot that did well during all the time even today: Reply Deutschland AG, the company I work for.    
    
    
    My copy of "SAP WebClient" http://bit.ly/oBIg5P arrived. Gonna start reading tomorrow after I finish "ABAP - Performance Tuning" #sapcrm    
    
    
    "You've just made the first step to becoming an expert on the subject of SAP Web Client" <- Wonder what I did the the last 5 years.. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Uhh, it is really time consuming to get a hang of Joomla when you see it the first time.    
    
    
    Working on my third post CRM 7 EHP1 upgrade. Always the same problem with enhanced components and inactive services. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Anyone know how to assign a user ID to an employee in SAP CRM 7 EHP1? In WebClient fields are locked. Do not want to use TX BP. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Did Seesmic cut the "Sign in with Twitter" dialog for its Web Client? Need to get an account now... Back to good old Twitter.com client    
    
    
    @esjewett Do not think about it. We are talking about DB here. You even get problems if the ticket is not printed in A4 but A5.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Judging from your tweets it took you 18 hours to get to work on your bike?! Tough times...    
    
    
    Just enhancing PipelinePerformanceManagment views in #sapcrm. I have seen some weird coding the past years, but never sth like that!    
    
    
    If you ever wondered how to not use a dyn search tag and rebuild it on a BSP page have a look at view PPM_DYNSEARCH/Filter.htm. #sapcrm    
    
    
    I really hat this earphone jack on my Acer Iconia to look like the one for power. A USB charger could have been so cool.    
    
    
    Just got a forces logoff from the clients system. Seems I should call it a day.    
    
    
    Btw. Anyone got problems with locks on ServiceRequests in #sapcrm not being removed when creating a followup? Mine stay a whole session.    
    
    
    New York seems a little quite: http://bit.ly/pkpG3h  but still people on the street inspite of hurricane #Irene    
    
    
    Only two more weeks until holiday. Best thing: Afterwards I get rid of my #Volkswagen EOS :-) Finally free of this piece of crap.    
    
    
    Another highlight from #sapcrm Marketing xPress: Getting views by ViewArea number instead of ViewName. Once s/o changes the config --> dump!    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor: Just posted a long comment to @sjohannes blog post about the SAP WebClient book.    
    
    
    Century City in Los Angeles does exactly look like Sim City on Bing: http://binged.it/n73WU3     
    
    
    Wondering if I can access us4368.wdf.sap.corp from our local system. At least CRMCMP_SURVEY/SurveyEdit calls it on the BSP page #sapcrm    
    
    
    @esjewett Maybe they don't care? Maybe they got no QA? Bad thing for SAP: I can see their source. Not able to for other companies...    
    
    
    @pixelbase thanks for the write up. conversation looked interesting, but could not follow it on twitter. it is just the wrong platform ;-)    
    
    
    The #sapcrm Wiki looks like some shiny marketing presentation: http://bit.ly/qpxLSG  Even got contact details to a "Service Manager"    
    
    
    Just a test how many new followers some words bring: #apple #ipod #iphone #ipad    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Yeah, becomes really annoying for document templates in #sapcrm.    
    
    
    Last day at work before a four week holiday. Last day on project after nearly four years. Feeling like leaving a whole chapter of my life.    
    
    
    Just recieved a very nice present from my customer. Really hard leaving here :-/    
    
    
    First life sign from Singapore: We had fantastic first days.Feels just like NY-City just cheaper&cleaner.Tomorrow Universal.Than Malaysia    
    
    
    @geirish I feel with you. Got to be in Düsseldorf at 11am. Usual time would be 8am ;-) Lazy mondays.    
    
    
    Kuala Lumpur really is a nice city. According to our taxi driver the shopping malls are solely occupied by tourists. Next is East Malaysia.    
    
    
    sitting at Jakarta airport. Flight is due in 35 minutes.Finally back in germany tomorrow :-) 15.5h flight. Stops at Kuala Lumpur & Amsterdam    
    
    
    There is nothing as sweet as Jetlag. Waking you up at 3 am, not f***ing able to get back to sleep for 2 hours.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Fraueninsel... sounds delicious. Or is it some kind of shoe shop?    
    
    
    Have to document code inline...Now developer who was here before did not document anything. Am I to document for him as well?    
    
    
    @pixelbase Ask for the uplink  to the Internet. A Gigabit for a whole village probably ;-) Sound like the 21 MBits HSP+ joke    
    
    
    @esjewett Yeah, deleting SAP Consultings #sapcrm Xpress enhancements would be nasty :-)    
    
    
    @sjohannes Is that your desk? Didn't have a treat?    
    
    
    Automated Voice Response systems really freak me out. Spent 10 minutes shouting at my mobile while trying to track a letter. Deutsche Post    
    
    
    My SGS2 synced with google now I got all spammers in my address book and 1000 appointments I do not care about :-(    
    
    
    Does it really make sense to reproduce http://help.sap.com  in the SAP CRM Wiki? http://bit.ly/rZljIm  #sapcrm    
    
    
    #sapcrm EHP 2 hit the "Restricted Availablity" today. Still in ramp up, no unrestricted date shown, yet. Anyone some first impressions?    
    
    
    Sometimes I wonder who invented the #sapcrm status table CRM_JEST. It is such a hassle to select a transaction that does not have a status.    
    
    
    When a consultant asks me in which table he should put his developer key, he is probably no good development consultant...    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Maybe this helps http://bit.ly/s0VQko  @thomas_jung @ivanfemia @juliusbussche    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Or to put it short. It will be one of the C functions in the kernel ,-)    
    
    
    It is quite shocking to see s/o program the SPLIT command in ABAP manually. Ahh, might have been a good practive ;-)    
    
    
    Fascinating: THe fourth part of the Eclipse movies is categorized as Horror. Wonder if that is a mistake or a man who had to watch it :-p    
    
    
    Twitter really is ambient communication. Can not catch up reading the last two days. If I missed you, msg or mention me.    
    
    
    There is fun in SAP - For #sapcrm global attribute tags one of the developers maintained the "Ultimative Answer" with value "42"    
    
    
    New Firmware for my old SGH i900 Omnia. New UI is SPB Shell and Android skin. Super fast and really cool looking. iPhone beware :-p    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvberge @sjohannes @johanvanzil With exclusive lock OK. Though wouldn't do it. BDT issues: tx. BUS7 FMs not called by BOL.    
    
    
    Ok guys. Stop buying faster CPUs, start buying faster hard drives. Just decoding three files. CPUs are at 30%. HDD is running hot.    
    
    
    Just installed Seesmic on my mobile. Anyone suggestions for a twitter&google+ client?    
    
    
    trying to post from spb shell    
    
    
    Samsung has got a patent on smilies?! OMG 8-0    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @tpowlas @sjohannes @roelvberge @johanvanzil We are runnuing #sapcrm itsm here, including incidents, but no solman. Sorry    
    
    
    @thorstenster Why did you choose Ipad 2 over GalaxyTab or Iconia?    
    
    
    Dropped my phone today. Got it in a cover protecting 3 corners and the back. Guess which corner it landed on :-(    
    
    
    Saw Jurassic Park yesterday. Now I'm wondering: Is it a pun that they named the girl "Lex Murphy" = Murphy's Law?    
    
    
    @paphko Layered interfaces and steroscopic output... Sound fancy. But can I still use my phone for calling somebody?    
    
    
    Happy new year everyone. Had a great time yesterday watching fireworks in Düsseldorf.    
    
    
    Interesting: My company just installed a SAP HANA sandbox system. Now I am wondering what to do with it. Any suggestions?    
    
    
    Ran into a problem with RFW in #sapcrm. Searching for STATUS_COMMON and another criteria returns different results depending on MAX HITS.    
    
    
    #sapcrm MAX_HITS = 100 returns 60 results. MAX_HITS = 200 returns 90 results. Bug is in FM CRM_BSP_OIC_1O_SEARCH_FROM_RF. Anyone know this?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor No filter or BAdI implemented.I checked the code. It seems like an error. The results "vanish" in the FM from line 335 onwards.    
    
    
    @se38 Judging from that video it could even be bats in that tree ;-) Anyway I know we got parrots in germany. Seen some in Wiesbaden as well    
    
    
    Found the problem with the sRFW query in #sapcrm today. It is not FM CRM_BSP_OIC_1O_SEARCH_FROM_RF but class CL_CRM_SRQM_SRV_REQ_RUN_BTIL...    
    
    
    ...#sapcrm selects status schema according to process type, this leads to doubled criteria if two transaction typs share the same schema.    
    
    
    @sapcrm I filed the issue in OSS 0000019943/2012. Hope it will get solved soon :-) #sapcrm    
    
    
    Backupping my 2 TB NAS over LAN. Too sad Linux can not handle NTFS drives with good write data rates. FreeFileSync estimates 14h for 380GB    
    
    
    There is nothing more fun than sorting a large pile of files on a saturday evening. Hope the database does not break, ever.    
    
    
    Why does Win XP place a blinking cursor in an input field, but I can not type until I manually click it with the mouse?    
    
    
    @NicholasK71 @applebyj @dakoller Thanks for the input. But my difficulty is to imagine any such scenario. What is #hana good for in #sapcrm    
    
    
    @thorstenster Read the Hitchhikers guide. Otherwise watch Spaceballs.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @PatrickMeurer86 Very good wiki entry! Posted one small suggestion as a comment. Maybe you would want to update your code.    
    
    
    @pixelbase Yes. When writing classes ABAP sometimes messes up the sections. You can "activate anyway" and it works. Better is to repair.    
    
    
    Anyone know which is the preferred framework for customer developments with TREX in #sapcrm: SAF or SES?    
    
    
    Wow, Sheldon hat bei der Big bang theory auf Pro 7 ein total cooles Wascheflatteil.    
    
    
    @NicholasK71 @applebyj @dakoller sounds great. Thanks a lot. Helps me to get some feeling what #hana is good for.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor How is it possible to set up custom search objects with Enterprise Search? Looked at documentation and system today.    
    
    
    @se38 Still present on my #sapcrm system. Got any further information on plans SAP might have? Maybe a new interpreter?    
    
    
    @koljareiss On a note: I have seen people on Bali reserve their sun loungers exactly the same annoying way. Hardly any germans there...    
    
    
    /me hungrig. geht in die Küche. /part . *carkas has left #twitter. <-- Still remember this thing named IRC :-)    
    
    
    @ttrapp @thorstenster Did not one of you write a blog about Android and SUP? Just facing a new challenge: Setup SUP with Android Tablet.    
    
    
    Received a tweet some weeks ago. Was important info. Searching for it, can not find :-( Where can I search tweets I received?    
    
    
    @evabraham Nah, it was not directed to me. Just was a link I found very interesting. Clicked, read the articel and now need it again.    
    
    
    @evabraham Ja... Twitter ist halt echt "ambient communication". Bei ICQ oder IRC hat man wenigstens ne ordentliche History :-(    
    
    
    How would I get the rights to download SAP CRM Sales for Android from the market as described in this note 1664439? #sapcrm    
    
    
    Does anyone have a information about #sapcrm 5.2 Version. Need to compare it to current #sapcrm 7 EHP2. Some high level brochures ;-)    
    
    
    @sapcrm That looks very promising. Thanks a lot! Though it does not feature #sapcrm 5.2 but 6.0 should do as well.    
    
    
    @derphil Happy Birthday!    
    
    
    WTF?! Someone disabled old list view in SE16 for NW Mobile 7.1. Now I can not debug my values into the tables anymore. What to do?    
    
    
    @citoki There is no SE16N in any NetWeaver version. Suppose the note will not help.    
    
    
    @sapcrm Why can I try iPhone/iPad, Windows and Blackberry CRM Sales APPs, but have to buy Android right away? No download from Sap Store?    
    
    
    While digging into the enhancement concept of #sapcrm Sales for Mobile you find code dating back to 2008. Quite a long development.    
    
    
    @thorstenster Yep, same here. My colleagues got two contacts for SUP & CRM Sales. One Sybase one SAP. Both are not responsible :-)    
    
    
    @dakoller @findyourquarter Looks good. Would have needed that a year ago. Flat between work, sports, shopping,no airtraffic,public transport    
    
    
    @thorstenster @dakoller @findyourquarter @rhirsch Monetize: Charge the same as real est. agents,but offer real value throuhg personalization    
    
    
    Is there any free RDP and VNC viewer for Android supporting multiple servers? PocketCloud only supports one.    
    
    
    @se38 Cool. When on a windows machine and click "Install" it displays a different language after click on Sign-In and browser Back, Back.    
    
    
    @se38 Better try that on my Acer Iconia.    
    
    
    Coolest SAP related post recieved today. 1-click SAP Notes:  http://bit.ly/xbWKAo     
    
    
    Just starting to refactor some code that integrates WebClient with WebDynpro. Hope I can port everything to WebClient :-)    
    
    
    Software not working. My task is to port it to #sapcrm webclient and fix it. Would be a lot easier if I'd seen what it does before it broke.    
    
    
    SAPLogon started with 100MB this morning. Now it reserved more than 500MB. Wonder what it does with it. No additional modes opened.    
    
    
    For anybody who wishes to generate guided activity pages in #sapcrm with custom namespace: Implement note 1618875 before you start.    
    
    
    @se38 Das heisst doch "All your base are belong to us" #nda    
    
    
    Worst thing about ABAP method chaining: It works only with functional methods. No IMPORTING supported :-(    
    
    
    @esjewett I suppose returning parameters aren't that bad if you only pass references. Concerning internal tables I am quite unsure.    
    
    
    @esjewett Thouht tables would be handled as references as well and only copied after first change. Read sth like that a while ago.    
    
    
    My favourite dialog of the day: "Marked objects will be deleted. Delete anyway?" Wondering what the designer of this popup thought...    
    
    
    When inside an ABAP class I get another instance of this class, I can access the instances protected variables. Is this correct OO?    
    
    
    Employee in front of me to her colleague: "I had 357 new mails in my inbox. Deleted them all. Can not read them anyway".    
    
    
    #sapcrm displays a message that it doesn't work with FireFox 10. Use about:config with param general.useragent.override to change user agent    
    
    
    @esjewett It blocks with a BSP error: <htmlb:content>: (*) This browser is not supported; for Design2003 the Internet Explorer as of 5.50...    
    
    
    @esjewett The really bad part is the rest that was cut off before: "...and the Mozilla as of 1.75 are supported" <-- I'm on Firefox 10    
    
    
    Anybody problems with OSS today? Anytime I try to open a note I get a "500 - Dispatching Error" #sap    
    
    
    The graphical buying center in #sapcrm crashes about every 5 minutes. Wondering if it got problems with Java 1.6    
    
    
    Wanted to know about HDD encryption performance. #mcafee compares 7200rpm drive with ssd #fail http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=54bpHHmVX-c …    
    
    
    Social Media is not the answer to everything. Stores shut down on facebook:  http://bloom.bg/wzoUxj     
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Did you try to move enhanced #sapcrm components between systems using #SAPLink? Does it work?    
    
    
    Back from holiday. Arrived save and sound in Cologne this morning    
    
    
    Currently reading the Steve Jobs biography. Everything I ever suspected about Apple design seems to be true.    
    
    
    Just listening to an old Captain Jack album. #OMG    
    
    
    Ok, off on the Autobahn. Ready for X-MAS    
    
    
    Note to self: Jogging on a sunny day, good idea. Soaking your mobile with sweat while tracking your run, bad idea.    
    
    
    Does anyone know if note 938591 for SGWI is still valid in #sapcrm ehp1? It is mentioned in help (http://bit.ly/GUoAba  ) but released 2006.    
    
    
    I definitely need to log into SCN soon. Always getting emails that someone is following me.    
    
    
    @sapcrm Sadly that note does not help me as I need integration of Lotus Domino 8.5. sGWI Version 5 is Exchange only :-(    
    
    
    Hmm, new SCN is complicated at a first glance. Where are the forums?    
    
    
    @fredverheul Thanks, finally found the "ABAP community". Is it just me or did the loading times increase significantly?    
    
    
    Damn. I can not even search for "IMAP CLIENT" in the new #SCN. It always alters my search to "IMP" "CLIENT".    
    
    
    day of bad discoverings today. ABAP does not support sockets. Telnet is not installed. No clue if I can put a program into the java stack.    
    
    
    Has anyone tried the "new" #scn with a mobile browser yet? Does it work? Good?    
    
    
    Some of the older blogs look messed up in the new #scn http://bit.ly/HZgGR0     
    
    
    @thorstenster @antichrista Germans do not capitalize english words at random. We got a system: Only nouns.    
    
    
    @thorstenster @antichrista that looks gross. Though I have to admit I do it for titles as well -> Campaign Management . I like camel case.    
    
    
    If I need to get a Adobe Credentials file as described in note 736902 to create Interactive Forms by Adobe, do I have to pay for it?    
    
    
    @johanvanzijl DO you know if I need a license/credential per form or just one for our dev-system?    
    
    
    #TomTom still did not fix the HD Traffic bug. Wunderful three days easter traffic without information. The last #TomTom I have bought.    
    
    
    @sapcrm Did you find any information on server side Groupware Integration? Send you my mail address a while ago, but did not hear anything.    
    
    
    Iron skys cant be for real. Nazis from the dark side of the moon?? is it watchable?    
    
    
    #logitravel just cancelled my hotel booking for tomorrow. The alternative is 37 km away from destination. I hate trade fair weeks!!    
    
    
    Did anyone come up with a good solution to do drag and drop of files to Internet Explorer? Want to upload Images directly from clipboard.    
    
    
    Since I subscribed the new feeds for #scn blogs I get a lot of content that are not blogs in google reader. Anyone else got problems?    
    
    
    Interesting: After Android 4 update my mobile worked for 2 days. Then crashed repetedly. Factory reset did not help. Full wipe did until now    
    
    
    Please please please #sap give me an option to order the entries in SPRO alphabetically.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Just wondering: What is a #MBP?    
    
    
    My SGS2 arrived at samsung repair facility. Hoping for a fast solution to get my mobile back.    
    
    
    I am in a very bad mood. Lost my USB stick with some important data :-(    
    
    
    Looking for a new USB stick. This must be the most expensive stick ever: 8GB for 907,86 EUR.At least shipping is free. http://amzn.to/ekyPUa    
    
    
    Just paid 5% more for my online order,because the other dealer wanted me to create an account first.Lazy me.Hail to Amazon Marketplace    
    
    
    The people who programmed the WebClient part of the Account Factsheet in #sapcrm obviously did not know what they were doing.    
    
    
    5:30 and everybody has left. Kinda lonely in here. At least some cleaning ladies are here as well.    
    
    
    @geirish Ever tried throwing a coin?    
    
    
    @geirish Sounds like you got promoted. Congratulations.    
    
    
    syskoplan AG renewed their Special Expertise Partner status with SAP for 2010/2011: Including #sapcrm (and many others)    
    
    
    Wondering: Has anyone ever tried http://www.onlive.com/ by now? Found it pretty impressing about a year ago when I first heard of.    
    
    
    Just had a meddle around with www.wolframalpha.com . The previously hyped Google killer ;-) Anyone remember?    
    
    
    Logged in again after some weeks of abstinence. Hope I did not miss anything relevant :-)    
    
    
    A little bit later: Happy new year everybody!    
    
    
    Learned this weekend: Windows & Linux passwords are 0 security when you have physical access to the PC and Windows is not in a domain.    
    
    
    Grml... Have to copy whole class because variables are declared private in #sapcrm Office Integration handler. No means of accessing them :(    
    
    
    Tried yesterday for 4 hours to get ActiveSync to work with my mobile. This morning I booted my PC. Everything works fine. Miracles of tech.    
    
    
    Does anyone know how to convert special characters that were encoded to ISO-8859-1 back to UTF-8? ABAP converters won't do :(    
    
    
    Better question: Why do Adobe Forms crash on non-Unicode systems when they get ISO-8859-1 encoded strings that contain special chars?    
    
    
    @yojibee @dakoller told me that you might now about unicode in Adobe Forms. Interested in answering me some questions?    
    
    
    @yojibee I tried that once. Only answer was that I should go looking in the Adobe Forums. Maybe you're right and I should try again.    
    
    
    posted question to the #sap #adobe forums about unicode: https://forums.sdn.sap.com/thread.jspa?threadID=1763058    
    
    
    @yojibee Thanks a lot! Already done the posting part: https://forums.sdn.sap.com/thread.jspa?threadID=1763058    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor what is excel reader?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor nice! Thought about a parser myself for some time after abap2xslx came up. Though it is parsing CRM Configs to Excel and back.    
    
    
    Implemented Facebook like business partner search in #sapcrm today. Quite cool seeing the partners popup while you search.    
    
    
    @yojibee try reading a book. Maybe you can put a nifty sticker on it that says "iRead" ;-)    
    
    
    Once again disappointed by #sap support: We know it does not work. We do not like it either. We will not fix it.    
    
    
    Development system: Does not have data. Test system: Is not configured properly. So... only one system left for troubleshooting. Thrilling.    
    
    
    Differences in customer support: Wrote #TomTom an email 10 days ago. No reaction until I called them. #Amazon needed 40 minutes to respond.    
    
    
    @thomas_jung Any chance to get ahold of this "Encyclopedia WebDynpronica" without attending #sapteched? 203 pages is massive.    
    
    
    Ok... I need 60.000 Lufthansa Miles to get my free flight to Bush Gardens in California. Any ideas except: Fly Lufthansa and earn Miles?    
    
    
    Really enyoning this thread in #sapcrm forum: https://forums.sdn.sap.com/thread.jspa?messageID=9463595&#9463595    
    
    
    Those JavaScript libraries of the #sapcrm WebClient are huge. Does anyone have heard of some documentation about them?    
    
    
    @thomas_jung Your probably right. After looking up "witty banter": http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=witty%20banter    
    
    
    @thomas_jung Do not get it wrong, I just had a laugh how so unrelated meanings can come to one phrase.    
    
    
    I just installed #ZAKE on our server.It updated #ZAKE itself from the SVN.Now the class ZCL_ZAKE_SVN contains errors: ZAKE_HOME is undefined    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor We had a lot of problems with BT126H_MAIL as well. Lots of hardcoded stuff in the view. Check the inbound plugs.    
    
    
    Odysse continues: Finding someone who is actively using #sapcrm server groupware integration with #lotus #notes    
    
    
    Read this article earlier: http://tcrn.ch/aqvc7N Is it true for SAP ABAPers as well? I fear so. Maybe time to move on.    
    
    
    Service from #tomtom makes me wanna puke. They addressed the return parcel wrong and I notified them. Now they want me to fix it. #fail    
    
    
    ABAPs badly documented API just made me program a new method after searching for 30 min. Just finished I find the exact logic one call away.    
    
    
    Well at least I learned a lot about week day computations.    
    
    
    #tomtom service experience: After they send my device to "Stadt,DE", they ask for my address. Quoting my previous mail with my address in it    
    
    
    Anyone know how I can block #foursquare updates? They really get annoying not containing any valueable information.    
    
    
    @yojibee Do not give in. The last time it overwhelmed me a whole 300g chocolate mysteriously disappeared.    
    
    
    Finally finished consolidating customers print templates. Time for weekend.    
    
    
    grml. My #RoundCube installation stopped working two hours ago. After login just sends me back to login screen after a few seconds.    
    
    
    Got mail from @sjohannes "BTW: If you never need moderator assistance...let me know". Suppose I can do that ;-)    
    
    
    been configuring my webspace the whole evening. My guess is: I can not change any php variable at all.    
    
    
    @esjewett You staying at antarctica currently? Or is it just summer sunshine in your display?    
    
    
    @esjewett Oh, thought you ment "dark" literally. Got the shades closed here as well. Damn summer is coming round after all.    
    
    
    The trouble with my hosting provider encouraged me to set up #CrystalWebmail. Bases on #Roundcube, but looks a little bit nicer.Gonna use it    
    
    
    Woke up at 7am this morning, ready to go to work. Took me some minutes to recognize that it is a holiday and I just forgot my alarm clock.    
    
    
    @esjewett Ask them for the protocol they made when you got the car.    
    
    
    Finally #tomtom service send me back my navigation system. Took nearly one month and numerous emails/calls to get a replacement. #fail    
    
    
    Darn, I am tired. Think I am getting ill. Maybe @yojibee spread the desease with her tweets:-p    
    
    
    @Reply_DE Haben wir da was mit #ByOD geplant?    
    
    
    Signed #hilton loyalty program just to avoid spelling out my address every week over and over again for the bill.    
    
    
    You know how it is: Some days just suck - Montags könnt ich kotzen    
    
    
    Saw the first sneak peek of our #syskoplan #reply video. Even it its raw version looks interesting.    
    
    
    @esjewett I believe the first scentence says it all.In my opinion there are people in the forum just to gain points for "reputation"    
    
    
    @esjewett  you Don Not get points. I believe the entry is there to stress that. Bumping threads with "alibi"information is bad style also.    
    
    
    Found a new interesting idea for CRM WebClient on #sap #ideaplace https://ideas.sap.com/ideas/1214    
    
    
    Finally completed the Starcraft 1 - Terran campaign. Took me only like 14 years...    
    
    
    @dakoller Probably... But I am getting bored by the game again. Could take a couple of months for Zerg campaign.    
    
    
    My new satellite reciever just arrived. Cruel world: Sun is shining, got a telephone conference coming up and no time on the weekend :-(    
    
    
    @thorstenster I liked the Wynn while visiting Vegas, though it was mainly because of  their spectacular dinner buffet.Don't know room prices    
    
    
    Am I legally allowed to use a google map layer in my OpenLayers?It's no Google API: http://www.google.com/intl/de-DE_US/help/terms_maps.html    
    
    
    @kojote Ok, mail is on its way. Will write the issue up in more detail.    
    
    
    @pixelbase @thorstenster I thought every iPhone was to big parts manufactured by/with Samsung anyway. Nexus is Google, so same story.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Your #DemoJam contribution looks very promising. Hope I have some spare time to test it out in the future.    
    
    
    Cruel cruel world. Paint and PowerPoint are currently the tools I use most on my job.    
    
    
    Now I got it. The full #Adobe Reader is only available by FTP. HTTP only offers the installer.Too bad if you do not have internet everywhere    
    
    
    That's what I call errecting yourself a statue for lifetime. Even including some advertisement. #sapcrm pic.twitter.com/zcwyINPM    
    
    
    Looking for a job in corporate finance for a friend of mine near Cologne or in NRW. Is: Dipl. Kaufmann, #CFA. Ideas? Message me :-)    
    
    
    is looking for documentation on the TAJAX tag library    
    
    
    Anyone know if there is a kind of API for material configuration in ERP? Some function modules or classes?    
    
    
    My employer #Reply upgraded their facebook page with some videos http://de-de.facebook.com/reply.deutschland/app_264666250248559 … featuring guess who... me. Take a look if you dare.    
    
    
    Wondering if this Note from #sapcrm is for real https://service.sap.com/sap/support/notes/1664070 …    
    
    
    Doing PowerPoints all afternoon long. Oh my gosh, there is absolutely no fun in that.    
    
    
    @jpenninkhof They are waiting for "Nordsee" to open up. Fish is only fresh in the morning ;-)    
    
    
    @sjohannes Either put a slice between the pages or try this: http://www.naturesgardencandles.com/candlemaking-soap-supplies/item/bacon/-BACON-Fragrance-Oil.html …    
    
    
    It really is interesting to watch my #roomba clean the floor. Wondering if I could build this robot.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor The Note does nothing and contains no information. It just points to Note 1642681. #sgwi #sapcrm    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Interesting... why don't they just use the Note with the content directly?    
    
    
    Programming ABAP and JavaScript in parallel is like hell made of . and ;    
    
    
    SAP Note  http://bit.ly/hzV0l4 is linking to a SCN Blog to explain what has to be done. Nice one @sjohannes    
    
    
    Half the department is gone to #DSAG meeting today. Kinda empty here.    
    
    
    OMG, JavaScript is so fricking ugly. Took me an hour to figure out how to call an object function in an mouseover event supplying the event.    
    
    
    Whereas the hard part was to do it in setTimeout and call clearTimeout for the same instance when mouseout.    
    
    
    Anybody got ideas how to directly access views in WebClient components? An URL would be best. Got to display a view in a DIV overlay.#sapcrm    
    
    
    I really would love to hook up with one of the WCUIF developers and get some insight into the PopUp handling.Any ideas? #sap #wcuif #sapcrm    
    
    
    @se38 Started wondering after reading @e_bcorp. Is anyone actually using #twibap in business cases?    
    
    
    @sjohannes 1337658 - Ready/Not Ready radio button gray out and cannot be changed    
    
    
    One day doing support. Damn, how I love development.    
    
    
    woohoo 90 minutes to finally get some coding done :)    
    
    
    Done my deeds for today. Good night!    
    
    
    Heh, looks like some extra time on the editor. "Just this little thing more" costs me hours of sleep    
    
    
    Anybody know where is the difference between a manual mouseclick on a button in CRM WebClient and javascript call: button.click(); ? #sapcrm    
    
    
    posted a question to the CRM forums regarding #WCUIF, Delta Handling and JavaScript http://bit.ly/cJEB0S #sapcrm    
    
    
    @thomas_jung Calling the noConflict() function in jQuery should take care of any conflicts. http://api.jquery.com/jQuery.noConflict/    
    
    
    @thomas_jung I am quite sure you already tried, but does not changing the include sequence of the libs help? Normal case: Last include wins.    
    
    
    Finally! Found the error and solved another of my SDN threads by myself. SAP documentation is worse in some places :(    
    
    
    Wow. I just withdrew from my first contract by chat. Times really change. Handling time < 5 minutes. I am impressed @klarmobilde    
    
    
    @se38 Hmm, sounds I should never publish anything on SCN ;-) Unless they promise me kidneys in exchange.    
    
    
    @se38 Yep. All questions asked on #SCN are for a company. Nobody has a SAP installation at home for private pleasures...    
    
    
    Forgot an FTP password today. Luckily I use #Filezilla that stores them in clear text in an XML file. Now thinking about security :-/    
    
    
    Refresh in Windows: F5. Refresh in SAP: F5 or F8 or SHIFT-CAPS-F6 or SHIFT-F2 or... What went wrong here?    
    
    
    I should start selling HTPC cases on ebay. The prices paid there are around 100 Euro higher than those I pay on Amazon...    
    
    
    Did anyone ever seemlessly integrate a standalone Java application into #SAP GUI? Just like Excel or Word?    
    
    
    How I hate forced rescheduling of my projects... but sometimes it benefits me more than anyone else :-)    
    
    
    Is it possible to use add. settypes (like in products) for order header? The EEWB documentation claims something like this.#sapcrm    
    
    
    Been musing with some colleagues about an older #SAP song. Anyone got a link to this. "S-A-P it is easy as 1-2-3" thing? Can not find it :(    
    
    
    Wanted to play The Witcher, released 2008. Now stuck downloading 2 GB of patches. What happend to games fitting on one 1.44" floppy?    
    
    
    The thing I like most about my notebook in winter: My fingers do not get cold :)    
    
    
    mcafee killed my daemon tools installation. piece of shit.    
    
    
    The TechEd website http://bit.ly/boBHqU can not be running on an SAP server. It is so responsive #sapteched    
    
    
    Learned something new today: In ABAP you can redefine methods as final. Better get a modification key to solve this "feature".    
    
    
    @se38 Nope. I was told that it is used by programmers to make use of the SE80 feature to collapse blocks of code. DO...ENDDO defines a block    
    
    
    My head is spinning. Read too much information today. At work could not do one thing undisturbed. Crazy day.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Thanks for the Video link. Now I managed to see what you did at #innowe10. Looks kinda cool. Got to get an iPhone ;-)    
    
    
    I got 7 days of vacation time left this year. Maybe I should start making use of it...    
    
    
    @yojibee Uhh I envy you. Tampa. Home of Bush Gardens and Tampa Bay Lightnings.    
    
    
    Found the Bat Cave! See maps.google.de with coordinates 26.358298,127.78389 . Only on satellite.    
    
    
    JavaScript is so very dirty. Registering anonymous functions for events is one thing. Deregistering them impossible without another variable    
    
    
    @thorstenster Preparing a workshop on SAP UI strategy. Ours, not SAP's - that would presuppose SAP has one. ;) <-- LOL, Tell me the outcome    
    
    
    @SergioFerrari You might actually like this page: http://www.thonky.com/qr-code-tutorial/part-3-mask-pattern/ … #qrcode    
    
    
    Design Layer in #sapcrm is complete junk. Not even possible to assign them by UI Object AND Subobject Type.    
    
    
    Hmm... Mailserver is configured to send out under any domain and it is highly trusted... Some system admins make me worry.    
    
    
    @yojibee @esjewett @maggiefox Wondering how GitHub and Google do the distribution.    
    
    
    @yojibee @esjewett @maggiefox Then I do prefer GitHub https://help.github.com/articles/github-terms-of-service … section F.1    
    
    
    Wuhu, learned something new today: How to rework generated table maintenance in SAP to do what I want :-)    
    
    
    After moving from Windows Mobile to Android I have problems remembering my SIM cards PIN code. #awkward    
    
    
    Putting a choclate bar next to your notebooks exhaust fan: #badidea    
    
    
    Interesting read about #amazon is letting your account be compromised: http://gizmodo.com/5969981/two+for+one-amazons-socially-engineered-replacement-order-scam …    
    
    
    It is so frustrating to find out that you wasted one hour debugging because the VMC buffered a customizing entry :-/    
    
    
    My laptop battery dies after 90 Minutes while surfing with mobile broadband. Time to get my book out.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor My framed @gapingvoid "Quality isn't Job One - Being totaly frickin' amazing is Job One" @SAPMentors <-- lol    
    
    
    #SAP developers doing a READ .. BINARY ... on an unsorted table in OneOrder search in #sapcrm. Third time we mention this to support :-(    
    
    
    My new Canon MG5450 works like a charm with Windows. Interactive setup, automatic discovery via WIFI.    
    
    
    Seems as if #ABAP does not allow recursive data structures :-( How do I model my folder with subfolders with subfolders... now?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Interesting that India leads every query in regards to SAP. Either people there like SAP or they search a lot.    
    
    
    @harshitkg @carkas @wolf_gregor Is it possible to activate absolute numbers in the Google graph or get them somehow else?    
    
    
    "Where can we find the customizing for BT BOL objects?" <- #sapcrm response in OSS to my error about a hardcoded BOL structure. So sad :-(    
    
    
    @sapcrm You got your post. Though I would have personally preferred to put it in the ranting forum. Feel free to move :-)    
    
    
    Why does PDFCreator always try to install some additional stuff on my PC when updating :-( Do not want PDFArchitect or Browser "Toolbar".    
    
    
    Dear #SAP developer: It is great you use method chaining in your ABAP! But please remember to catch exceptions from all methods.    
    
    
    One video that is really worth watching & considering: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F7pYHN9iC9I …    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge The COMPONENT_LOADING BAdI is the way to go. Queried during runtime and in workbench. Hard to put in 160 chars ;-)    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge Nevertheless I still see the problem in enhancing already enhanced components. Fear modifications are necessary.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge Did look into our #sapcrm system today. Class CL_BSP_WD_COMPONENT_DESCRIPTOR in CONSTRUCTOR. Needs modification.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge I used BAdI BSP_WD_APPL_WD for this task. Implemented both methods so that we get a /SYSKO/ as class prefix.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @roelvdberge Thought you were still in the "I want to create a template case". For new generation it is BAdI CLASS_GENERATION.    
    
    
    Just putting 23 MB/s through a network cable. Wishing wireless would be anywhere near that speed :-/    
    
    
    Wondering if starting Virtual PC with an image from external USB HDD is faster than from encrypted 2,5" internal HDD.    
    
    
    Adding a new field to GenIL component PML is probably going to take me the whole day. Great enhancement concept #sapcrm. No BAdI, no Appends    
    
    
    Using persistent classes as API for a GenIL component... Now even modification of standard will not help. How am I going to set my data?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor It is. In my case it is these Mail Forms that can be used as templates for outbound Emails.Link named "Mail Forms" in Marketing    
    
    
    Made new BOL objects possible in #sapcrm GenIL component PML by massive enhancements in class CL_CRM_PML_IL_MAILFORM.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor From me as well. I wish you a fantastic birthday and a succulent cake.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @tsanstef @roelvdberge Do you have a screen shot? I suspect CSS rendering error. Try a different Style in WebClient. #sapcrm    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @tsanstef @roelvdberge @sjohannes CHTMLB or THTMLB?Check BSP crm_thtmlb_test/multiAreaFrame.htm & BSP_DLC_OVW/OvwViewset.htm    
    
    
    Updating my #LinkedIN profile after 3 years of negligence. Quite confusing, but result looks good :-)    
    
    
    Interesting: #LinkedIn lets me add #XING as other profile on the web. #XING does not accept #LinkedIn.    
    
    
    Big fun: Explaining to SAP support that DELETE LT_ITAB will delete all entries in the table and not only the current line of the LOOP.    
    
    
    Colleagues of mine from forge #Reply are developing a computer game http://www.polygon.com/2013/3/26/4150380/joe-devers-lone-wolf-gamebooks-reborn-as-a-mobile-e-book-rpg-hybrid …
Fascinating where our company moves.    
    
    
    @Nicolas_Busson Yeah. Feels weird when english recruiters call for the first time. Gets annoying the umpteenth time.    
    
    
    Very good April Fools from YouTube: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H542nLTTbu0 …    
    
    
    And one from #Twitter themselves: http://blog.twitter.com/2013/03/annncng-twttr.html …    
    
    
    In for a treasure hunt? Google Maps april fools: http://maps.google.com/treasure . Way better than Google Nose an Gmail Blue.    
    
    
    @sjohannes Do you have a TOC for your #sapcrmtpp book already? Eager to know what is coming.    
    
    
    @sjohannes I am sure I can get sth out of it :-) Always looking for best practices and patterns. Our juniors need to learn too.    
    
    
    Anybody integrated a nice WYSIWYG Editor in #MantisBT ?    
    
    
    Wondering how long it takes before Excel is proposed as our bug tracking tool...    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @sjohannes You might be lucky with BAdI COM_PRODUCT_SE otherwise it is classes. Altered the product search a long time ago.    
    
    
    After upgrade to #sapcrm 712 it is migration to the #hana database tonight. *CrossingFingers*    
    
    
    First time logged on to our new #sapcrm 702 sandbox. Feels kind of awkward being the first user to create anything.    
    
    
    Born on the 31st of March? Not in #sapcrm. pic.twitter.com/YUe7TnqCbO    
    
    
    Space, the final frontier. Help me get there:
http://space.klm.com/place/2fad00bcb8c4e4a1574b98795b7abb92e18ad2c98d6de908e2dea7bbb036e276 … #KLMspace    
    
    
    @harshitkg @sjohannes @wolf_gregor @VishnAndr Wow, did draw some attention. Our systems are quite up to date #SAPCRM 701 SP 09 and 702 SP 06    
    
    
    @harshitkg @sjohannes @wolf_gregor @VishnAndr pic.twitter.com/3R9jpFKOpQ    
    
    
    @harshitkg @sjohannes @wolf_gregor @VishnAndr pic.twitter.com/AocDvIw8cu    
    
    
    Our #sapcrm after 712 upgrade and #HANA migration disconnects every hour from the database... Happy developing :-(    
    
    
    #ZoneAlarm Free setup features one really useful checkbox: "Skip all offers". One software I stay with for years.    
    
    
    Wondering if the #Amazon #kindle 3G map can be seen as developed areas also: http://client0.cellmaps.com/viewer_de.html     
    
    
    @se38 At least you are not alone. Hamburg can be nasty when it's rainy. Wish all of you a lot of fun @ #sithh.    
    
    
    @thomas_jung All these pictures make me want to go to Orlando again. Though i prefer the Universal Studio parks and Sea World.    
    
    
    @roelvdberge @lvhengel @thomasritter Oh how I wish I could have been there :-/ Any slides from #sithh going to be posted to the Wiki?    
    
    
    Just registered for #openSAP. Now find out what it is all about :-)    
    
    
    @se38 Do not worry.I'm a professional.I already know how to correctly spell HANA ;-) Lets see where it takes me.    
    
    
    @se38 Hmm, the final test for week one in #openSAP for #hana is only ten questions in 60 minutes? Did I miss something?    
    
    
    @roelvdberge @SAPPRESS @sjohannes Is it coming out tomorrow? Sap-press.de writes "end of June".    
    
    
    Testing phase is fun. Error description "Fields are not editable". My solution "Pressing the EDIT button will switch to change mode".    
    
    
    True words from SAP. Who would have guessed... pic.twitter.com/mcJn09bV7Z    
    
    
    @sjohannes @roelvdberge @Nicolas_Busson @harshitkg @wolf_gregor Had problems with AET and BW Datasource, too, manually adjusted the source.    
    
    
    So many people on #SCN writing about things they do not have a clue about: http://scn.sap.com/message/14141663 …    
    
    
    Now up for some more #BadgeVille configuration.    
    
    
    Enjoying Dr .Lorenzo Cavallaro: "That time there was no hotline: "Hey I took over a bot net. What should I do?" https://class.coursera.org/malsoftware-001/lecture/3 …    
    
    
    I am getting impressed really often today #coursera runs on Android in my dolphin browser. This includes videos! Good work guys!    
    
    
    5 minutes to another interesting meeting    
    
    
    When you are convinced the bottom is hit on #scn, someone replys to the thread without having read any of the posts http://scn.sap.com/message/14147155#14147155 …    
    
    
    @jpenninkhof @se38 I've recently been to Cuba. I understand Snowden. Wrong place when you are addicted to the Internet.Would prefer Ecuador.    
    
    
    I have watched 529 episodes of The Simpsons. What a massive amount. But just 9,2 days in 25 years.    
    
    
    @harshitkg Do you mean Audience Discovery&Targeting? Are we going to have the nifty graphics in CRM? http://www.saphana.com/community/learn/solutions/enterprise-applications/customer-intelligence …    
    
    
    #SAPCRM hero of refresh keys. CTRL+SHIFT+F6 - guess which transaction I am in.    
    
    
    The next part of my #roomba fails. Designed to outlife warranty by just two months. The second plastic gear is broken pic.twitter.com/FqfqP640E2    
    
    
    Finally made it back to Bavaria. See if #sapcrm 7.0 is now ready with EHP1... If not it will be a very boring day.    
    
    
    #sapcrm system is still grounded with the upgrade... will be a rather slow day with no development.    
    
    
    @se38 @thomas_jung SAP Press tells me it is available from February 2011... That is now... http://www.sap-press.de/2406    
    
    
    @sapcrm Concerning the #sapcrm EHP1 RampUp?I can't work because the customers system isn't running due to 3 open "very high" OSS messages    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @Nicolas_Busson @sjohannes @harshitkg @roelvdberge I also thought that SmartValuhe helps do the trick http://help.sap.com/saphelp_crm70/helpdata/en/80/d1fe7d1c814eeda259e30923ce3f63/frameset.htm …    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @Nicolas_Busson @sjohannes @harshitkg @roelvdberge SVH is the answer. Table CRMC_SVH_ENTRIES stores 5 values per INPUT field.    
    
    
    @sapcrm I asked for the numbers today. Two of the messages have been resolved meanwhile. The remaining is 93502/2011.    
    
    
    @sapcrm As mentioned I'm just an external consultant and not direclty involved in the upgrade process.I can only relay information. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Is #sap #scn currently down? Can not reach https://scn.sap.com/     
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @Nicolas_Busson @sjohannes @harshitkg @roelvdberge Suppose you have to do that yourself. JS is not there http://pastebin.com/9spHemQD     
    
    
    @se38 Really wondering if this helps in readability of ABAP. Inline DATA declarations... Do you know if ABAPDoc works for SAP GUI as well?    
    
    
    Ever wondered why things behave different in #sapcrm #webclient? Brilliant data interface by #sap pic.twitter.com/4ai1VoKihK    
    
    
    Latest patch on #sap #hana database. Hope it will run smoothly now.    
    
    
    @sjohannes Just reading the first chapters of your book http://www.sap-press.de/katalog/buecher/titel/gp/titelID-3194?GalileoSession=53681149A6-zwhUP72E … Thank you for mentioning me :-) My first time in a book.    
    
    
    The current #daftpunk album somehow reminds me of 8 bit soundtracks of the 80s computer games.    
    
    
    Some weeks ago s/o posted a link about #GMAIL and visualisation of contacts. Anybody still have it? Think article was written by @dahowlett    
    
    
    Ahh, holiday time in germany. My #sapcrm OSS messages have not seen any update during the last 3 weeks. Lucky they are not that important.    
    
    
    wondering if i should by #avm fritz!powerline adapters to tackle the jammed wireless channels in my area. Anybody any experience with this?    
    
    
    Nice! #sapcrm #ehp3 allows deep table enhancements using #aet. Also includes business partner dublicate check on #hana.    
    
    
    Hoped that #amazon would ship my parcel today. Obviously they are affected by the people on strike.    
    
    
    #spotify is the coolest thing ever for listening to video game music interpreted by big orchesters :-) Huge catalog. Just awesome.    
    
    
    Too much vor SAP: "The specified regulöar expression ".*(=0D|=0A|=0A=0D|=0D=0A).*" is too complex." I did not put the 'ö' there ;-)    
    
    
    Cool graphics of the world:
http://twistedsifter.com/2013/08/maps-that-will-help-you-make-sense-of-the-world/ …
I like #12    
    
    
    @Ascara In Deutschlan fehlt Legoland. England (AltonTowers, Thorpe,M&Ds).USA(SeaWorld,2*Universal,Disney-MK,Bush Gardens).Singapur(Universal    
    
    
    I really envy Startrek. An unkown vessel floating in space.First Contact.Then directly interface with their technology.Zero config required.    
    
    
    Spent two wonderful days at #AltonTowers. Have to say again: In my opinion the most scenic park I have ever been to.    
    
    
    Today it is Birmingham. Curry capital of the nation they say.    
    
    
    @pixelbase any recommendations on: indian Restaurant and a good leisure spa/swimming/bath?    
    
    
    On top of birmingham at the new library. Waiting for the elevator to the 9th floor.    
    
    
    "The ink my have run out" <- If the printer does not know for sure how should I? Not really happy with my #canon #5450 printer :-(    
    
    
    Still baffeld by the guard change at #Windsor castle. The band really played the #StarTrek TNG opening theme. #BritishHumor    
    
    
    @se38 @wolf_gregor I like it. The figure perfectly relates to the topic ;-)    
    
    
    Learned a about a new topic today "Social Loafing". Good thing: Teams reach the minimum productivity per person with 20.    
    
    
    Just making my way through campaign qualification of SAPs CRM Marketing eXpress solution for #SAPCRM. Plain horrible. Who developed this?    
    
    
    Worst coding seen today: Someone redefined a method with the remark that only then it calls other redefined methods. (They are not private!)    
    
    
    Wahh, they are using a test message class and only a single message. Writing all text hard into the code in msgv1 in german. #sapcrm    
    
    
    Lets see if I can train Spotify to play only Hip Hop songs for a radio station named "Evanescence"    
    
    
    Just installing #PDFCreator. Why does every program come with AddWare nowadays. And why do they always try to sneak it in. #fail    
    
    
    For #sapcrm developers. User Parameter WCF_POPUP_DBG = X lets the WebClient open PopUps in a normal Browser window. With a maximize button.    
    
    
    When I hear the title track of the film "Hackers" I still get this feeling :-)    
    
    
    Wonderful programming: LOOP AT... next statement is a CHECK. Why do we have LOOP with WHERE conditions again? #ABAP    
    
    
    Still wondering if my token does make any difference between 0 and O. Either I am very lucky or it does not.    
    
    
    Kudos to the the developers of #SAPCRM SavedSearch WebClient component. Best documented SAP code I have seen in years!    
    
    
    Time for the #Mediaportal 1.5 Upgrade. Since installation of 1.4 over 1.3 I had some minor issues. Thus it is time for a clean install.    
    
    
    I hate #samsung for not giving the Galaxy Tab 2 7.0 a USB plug instead of the proprietary connector. Charging is hell.    
    
    
    I have two chargers for all my mobile devices. One for my Samsung Galaxy Tab and one Micro USB fitting everything else.#fail    
    
    
    In top oft the Burji Khalifa in Dubai. Sun is down and still 33 degrees.    
    
    
    Our Italian @Reply_DE @ReplyLivingNet just release #LoneWolf to iOS and Android http://www.reply.eu/en/newsroom/newsitaly/readd/,15037 … Review here http://it.ign.com/recensione/10229/recensione-ipad-iphone-android-joe-dever-lone-wolf …    
    
    
    Excellent piece on #microcopy http://bokardo.com/archives/writing-microcopy/ … Wondering if this would help #sapcrm to be more user friendly.    
    
    
    Wondering if #SAP could do a SSO to alls SAP pages like SCN, MarketPlace, DSAG... without client side certificate.    
    
    
    Damn DHL just drove by without delivering my new display :-(    
    
    
    Ok, UPS passed our house, too. Suppose my display is not coming today.    
    
    
    Interesting "Value Help" seems to be a term coined by #SAP. Wondering why nearly no one else uses it. All "Input Help"?    
    
    
    No new display today either :-( UPS, DHL and DPD already passed."Instant availability" obviously means 4-5 days for http://www.notebooksektor.de     
    
    
    Finally finished my #Avisynth script to turn SBS 3d into line-interleave 3d for #Fujitsu P23T-6 FPR 3 using Media Player classic :-)    
    
    
    My first day enjoying #sapcrm EHP1. All custom fields in Quotation search are gone. Designlayer ate them. Need to be present in DesignObject    
    
    
    So much to do, so little time. Still no dinner. Maybe I should start training to sleep only once every 36 hours.    
    
    
    When computer games come alive: http://youtu.be/bYP4wKD-6J8     
    
    
    @sapcrmtpp @bussonnick @san2787 I would definitively recommend reading, helps you develop functionality that runs in CRM not just IC :-)    
    
    
    @JohannesSchnatz AFAIK it is planned maintenance until tomorrow. Read somthing like this during the week on #SCN.    
    
    
    Just heard that one of SAPs Product Managers was impressed by the product configuration UI I developed for #sapcrm WebClient :-)    
    
    
    Wanted to watch a movie this evening. Forgot it at home. This can still happen in our digital age.    
    
    
    Sometimes I am feeling really sorry for the guys in #sap support :-(    
    
    
    @bussonnick  I love that one =)    
    
    
    Who would have thought that #SAP delivers a solver for linear equations with every installation out of the box!?    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor @sjohannes @bussonnick Has anyone of you already seen the new "mobile" BSP Tags? The library is "M". See BSP App. CRM_M_FRAME.    
    
    
    @sjohannes @wolf_gregor @bussonnick Ahh thanks. First time I noticed it, but you are correct. Creation is around 2008. Too sad :-(    
    
    
    @bussonnick @sjohannes @wolf_gregor There is a CRM_M_TEST you can execute in SE80. Sadly it is not too impressive either.    
    
    
    @roelvdberge @bussonnick @wolf_gregor @sjohannes @h_neumann @harshitkg Too bad I have to wait until next year before our CRM gets EHP3    
    
    
    Now starting to read up on all the #sap #OpenUI5 stuff that happend today    
    
    
    Kreatives Schreiben - continued http://www.mykasper.net/joomla/index.php/stuff/7-kreatives-schreiben-continued …    
    
    
    Greetings to the @Reply_DE Social Media Command Center ;-)    
    
    
    @smashmouth goes christmas on http://open.spotify.com/album/7FbUjbPGtILUqdWSLIs5Tu …    
    
    
    Never thought #SAP could do such an awesome introduction to a library https://openui5.hana.ondemand.com/#content/Overview.html … #openui5. Kudos!    
    
    
    Everybody seriously thinking about investing in #BitCoins must be of a gambling nature http://bitcoincharts.com/charts/mtgoxUSD#rg360ztgCzm1g10zm2g25zv …    
    
    
    Time to update my Defy+ to Android 4.4.2. Hope everything works well.    
    
    
    Grml, finally got TWRP working after bootmenu in CWM. Now a reboot during CWM 11 flash :-( Phone seems bricked :-(    
    
    
    So much for a quick flash of Android 4.4.2.    
    
    
    OK. Back to Android 2.3.6 now with root.    
    
    
    Funny how much slower Android 2.3.6 is compared to 4.2. Thought it would be other way round.    
    
    
    Update from Stock worked perfectly. Finally my Defy+ is running Android 4.4.2 :-) Time to install the APPs.    
    
    
    Fair enough I can create Excel .XSLX files in XML. Anybody know how to create VBA Makros? They are binary in the .XSLM container.    
    
    
    Some #SCN threads really make my day: http://scn.sap.com/thread/3478474  . I should propably add another reply "We ask, but we do not listen".    
    
    
    When I sat down to write a QR Code generator in #ABAP, I never thought it would be so much work :-/    
    
    
    Sounds like you are having a lot of fun at #replyhackathon. Looking forward to the final presenatitions.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/LckhQ clearly shows why IE is not good. Lacking behind in feature implementation and JavaScript execution speed.    
    
    
    Am I doing something wrong? Customer has got 36 hour week. Everybody leaving about now... Got about 2 h left.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor Customizing #sapcrm is never fun. Most of the time it is pain an sorrow.    
    
    
    @wolf_gregor The #sap #dkom is only open for SAP employees, correct?    
    
    
    @sapcrm @wolf_gregor Do not get it? What questions? Customizing in SAPGUI being a pain in usability is not a question.    
    
    
    @yojibee You seem out of luck. Maybe you can do the same as @ttrapp and ask nuns to pray for you ;-)    
    
    
    @thorstenster @ttrapp @yojibee Maybe we can even do a iPray App. Afterwards extend it to "FernReiki" - http://bit.ly/clkn3p    
    
    
    Maybe I should do remote consulting. You send me 20 Euro and your problem.I think of you and your problem.If it gets solved I get 20 Euro +    
    
    
    "Sybase - An SAP company" -- Brilliant how some people treat english grammar in their company logos.    
    
    
    @esjewett The use of A and AN in english language: http://bit.ly/gywJ5y    
    
    
    @esjewett But maybe I am mistaken. Some people in the US told me that times are "more bad" recently...    
    
    
    @esjewett @se38 Interesting, that is what happens when you are german. I pronounce SAP like "ZAPP". I hate spelling out single letters ;-)    
    
    
    Woho, just ordered a whole lot of books from SAP Press. CRM WebClient, ABAP Performance, Next Generation ABAP development.    
    
    
    Arrived at Würzburg.Nobody on strike today :-)    
    
    
    Great #sapcrm got additional JS files,with priority.What do they to?!Select with ORDER BY ASCENDING then concatenate the includes DESCENDING    
    
    
    Wuhu. Customer went live with #sapcrm EHP1. System up and running. Still issues with dumps in shared memory. 500 MB just is not enough :(    
    
    
    @thorstenster Someone got the same idea as you had some months ago: https://weblogs.sdn.sap.com/pub/wlg/23714    
    
    
    