@charliejssmith Please, furnish me with the deets!    
    
    
    @petermcneive Well, I'm seeking to fill the void of an Art Director in mine...    
    
    
    @digitalgurus kerching! Check me one time http://www.toverbanda.com     
    
    
    'A rather intolerable pain in the head, brother-sir. Should be over by this after-lunch.'    
    
    
    Imagine yourself runway modelling…. http://www.we7.com/listen/Malcolm-McLaren/Deep-In-Vogue/radio?song=232857 …    
    
    
    Cheap rashes bring me out in jewellery.    
    
    
    Ocelot like life. http://www.we7.com/listen/Depeche-Mode/Master-And-Servant-Single-Version--2006-Digital-Remaster/radio?song=726326 …    
    
    
    @garyfawcett1 @nicotatz Try www,http://toverbanda.com  instead #justsaying    
    
    
    'Reference example overleaf without referencing the fact it's an example overleaf' #FML    
    
    
    'You don't understand about runnin' with the gang, 'cos you don't...' http://www.we7.com/listen/Black-Lace/Gang-Bang/radio?song=1476490 …    
    
    
    'Pacific Rim' #chortle    
    
    
    The Aquabats! Burger Rain Music Video - The Hub: http://youtu.be/pYlafjh0qak     
    
    
    @TUnit916 howdy! Please tell me more! To whom should I send an email with my deets?    
    
    
    @DirectFocus so...may I reapply? Please?!    
    
    
    @TheDrum 'this is not just multichannel marketing...'    
    
    
    Gammadeus, Gammadeus, Gammadeus!    
    
    
    @Scribblingsnook Morning Snickers. How bist du?    
    
    
    @Scribblingsnook Not three bad. Got a few l'il schemes up me sleeve...You still Leino-ing or totes dedicated to booque?    
    
    
    @Scribblingsnook Cool - you working with 'em? Do send my love. Seen any other former Renegades lately?    
    
    
    Cilla is the new 'black' #busintraffic    
    
    
    @thebrandunion DM!    
    
    
    @TBWAManchester Yes. It could. But it's out of my hands now...#choosewiselyteam    
    
    
    @chomoi DM! What's the craic?    
    
    
    Oops! http://instagr.am/p/UbY0ktkn3R/     
    
    
    @a_copywriter Brevity? Heard she make a mean toasted cheese sandwich...    
    
    
    Crap. The Content Marketing Deluge. by @velocitytweets on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/dougkessler/crap-the-content-marketing-deluge …    
    
    
    I'm off the chain! (Glad 'cos it was starting to chafe).    
    
    
    Rhythmically brushin' my shoulders... http://www.we7.com/listen/Nelly/Hot-in-Herre/radio?song=1328158 …    
    
    
    @chomoi You're followed! In a non-stalky way of course...    
    
    
    @NMuels That makes you sound heavy though...    
    
    
    @snumo What up? Whassa best email to send to?    
    
    
    @DirectFocus That mean I'm outta the running? #ohman    
    
    
    Need to find a cult to help me self actualise. Any suggestions? Can't do the whole 'God' thing though. #roastlambofgod    
    
    
    Take a step back, look into the mirror. Surprise, Surprise like Cilla, it's a killer. #ohnothatstheword    
    
    
    Odd sensation. Bashed my knee but then got a soothing rush of adrenaline that's currently cooling my ears. Does that make me a masochist?    
    
    
    *Twiddles bow tie for effect*    
    
    
    @GinnyRoberson Hear you loud and clear. If you find any, lemme know too 'kay?    
    
    
    Mamals http://pinterest.com/pin/182536591118748574/ …    
    
    
    Sharp UFO http://pinterest.com/pin/182536591118748577/ …    
    
    
    Evidence suggests Mork used a Skype prototype during his end of show chats with Orson #comeinorson    
    
    
    'Gurning For Profit' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Back To Black: Cilla's Battle With Depression' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Hold On Tight: Confessions of a Clutch Bag' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Pump Up the Preserve: Formalising Popular Music' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Intermittent Dolphins: A Life in Divergent Thinking' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Sellafield: The Fallout' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Three Mile Island Dressing' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'The Adventures of Carl Fudge' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Master Don and the Winged Reptiles' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Felix: Cat Amongst The Pigeons' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Derek, Wine, And The Building Trade' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'When Felicity Arrives' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Father Dinner' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Standing Nonchalantly' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Epples, Bononos and Aranges' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Why Can't Bobby See Me?' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Fork Off: How I Learned To Love Knives And Spoons' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Do It For Margaret' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Berg Al Arac: John Nettles On Islam' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Pesky Tarians! A Life Eating Fish' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'The Court of King Prawn' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Ivan or Evan?' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Frog on the Tyne: A Francophile Adrift In Newcastle'#booksimaywrite    
    
    
    Finally, an opportune moment to break the horsemeat taboo here in the UK, and what does Tesco do? Apologise.   http://www.brandrepublic.com/bulletin/brandrepublicnewsbulletin/article/1167264/tesco-print-ads-apologise-horsemeat-contamination/?DCMP=EMC-CONBrandRepublicdailynewsbulletin …    
    
    
    3LW - No More (Baby I'ma Do Right): http://youtu.be/drvS9w-lTMc     
    
    
    'Take Your Momma Car Home...!' http://youtu.be/TsnEU5hFZGc     
    
    
    Am I Eukanuba?    
    
    
    Sheena: Full of Easton Promise http://www.we7.com/listen/Sheena-Easton/Morning-Train-Nine-To-Five--Edit/radio?song=1790280 …    
    
    
    Dane Bowers reveals a penchant for human lollipops… http://www.we7.com/listen/Another-Level/Freak-Me+/radio?song=283510 …    
    
    
    A1 takes a stand against group sex… http://www.we7.com/listen/A1/Be-The-First-To-Believe/radio?song=1549450 …    
    
    
    Black Lace stay true to their gangsta roots http://www.we7.com/listen/Black-Lace/Gang-Bang/radio?song=1476490 …    
    
    
    Ethnic stereotypes persist as 'Hula Mistress' from Waikiki sells pineapples, while playing ukulele http://www.we7.com/listen/Black-Lace/Agadoo/radio?song=1476472 …    
    
    
    @ChicagoHRgirl Howdy! May I email you directly about this?    
    
    
    Turns out I know all the lyrics to Pulp's Disco 2000 #whoknew
#chooőn    
    
    
    @FirstBSA Hi there. Hear weather's bad up in Chepstow - are services running as normal there?    
    
    
    @FirstBSA Is the X10/X11/X14 running ok?    
    
    
    @FirstBSA Thanking you:)    
    
    
    @CitizenGibbon Still reeling from the fact the man behind the toilet revamp’s surname is ‘Johns’    
    
    
    The devil’s not in the detail, it’s in the delivery #thinkaboutittakeasecond    
    
    
    This tune still punishes me…http://youtu.be/Qf87MJcWZQI     
    
    
    Goosebumps! http://youtu.be/gt-2Ijppbiw     
    
    
    How Advertising is Like Parenting Your Three-Year-Old Kid http://disq.us/8c6nyr     
    
    
    @claysummers Defo the Pomegranate. It can do everything else. Google it.    
    
    
    @PSFK Free coffee??    
    
    
    Former Collingwood pupils. Tell me I'm not only one to be haunted by memories of those draconian tyrants, the Richardsons...?    
    
    
    Stands nonchalantly, gestures pugilistically, fails dramatically.    
    
    
    Yeah, you guessed it, not found anything engaging to read this morning #needsmust    
    
    
    'Tell me, why did you get a 'ring'? You spoke during luncheon?! Want a slaaaap?!'    
    
    
    Long spindly fingers serve the acidic bite of searing pain on a quivering leg #collingwood    
    
    
    Fifty Shades of Richardson #collingwood    
    
    
    Man, when I blow that Rex what! http://youtu.be/dTek4AdPkik     
    
    
    Skunk, smell, tortoise in the shell. http://youtu.be/Ccq4oy0KZiI     
    
    
    @MMGYglobal *Raises hand* Hey! Right here! *Twiddles non existent bow tie for effect* Check me one time at http://www.toverbanda.com     
    
    
    @viacreative @refreshteesside I'm the cat! Check me one time: http://www.toverbanda.com     
    
    
    @Ethan_Jameson  Well, wouldn't mind having a crack on the old ice up there....you open to hiring from abroad??    
    
    
    Back pounding the streets...anyone need a copywriter? Can also be a PR or journo. Or a goatherder. I'm like Mr Ben, but with bills to pay.    
    
    
    @marketingjobsie Ding dong! Can I email you direct please?    
    
    
    @benisthemenace deets please monsieur! For the CW role.    
    
    
    @akihaytrabajo anyone I can email to apply directly?    
    
    
    @benisthemenace sure thang - dave@toverbanda.com - look forward to hearin' from ya.    
    
    
    Nothing lifts the spirits like a trip up the M5 in the driving rain with a Smiths CD for company #thisjoblesslark #copywriter #penforhire    
    
    
    Anyone know of a good place to hotdesk for the day in #Lydney or #Chepstow?    
    
    
    @Jimhaven Surely the response 'Like a boiled shoe coated in tar' would silence such an inane enquiry every time...?    
    
    
    'Want a facking slaaap?' Try it! http://ow.ly/i/1rFwQ  #collingwoodevil    
    
    
    The more time I spend among the general public, the more I realise that every single one of us lives an odd little life of quiet desperation    
    
    
    @JadeEliseMkting @Marketing_Chap Ready and waiting - drop me a mail - dave@toverbanda.com    
    
    
    @Nero Bless you Milo x    
    
    
    @joycebethoney Please, tell me more! Or email me dave@toverbanda.com    
    
    
    Who said unemployment didn't come with any benefits?...! #daddydaycare http://instagr.am/p/VL2o0fEn3B/     
    
    
    'That's not my Richardson! His beard is too fluffy.' #collingwood    
    
    
    'That's not my Richardson! Her fingers are too spindly' #collingwood    
    
    
    'That's not my Richardson! His demeanour is too jolly.' #collingwood    
    
    
    'That's my Richardson! His methods of torture are so mediaeval!' #collingwood    
    
    
    Yee harrr! http://instagr.am/p/VOdbomkn4L/     
    
    
    @andrew_shore The more I think about it the more barbaric it seems. The fear still haunts me. Especially now I'm a father.    
    
    
    43% of Belgians lose their virginity at Bring and Buy Sales #fact    
    
    
    One minute you're smashing crockery and sampling jam, the next you're fornicating whilst eating chips with mayo #bring #buy #sale #belgian    
    
    
    Turn a part of the body from a noun into a verb. Sounds like a way to inflict pain or an obscure sexual practice, doesn't it?    
    
    
    Why is there a plastic shark in my bed?? http://instagr.am/p/VSWrjREnw9/     
    
    
    Letter from Liz (The Queen, not my wife) and it's not even my 100th Birthday! Still it's seven months… http://instagr.am/p/VSWRmFknwY/     
    
    
    @BoydRoberts Sure - right here! And also - http://www.toverbanda.com 
Check me one time!    
    
    
    @dandanflood I'd love to - http://www.toverbanda.com  - or DM me for deets!    
    
    
    'Croydon...You're Croydon running through my veins' #alicecooperreworked    
    
    
    @amitbalan VUDU people!    
    
    
    @TwoBitCircus All roads lead to http://www.toverbanda.com ...or just dm me!    
    
    
    @jami_bee Am UK based but keen to find out more! Check me one time http://www.toverbanda.com     
    
    
    Any old, unwanted or disused words? Tired collateral or web content in need of a tune up? Then email dave@toverbanda.com    
    
    
    Any old, unwanted or disused words? Tired collateral or web content in need of a tune up? Then email dave@toverbanda.com #copywriter #ff    
    
    
    Duplo Duck Temple #toomuchtimeonmyhands http://instagr.am/p/VhctWUEn4N/     
    
    
    @strojer Hey Mikkel! Did you get my application? Whatcha think??    
    
    
    @strojer Excellent - keep a keen eye peeled! When's the deadline?    
    
    
    Dreamt a joke last night - Which crime writer is also a psychic? Frederick Foresight...    
    
    
    Hey, Findus! Hire me as your copywriter and we'll get that packaging updated. Just so I know, what's in your 'beef' crispy pancakes?    
    
    
    @cogsagency Any CW roles out that way??    
    
    
    @samuelcrocker Let's talk Samuel - ! dave@toverbanda.com    
    
    
    @BlandyDoes If you're happy to work with someone slightly further afield - I'm right here in Gloucs!    
    
    
    @Helen_McCarrron @Creative_Boom Got any CW roles in the South West going on??    
    
    
    Really fucking hate that Trevor Nelson Collection ad. Shiny smug git endorsing an eclectic spool of second rate easy listening tunes.    
    
    
    @Type_Emma Move the agency to Bristol and we're in business! Are you open to freelancers??    
    
    
    @seanuk I'm there! dave@toverbanda.com    
    
    
    @DigitSign Pass it this way! dave@toverbanda.com    
    
    
    @gingertcg Check me one time - http://toverbanda.com  - dave@toverbanda.com !    
    
    
    @GlosJobs Howdy! Y'all got any work for a sharp shootin' copywriter needin' a little silver? dave@toverbanda.com. Thanking ya kindly...    
    
    
    @jbvit_sf aren't we all darling, aren't we all...    
    
    
    At what point does being 'a bit fat' become life threatening? Thinking of becoming morbidly obese to mask my housebound unemployment shame..    
    
    
    And I thought the show 'Splash' was TV at its worst..but that was before I knew 'Love in the Wild' existed.    
    
    
    @HayesThompson Bingo!    
    
    
    @big_bazzle Sounds interesting - drop me a line! dave@toverbanda.com    
    
    
    Can you walk slowly and sensuously down a corridor? Then you too could join the Honeyz new line up #bigreunion    
    
    
    @HayesThompson Dunno. Enlighten me...    
    
    
    @PMahon2011 @DialogueIreland To whom do I send an email of application??    
    
    
    @MissJJN oh bugger! Need to delete it anyway...    
    
    
    Googie Knight! http://instagr.am/p/V1UEeckn9H/     
    
    
    @LinnihanFoy So, uh, I hear you're looking for a copywriter...I'm the cat! See why at http://www.toverbanda.com !    
    
    
    @RovioHQ I did! Yesterday in fact. Still not convinced? Check me one time: http://www.toverbanda.com , or check me two time:...    
    
    
    @KerryKatona7 You can run and tell that homegirl, homegirl!    
    
    
    @hollybrocks That's Wordwang! #thatmitchellandwebblook    
    
    
    @PSFK @HamillHimself @guardian 'Use The Fork, Luke: Obi- Wan On Dining Etiquette' #anotherbookyoucouldmerchandise    
    
    
    @captainsboston You've obviously not seen the YouTube video to promote the crappily titled 'Pink Champagne and Apple Juice'...    
    
    
    Welcome to the Last Supper! Our special today is battered God...and chips. Add curry sauce or mushy peas for just £1.    
    
    
    @RobTrapnell Gonna butt in and say 'I'm interested!'...    
    
    
    @RobTrapnell  You know what? That's the only time I can't do next week! Be great to meet up anyway. What day's are you free next week?    
    
    
    Mrs Mc'Epic'Phail #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    Rrrrrosie Redstick. The surprising alternative to Boris Breadstick #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    Snarling harpies instead of teachers. #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    Mashed potato containing mystery 'black bits'. Delightfully served by an androgynous trout called Mrs Pratt. #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    Bimonthly bowls of sick masquerading as soup #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    4 year olds eating lunch in complete silence #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    Dinner blazers. Sandals or plimsolls. Satchels. Caps. #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    A playground containing a climbing frame that no-one was allowed to climb on #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    'And some of us are leaving, our Collingwood days are done. But we will all remember them and treasure them, every one.'#collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    I'm a hog. Je suis un hog. Hoggy, Hog, and Hoggy #hogtv    
    
    
    The Yeeeeeeeeeeellow Book #collingwoodreloaded    
    
    
    What's Up, Catsup? #noideaatallaboutthis    
    
    
    Nancy Narcissist, I'd like you to meet Derek Diatribe...    
    
    
    @RobTrapnell Cool. I'll be in touch...    
    
    
    CGI butt trumpets. More real than real butt trumpets.    
    
    
    No hands! http://instagr.am/p/WMYf2LEn3D/     
    
    
    @juliaadlib Check me one time! Sent you my deets already!    
    
    
    @lizbonline Oh I'm so applying for that!    
    
    
    @sarahmoir Oh Sarah! If you'd just give me a chance here...    
    
    
    @swcreativejobs @TeamSocialHeads I've applied! Freeze the recruitment drive!    
    
    
    @Lucy_Lawson Whatcha need? Someone remote or in-house?    
    
    
    @weareemo Howdy! Ah jes' sent in mah applercation...Y'all git it?    
    
    
    @mediaguardian Some public school traditions never die do they?    
    
    
    @gavrog @LBiEdinburgh Don't s'pose you've got a CW one going as well have you?    
    
    
    Reply to @davetrott What does that make The Tonys then?    
    
    
    @vikkichowney I'd be more impressed if it was a deer, with sparkling antler detail that's velvety to the touch. A boy can dream I spose.    
    
    
    Channel marketers at Chanel must have the most confusing job titles.    
    
    
    @Scribblingsnook @vikkichowney Well, one must remain chipper Snookie. One must try at least...    
    
    
    @albionlondon Finally, having Predator-like vision can save lives!    
    
    
    @guardian And the food's getting worse I guess. Neigh doubt about that.    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck How bout a tweet campaign to quell his anger    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck If we can harness the power of social to send him happy thoughts, we can put him in the right frame of mind.    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sjvUX1CEdL4 … Or should that be oyster for the duck?    
    
    
    As @Seal has ears, surely he should be called Sealion. @SnoopLion you've made a leonine transition. Can you offer any advice?    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck Well, we need a 'Bob - Anger chart' for starters....    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck ...Followed by a real time app to sync positive tweets with his reduction in temper...    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck ...And an objective - i.e. if he reaches his target in x days, then y will employ him...    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck ...This would all need to be housed on a web page, enabling supporters to literally see his anger go down - or indeed up    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck Of course there will be 'haters' who won't want Bob to get a job, so we need to work against this.    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck Bob will need to vet tweets in real time and respond to both good and bad. In doing this we're raising his profile...    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck ...And increasing his chances of employment with our cause...so whatcha think?    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck Give me someone who can build and design the web page/anger chart and I can handle the rest...    
    
    
    Nursery rhyme matriarch resorts to theft to feed dog #oldmuggerhubbard    
    
    
    15 kid single mum vacates shoe for plush wellington mansion on taxpayers' dime    
    
    
    @MonnyMoo79 Ding dong! How can I help?    
    
    
    @IdentityKits I'm just a hop away in Gloucs...DM me!    
    
    
    Turtle babies! http://instagr.am/p/WWnCmbEn_m/     
    
    
    Oh my! http://instagr.am/p/WWnI7xkn_r/     
    
    
    Breach Penguin egg birth! http://instagr.am/p/WW9ygwkn0c/     
    
    
    @Mills_W Me too. Good to see horses do something useful - other than bulk up our processed beef!    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck So. We making this happen then??    
    
    
    @charltonbrooker @danielmaier It's like the Shake and Vac. But 2.0    
    
    
    @sab_official stop time. Mostly.    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM @BobMcDuck Bob don't seem into it though...    
    
    
    @SechinTower Don't you mean Optimus Primary??    
    
    
    If you can't identify the local din, then chances are it's you. Or me. If I live near you.    
    
    
    New idea. Smart phones powered by methane. Parp phones #holdtobuttheyprestocharged    
    
    
    Jesus and champagne. Lounging in a holy hot tub.    
    
    
    Once you've had personal trainer, round two's a no brainer! #jobsatisfaction    
    
    
    @BrandWriter @Srostohar @T3ThinkTank Sounds like a plan! Kinda broke though. Any spare tickets...and maybe airfare #sxswenvy    
    
    
    @Bristol_Media Oh I am soooo doing that!!    
    
    
    @weareemo Y'all still looking?    
    
    
    Am giving serious thought to wearing a three corner hat. Should enchance my quest to appear more Jacobean.    
    
    
    Old King Coleford was a merry old Salford, and a merry old Salford was he....    
    
    
    Pogo Sticks? Unicycles? Dogs with pointy hats and ruffled collars? That's how the Circus gets you...    
    
    
    @MissJJN Yes. I do good?    
    
    
    So, finally here @UCASMedia @ucas_online Don't y'all be stranger...stop by, say hi!    
    
    
    So begins day 2 at UCAS. Think of me as Ryu from Street Fighter 2. The pen, however, is my weapon of choice. 'Uuuuuucas! Uuuuucas!'    
    
    
    Ketchup Brand Felix Immortalizes Its Facebook Fans In…Ketchup http://www.fastcocreate.com/node/1682599  via @FastCoCreate    
    
    
    Ain't nuthin' goin' on but the sandwich.    
    
    
    @big_eye_deers There is little gastronomically delightful about a hog's anus #yumyumpigsbum    
    
    
    @big_eye_deers We need a new phrase to illustrate deliciousness...    
    
    
    @big_eye_deers How about 'delightful, delightful, chocolate trifle' ??    
    
    
    @big_eye_deers You must send me a piece then!    
    
    
    @big_eye_deers so what else you got? #winnerwinnerchickendinner    
    
    
    @CrunchyMedia Please, call me 'Dave'.    
    
    
    @CrunchyMedia Crunchy eh?    
    
    
    @CrunchyMedia Not three bad at all...got a real job and everything!    
    
    
    @CrunchyMedia UCAS! I'm the new copywriter - since yesterday.    
    
    
    @CrunchyMedia Got an opp to push your way actually...will send deets across...    
    
    
    @CrunchyMedia Yesterday!    
    
    
    People with the surname 'Richardson'. To save valuable time consider shortening your name to 'Dixon'.    
    
    
    @TheDrum Sure. Mostly debate around which brand each TV ad relates to...    
    
    
    Recruiters. Y U No Write Good Job Ad? http://www.welove9am.com/blog/recruiters.-y-u-no-write-good-job-ad …    
    
    
    @danebowers So...are we gonna see AL back together in ITV's Big Reunion? C'mon you'd knock Blue for six!    
    
    
    @RovioHQ Rovio, O Rovio. Where for art thou, Rovio? Did you find a new copywriter yet??    
    
    
    @strojer Hi Mikkel. Hope all's well. You still recruiting for a copywriter huh?    
    
    
    @markchalmers Grand news on your new position, Mr C! Big congrats to you.    
    
    
    @strojer Does that mean I'm still in the running???    
    
    
    Dreamt I started an ad agency called 'Magnificent Shields' #maybeoneday    
    
    
    @KerryKatona7 Can you confirm Another Level are joining the line up?    
    
    
    Cross-eyed brands see double digit growth both on and offline #fact    
    
    
    A quarter of UK citizens say they make up 25% of the population #truedat    
    
    
    @Thisisglos Smash, crash, squelch!    
    
    
    @TheEconomist Aren't they the disciples in formal business attire?    
    
    
    I think I'll wear for Easter a bonnet made of lace.    
    
    
    Still love the courtroom imagery conjured by Blue's 'All Rise' #bigreunion    
    
    
    And who could forget the 'polyphonic ringtone' opening to 'Fly By'...?#bigreunion    
    
    
    Or the cheeky reference to 'All Rise' in the intro to 'Too Close' literally inviting us to dance like a sensual call to action #bigreunion    
    
    
    But what is said immediately before 'All Rise' in the 'Too Close' intro? Sounds like 'Bruv. God damn' in a muffled robotic tone #bigreunion    
    
    
    But all this aside, I've a newfound affection for Anthony Costa. He's on track to replace Dane Bowers as my boy band man crush #bigreunion    
    
    
    And just how old is Spike from 911? He looks like he'd benefit from a good spoonful of cod liver oil to limber up his joints #bigreunion    
    
    
    Always great to see Danny Dyer on #celebjuice. He's everything a man should be...    
    
    
    Oh well. Back to celeb spotting in my new job. Sigourney Weaver works in the commercial dept...    
    
    
    ...Ross Kemp drives a forklift truck here too...    
    
    
    And I've seen five different Paul McKennas. What will today bring??    
    
    
    General Smarm of McKenna....    
    
    
    Poetic? Just is.    
    
    
    @virginmedia H from Steps in HD. Defo.    
    
    
    @virginmedia Actually it'll be a joy to see the wrinkles on Paxman's face in no holds barred high defintion.    
    
    
    @virginmedia or Michel Roux Jr's signature Gallic charm...    
    
    
    @virginmedia But most of all I'll enjoy seeing the golden aura emanating from Kate Humble's wispy locks. Finally.    
    
    
    @virginmedia Yeah. Bet he started on them for ten...    
    
    
    Who'd emerge as victor in the battle of Mousse T vs. Hot and Juicy?    
    
    
    @leeclowsbeard Have you ever considered entering a Whisker Contest? Y'know where hairy men preen themselves for bearded glory?    
    
    
    @leeclowsbeard Ever get food stuck in you?    
    
    
    @leeclowsbeard Fave celeb beard?    
    
    
    @leeclowsbeard Is it safe?    
    
    
    Hold out your arms with palms facing upwards. Now shrug your shoulders rhythmically. Hey presto! Instant street dance!    
    
    
    I once penned a letter in red ink to suggest my anger. I also used an impossible date to accentuate my contempt. #36/90/876000    
    
    
    If I were to tame lions, I'd ensure I finished my routine with a gesture and a smile.    
    
    
    Old procrastinators never die. They don't get around to it.    
    
    
    Aaaargh! Stop bringing the electric seagull to orgasm! #madeinchelseathemetune    
    
    
    Laughed out loud to myself outside train station. This was in my head...'Uncle Fungal. Mother's brother unleashes mighty mushroom' #wtfidk    
    
    
    @MichelleSacco @clarkythetitan Go Team Bechelle! Rooting for y'all! #loveinthewild    
    
    
    Just read the word 'Samsung' as 'Sausage' #needmorecoffee    
    
    
    @MichelleSacco @clarkythetitan...Or you could become known as Team Bechamel. Quite a 'saucy' name don't you think??    
    
    
    @claysummers Yummy like a mummy with a runny cunny??    
    
    
    Great name for a Chinese takeaway... http://instagram.com/p/XaOPK5kn2d/     
    
    
    Headless chicken! http://instagram.com/p/Xg2ynjEn5r/     
    
    
    Mine too! http://instagram.com/p/Xg27okEn51/     
    
    
    Easter Bunny?! http://instagram.com/p/Xg3M0uEn6F/     
    
    
    Rumbled. With eggs! http://instagram.com/p/XhTeulkn-F/     
    
    
    What is it about salad bars that excites me so much? #wouldntthinkittolookatme    
    
    
    'If salad be the food of love, munch on'. Hey, if I keep this up I'll be able to fit into my new mankini this summer! #visualtreat    
    
    
    And in other news #loveinthewild is on tonight! #yay    
    
    
    Workplace Celeb Lookalike Update! Saw bearded Paul Nicholas today. Had to do my utmost not to sing theme from 'Just Good Friends' to him.    
    
    
    And Egon Spengler from Ghostbusters appeared from nowhere today. He's like that though. I know who to call...    
    
    
    Oh yeah...saw a ginger Jerome Flynn too the other day. No sign of Robson though. Probably too busy 'Extreme Fishing' or stuck #upontheroof    
    
    
    Also spotted: old Dane Bowers, young Jimmy Durante, bald Derek Jacobi and female Tim Curry.    
    
    
    That's not my Richardson! His red stick is too rrrrrosy! http://instagram.com/p/XpmZeyEn0y/     
    
    
    @strojer Hi Mikkel. D'you get the email I sent the other day? Be great to catch up soon :)    
    
    
    @mindykaling yet it's made your ability to give lengthy explanations curiously more robust...    
    
    
    Have started speaking to myself in a Werner Herzog voice. So this is what Kinski had to endure...no wonder he went mad.    
    
    
    J'attends le train http://instagram.com/p/X-J_Xvkn4O/     
    
    
    See what they did? #cleverdicks http://instagram.com/p/X-Ka2pEn5B/     
    
    
    Think about it...RT @10Yetis: What do u say to sumone who takes Ur cheese? That's nacho cheese :-)    
    
    
    Smokin' Jaguar! http://instagram.com/p/X-vmUeEn3o/     
    
    
    Back to the wild! http://instagram.com/p/YGKqASEn9K/     
    
    
    @Wexley Done! Can I pay in monthly $1 installments??    
    
    
    Bonking Brummies. Him: Scream me name! Her: What's yer name? Him: Thought yer knew? Her: Oh....God! Him: Close enough. #curtaindown #tweatre    
    
    
    Shaving Scousers. S1: Gonna keep me beard. S2: Glad to hear it (!). S1: I love me pet parrot. S2: Eh?? #curtaindown #tweatre    
    
    
    Courting Cockeys. Him: I fort you luvved me. Her: I do...as a mate. Him: I ain't gonna do pedis wiv ya. Her: You sayin I'm a nonce? #tweatre    
    
    
    Need. A. Second. Wind. #rasp    
    
    
    Open question - Whatcha think of 'Cronkite' as an ad agency name? #agencylife    
    
    
    @strangestpet how are ye wee man?    
    
    
    Five fabulous uses of Vine: imagination and patience help to create the best videos http://thedrum.com/cMh     
    
    
    Blockbusters - the First Hand Jive: http://youtu.be/5Z_uqL8opW8     
    
    
    Surely we must be inside of the dream we long to live?    
    
    
    Beige sedation and tepid simulation #overandout    
    
    
    Anodyne shrieks and gutteral croaking    
    
    
    I could understand the purpose of the chase if Roadrunner had something meaningful to offer society...#meepmeep    
    
    
    Can creatures with beaks 'gurn'?    
    
    
    Homoerotic Roadrunner languishes on a velvet chaise longue, casting a lusty gaze in Wile E Coyote's general direction #meepmeep    
    
    
    Coyote responds with a nonchalant shrug, adjusts his cravat, before closing the drawing room's sizeable door. It firmly locks behind them...    
    
    
    Owen! Get me a thhoda! Ya lousy poop! #throwmommafromthetrain    
    
    
    With all the hype around defying gravity, ruby slippers, lions, tin men etc, no-one's bothered to tell the salamander's tale #lizardofoz    
    
    
    Chewin' the fat over ice cream http://instagram.com/p/YVEoY5kn2C/     
    
    
    Big weekend. Done. http://instagram.com/p/YYTsnrEnz0/     
    
    
    What is innovation? And how do you incorporate it effectively? http://thedrum.com/cNG     
    
    
    Party's here on the Westside...http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0hiUuL5uTKc&list=RD02q3qDESAvzh0 …    
    
    
    Features some mad Grade 2 piano skills http://youtu.be/7Wt1nvsoKno     
    
    
    Where you yo-yo, I will knickers. #gilmoregirls    
    
    
    No Eye Deer http://instagram.com/p/YgBW0DEnym/     
    
    
    Rowland extols the virtues of graft via the medium of freemasonry: http://youtu.be/py_PavqqOao     
    
    
    @wearerenegade 'Wallace! Can you hear me?'    
    
    
    I'll be your friend @KELLYROWLAND #grangehill    
    
    
    Man on bus has bowtie on #twiddleitjustalittlebit    
    
    
    Thinking of changing my name to 'Awesome Welles' #greathuh?    
    
    
    Marjorie was a fucking saint. A mucky Mother Theresa. Enid could tell from the lines that framed her aged, painted face. #openingtoastory    
    
    
    It was her ‘unclean’ sensuous features and visible wantonness that had been her saviour #nextbit    
    
    
    Oh yeah, she’d lived alright. Not even a generous veneer of peach foundation could disguise that.#excerpt    
    
    
    Clandestinely servicing the upper echelons of the Third Reich had its advantages #thatsallfornow    
    
    
    Enough pseudo-literary pretension #ahbedtime    
    
    
    Sub, Stan, she ate.    
    
    
    What do you get when you mix wine with new furniture? Cabinet so very young.    
    
    
    Why Channeling Your Inner Weirdo Helps You Get Ahead At Work  http://www.fastcompany.com/3008855/why-channeling-your-inner-weirdo-helps-you-get-ahead-work …    
    
    
    I've an urge to milk my uvula like an udder. Hey, why not?    
    
    
    New TV show idea. People stand before a panel of judges and do absolutely nothing. Their friends and relatives cry backstage.    
    
    
    Or a music contest where performers experience what they're singing about in real time, to ensure authenticity.    
    
    
    Or a talent show where people compete to be the nation's best HR manager.    
    
    
    Or a show where members of the public compete to win the coveted title of 'Britain's Leading Amateur Proctologist'    
    
    
    Or a show where the star prize is a swim in a lake.    
    
    
    Contestants try to put each other off their food 'by whatever means possible.'    
    
    
    'Britain's Got Talons'. Like Crufts, but just for birds of prey.    
    
    
    Are nuns known as 'birds of pray'? #praynotpreyseewhatidid?    
    
    
    This is a test... #yam    
    
    
    Just got really angry at the sight of a man driving a droptop #notsurewhymaybeitwashissmarmydemeanour    
    
    
    @motherny Meh - what does she know?    
    
    
    @marianne237 @RicardoDiaz @thaz7 @dmklee @EaterNY Urdadi's 'sposed to be putting in an appearance too, I hear..can you confirm?    
    
    
    @mindykaling Not Pussy Riot though, alas...    
    
    
    Morning, good people! Ready to be awesome today?    
    
    
    Apparently rude hedgehogs are called 'piggybanks', or so Noah tells me.    
    
    
    He also created a barricade of toys in the garden, calling it a 'housebaber'. Matilda has since adopted this word as a nickname.    
    
    
    @carwash_cat It's in my porcine dna! Howz Welly treatin' ya?    
    
    
    The Yiddish Handbook: 40 Words You Should Know: http://www.dailywritingtips.com/the-yiddish-handbook-40-words-you-should-know/ …    
    
    
    Breakfast with a grown up spoon! http://instagram.com/p/YwfM_okn6U/     
    
    
    Go Home Roger - literally - ! http://youtu.be/DB7pPArGXfU     
    
    
        
    
    
    Even Good King Wenceslas had his off days. He looked out on the feast of St Swithun and a bird shit in his eye. That was a bad time for him.    
    
    
    And today's theme song is...http://youtu.be/BY2OFztWiuY     
    
    
    Aged 11 I wanted to change my name to 'Hoagie'. Shortly afterwards I had my first 'fear of death' ephiphany in East Grinstead Sainsburys...    
    
    
    More than 20 years on and I've come to terms with the inevitability of death, but the name 'Hoagie' haunts me...    
    
    
    Hoooaaaggiiiieee! Hooooaaagggiieee! Hooooooooaaaaaggggiiiieeee! #hauntedbyhoagie    
    
    
    How odd it is that some people go to Australia - as if it were, say, akin to 'visiting a friend'. It's the nonchalance that gets me.    
    
    
    But some people do, you know? I wrote a song about that once #somepeoplejustgotoaustraliaasifitwerenothing    
    
    
    Me: What you up to this week? Person: Going to Australia... Me: Oh wow! Tell me more! Person: I'm just going to Australia. #oznonchalance    
    
    
    Don't mind if I do! http://instagram.com/p/ZBcaEjEn6z/     
    
    
    How IBM Turned Its Scientists Into Atomic Moviemakers http://adage.com/u/s88JJa     
    
    
    Daft Punk - Voyager: http://youtu.be/CqZgd6-xQl8     
    
    
    Why is it that every time I look in the mirror I expect to see Zack from Saved By The Bell staring back at me, and instead I see Nick Frost?    
    
    
    Mini fanfare tooting in my head #trumpetytrump    
    
    
    So Fergie's retiring. The Black Eyed Peas will never be the same...    
    
    
    ...But good to know Moyles will soon be back in employment after his departure from Radio 1. Can just see him up on stage singing 'My Humps'    
    
    
    See? SEE?....Artist collects DNA from discarded hair and nails, 3D-prints owner's face http://bit.ly/13f2e0l     
    
    
    And the award for oddest thing I've seen today goes to... http://instagram.com/p/ZGTdF5En59/     
    
    
    Well... ain't we a pair... raggedy man! http://www.hark.com/clips/mnskzwwkcp-well-dot-dot-dot-aint-we-a-pair-dot-dot-dot-raggedy-man-dot-dot-dot-goodbye-soldier …    
    
    
    Yiu win't hiff ti tik a midical or answir iny quistions abart yir hilth #cornhilloverfiftyplan #radioalarmclock    
    
    
    Rrrrrrrrrrrrrosehill! #thatisall    
    
    
    In Grandad's van... http://instagram.com/p/ZfjVAgkn6C/     
    
    
    How Coca-Cola Used Vending Machines To Try And Unite The People Of India And Pakistan http://www.fastcocreate.com/node/1683001  via @FastCoCreate    
    
    
    New favourite website. 'Look for this sign, where you sleep or dine...' http://bugsburger.com/     
    
    
    Dammit! Why did I never learn to play the violin? Really wish I had in times like these #satonabus #eeeeeethatsthesoundofaviolinplaying    
    
    
    I'd probably go crackers like Paganini...guess I could fuse his music with 90s R&B #paganiniandpliers    
    
    
    What do you get if you cross an R&B has-been with A5 posters? Chaka Demus and Flyers. #stickingtodayjob    
    
    
    OMG what if Chaka Khan married Chaka Demus?! She's better off marrying Imran, Aga, or Shere #khan    
    
    
    Bruce Willis is fed up of his kids borrowing the family Hummer. He now just presumes that 'Rumer has it...'    
    
    
    Black Lace's new violin composition shocks Royal Albert Hall audience with satanic 'call to arms' #paga-doodoodoosacrificegoats-anini    
    
    
    Penzance? I prefer Rubrkatpillaz.    
    
    
    Apparently search behemoth, Google, is developing 'smart' anus cleansing hardware #googlearse    
    
    
    *chuckles* Just recalling a song I wrote when I was ten; a Michael Bolton-esque ballad called 'Let Me Fulfil Your Needs'...    
    
    
    And the time I performed the Grease 2 number 'Let's Bowl' in the living room, blindfolded: to avoid the disapproving gaze of my father.    
    
    
    What do you call a Clown in Essex? A Claaahhn.    
    
    
    What do you call a Clown in Scotland? A Clooon    
    
    
    What do you call a Clown in the circus? Homeboy.    
    
    
    What do Clowns call clowning around? Gainful employment.    
    
    
    It's official. The Red Nose has emerged as victor in the Clown War for Semiotic Supremacy...    
    
    
    Red, Red Nose: Clowns banished from Big Top as plans for 'mini bike semiotic supremacy' coup emerge...    
    
    
    Even pirates need Mummy's help...sometimes http://instagram.com/p/ZvMgQDEn0w/     
    
    
    Why 'cat o'nine tails'? Why not 'dog o'eight tails'? Or 'hamster o'four tails'?    
    
    
    Or 'gerbil o'three tails'?    
    
    
    Dolphin o'ninety four tails?? #thatsjuststupid    
    
    
    And why limit ourselves to tails? #manateeothirtyonearms    
    
    
    Or change the whole paradigm of 'animal + number + body part' to something else entirely #vegetablelettermusicalinstrument    
    
    
    Aubergine o'G Banjo    
    
    
    Red Onion o'W Cello    
    
    
    Aged 11, I illustrated a story about slavery, written in History class. Me, beaten with cat o'9 tails, wearing a Global Hypercolor t-shirt.    
    
    
    @SR_Chep Fkshh! Fkshh! But will the lash marks show in a darker shade of purple on my heat sensitive shirt?    
    
    
    Lovejoy: The College Years #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Hyacinth Bucket P.I. #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Father Ted Investigates #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Band of Golden Girls #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Beauty and The Beast Enders #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    21 Coronation Street #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Birds of A Feather: Special Victims Unit #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Ian and Ally McBeale #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Dawson's Jonathan Creek #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    @HayesThompson Wiggle the lines around, add a syllable or three and you'll have a haiku. But Nice #likethebiscuit    
    
    
    @hollybrocks ooh is Vine on Android now???    
    
    
    Goodnight Sweetheart SG1 #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    NYPD Blue Peter #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Last of the Summer Wine: Life on the Streets #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Poirots of the Caribbean #transatlantictvmashup #notstrictlytviknow    
    
    
    The Darling Buds of Baywatch #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Antiques Roadshow: The Sarah Connor Chronicles #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Bergerac P.I. #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    The Alan Partridge Family #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Six Feet Underground Overground Wombling Free #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    The Real Housewives of Keeping Up Appearances #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Emmerdale:Deep Space Nine #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Lewis: The Next Generation #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Press ups I have done. No. 15: sluggish, but redeemed at the end with a neat little hand flourish - a gesture and a smile, if you will...    
    
    
    Meals I've had. No.1: milk. Comment: Tasted better in past life when taken from a wild yak, out in the central Asian steppes. Boob away mum.    
    
    
    Air Transat is giving away 4 direct return flights to Canada. Enter now for your chance to win! http://strutta.me/l/1sv8g     
    
    
    Keeping Up with the Appearances #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Where the Hart to Hart is #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Take Me Out: Sopranos Special #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Greavsie and The Saint Elsewhere #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Different Brush Strokes #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Brian Dowling Investigates #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Dirty Sexy Cash In The Attic #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Bargain Hunter #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Real Rooms Of Orange County #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    LA Lawson: Nigella Bites #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    South Parkinson #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    The Crocodile Shoe Diaries #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Come Dynasty With Me #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    @Agent547 Howdy! Good to hear from ya :) I'm not sure anyone else from uni going at Twitter hammer'n'tongs...howz family life treating u?    
    
    
    Apparently Dane Bowers once made a pilot episode of a sitcom called 'Bow to the Bowers'. He played himself, but more arrogant.    
    
    
    Life of Grime special: Sex and the City #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Optimus Prime Suspect #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    He-Man and the Masters of the University Challenge #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Tour of Duty Free #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    2.4 and a Half Men #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Homeland to Roost #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Rod, Jane, and Freddy's Nightmares #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    To The Manor Bourne Identity #transatlantictvmashup #oknotjusttv    
    
    
    Melrose Place in the Sun #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Peppa Pygmalion #tvfilmmashup    
    
    
    Brothers and Sister Sisters #tvfilmmashup    
    
    
    Gilligan's Island of Dr Moreau #tvfilmmashup    
    
    
    You Rang My Lord Vader #tvfilmmashup    
    
    
    Mr Wroe's 40 Year Old Virgin #tvfilmmashup    
    
    
    The People Under The Upstairs Downstairs #tvfilmmashup    
    
    
    Jerry Springerwatch #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Twin Peak Practice #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Brookside Story #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    Rent A Ghost Whisperer #transatlantictvmashup    
    
    
    It's like I'm on an NYC subway train...but in Gloucestershire! #arriva    
    
    
    Reasons to hate guinea pigs. Part one. http://instagram.com/p/abj3smkn-V/     
    
    
    @adamtbailey *Raises hand in frenzied excitement* Ooh! Ooh! What I gotta do, sir?? LinkedIn? You got it.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Saatchi seen 'nursing hand' after second tiff #nigellabitesback    
    
    
    New shipyard owners: struggling with a name? How about 'Hickory Dickory Dock'? #youcanhavethatforfree    
    
    
    Just seen a rodent scale a timepiece! Yes, a mouse ran up the clock!    
    
    
    Lunchtime. I know this because the clock struck one.    
    
    
    Portrait of a Feline Roadside Picnic: The Mouse, Ran Down.    
    
    
    Where was I...oh yeah...if you're tasked with branding a new shipward, consider the name 'Hickory Dickory Dock'.    
    
    
    #casualuseofnurseryrhymesineverydaychatter    
    
    
    @strangestpet 'Havid Dockney'    
    
    
    @raywlin @foursquare Howdy there location-based tech pardners! Did y'all git my applercayshun? I jus gotta git thayt gig! Whatcha'll say?    
    
    
    Thought woman sat opposite on the train was on a conference call but she ended it with a 'Love You' #deadgiveaway    
    
    
    Maybe she's in love with several people #heightsoferoticism #screammename    
    
    
    Just saw a man in a dress...no wait...hang on #womanwithsevereblokeshaircut    
    
    
    A pensioner's listening to his mp3 player and drinking lager. He knows how to get down with his bad self on public transport #mandem    
    
    
    If referencing public transport in a hurry, can one use the term 'public tranny' or even 'pub tranny'? #trannyp    
    
    
    Reaching top speed aboard this fine mode of public tranny #zoomzipzoom    
    
    
    To get down quickly to Miami, I rode full pelt on public tranny #poetic #rhymes    
    
    
    @foursquare I've located your next copywriter! He's stuck in rural England - save him, please! http://4sq.com/19VW5e5     
    
    
    Video? On Instagram? I feel a branding opportunity coming on... #videogram    
    
    
    Never Mind The Biloxi #albumplacenamemashup    
    
    
    Melon Collie and the Infinite Salford #albumplacenamemashup    
    
    
    So many painted horrors. Everywhere.    
    
    
    Bat Out of Hailsham #albumplacenamemashup    
    
    
    Loving the new WeLove9am website and vid! http://vimeo.com/welove9am/whatwedo …    
    
    
    Who writes this stuff? Oh yeah... http://wp.me/p1AbAC-5d     
    
    
    Why do people feel the need to keep their paths weed free? What do they plan to do on them?? #pathofleastresistance #weedol    
    
    
    Female werewolf tunefully enquires about online dating. Replicas of her appear. Suddenly she's courting a hunchback #plentymorefishtvad    
    
    
    From now on, when referring to others, place the word 'Old' before an abridged version of their surname - and add a letter 'y' on the end.    
    
    
    Eg 'Old Barty'    
    
    
    @lpc @sloh @af @raywlin I've located your next copywriter! He's stuck in rural England - save him, please! http://4sq.com/19VW5e5     
    
    
    @Agent547 Nah. It's a true thing.    
    
    
    The most famous brand from each US state: Apple in California, Starbucks in Washington and…Hooters in Florida   http://po.st/iZDvfP     
    
    
    Why are my teeth tired??    
    
    
    Everyone goes on about 'Cider with Rosie' but there are other alcohol-female name combos. I can endorse 'Lager with Lizzie' for example...    
    
    
    'Bitter with Gertie'    
    
    
    'Perry with Agapanthus'    
    
    
    'Vodka with Marion'    
    
    
    Or why not reconfigure the concept to combine Indian cuisine and male names? 'Chicken Balti with Simon'    
    
    
    'Prawn Dopiaza with Gideon'    
    
    
    Woken by the sound of my brain singing 'Goin' Loco Down In Acupulco' to the rest of my body.    
    
    
    The End Of Advertising As We Know It—And What To Do Now http://www.fastcocreate.com/node/1683292  via @FastCoCreate    
    
    
    Zugar La Lar Lah #reptilianlionservant    
    
    
    @Agent547 Does this qualify as 'deep'? I'm just not sure...http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Machine_elf …    
    
    
    @phebeelhard isn't real, but follow him anyway - if only for his profile preamble.    
    
    
    I think I have a nice face, but it's what's inside that counts #intheface    
    
    
    It's back: the metallic tang that frequents my mouth and prickles my inner ears when I hear a plastic bag rustle in a soundproof room #often    
    
    
    Perhaps it was 'the trumpet' referred to in Mambo No. 5 that tore down the walls of Jericho? Or one akin to it. You never know...    
    
    
    People don't care to talk about trumpets like they used to when I was a kid. Why, back then there was an abundance of them!    
    
    
    An idea. The faces of hated public figures on urinals. The bowls act as mouths. They speak stock phrases but gargle and quieten when used.    
    
    
    @lpc @sloh @af @raywlin @foursquare Come on guys! You're still looking right? I'm still waiting to be found...http://4sq.com/19VW5e5     
    
    
    @HH_DM Check out http://wearevacuous.wordpress.com  #reclaimtheword #marketing    
    
    
    @OfficiallyCleo Ever considered performing a tribute to the late Iron Lady? #mrsthatchercomingatcha    
    
    
    @VisitDevon Consider stealing Cornwall's culinary crown by inventing a dish called the 'Torquiche' #youcanhavethatforfree    
    
    
    Wow! Who knew? Beyonce is the Devil incarnate!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=idAz7mFKPrc …    
    
    
    @Jessops Idea. Put 90s kids TV faves 'The Riddlers' in your ads. Think of the fun you could have with nomenclature confusion #mossop    
    
    
    @GreggstheBakers Put the words 'mouth watering' and 'local' on your packaging. Then charge five times more.#workseverytime    
    
    
    @glastofest Keep the 'Pennywhistle and Purple Cords' brigade away next year by promoting yourself as a meat vendor instead of music fest.    
    
    
    @PGUK Reignite interest in your 'Proud Sponsors of Mums' campaign by flipping the focus #disheartenedrejectorsofdads    
    
    
    RT: @PGUK Reignite interest in your 'Proud Sponsors of Mums' campaign by flipping the focus #disheartenedrejectorsofdads    
    
    
    @dyson Cement your reputation for innovation by breaking free from the shackles of unfortunate nomenclature and rebranding #livedaughter    
    
    
    People called 'Nan'. Confuse and confound others by becoming a mum. Or a dad.    
    
    
    James Bond will return in 'Quantum of Doris'    
    
    
    @VisitDevon @EnglishRiviera @englishriviera1 People, let's do this. I'm serious. If you are too, let's talk. email me dave@toverbanda.com    
    
    
    The Last Cuppa...#starbucks http://instagram.com/p/bW_3imEn7e/     
    
    
    WTF?? #mediagonetodogs #justwhy http://instagram.com/p/bYBTEZkn_l/     
    
    
    Right, so we'll just wait here at the bus stop whilst the driver has a snout and texts his mum. I'm in… http://instagram.com/p/bY_KNfkn9b/     
    
    
    Whert? Nyoway! Ee's nart bin shaggin' er down Eeversham 'as ee? Ee's ownly jurst gaat out of jail!  #busslapperconflab    
    
    
    @ringomoss Not on my bus Ringo. Not today. Not when I'm fag free with major cravings. In the words of Vanilla 'No way. No way.' #mnamna    
    
    
    Captions please!..'Really?? All over his face!? Clowns will be clowns...!' http://instagram.com/p/bZDafyEn0G/     
    
    
    'Jellyfish Eyes' Feature Film By Takashi Murakami | Yatzer http://www.yatzer.com/jellyfish-eyes-takashi-murakami … via @Yatzer    
    
    
    @strangestpet Candy-coloured clown...http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zbxsmcT7GOk …    
    
    
    @claysummers I came to saw. And conquer.    
    
    
    14 Google Tools You Didn't Know Existed http://on.mash.to/15k39O8     
    
    
    Night, night everyone! http://youtu.be/zbxsmcT7GOk     
    
    
    #modernlove http://instagram.com/p/baoTYyEnwB/     
    
    
    Polly wants a cracker. Now. http://instagram.com/p/bapAVmEnwc/     
    
    
    #imagine #thatsdeep http://instagram.com/p/bdDaJzkn5M/     
    
    
    A cautionary tale... http://instagram.com/p/bdDpZhkn5g/     
    
    
    A cautionary tale. Part 2 http://instagram.com/p/bdD3P5En56/     
    
    
    R.I.P Norwegian Blue. http://instagram.com/p/bdFXq4En8i/     
    
    
    I knew him well...#pooryorick http://instagram.com/p/bdGop-kn-H/     
    
    
    @davetrott 'Welcome to Premier Inn' -  Lenny Henry    
    
    
    'Up all night to get mucky' http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5NV6Rdv1a3I …    
    
    
    http://instagram.com/p/bfwbK8En3E/     
    
    
    @MacLarenVan CW eh?? Sounds 'inarresting'. Y'all got more deets to hand?    
    
    
    @maclarenvan Y'all've never hearda 'Cajun Cowboy English'? You'll find it in the dictionary under 'I'. For 'irony'.    
    
    
    @CreatureSea Suits you well!    
    
    
    Literal Movie Posters: What's Really Going On - Sabotage Times http://j.mp/186SES6     
    
    
    I had a little salesman/Nothing would he bear/But a pinstripe jacket/And a golden stare    
    
    
    Pulp's Disco 2000. Perfect for a 7:15 am singalong #loveit    
    
    
    Hungry Eyes: http://youtu.be/6oKUTOLSeMM     
    
    
    Spanish Eyes: http://youtu.be/F4s__QO9kG0     
    
    
    Private Eyes: http://youtu.be/anLfoy2XsFw     
    
    
    http://w3w.cm/lifted.calls.stream … #w3w    
    
    
    Soon to be visiting hoodie.luncheon.segment...
http://w3w.cm/hoodie.luncheon.segment … #w3w    
    
    
    If I was both attractive and interested, I'd be 'hot' and 'bothered' #truedat    
    
    
    http://w3w.cm/these.across.fades … #mydesk    
    
    
    Malcolm McLaren - Waltz Darling: http://youtu.be/nFnTo77IV2s  #onthegoodstufftoday    
    
    
    On the topic of Old Malcy, thought I'd wheel this out.#shitsandgiggles http://wearevacuous.wordpress.com/2012/06/08/in-imitation-of-a-reverse-letter-s/ …    
    
    
    Advertisers. Please refrain from using the word 'Only' as a prefix to pricing. Eg 'Manchego Eel Pies! Only €15!' #likeincestitsrelative    
    
    
    And unless you plan to use them out of context, don't use the terms 'mouth-watering' or 'local' #sadpanda    
    
    
    So...'mouth-watering, local ham' = bad    
    
    
    But 'mouth-watering, local lampshades' = good. #changeyourperspective    
    
    
    Chauvinism, Chivalry and Ostentation: The Life of a Westside Player #imaginedthesistitles    
    
    
    'Ooh Betty!' Towards Haphazard Inepititude: The Politics of Frank Spencer #imaginedthesistitles    
    
    
    Medicinal Porpoises: The Case For Testing Drugs on Dolphins #imaginedthesistitles    
    
    
    Mylene Klass: Muted Exoticism at the Crossroads of Otherness #imaginedthesistitles    
    
    
    Super Saver Returns: Egotism and Public Transport #imaginedthesistitles    
    
    
    Cornish Pastiche: Analysing the Relationship Between Humour and Indigenous British Snacks #imaginedthesistitles    
    
    
    Faith No More - Spanish Eyes: http://youtu.be/k9a5GYcdOno  #classy    
    
    
    Elvis Presley - Spanish Eyes: http://youtu.be/mIyXFyR9JBQ  #inspirational    
    
    
    IVO ROBIĆ - Rot ist der Wein (Blue Spanish Eyes): http://youtu.be/Qxjv22-7gOU  #german    
    
    
    Engelbert Humperdinck - Spanish Eyes 1969: http://youtu.be/F4s__QO9kG0  #definitive    
    
    
    Thierry Hazard - Le jerk: http://youtu.be/zQaecccL4PE  #loveit    
    
    
    Buy A Timeshare In The Ultimate RV Park Doomsday Shelter http://www.fastcoexist.com/node/1682570     
    
    
    Old Man Prawno Star http://fc05.deviantart.net/images3/i/2004/166/d/4/Hardcore_Prawn.jpg …    
    
    
    The Curious Banana Eel http://4.bp.blogspot.com/_VTfI-JBeWfc/TICsp7hy_TI/AAAAAAAAAUY/C7ZyB5LtPaQ/s320/normal_spotted-garden-eel-2.jpg …    
    
    
    There's something intrinsically life-reaffirming about the Big Brother theme tune #audiosensuality    
    
    
    Is it wrong to love the Lightning Seeds? Oh well... #marvellous    
    
    
    Stop the Press! #headline http://instagram.com/p/b23vF8kn5S/     
    
    
    All of Jay-Z’s 99 Problems, Illustrated http://www.fastcocreate.com/1683399/all-of-jay-z-s-99-problems-illustrated …    
    
    
    Loving the Grade 2 Xylophone intro: http://youtu.be/Kw-Fl_xGpyY     
    
    
    What the hell?? http://instagram.com/p/b36Zt-En0s/     
    
    
    And in other news...apparently football and casual racism are seasoned bedfellows...#badtouch http://instagram.com/p/b36lrUkn0-/     
    
    
    Back in the 1920's, rhythmic hand clapping was considered a viable form of popular entertainment. #junkhistory    
    
    
    Don't we all?? http://instagram.com/p/b5YKGzknz0/     
    
    
    The end result doesn't have to be 'out there' but there's nothing governing the process behind it #NoteToSelf    
    
    
    There is a distinct gap between the way 'process' and 'product' manifest, but both are ultimately concerned with originality #NoteToSelf    
    
    
    If God won't love you, Satan will. And your mum. Apparently... http://www.vice.com/en_uk/read/satanists-turned-the-founder-of-the-westboro-baptist-churchs-mom-gay …    
    
    
    The Returned is AMAZING! Why didn't I find this out sooner? #latetotheparty    
    
    
    Matilda meets Daft Punk! http://instagram.com/p/b_cze5knzS/     
    
    
    Morning Gromit! http://instagram.com/p/cAzyt8kn8s/     
    
    
    Powerful! http://instagram.com/p/cEUvzsEnxL/     
    
    
    Bosque Y Mar http://instagram.com/p/cHhFngEn02/     
    
    
    Mundomar! http://instagram.com/p/cJE2Bmknxf/     
    
    
    Captions please! http://instagram.com/p/cJQ3mCkn6B/     
    
    
    Sierra http://instagram.com/p/cKIBz8kn9g/     
    
    
    Not a brand I've heard of...#toaster http://instagram.com/p/cPCrPTEn_r/     
    
    
    Must...have...breakfast...! http://instagram.com/p/cgBbLlkn9A/     
    
    
    Today I will mostly be a 'hot mess'...well. it's hot and I'm a mess...    
    
    
    Zut! Il pleut. #naymatterimstillahotmess    
    
    
    And my theme song today is 'Leave Your Hat On'. The Joe Cocker version, not the version sung by that wife beating sex fiend, TJones.    
    
    
    'Norman had a look of sexual desperation plastered across his face as the delectable treat that was Mildred shimmied by' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'It was the sound of squirrels weeping that most peturbed me. That and the stench of tepid perfume #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Dressed as Mary Magdelene she'd mistaken every bearded man at the party for Jesus. The real Jesus' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Without knowing why, Peter was taken with the dog's playful sense of postman-baiting.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    This week, I shall mostly be 'voguing' http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GuJQSAiODqI&list=RD02JQ2DVwSVIIo …    
    
    
    Once the swelling on his tongue had gone down, Martin found he was able to speak Latin. Fluently. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Mike's felt his pants quickly fill with icy Lemon Fanta. But curious hands told a different story #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    And there it lay, among his father's ashes. The scrotal piercing he'd often spoken of, glinting in the dwindliing sunlight #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Despite an undersized appendage, Beryl's hand were remarkably large #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    It all began with the white cat and his blood stained fur. Tony never really liked goats but melons drove him wild #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Bucking in feigned ecstacy was a familar chore for Deborah. Henry's strokes droned on. All she could think of was Majorie #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    The crack of a twig. A decandent chocolate twig. 'We must leave Ned!' I called. Too late. The Matchmakers held his gaze. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Jonesing' - to crave/desire #newbestword    
    
    
    Doreen: the toilet attendant #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Frederick: he who willingly imprisons badgers #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Patricia: she who searches for rice in cow dung #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Sally: she who is an adjective acting as a proper noun #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Michael: adored by squirrels #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Lucas: admits to French university #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Robert: apple diver #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Margaret: sensuous, delightful nose #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Theresa: Spanish woodland nymph #newnameaning    
    
    
    David: protects the eels with powerful glances #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Janet: mighty dictionary keeper #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Drago: son of Peter #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Peter: father of Drago #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Lorraine: Scottish variant of 'Kelly' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Boris: bumbling alternative to 'Cameron' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Amber: she whose dreams of success are shattered; or pole dancer #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Dennis: imbibes detergent #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    George: small lover of Maria #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Maria: hoardes toothpaste in case of apocalypse #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Stanley: 'the porcupine is of German origin' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Colin: 'blessed by dolphins'#newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Gertrude: 'excessively offensive with no good reason' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Jerome: 'fellates Bulgarian tourists' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Paul: 'elegant livestock feed salesman' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Cerys: 'milky duck' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Solomon: 'runs small successful chain of fried chicken restaurants in the Tri-state area' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Selena: 'once fell asleep during Dr Zhivago' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Louise: 'tarmac seamstress' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Zane: 'fiddler on the roof of your mouth' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Jonty: 'legendary percussionist' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Terence: 'filthy dermatologist' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Yolanda: 'shops only at Matalan' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Helen: 'vehemently denies button is missing' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Eric: 'a preference for winged horses' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
        
    
    
    Gemma: 'solvent matriarch who willingly tends wounds' #newnamemeaning    
    
    
    Why isn't music like this any more? http://youtu.be/Kqj6TzgPBiU     
    
    
    Milicent shuddered her way through another meaningless orgasm. 'Are the terrapins capable of such hatred?' she pondered. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Coco's dog bore the burden of a pointy hat and frilly collar. Mike could see the crushing humiliation in his eyes. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Pierre was moved to tears at the sight of my open sores. He gently stroked the most horrific with his one good toe #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Cheryl gasped when she saw the time. The vicar was due in three hours! And she'd not yet slaughtered the goats! #badnovelopenings    
    
    
        
    
    
    Lenny's eyes pixelated the vision that stood before him. Was it really a nude Sheena Easton? Why was she eating Frazzles?? #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'I can't remember the last time I ate a nail file,' he said. 'Might have been '98. The year I began dental nursing' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    The Piglets ~ Johnny Reggae: http://youtu.be/0dVseBq-MSA  #reggaesauce    
    
    
    'God he's evil! Proper little jobsworth that fat knacker is!'. Maureen had a cob on. That much was pretty fucking obvious. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Seepage. Everywhere the eye could see, seepage. Clouded by the effects of the Culminator, Chet was drowning. In seepage. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Mandy stank. Really stank. Reeked. But of what? Bin juice? It was hard to tell given the day she'd had. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'And now, ladies and gents, observe closely...as I am sick in my mouth!' Clarence had gone too far this time. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    The giantess yelped as they cut her heels again. 'Alright! I'll free the seagulls! But you have to get off my feet!' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Ben was the only one left to greet the Four Horsemen. They were too late. The aliens had got there first. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Mother caught ithe substance in in her empty tea cup. Pure liquid Plague. Straight down the hatch.#badnovelopenings    
    
    
    The fact was clear: the cat had AIDS. But Baz was more upset that he'd found this out from the psychic and not from Mel. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Although drenched in chip shop curry sauce, Colin was effecftively able to manage a 'half mast salute' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Picture it. A circle of plump prawns drizzled in chilli oil, with strips of teryaki beef arranged in v-shapes. Dish called 'Prawn-O-Moo-V'.    
    
    
    Milicent shuddered her way through another meaningless orgasm. 'Are the terrapins capable of such hatred?' she pondered. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Good day, aliens!    
    
    
    Today I shall mostly serve and make replacements.    
    
    
    Phelps swaps 'dope' for 'pope' #godvertising #busvertising http://instagram.com/p/cvich_En57/     
    
    
    Today's theme song: http://youtu.be/8hYtUYiuzkw     
    
    
    North Americans: align the way you pronounce the word 'God' with British English speakers. Say 'Gored' not 'Guard' #somethingdifferentinnit    
    
    
    Escorts: confuse customers and Police alike by referring to yourselves as prostitutes when advertising your services #behonest    
    
    
    Dog lovers: silence accusations of bestiality by referring to yourself as a 'dog liker' #go #on    
    
    
    Men: confuse people by wearing a dress occasionally #tryit    
    
    
    Wafer munchers: save money by not purchasing ice cream #makessense    
    
    
    Men with large breasts: make yourself useful by learning to lactate #milky    
    
    
    Dairy cattle: make farmers' live easier by producing your own butter, cheese, youghurt etc #lazycows    
    
    
    Aliens: stop speculation about your presumed existence simply by arriving on Earth #areyououtthere    
    
    
    People with no feet: count yourself lucky. You could have no toes. #uhhuh    
    
    
    Dogs: confuse postmen by not chasing them down #leave    
    
    
    Soup drinkers: make the most of summer by not having soup #slurp    
    
    
    Dentists: stop repeat business by removing all of your patients' teeth #gummy    
    
    
    Horses: stop unsettling humans by passing youself off as beef in cheap microwave lasagna #neighsayer    
    
    
    Dogs that have been eaten: get your own back on the people that slaughtered and served you as dinner by putting them on the menu #longpig    
    
    
    Pigs: stop being greedy and rolling in mess, and maybe people will stop calling you 'pigs' #pigfaces    
    
    
    Pastry chefs: offend customers by fashioning 'turds' out of chocolate and serving them alongside every dessert ordered #mmm    
    
    
    Michael Douglas fanciers: manifest a sexual encounter with the Hollywood star using sorcery #wizardssleeve    
    
    
    Anyone else recall that episode of cartoon 'The Real Ghostbusters' where they met the spirit of famous crime writer Agatha 'Bristie'?    
    
    
    Earth Mortality Syndrome???? http://instagram.com/p/dL5aWMknxU/     
    
    
    As an anthropologist, Sian was embarrassed by her past confusion. 'So I once thought Homo Erectus was a porno. Big deal.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'We're not married anymore, Freda. Not since you left me for that Lovejoy lookalike. The one who rode a Penny Farthing.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Drunk or not, Peter would have his day in Margate. 'Sexxx...' he gurgled at the hotel porter. 'Baked beansss' he slurred. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Piss off, Gary!' Matt warned his dead brother. 'You can't have Jean. She's with Manuel now. Let her be. Move on.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Serendipity favours the fortunate.' A vacuous platitude Larry's mum had lived by, before they ate her. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Wait! That's Sammie's breast milk! Don't drink it!'. Andy was too late. Boris had already exploded. #badnovelopening    
    
    
    'Daddy paid for everything!' Elsie gloated. 'Even bought me a new moral compass. Doesn't work though.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Mike welled up at the thought of Bev. Why not call it the 'badger position'? Or the 'whelk position'? Why always 'doggy'? #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    "Today, a verb change" Tiberius announced. "From now on, 'snaking' will hereby be known as 'eeling'. No discussion." #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Jake was back in the driver's seat. 'I'm like an evolved seal,' he said to himself. 'Beyond slippery. Just sticky now.' #badnovelopeninga    
    
    
    The ocean's calling... http://youtu.be/InBXu-iY7cw     
    
    
    My new 'Life Anthem' http://youtu.be/9yjB-PH1_60     
    
    
    'Pick up the pace l'il doggy!' Mavis trilled at Doug. His mouth gag would soon slip, freeing him from sexual servitude #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Mum brushed away the tears on her lapel. 'Basil's your real dad, not Tamara. She was...my sister.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'I am needing application of pleasure. Very soon.' Helga was just as forceful in her clunky English as she was in the dojo #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Doris' dirty dog, Dodger, disintegrated, dying dutifully. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    His warped smile made the trip almost unbearable. 'I was born under cover of tent'. Sarn picked her words carefully #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Duncan's head oscillated steadily, just as Rick James sang the opening to Super Freak. 'Very kinky girl!' Dunc sniggered. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Porking?! What on Earth is 'porking'?!' Shiloh was gonna get it. Big time. And all because of the the 'curly tailed verb' #badnovelopening    
    
    
    Gummo - on the couch: http://youtu.be/-RViHHn8RpE  #greatestevermoviescenes    
    
    
    Julien Donkey Boy - Werner Herzog takes a drink: http://youtu.be/hiBv1pNR0do  #greatestevermoviescenes    
    
    
    'The cat is dead, Mr Schrodinger...no, wait...it's alive...hang on, it's not moving. Was that a tail twitch?' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Sweet Whilli Crap #nowatkfc    
    
    
    Sheena: full of Easton promise.    
    
    
    If, according to Sheena Easton 'Night time is the right time' to make love, then #isitok to fornicate during daylight hours?    
    
    
    Fancy a knuckle sandwich? Come to Greg's. Try the all-new 'Wallace Wallop'. Pasties don't come much tougher than these. Luvverly Jubbly.    
    
    
    Who's the badger-bearded thirty something singing 'Rock the Boat' on the D Bus? Damn right! #cheltenham #ondbus    
    
    
    'Bernard the Bollinger Bolshevik!' Sid spat his words accordingly. 'Still working class I see.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    An elderly lady is showing me her toes on the train home. And she's the one looking worried...    
    
    
    @Katedavis121 I couldn't tell exactly...think she was concerned it was some kind of fungal infection. They weren't tasty toes, so maybe...    
    
    
    There's something inherently sexual about the way pro chefs jiggle their panhandles. Freud would have a field day...    
    
    
    My Own Private Idaho - Daddy Carroll http://youtu.be/cxaoRomwxsk  #greatestevermoviescenes    
    
    
    No Box! It's not your decision! http://youtu.be/rdhRf0OCx5c  #greatestevermoviescenes    
    
    
    Mr. Hans performs Der Adler http://youtu.be/u6urMHA7KX0  #greatestevermoviescenes    
    
    
    Stroszek: the Dancing Chicken: http://youtu.be/IcoqeNdMAfA  #greatestevermoviescenes    
    
    
    I love Udo Kier: http://youtu.be/48aDwuBoEyg     
    
    
    Fuckin' Screech! #CBB    
    
    
    My new super power of choice: Phil Collins' singing voice #turnitonagain    
    
    
    Why did no-one tell me? Inglorious Basterds is AWESOME #lateasusual    
    
    
    'Come on - it's only frogspawn!' Claudine had forgotten Emile's aversion to using gelatinous pond matter as hair gel. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Middle Class sensuality!' Mildred choked on her eclair at the very notion. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Just been endorsed on LinkedIn by none other than Bobak from Another Level! #lickmeupanddown #bucketlisttick    
    
    
    Dinner in the bath! #TreatYourself    
    
    
        
    
    
    New theme song http://youtu.be/PyamU4m-WxU     
    
    
    Pop-speckled by the glitter shower, Gary's crutch gave out, tumbling him head first into the camp mess beneath him #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'I'm not lying!' Nick protested. 'I did see Ben deposit something formless into the dumpster.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    @rltwright Glad you like! Not sure JHJ makes the list...but Kim Wilde's there...?    
    
    
    When I last met Mike he was bi. Now he was mono. His vision had worsened. Evidently. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Now, she could finally showcase her ears without fear of retribution. She was safe. Ned was just meat now. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    '12 inches!' Gloria exclaimed, a little too loudly. 'Cor! That's the same as a foot! How you've grown, Hammy!' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    The dove landed hastily for the last time, its organs in full view of the predator as they snagged on a loose branch. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Yeah, he'd slept with a few guys. He was cool with it. Still did it for cash occasionally - even now he was President #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    O Benelux! Your depths astound and gratify, like the mayonnaise you're prized for, coating fries like a creamy embrace #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Percival's gaze went beyond desire. It was a future together. Hand holding, kicking autumn leaves. Stupid stuff like that. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    A swathe of dwindling gold light surrounded them. It was magical, like the first time. Except it was the last. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    His chest rose and fell, undulating like the waves that were calling him. She knew it. But her tears fell nonetheless. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Clarence stood still, breathing her in once more. If he could take a scent with him, this would be it. This moment. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
        
    
    
    He liked her, that was clear. Apart from her navel. That he could not abide. Body shots were out. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    She drew him closer, whispering softly. 'There's shit on your slacks.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    The cat purred loudly in ecstacy. Meow Meow was back in the game. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    His tanned paunch hung loosely over his belt. 'D'you want me to lose the jeans too?' He bellowed saucily #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    She could never love him in the same way. Not while she was coated in breadcrumbs. He called her his 'Sexy Findus Pancake' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Beetroot?!' Margot screamed. 'Beet-harking-root?! More like parsnips, given his shoddy beige appearance!' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Stop it Pedro! You're in the wrong bit. Use your hands like I showed you...that's it! Now bite down. Hard. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Dean's stomach growled loudly. He tried to pass off the noise as an anal eruption, but Freda knew the truth #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'So...who do you love then?' Steve enquired. 'Me? Doug? Penny? Or is it Marduk? It's sooo Marduk isn't it??' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Get lost!' Sally yelled. 'I am lost,' replied Loz. 'In your eyes. They're beautiful. Especially the left one.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Next time I go on a date it'll be with Simon,' Bina decided. 'Or Mikey. Maybe Del. But not Old Waxy. No way.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    The smell grew more pungent the nearer they got to the socket. Their screams were silenced by the spectacle before them.  #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    It went beyond the rational. Even the diseased badgers mattered. Brian kissed their decaying flesh, weeping #badnovelopenings #fanfiction    
    
    
    If I was a girl, I should like to be known as Amy Hamburger. Or Rebecca Galleria. #demsmoneynames    
    
    
    I'd be proper hot too. And I'd know it. If I was a girl. Like headturning hot. And I'd show it.    
    
    
    Sol flicked his cigar at the quaking stripper. 'C'mon Sugar Tits, dance!' He was more abusive than most ten year olds. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Gurning was second nature to Phil. Mouth covers 'tache covers nose covers brow covers head. He'd win, for sure. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'I see you're quite the squirter!' Hans said. still sopping wet. 'My turn to emit!' He announced, taking the water pistol #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Gaaahhhhhd!' The voice became clearer as Gina approached the bedroom. 'That's some loud praying!' She thought to herself. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Forward-leaning anus gyration, known as 'twerking', joins murder, incest, and cannibalism as Satan's handiwork' he said. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Jason sniffed another line. 'Bastard semi-quavers always get stuck in me nose!' He moaned, picking a second sheet of music #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    Bert didn't care. As a dog, he'd been neutered a week ago. As a parrot however, it was a different story. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
        
    
    
    'I want you. Even the bruised bits. I've got bruises too. Remember when you hit me with the ketchup? Kept that bruise.' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    B'Jesus! B'Jesus! Budgie's Ass!    
    
    
    ...and to think people build entire careers following video debasement here in the West... http://instagram.com/p/doOi6sEnxa/     
    
    
    'Tit Milk Tara, the terrific Turkish tart, tantalisingly tumbled toward Toronto.' Milo's recital met rapturous applause. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Mummy, oh mummy!' Sadie called. 'Got my leather catsuit? Got it for me, mummy? Yeah? Got it? Leather puss-in-suit?' #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'Slutting's hard,' Tina said to her feet. 'I need a chemical peel.' So she made one. Out of loo block and paint. #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    'I've never seen one,' she said innocently. 'May I see yours, Pablo?' He stood still, letting her explore his tepid scalp #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    #creative #inventive http://instagram.com/p/d1Bp5Kkn6S/     
    
    
    Look at the poor cyclist! Got a bike, but still uses the train for long distances #violins http://instagram.com/p/d1BrR-kn6U/     
    
    
    Her captivating scent set my nostrils aflare. Notes of sweet cinnamon, offset by undertones of ham...and crude oil #badnovelopenings    
    
    
    See Your Favorite Brands' Logos Redesigned With Added Reality http://www.fastcocreate.com/1683438/see-your-favorite-brands-logos-redesigned-to-reflect-reality …    
    
    
    This is a neat 90's playlist... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TlLWFa1b1Bc&list=RD02TUC2b-OSZ00 …    
    
    
    There are only two kinds of songs these days: all the good ones are written by Pharrell, all the bad ones are by Bruno Mars. That's it.    
    
    
    I'm defo not going on The X Factor. Everyone who 'gets through' finds out their nans or mums are prostitutes. I'd hate that.    
    
    
    Plum Scrumpers: On Yer Bike! Walking: the surprising alternative t... http://ucasplumscrumpers.blogspot.com/2013/09/on-yer-bike-walking-surprising.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Where has this 'classic' been hiding? http://youtu.be/yCBmBq-KRIc     
    
    
    Crossword clue: 'Socially pretentious people'. 5 letters. Starts with 'A'. Ends in 'S'' #Arses ?    
    
    
    Today's theme song: http://youtu.be/C79spWeuakU     
    
    
    Can't decide if I like this or if it's bullshit...so it must be good. http://www.fastcodesign.com/3016945/infographic-of-the-day/taste-the-london-underground-with-this-synesthesia-subway-map …    
    
    
    Got a sudden urge to travel back to the 80s and release a single titled 'HamletSexPerformanz' #electricdreaming    
    
    
    Elon Musk Ox    
    
    
    @kellcomminc Curiouser and curiouser... you seek two entities to cover both vocations, or a singular fusion of the two?    
    
    
        
    
    
    An apt name for Gloucester station: http://w3w.cm/dull.longer.zones … #w3w    
    
    
    http://w3w.cm/dull.longer.zones … #w3w    
    
    
    @kellcomminc How 'bout that CW role? Whatcha got going on there??    
    
    
    Maypole syrup #stringy    
    
    
    I reckon I'd defo give out a 'wailing soprano solo' like the mums off the telly if I had to give birth. It's not easy. #ooohhhaaaahhoooohhh    
    
    
    Videogramme! Videogramme! Vid-hee-o-gramme! #videogramme    
    
    
    Kickstarting: AppSeed Turns Your Sketches Into Apps http://www.fastcodesign.com/3017637/kickstarting-appseed-turns-your-sketches-into-apps …    
    
    
    @kellcomminc Hi Bill. Keen to reply to your note, but can't as you don't follow me...if you follow...?    
    
    
    Today's theme song - Take You Meat Out Me Rice: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZqWLwZIncec&feature=share&list=PL45616DC0920AE08A …    
    
    
    These Surreal GIFs Are Made From Vintage Photos And Wit http://www.fastcocreate.com/3017349/these-surreal-gifs-are-made-from-vintage-photos-and-wit …    
    
    
    The legacy left to us by 90s music/technology: http://youtu.be/CWRMvC8mXAA     
    
    
        
    
    
    Today's theme song..in videogramme form http://youtu.be/o7crzDEjmTw     
    
    
    Amazon to launch oval shaped e-reader next Easter. Free book inside each one #kindleegg #productmashup    
    
    
    Condom assemblers lash out at being made to work 'under Durex'.    
    
    
    @izgzagadv Howdy! You need a person on your doorstep or are you willing to put someone up?? Interesting...very interesting    
    
    
    Yes! You heard right - Danny Dyer joins Eastenders cast this Xmas!!! #malcolmsmith http://instagram.com/p/e6nrp8kn-b/     
    
    
    Krankie Panky: Couple reveal swinging 'ding dongs' http://bbc.in/ugKac0     
    
    
    International exchanges: marketing at the crossroads of culture | UCAS Media https://www.ucasmedia.com/2013/blog/International-exchanges-marketing-at-the-crossroads-of-culture …    
    
    
    @MissJJN I ent bin dooin it laaaang! Congrats on the promo btw!    
    
    
    @Hare_Hart Can I apply? I've been known to sniff out a joke or two. Heck, I've even got my own fragrance #scentsofhumor    
    
    
    @Wingnutinc So...y'all git mah deets? Yessir that's raht, I'm one of them thurr cee dubyas #writernotfigher    
    
    
    @leeclowsbeard Even at airports?    
    
    
    @MissJJN That won't be hard, I assure you! Glad you're getting on :)    
    
    
    @adamlaker @Groupbrand Absolutely. You got 'em going spare? #writernotfighter    
    
    
    @d_fernandez16 To borrow a phrase from Grease: 'Tell me more, tell me more!' #writernotfighter    
    
    
    @QuinBc Crikey Moses! More deets please...!    
    
    
    @adamlaker @Groupbrand Romeo done! Check your inbox and we'll go from there...    
    
    
    14 Google Tools You Didn't Know Existed http://on.mash.to/15k39O8     
    
    
    @ModernClimate Word. Add another. And another. Sentence stringing, that's my bag...mind if I try my luck at this temple of creativity?    
    
    
    Abhorrent. http://youtu.be/pEUmhXCmXLU     
    
    
    See A Sofa Made From Brain Waves And 17 Other Amazing Products Of Digital Fabrication http://www.fastcocreate.com/3017465/digital-fabrication-gone-wild-out-of-hand-makers-use-brain-waves-to-design-furniture …    
    
    
    Obama's speech highlights rise of 3-D printing http://www.cnn.com/2013/02/13/tech/innovation/obama-3d-printing/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    8 Keys To Creating An Emotional Connection Between Products And People  http://www.fastcocreate.com/3017976/industry-pov/8-keys-to-creating-an-emotional-connection-between-products-and-people …    
    
    
    @ModernClimate  C'est vrai...that a problem...?    
    
    
    @MaudeChild Sterling stuff! #brandstakenote    
    
    
    @MaudeChild No praablem! It outlines some of the ideas I'm exploring around what brands can do to increase authentic engagement. I'll DM you    
    
    
    Shock and ore http://monocle.com/magazine/issues/68/shock-and-ore …    
    
    
    Could this be the strangest illustrated encyclopedia ever created?  http://www.psfk.com/2013/10/imaginary-world-encyclopedia.html#.UmGjzIUjqt4.twitter …    
    
    
    College course asks students to develop Google Glass apps as homework http://www.psfk.com/2013/10/college-course-google-glass-app.html#.UmGj7uNYQ_g.twitter …    
    
    
    How brands can take advantage of sound design to make their marketing message heard http://www.psfk.com/2013/10/brand-marketing-sound-trend.html#.UmGkyd2UVQk.twitter …    
    
    
    Fukuppy: Japan's Latest Attempt at Mascot Greatness http://www.brandchannel.com/home/post.aspx?id=ea1bd398-e6dd-48c6-a4fa-fa85666a5b9c …    
    
    
        
    
    
    This Map Shows What Every Country Leads The World In http://www.fastcocreate.com/3020280/creativity-by-the-numbers/this-map-shows-what-every-country-leads-the-world-in-and-its-not-e …    
    
    
    "Tiny Games" Promises A Game For Every Occasion And Every Location http://www.fastcocreate.com/3020271/tiny-games-promises-a-game-for-every-occasion-and-every-location …    
    
    
    So What Exactly Is Native Advertising? http://huff.to/19Q0Kgs  via @HuffPostUK    
    
    
    An "All You Can Eat" College Degree Could Be The Future Of Higher Education http://www.fastcoexist.com/3020185/an-all-you-can-eat-college-degree-could-be-the-future-of-higher-education …    
    
    
    Ch5 – Snorri gets fired for spying on the evil illusionist and for stealing a necklace carved from a deer’s antler...#dubiousexposition    
    
    
    Don't you wish you could go back?: http://youtu.be/PYND4zwDHvM     
    
    
        
    
    
    The toy everyone will want this Xmas..: http://youtu.be/ItuyFU3Zchk     
    
    
        
    
    
    This Interactive “Mood Map” Reveals Where You're Supposed to Live, By Temperament http://www.fastcocreate.com/3020843/this-interactive-mood-map-reveals-where-youre-apparently-supposed-to-live-by-temperament …    
    
    
    Cellulite skies #powerful http://instagram.com/p/gH2VjLEn2Y/     
    
    
    @Metro_showbiz As Danny Glover said in Lethal Weapon 'I'm too old for this'. But he never read the Hunger Games...#MetroHungerGames    
    
    
    What does content marketing have in common with Dubai? Find out in our latest UCAS Media blog post! http://lnkd.in/bKTFkwc     
    
    
    “Putting things in things” by @willsh https://medium.com/editors-picks/fba6ce3d1ed6 …    
    
    
    @Metro_Showbiz Quench my thirst for the Quarter Quell! #MetroCatchingFire    
    
    
    @jag105 Sounds most intriguing! Furnish me with more details, please!    
    
    
    Wow! Imagine being both sexy AND cross-eyed! Cor! Cor! #cor    
    
    
    Eyes...both...bearing centrally...can't stop them...from looking at...nose... #doublevision    
    
    
    If Beyonce was Scottish, would she address 'all the single laddies' ? #ringonit    
    
    
    I see...Broken, alcoholic Batman wonkily etches his signature symbol for disbelieving barfly buddies
#RorschachDoodle http://g.co/doodle/nmbpy7     
    
    
    Now I'm 34, is it ok for me to like Billy Idol? http://youtu.be/PinBVYKQGeM     
    
    
    @strangestpet Thanking you, juicy Brucie! How are ye wee man?    
    
    
    When The Quantified Self Gets Creepy: Turning David Cronenberg's Science Fiction Into Reality  http://www.fastcocreate.com/3021398/when-the-quantified-self-gets-creepy-turning-david-cronenbergs-science-fiction-into-reality …    
    
    
    @strangestpet Wish I could mate but working in Cheltenham these days. You ever up this way?    
    
    
    Great idea...only thing better is the company name...http://www.springwise.com/design-your-own-gourmet-sausages/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    'High class, nice ass' #withaonesunship: http://youtu.be/kM77K9DsLDQ     
    
    
    iPad users: Check out the new UCAS app - the Little Guide to Higher Education. https://itunes.apple.com/gb/app/ucas-the-little-guide/id740527898?mt=8 …    
    
    
    Am I the only person in the world who loves this song???: http://youtu.be/ixBryyQSrD8     
    
    
    'Rememba dis?!' http://youtu.be/HV9VzsXCFh4  #romeodone    
    
    
    Hey! Michael Bay! Found the lead Decepticon for your next Transformers movie.#naughtytech http://instagram.com/p/g45ICyEnxI/     
    
    
        
    
    
    The seven deadly sins of email marketing to students. | UCAS Media https://www.ucasmedia.com/2013/blog/The-seven-deadly-sins-of-email-marketing-to-students …    
    
    
    Benny's Song (Five Kids to Feed) - 1990 Total Recall Music Video: http://youtu.be/LAtBmQ0xFgs     
    
    
    This is my current fave song: http://youtu.be/SeIJmciN8mo  #hoopdehoopdehoop #iowndat    
    
    
        
    
    
    How long is a piece of string theory?    
    
    
    Beware the 'scorpican'! #powerful http://instagram.com/p/hLb7K7En4Y/     
    
    
    See Google Ring Toss, Adobe Face Cream, Durex Dinghies, And Other Unexpected Brand Extensions http://www.fastcocreate.com/3022272/see-google-ring-toss-adobe-face-cream-durex-dinghies-and-other-unexpected-brand-extensions …    
    
    
    A drop of snail plop... http://www.psfk.com/2013/11/snail-digested-paper-material.html?utm_source=Sailthru&utm_medium=email&utm_term=daily&utm_campaign=Daily%202013-11-28 …    
    
    
    @telly_Ads Better late than never!    
    
    
    @komoot Gotta say - a great way to get the right person's full attention...#niceone #promoteyoursocialmediaperson    
    
    
    How does she make any money from that shop? How does she live?? Or am reading too much into 'Miranda'?    
    
    
    Having my six month catch up with the Backstreet Boys: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1jkH7An7dKk&feature=share&list=RD4fndeDfaWCg&index=15 …    
    
    
    There are numerous reasons I find this funny... http://instagram.com/p/hiDF5mkn0R/     
    
    
    Portrait of a gurning posh twot doesn't entice me into going racing... http://instagram.com/p/hiD0q3kn0s/     
    
    
    Inspirational...http://youtu.be/B2Tkx6BgRFE     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Armoured Van Helmet: http://youtu.be/wxkgvvJiLqs     
    
    
    How To Become A Master Of Creativity: Work It! http://lnkd.in/d75BgqS     
    
    
    Best music video ever. Really. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SPlQpGeTbIE&feature=share&list=RDSa3VDErv2wk&index=19 …    
    
    
    'Eating Game' takes on a whole new meaning... http://www.psfk.com/2013/12/video-gamer-canned-meal.html?utm_source=Sailthru&utm_medium=email&utm_term=daily&utm_campaign=Daily%202013-12-09 …    
    
    
    A train host is a curious creature; one that can munch crisps, facetime friends, and still show vague disinterest in passengers' concerns.    
    
    
    The train host also sports a scouse brow and a strong Brum accent.Although an employee, she wears civilian clothes, adding to the mystery...    
    
    
    O train host, your mild contempt is thinly veiled laziness. Overcompensating for your insecurities, you exude crude arrogance...    
    
    
    O train host you shall be counted among the vacuous on the Day of Judgement. But munch on crisps in your ignorance...    
    
    
    O train host your hair is near white, yet your thick brows are black as night. Painted caterpillars bridging forehead and eyesight...    
    
    
    O train host I implore you; resist the urge to broadcast hopes and fears to your captive audience. Seek redemption and peace, o train host.    
    
    
        
    
    
    For all you marketers out there...:) http://lnkd.in/dBrgPdQ     
    
    
    Loving the latest Hollyoaks opening, particularly the Multiple Miggs-esque 'liquid wrist flick' performed by the pramfaced female reprobate    
    
    
    Must... resist... urge to knock hats off posh racegoers' twottish heads...#cheltenhamraces    
    
    
    Début de Soiree - Nuit de Folie http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yTzyJ7kDLL4&feature=share&list=RDT7YJoGXs2i8&index=2 … e    
    
    
    No. Way. Jose. http://instagram.com/p/iEmSqPEn43/     
    
    
    How the “internet of things” will replace the web http://lnkd.in/ddgBGNX     
    
    
    Content Crusades: The next generation in branded storytelling http://po.st/lJIYLt     
    
    
    What Should We Do With Abandoned Airports?  By Shaunacy Ferro http://www.fastcodesign.com/3023705/terminal-velocity/what-should-we-do-with-abandoned-airports … via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://www.psfk.com/2013/12/mental-illness-tshirts.html#!qpSOQ …    
    
    
    hello! and this is my new videogramme! https://vine.co/v/hEbOHPUMQqi     
    
    
    What the Heck Is Blue Raspberry? http://shar.es/9nESG  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Struggling musicians. Simply add the words 'featuring Pitbull' to your next single's credits. Hey presto! Instant success!    
    
    
    Will Smith - the cross-dressing years: http://youtu.be/Tc1IphRx1pk     
    
    
    @HumanautSpeaks Gee willikers! Better get my applying blades on...sharpish!    
    
    
    Crumbs! How interesting! http://m.mentalfloss.com/article.php?id=31904 …    
    
    
    Puppy love... https://vine.co/v/hYHJpZexBhm     
    
    
    Sheer and utter genius. http://youtu.be/0zK5l_JnB2o     
    
    
    Finally figured out who the subject of this song is...'Time' http://youtu.be/tyANFcnrM8I     
    
    
    Good idea to start a letter with: 'It’s that time of year again. Y’know, the new time. The new time of year. The New Year...' ???    
    
    
    @charliejssmith Please, furnish me with the deets!    
    
    
    @petermcneive Well, I'm seeking to fill the void of an Art Director in mine...    
    
    
    @digitalgurus kerching! Check me one time http://www.toverbanda.com     
    
    
    'A rather intolerable pain in the head, brother-sir. Should be over by this after-lunch.'    
    
    
    Imagine yourself runway modelling…. http://www.we7.com/listen/Malcolm-McLaren/Deep-In-Vogue/radio?song=232857 …    
    
    
    Cheap rashes bring me out in jewellery.    
    
    
    Ocelot like life. http://www.we7.com/listen/Depeche-Mode/Master-And-Servant-Single-Version--2006-Digital-Remaster/radio?song=726326 …    
    
    
    @garyfawcett1 @nicotatz Try www,http://toverbanda.com  instead #justsaying    
    
    
    'Reference example overleaf without referencing the fact it's an example overleaf' #FML    
    
    
    'You don't understand about runnin' with the gang, 'cos you don't...' http://www.we7.com/listen/Black-Lace/Gang-Bang/radio?song=1476490 …    
    
    
    'Pacific Rim' #chortle    
    
    
    The Aquabats! Burger Rain Music Video - The Hub: http://youtu.be/pYlafjh0qak     
    
    
    @TUnit916 howdy! Please tell me more! To whom should I send an email with my deets?    
    
    
    @DirectFocus so...may I reapply? Please?!    
    
    
    @TheDrum 'this is not just multichannel marketing...'    
    
    
    Gammadeus, Gammadeus, Gammadeus!    
    
    
    @Scribblingsnook Morning Snickers. How bist du?    
    
    
    @Scribblingsnook Not three bad. Got a few l'il schemes up me sleeve...You still Leino-ing or totes dedicated to booque?    
    
    
    @Scribblingsnook Cool - you working with 'em? Do send my love. Seen any other former Renegades lately?    
    
    
    Cilla is the new 'black' #busintraffic    
    
    
    @thebrandunion DM!    
    
    
    @TBWAManchester Yes. It could. But it's out of my hands now...#choosewiselyteam    
    
    
    @chomoi DM! What's the craic?    
    
    
    Oops! http://instagr.am/p/UbY0ktkn3R/     
    
    
    @a_copywriter Brevity? Heard she make a mean toasted cheese sandwich...    
    
    
    Crap. The Content Marketing Deluge. by @velocitytweets on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/dougkessler/crap-the-content-marketing-deluge …    
    
    
    I'm off the chain! (Glad 'cos it was starting to chafe).    
    
    
    Rhythmically brushin' my shoulders... http://www.we7.com/listen/Nelly/Hot-in-Herre/radio?song=1328158 …    
    
    
    @chomoi You're followed! In a non-stalky way of course...    
    
    
    @NMuels That makes you sound heavy though...    
    
    
    @snumo What up? Whassa best email to send to?    
    
    
    @DirectFocus That mean I'm outta the running? #ohman    
    
    
    Need to find a cult to help me self actualise. Any suggestions? Can't do the whole 'God' thing though. #roastlambofgod    
    
    
    Take a step back, look into the mirror. Surprise, Surprise like Cilla, it's a killer. #ohnothatstheword    
    
    
    Odd sensation. Bashed my knee but then got a soothing rush of adrenaline that's currently cooling my ears. Does that make me a masochist?    
    
    
    *Twiddles bow tie for effect*    
    
    
    @GinnyRoberson Hear you loud and clear. If you find any, lemme know too 'kay?    
    
    
    Mamals http://pinterest.com/pin/182536591118748574/ …    
    
    
    Sharp UFO http://pinterest.com/pin/182536591118748577/ …    
    
    
    Evidence suggests Mork used a Skype prototype during his end of show chats with Orson #comeinorson    
    
    
    'Gurning For Profit' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Back To Black: Cilla's Battle With Depression' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Hold On Tight: Confessions of a Clutch Bag' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Pump Up the Preserve: Formalising Popular Music' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Intermittent Dolphins: A Life in Divergent Thinking' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Sellafield: The Fallout' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Three Mile Island Dressing' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'The Adventures of Carl Fudge' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Master Don and the Winged Reptiles' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Felix: Cat Amongst The Pigeons' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Derek, Wine, And The Building Trade' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'When Felicity Arrives' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Father Dinner' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    'Standing Nonchalantly' #booksimaywrite    
    
    
    