Who has every remix I've done in their music playlist?    
    
    
    #MusicMonday: @CapitalCities feat. Hans Inglish "Safe and Sound" (Remix) http://snd.sc/185E4X5     
    
    
    @ceesita_ My new remix is out. Enjoy! http://snd.sc/185E4X5     
    
    
    @chrisnycvillage Thanks  for the follow Chris. Would love to collaborate with you on something in the future.    
    
    
    Shout out to you @briecrump :) Thanks for following    
    
    
    My boy got me out here working on his car smh. Thought my mechanic days were over. #MadBoltsLeftOver http://instagram.com/p/cp2O4-PiNe/     
    
    
    #NP: @CapitalCities feat. Hans Inglish "Safe and Sound" (Remix) http://snd.sc/185E4X5  #Retweet    
    
    
    Anyone remember the days when u could be outside playing & everyone went home at 8pm cause it was TGIF on TV? Lol #FamilyMatters #StepByStep    
    
    
    Ludacris' mixtape is bananas....damn    
    
    
    only watch up to two hours of tv a day" oh well i dont have time to watch tv because i stay on the internet all day so im good and healthy    
    
    
    If my entire family died but there was pizza at the wake, a part of me would still be like "yay pizza"    
    
    
    The industry could care less about "talent" really...It's nothing personal just business though right?    
    
    
    @cassyofLondon yup    
    
    
    Drank 1 Sam Adams and I'm swaying. Wtd? Haven't drank in so long my body doesn't know what to do right now. Smh    
    
    
    See...I even misspelled wtf? ......wtf? Lol    
    
    
    @Geordaina Take one from a.neighbor. I mean borrow one    
    
    
    Yo Stephen Colbert is THE MAN ...Seriously. He just gave it to MTV and Viacom for @DaftPunk not appearing on his show lol    
    
    
    Yo thus show Drunk History on Comedy Central is funny as hell. First time seeing this.    
    
    
    @CityOfPastele no prob babe    
    
    
    Photo: #Inspiring others is one of the main reasons I do #music. Messages like these help keep me focused on... http://tmblr.co/Za0yWtrgUkz4     
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe Cheescake is my favorite desert. Creme Brulee is a close second.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I have a slight fear of pigeons    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I learned to fly a plane when I was 13    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I went to a Catholic School for 8 years and I use to be an Alter Boy    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I'm a 80's Pop Fanatic. It was the best era of Pop in my opinion.    
    
    
    @RettaWorldPeace @Geordaina Yall was sippin extra from the Wine huh? lol    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I once performed on 106nPark and Flopped BIG TIME!!    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I use to buy Wu-Tang albums just so I could hear Method Man's verses.    
    
    
    @DJCategory5 Damn all the ex Catholics are in music? lol    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I Consider myself a Deist. Don't know what that is? Well--> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deism     
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I get along with Lesbians extremely well. #Random    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I helped build the first 8 production engines on the Airbus A-380. Largest airplane in the world. PIC: pic.twitter.com/6qtRULQQL0    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I don't realy have a whisper voice. I'm usually always calm but I can yell over anyone. Any challengers?    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I can't perform AT ALL if I'm even slightly drunk or high. I will forget lyrics. It's happened to me    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I like women who are taller than me for some strange reason.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe The first producer I ever worked with was @blacklight_diaz when I attended @FullSail. Our first song was called "NYC Rhythm"    
    
    
    Semi embarrasing footage of me performing my first song ever circa 2004--->http://youtu.be/tO29gzRGqBc  Produced by @blacklight_diaz    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe The first remix verse I ever did was to @CassieSuper's "Long Way To Go" in 2006. Check it out http://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/my-very-first-remix-verse-2006 …    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe When Myspace was poppin, I had 1mil+ plays on a song which got me a deal with now cuurent pres. of @RepublicRecords    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe First love song I wrote was for->@Boogsneffect<- Putting her on blast but she wont care. My boy @izzyspeakslife sang the hook    
    
    
    Actually the song was for my boy's girl but I jacked it and put my verses on it. He was cool with it though. #SuperSappy    
    
    
    @THEREALCHOZN I know exactly why actually. it's the same reason every guy gets stuck watching Telemundo not knowing what they're saying    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe One of my favorite movies is "The Orphanage" by Gullermo Del Torro    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe Favorite Childhood movie is probably Wizard Of Oz. Part 1 and 2. A lot of people don't know there's a part 2.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I played piano at Carnegie Hall in NyC when I was 6. I regret stopping cause I can barely play now. Just enough though.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I have a thing for Middle Eastern women. And I LOVE Middle Eastern Food.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I thrive off competition. I'm still waiting for the day a rapper disses me in a song lol #SeriouslyThough    
    
    
    The biggest lie in America is that hard work ALWAYS pays off. It doesn't. Ask any poor person that works super hard.    
    
    
    #NewMusic @CapitalCities feat. Hans Inglish "Safe and Sound" (Remix) http://snd.sc/185E4X5  #Retweet    
    
    
    New favorite song: Tennis Court by @lordemusic http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D8Ymd-OCucs …    
    
    
    I've been getting subscriptions to Outsiders magazine out of nowhere to my house past 2 months. Someone trying to tell me something? Lol    
    
    
    Obama doesn't think Snowden is a patriot yet what he did is directly leading to the #NSA reforms he's putting out. Sounds patriotic to me.    
    
    
    Anyone at all thought it was funny that the plane at the end of Fast and Furious 6 took like 35min to take off? That's a long runway #smh    
    
    
    Gonna need to remix a One Dirrction song soon. That's overdue    
    
    
    @Zakswfc   lmao. Too funny    
    
    
    @Zakswfc All my latest is on http://www.Soundcloud.com/HansInglish  I have a new project with @pixikills as well coming soon. Check em out    
    
    
    Did you know that Affirmative Action benefits white women the most? Learned something new today    
    
    
    Damn @BonnieMcKee  you did it again. @katyperry 's new single #Roar is dope. You have the golden pen.    
    
    
    Ask me anything @ http://ask.fm/HansInglish     
    
    
    #PSA #AintNoBodyGotTimeForThat #ThatClubLooksPoppin #TheAudioIsGreat #SaidNoOneEver http://instagram.com/p/c41-uTPiL-/     
    
    
    VIDEO: Woooww @DonLemonCNN went in on @UncleRUSH Sheeessh. He made some really great points though I must say http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6cPk5dBxPyo …    
    
    
    @empire_live Thanks for the follow guys. Your stuff is great. If you ever need a feature verse or something don't hesitate to hit me up :)    
    
    
    Elon Musk just dropped his plans for the Hyperloop today which got me thinking. He is definitely the real life Iron Man. #Undisputed    
    
    
    Good morning #InglishMajors. At this time of the morn, the only thing I can think to say is something cliche sooo, "Rise & Grind" people!!!    
    
    
    @djrossone lmao off at your Kendrick comment    
    
    
    NICE!! Lorde Becomes The First Woman To Top The Alternative Chart In 17 Years http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/08/12/lorde-first-woman-alternative-chart-17-years-royals_n_3745113.html …    
    
    
    Imma let Kendrick Lamar finish but @LupeFiasco had the best verse of 2013 on 'Bad Decisions"    
    
    
    @emanuelhouse  thanks for the tweets E.    
    
    
    Big shout out to @sheenasakai. Super talented singer. Check  her out guys    
    
    
    @IM_YOUNG_D Appreciate the follow homie    
    
    
    I've said this before and I'll say it again. @DawnRichard's album "GoldenHeart" is the sh**    
    
    
    @deejaymig  Appreciate the love man    
    
    
    Much Love to all my #Greeks. Always supporting hard.    
    
    
    Just wrapped up the mix for an exclusive track I have coming with @pixikill Get excited #InglishMajors Coming Sooon! #electropop at its best    
    
    
    Patiently explaining to a 5yr old that night lights only mean u will SEE the monster as it rips u apart..sometimes not knowing is better    
    
    
    Best Kendrick Lamar response is definitely Papoose's. Check it out. DAMN!! https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=wF6p58cl5A4#at=142 …    
    
    
    @OMGitsShateezy lol very good way of putting it.    
    
    
    Watching @jasonderulo live right now. Gotta support my Haitian brothers-> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WqjXN5RRYsw …    
    
    
    This music industry will suck the life out of you... seriously.    
    
    
    @Bethliliani Hey Beth. Como Esta?    
    
    
    @juliane115 for sure :)    
    
    
    Quick shoutout to a few Top of the class #InglishMajors who mean a lot to me @channtiee88 @katy_batyox @theduchessv79 @Geordaina #Love    
    
    
    @AlyxCullen Nice blog btw    
    
    
    Gottta show @YourMusicRadar major love for always supporting my remixes.    
    
    
    #KeepCalm & #SpeakInglish http://instagram.com/p/dHp7z6viNN/     
    
    
    Watching House Party 2 thinking why can't parties be like that again? Now everyone just stands around mean mugging each other    
    
    
    Every time I watch #Catfish I can't help but think education has failed these ppl since all they needed to do was a simple Google search.    
    
    
    In 2013 you SHOULD NOT be getting catfished...seriously. If you had real sex instead of phone sex, you wouldn't be in those situations.    
    
    
    Follow me on Instagram People. I post the most beautiful pictures of Subway sandwiches and add the hastag #foodart & #foodporn @HansInglish    
    
    
    The video to my single #RealityShow is actually a compilation of videos I've taken at clubs etc. over the years http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W9hP6loboXE&feature=share&list=PLVIL-byuop6A1Ng44Wr6hFft-0uMjzXJe …    
    
    
    #FunFact I recorded Reality Show with Johnny Nice who was an engineer & producer on Rihanna's first 2 albums    
    
    
    @nilesG Hey Niles. Would love for you to take a look at some of my material if you get some time. Have a great Sunday and thanks in advance.    
    
    
    #FunFact It took 48 different mixes of my song #DanceDruggie before I was completely satisfied. @blacklight_diaz was executive producer    
    
    
    #FunFact I recorded the idea for #DanceDruggie in 2009 and never released it till early this year. I didn't like it's original production    
    
    
    #FunFact I did my first "Hip-House" track in 2004 and A&R's at record labels straight shitted on me saying it woud never work #GoFigure    
    
    
    @kacee_cox Yeah so what... :)    
    
    
    #ProducersToWatch --> @DemitriMedina @blacklight_diaz @CapBeatz    
    
    
    #StraightUpTellSomeoneTheyreHot @mishapagano #JustSaying    
    
    
    Maybe I shouldn't partcipate in this #StraightUpTellSomeoneTheyreHot T.T.. I know some ppl are gonna catch feelings if I dont mention them    
    
    
    #FunFact My video for #RealityShow is a compilation of personal videos Ive taken at clubs etc. over the years http://goo.gl/SXBAOw     
    
    
    @carlaelyse lmao...save the energy for when I shoot official video ;)    
    
    
    @freemagz Appreciate you guys adding me to your Soundcloud.    
    
    
    I really only produce for myself but if any Pop or EDM artists need a remix or original done for a good price, hit me up.    
    
    
    Are you a vocalist and live in NY? Looking for a singer to reference songs for major label Pop artists. Great exposure opportunity. Hit me    
    
    
    Agree RT @toscamarleen: The 'fat' twin has a nicer body. Why does the other twin think its ok that i can see her chest plate @nicoleandbri    
    
    
    @toscamarleen no but i knew who you were talking about because that show is on right now l lol    
    
    
    @toscamarleen Yeah they are really good on WWE but the show is not for me. Can't deal    
    
    
    Intimidation of journalists by the US & British Gov't is not ok Mr. @BarackObama #RIP Investigative Journalism    
    
    
    @Katy_Batyox lol It would be slightly if I didn't see it an hour late    
    
    
    Just touched down at @PattyLaurent's Pre VMA myxer with @RSVPLifestyle . Looking sexy in here.    
    
    
    Ladies, if you want to see Jason Derulo perform tonight come out to Finale on 199 Bowery St. NYC Drinks on me. Hit me up if you're coming    
    
    
    Honestly @martinsolveig's - The Night Out sounds so crazy in the club. Love that song http://goo.gl/LDnr55     
    
    
    Ok....@360ismusic ...SOB's..... Queens is in the building end of story. #Crazy    
    
    
    @Mackey_Memo Do what you do homie. Appreciate the love.    
    
    
    Got a remix to Bruno Mars' Treasure coming in the next day or 2 for all my #InglishMajors    
    
    
    If you have the Palladia channel turn to it now. This is giving me life    
    
    
    @Katy_Batyox nah I meant like the actual audio quality of the microphones etc. at live shows in the past.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @ShesRYAN ..Enjoy your day even though it's shitty outside.    
    
    
    Someone needs to tell attractive people that their stories are boring.    
    
    
    I bet the Al Qaeda recruiting video is just footage of Americans waiting in line 3 hours for Cronuts.    
    
    
    Been working on a song with someone in Paris for like 2 months & Ive already done like 6 different versions. Still not where it needs to be.    
    
    
    Right about now I need like 4 shots of Tequila    
    
    
    Been working since this morning and I'm just now remembering to eat dinner. Smh I can't be doing this anymore.    
    
    
    @Geordaina Oh I need that lol.    
    
    
    Man vs. Nature  #UpperEastSide #NYC http://instagram.com/p/dXIsLQviFD/     
    
    
    @NinaRawz wait you in NY?    
    
    
    @NinaRawz smh and you aint hit me up? Really? -_-'how long are you here?    
    
    
    @NinaRawz ahhhh man. Worst time. I'm working till late on a project right now. You leave tomorrow what time?    
    
    
    Some people say waaay too much on twitter I swear. Certain things are better kept to yourself    
    
    
    Ok people get excited because this @pixikill  x @HansInglish collaboration just rounded 3rd base. Release date TBA...    
    
    
    @NinaRawz lmao well I DM'd you so just hit me tomorrow whenever    
    
    
    Got an early surprise for you guys. Go to my Soundcloud page--> http://www.soundcloud.com/HansInglish  #Retweet    
    
    
    Just linked up with @NinaRawz while she's visiting NYC. Super cool peoples. Been supporting me on radio & social media for 3 years plus.    
    
    
    Always dope how twitter can bring people together. I've met some of the best people on here. Thankful    
    
    
    @Marcus_Pepe  Appreciate the tweet Marcus    
    
    
    #MusicMonday Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  #Retweet    
    
    
    #MusicMonday Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  #Retweet ..    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva true. That song is def. Not a good as treasure.    
    
    
    #MusicMonday @BrunoMars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  #Retweet    
    
    
    Have you heard my new Bruno Mars "Treasure" Remix? Check it out!! http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  #Retweet    
    
    
    @Geordaina Maybe it is. You just never know hahaha    
    
    
    @Akin9603 @minnely101 Check out the Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. @HansInglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  Think you'll like it :)    
    
    
    @M0weezyANA @sbrem71 Check out the Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. @HansInglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  Think you'll like it :)    
    
    
    Someone care to tell me the point of decaf coffee? It's like smoking a fake cigarette.    
    
    
    Need some listening material on your way to work? Check out my Bruno Mars #Treasure (Remix) on Soundcloud http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    @j_buzzi Happy Birthday homie    
    
    
    Need some listening material on your way to work? Check out my @BrunoMars #Treasure (Remix) on @Soundcloud http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    So I just saw Miley Cyrus' VMA perforce and....wow, can you say black culture exploitation at it's finest. Who are the people on her team?    
    
    
    Why do white people want to be "ratchet" so bad? And why are they abusing the word 6 years after Hurricane Chris sadly introduced it?    
    
    
    Can we leave the twerking to @Ciara? PLEAAASSSEEEE!!!    
    
    
    I just saw someone by themselves not looking at a phone. Hope they're ok.    
    
    
    Lmao .true RT @Geordaina: @HansInglish should have lent them your charger....    
    
    
    Met the group @pixikill 3 weeks ago on Instagram...Yes Instagram and we decided this needed to happen.… http://instagram.com/p/diIuZwPiGU/     
    
    
    "To be interested in the changing seasons is a happier state of mind than to be hopelessly in love with spring." -George Santayana    
    
    
    Let's set the record straight. Twerking has been around since the 90's. Why is it such a new phenomenon all of a sudden?    
    
    
    I guess @diplo is probably responsible for making twerking popular on a National and if not an international level    
    
    
    "No problem can withstand the assault of sustained thinking." -Voltaire    
    
    
    #InglishMajors I need sime inspiration right now. Send me a link to song that really gets you motivated to take on the world. Anything...    
    
    
    @Zakswfc Always good to catch em by surprise ...thanks homie    
    
    
    Honestly these motivational songs everyone's sending my way are giving me life right now. Keep em coming...    
    
    
    @DJMMMusic didn't forget you man. Will have your drop tomorrow    
    
    
    @meghna_sangwan Good Morning buddy. Have you heard my Bruno Mars #Treasure (REMIX) ? -> let me know what you think http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    @KittyCavas Happy Birthday homie. Hope all is well and you're enjoying yourself :)    
    
    
    Meet me on the corner of...umm, what street is this? #NYC #Me http://instagram.com/p/dpuwrNviN7/     
    
    
    Chick asks me where she can get the D. I paused for a second & just had to laugh. I was like "oohhh the D TRAIN? U can get it at the corner    
    
    
    #Retweet Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    There's nothing that leaves you more fatigued than an unfinished task    
    
    
    @darcieGNO congrats that's huge!!    
    
    
    @DJMMMusic yeah i sent it yesterday    
    
    
    @DJMMMusic Going to check in a few when I get back to the crib    
    
    
    @MishaPagano ask jokes aside though, coffee table books are aleays good. Try "The Creativity of Ditko" "The New Erotic Photography 2"    
    
    
    @MishaPagano and there is always this one which is popular for select audiences http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/0767917537 …    
    
    
    You really think the US cares about 500 children dying in a chemical attack? The 1st Gulf War we killed 500,000 children w/out blinking    
    
    
    Big shout out to @iamkingdeco #Talent    
    
    
    I'm urging everyone to write to their Congressman and protest @BarackObama striking against Syria. All my NY'ers contact @cbrangel    
    
    
    #NowPLaying @BrunoMars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    Well since @ElectricZooNY is canceled, everyone can just go to the Bronx Zoo    
    
    
    @BrideOfChucky__ yeah    
    
    
    OH man I had the Fig & Mascarpone Cronut and that s*** is POPPING. Best flavor yet.    
    
    
    Via @Gawker: Dear Khary (An Autobiography of Gentrification) http://goo.gl/hRLWKg 

-Wow this was such a great read I just had to share it.    
    
    
    If you think that the U.S. morally cares about 1,400 people dying in a chemical attack in #Syria, I have a bridge to sell you #JustSaying    
    
    
    is there anything more capitalist than a peanut with a top hat, cane, and monocle selling you other peanuts to eat    
    
    
    @iGetMuzik Appreciate the follow guys    
    
    
    Back on it!!! I'm live at #SullivanRoom, #NYC Wednesday 9.4.13 for a college end of the summer party… http://instagram.com/p/dxn6MfviLi/     
    
    
    If you want exclusive content and news sign up for my email list here: http://bit.ly/Q8gLab     
    
    
    So apparently the girl who died at EZoo took 6 hits of Molly. WHY would anyone do such a thing? 6? Really?    
    
    
    Oh BTW, I'm live at #SullivanRoom, #NYC tomorrow 9.4.13 for a college end of the summer party 18+ http://Instagram.com/p/dxn6MfviLi/ ”    
    
    
    @ezralevant @carney @teapartyorg @loudobbsnews Wait, u guys realize that a lot of Presidents have been photographed w/ feet on desk right?    
    
    
    Sara Bareilles said there was no beef but Katy Perry's "Roar" sounds so much like "Brave". In the hood thats like someone stealing ur chain    
    
    
    TONIGHT:  live at #SullivanRoom, #NYC Wednesday 9.4.13 for a college end of the summer party… http://Instagram.com/p/dxn6MfviLi/ ”    
    
    
    Good morning everyone!!! Just want to thank all the fans that came out to my show at Sullivan Room and showed love. It was crazy    
    
    
    Much love to @thedreamlab Robots for performing with me and much love to their whole crew. Hopefully we can do it again at some point    
    
    
    Shout out to all the #InglishMajors who showed love last night at #SullivanRoom, #NYC. #live #show… http://instagram.com/p/d4qOKnviKU/     
    
    
    Rocking out @ Sullivan Room with The Dream Lab Robots. 
#pheeders #electro #photography #pop #edm #hiphop ... © 2013 http://pheed.com/p/33177464     
    
    
    @Channtiee88 cause you're a boss. We all know that    
    
    
    Another dope shot of my performance at #SullivanRoom taken by @mikemckay24 http://instagram.com/p/d9hle4PiNF/     
    
    
    "Smooth Criminal" #photography #pheed #pheeders #fashion http://pheed.com/p/33475899     
    
    
    @Channtiee88 like you're new avatar btw    
    
    
    Is Breaking Bad delaying tasks in anyone else's life like it is mine?    
    
    
    Hands down @923NowFM plays the best music on Sat. Night I swear    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana Tired from all the sex drugs and rock n roll . Mostly all the drugs...'.........in "Breaking Bad"    
    
    
    Cowboys ALL day. Goodnight...    
    
    
    Oh, hey @justinbieber... http://instagram.com/p/eC1qz2PiHf/     
    
    
    Yesterday was crazy. Got to meet Justin Bieber, Paris Hilton and Miguel at Dream Hotel    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva lol not sure he would take the advice but he was cool enough to stop, say hi and take a pic so some credit due    
    
    
    Love my city!! Rooftop #DreamHotel #PHD #NYC @ Dream Downtown http://instagram.com/p/eDZphaviIx/     
    
    
    9 out of 10 men prefer a girl with a big butt. The 10th man prefers the other 9 men.    
    
    
    I'm thinking the saddest thing about this whole Gucci Man beef on twitter is the complete disrespect of the English language    
    
    
    Just voted on a really old voting machine. Starred at it for 5 min before I knew what to do. Now I know how older ppl feel at digital polls    
    
    
    Naked girls and Disco Balls...    
    
    
    @NataliaKills  album "Trouble" on repeat...    
    
    
    Yo @ADreamOfficial is killing it in the game right now. @ladygaga 's song "Swine" is CRAZY! That beat is so sick man    
    
    
    Is Flo Rida serious with this new Beamz product he is selling? WTF???https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=vVQpaGeW3xo …    
    
    
    Good morning everyone!!! Hope your day started off on a positive note    
    
    
    Damn @real_mistercee is resigning from hot 97. Crazy that it's his last day today. Been listening to thus dude since like 1999    
    
    
    #tbt coming off stage at Highline Ballroom and got mobbed by a group of girls from the UK. Thoughts in… http://instagram.com/p/eK9XLpPiEh/     
    
    
    Maybe teenagers just aren't strong enough yet to remove the sticker from their hat    
    
    
    Have we worked together in the past or recently? Add me to your connections on linked in here: http://lnkd.in/bEZD5Um     
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Man I'm jealous. Save me a slice    
    
    
    #LoneyGirl Exhibition @ #MartosGallery..Who wants to roll with me tonight 6pm? http://instagram.com/p/eNkWirPiAO/     
    
    
    @colortheory Hey Brian appreciate the follow. Loving your stuff. Would love to collaborate on something in the future if you'd be down    
    
    
    RT  “@patbits: “What are the specs on those pecs?” My dream girl says to me at the E3 Square Enix booth.”

-Who? Sasha Grey?    
    
    
    @toscamarleen does that mean you in the area?    
    
    
    @colortheory no problem man. Good music is good music    
    
    
    Summertime Sadness...    
    
    
    If you live in NY and you're not listening to @DJYONNY on Friday nights @923NowFM somethings wrong with you. #justsaying    
    
    
    Shout out to @BChamp_ & @MariaVitagliano ..Been a while since I've meet such hard working and humble people like you guys. #Salute    
    
    
    @BChamp_ @MariaVitagliano man I can't get "Ambiance" out of my head #wtf  lol    
    
    
    The homie @TravieMcCoy is filming a video right across the street from me. Watching the action with my binoculars lol    
    
    
    Spent the day getting the "What are you doing with your life speech" from my parents...Happens once every few months    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of "Giving Away Tons of Personal Data to Corporations and Government Agencies Because I'm an Idiot" on FourSquare!    
    
    
    @_1337_x3_ Hey thanks for the follow btw :-)    
    
    
    @DJCoopDaVillain Yo you dipped out already?    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to my cuzzo @RonAustinJr !! Hope you enjoy all the lube and condoms bestowed upon you by the family lol    
    
    
    Watch "Maejor Ali - Lolly ft. Juicy J, Justin Bieber" on YouTube http://goo.gl/K1Bq7J 

-Justin spittin verses now? He kinda killed it    
    
    
    #tbt Fashion week 2011 with my cousin @nakitabanana http://instagram.com/p/edF_UqPiBg/     
    
    
    Songwriting, Songwriting and more songwriting    
    
    
    Newest TV Show addiction is "Suits"...Really good show    
    
    
    Big shout out to singer @SitaraKmusic Her voice is amazing. Be sure to follow her people.    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana Did @RonAustinJr win an award? Did he do a speech? I'm mad I'm missing it but there was a situation. #HeavyFlow    
    
    
    Do everything with the thought process that your character may just be getting tested...    
    
    
    Quick look at my #SullivanRoom #show 2 weeks ago with @thedreamlab Robots. Head to my YouTube page for… http://instagram.com/p/ek0B1DPiK_/     
    
    
    Artists still think they can get record deals by doing demos? lol that's funny...    
    
    
    Best new Jersey in the NFL has to go to the Miami Dolphins hands down. #tough    
    
    
    With that said, what's up with the new two tone Garbage Man Green Jets uniform?    
    
    
    Video: Some footage of me live at the Sullivan Room, NYC. Amazing all the love these kids showed.  http://tmblr.co/Za0yWtvpu7fl     
    
    
    Is it national post a baby pic on Facebook day?    
    
    
    Girls heres how to tell if a guy wants you for sex: 

1) He does    
    
    
    Shout out to @louddigital for the great event last night. Had a lot of fun. @wale and @myfabolouslife killed it http://thbs.co/p/BPGGIP?ref=ipad …    
    
    
    Attention everyone: When you Shazam a song, you don't have to hold your phone up in the air becuase it's a song and sound goes everywhere!    
    
    
    There's a haunted house in Philly where you go through it completely naked. I really wanna do that    
    
    
    @toscamarleen would you do it?    
    
    
    Why is Chelsea Clinton wearing one of Shaba Rank's jackets on @TheDailyShow ?    
    
    
    Grand Theft Auto reminds me of Florida. Except one lets you shoot people without consequence and the other is a video game.    
    
    
    Cowboys Nation #ThatllBeAll #NFL    
    
    
    I need some leather jogging pants. Just want to see how that works out ..for jogging    
    
    
    @MishaPagano lol I actually would do it. That would be truly overcoming your fears. I think it's a great idea.    
    
    
    @MishaPagano Lmmfao Oh that's why you're on haunted house boycott.Got it. Have you ever been to the ones in Orlando at Islands Of Adventure?    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana Williamsburg is being gingerbreaded too.Don't do it    
    
    
    #GoodByeBreakingBad I might get emotional    
    
    
    Beware drinking from plastic water bottles. The chemicals used to make them are linked with infertility, birth defects & cancer    
    
    
    @HabbGaga  thank you so much. I really appreciate that. Where did you hear the remix if you don't mind me asking?    
    
    
    @HabbGaga Wow. So crazy how people discover new artists. That's dope. I love Natalia Kills. Been a fan since she was "Verbz" on Myspace lol    
    
    
    @HabbGaga yeah she used to be a rapper and was really good actually. She changed her whole image up.    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana true    
    
    
    #Soundcloud @BrunoMars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    "I've realized that business and being polite DON'T match. You can be fair but me being polite is me not being fair to myself."    
    
    
    @nakitabanana . http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pt8VYOfr8To&sns … #WorkBxxch #Yup    
    
    
    Excuse me while I watch this Britney #WorkBitch Video http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pt8VYOfr8To&sns … ..Who thinks I should remix this?    
    
    
    Sometimes I hate that I can't have too much of an opinion being in the music industry. Everyone gets offended so easily    
    
    
    Evev better though---> RT @arcadefire: Here Comes the Night Time http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_fFAKrIntzY …    
    
    
    New Yorkers, please stop damaging our covering up new Banksy pieces before i get to see them. Thank You -MGMT    
    
    
    Fact: The ACA was signed into LAW through a constitutional process and deemed by the Supreme Court to be Constitutional so WTF is the prob?    
    
    
    Man this Reflektor album from @arcadefire is going to be BANANAS    
    
    
    @arcadefire has six Haitian percussionists featured on the album. That's the first thing I thought when I heard #HereComesTheNight    
    
    
    @RealRageJunkie I recommend checking out newcomer @blacklight_diaz https://soundcloud.com/blacklightdiaz  #DopeEDMProducer    
    
    
    Hppay Birthday to the homie @elenikaterina !!!    
    
    
    Big shout out to @SitaraKmusic who is working on a song I wrote right now. You are beyond incredible and immensely appreciated. Thank You    
    
    
    @Channtiee88 Your avatar looks like you were in my "Ah Yeah" video lol Did you see it?    
    
    
    I hear @thedoctorluke needs songwriters.... #ILikeToDream but seriously I can write u some smashes. Just 1 song #IChallngeYourWriters    
    
    
    @Channtiee88 lol yeah but i get to place the hand prints on the re-do :)    
    
    
    #tbt Interviewing Joe Jackson a few months after MJ died. #BestMomentOfMyLife #WishEdHardyDiedInstead… http://instagram.com/p/fA415BPiN0/     
    
    
    #InglishMajors: Be sure to check out this great Non For Profit >>@tpscommunity. They fund small projects in impoverished countries worldwide    
    
    
    @tpscommunity is a new Org. run by some great people that I had the pleasure meeting. What they are doing is great. Check them out!!    
    
    
    @sold_inc    
    
    
    C'mon Tony Romo.WHYYYYY!!!###    
    
    
    @mlebean You're seriously a big inspiration to me as a songwriter/engineer. Not enough females in the game doing what u do. Love it #Talent    
    
    
    The government basically un-friended us.    
    
    
    @Katy_Batyox it's a little late but I wanted to wish you a Happy Birthday. Keep being the positive spirited person u are & enjoy ur night!!    
    
    
    Spent the last few weeks studying mixing & vocal arranging techniques on some of my favorite songs. Learned some great things. #growthweek    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @TarynPapa !!! Sending love your way :)    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Ok not a prob. Let's go to @CityOfPastele 's show tomorrow :)    
    
    
    @CityOfPastele What time is your show? Looks like I'm performing tonight as well but much later at Stash    
    
    
    Tonight I'm making an appearance at Stash, NYC for a college 18 plus party if anyone wants to come give me a hug cause I need one lol    
    
    
    @RheaPasricha I know you're always looking for writers & since you're going to be in NY, I would love to possibly meet with you when ur here    
    
    
    @cassyofLondon It's so cloudy over there everyone needs one. I might be out there early next year actually    
    
    
    How to make a relationship run smooth: Break up with the person then continue seeing them like nothing ever happened. Arguments over.    
    
    
    @CityOfPastele sorry i couldn't make your show. My soundcheck was at 10:30. How was it?    
    
    
    @CityOfPastele good. I hate missing your shows. I always live hearing ur new stuff. You know, the songs you keep a secret from everyone :)    
    
    
    Great session today with mariavitagliano. She absolutely killed this song I wrote. #ManListen… http://instagram.com/p/fbQLubPiBw/     
    
    
    @DJMMMusic I don't even know. My phone tweeted that on it's own    
    
    
    Geek Tweet: For any of you engineers looking for a DOPE compressor to add to ur arsenal, check out the @fabfilter Pro-C. DOES IT ALL & WELL!    
    
    
    @JMCPrinting Got you locked in    
    
    
    @fabfilter Thank u for your incredible plugin visualizations. Makes.my life that much easier and helps me really understand what's happening    
    
    
    C'Mon #NYPD. He actually raising property values. Let him live. http://instagram.com/p/fkqe-rviF5/     
    
    
    #tbt Me and my cuzzo @ronaustinjr been daper since the age of 5 lol http://instagram.com/p/flBMHjviG2/     
    
    
    @AkaashSingh great meeting you man. Let me know when your next show is    
    
    
    On a set playing a doctor cause you know, f*** it why not? Anyone need a prescription? http://instagram.com/p/flxeymviAs/     
    
    
    Its really ironic that we had a Govt shutdown that cost a total of $24 Billion all over Obamacare which would cost an estimated $1.1 Billion    
    
    
    My song "Ah Yeah will be featured on @MTV's new show "Scrubbing In" Premiering Oct. 24th!! @scrubbinginMTV Tune In http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nepXwqSgajo …    
    
    
    Just had an awkward moment of telling someone they left their shoes under my bed and then having them say they don't own them. Yikes    
    
    
    Ultimate trap RT @JustinRosePHC: @HansInglish lmao that's happened to me too many times    
    
    
    Everyone in my family who works in the corporate world always comes home telling stories about something racist thei co-workers said lol    
    
    
    @ChelseyFerri Not sure cause they're keeping me in the dark on that but thanks. I think it will be a great show despite controversy    
    
    
    Its full blown summertime again out here in NY. Damn!!    
    
    
    Tell me how my cousin @patbits had coffee with @NataliaKills and didn't tell me smh. I'm hurt lol    
    
    
    @Dhaniscorp THANK YOU for tweeting the Minecraft Parody :)    
    
    
    @patbits Yo have you seen this? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UiiS-TSuE1M&feature=youtu.be … I'm in minecraft history now lol    
    
    
    Why is the beat for @Krewella's "Live For The Night" so damn EPIC. Man @omgRainMan really did his thing on that. I wanna jump on couches now    
    
    
    Thug Prolly,Yo come Polly,He wanna f* a bad Dolly,Pop Molly. I hope ur mothaf** pockets got a pot belly or is it dat u neva ball,John Salley    
    
    
    Nicki Minaj Minaj Killed that vere on Chris Brown's 'Love More" woooo    
    
    
    Is @Zendaya the new Cassie? Oh shit...    
    
    
    Who's at the #AES Convention right now?    
    
    
    Have yall heard my @drake "The Motion" Remix?  Download it and blast it on the way to the club tonight https://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/drake-feat-hans-inglish-sampha …    
    
    
    While you're at it you might as well download my J Cole Villuminati Freestyle too http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PvLPm-jDIgM&list=PLVIL-byuop6DcwihDnQAtS4U3A0SoOdnm&index=6 …    
    
    
    If you're out and about in the city tonight, come join me at Suite 36 Free to get in and drinks on us. 11:30pm List: @RSVPLifestyle    
    
    
    @IncredibleLAGO Wish you were you at #AES this weekend? They definitely needed a talented female engineer to be present and give tips    
    
    
    @MasonBetha Has a new album coming called #NowWeEven. Interested to see what he does lyrically on this one.    
    
    
    Thank god I have the newest, fastest phone so I can mindlessly check the same three apps 500 times a day.    
    
    
    @THEmrMEOLA lol I'm sure everyone can    
    
    
    @J_Grys Don't ask me to help you put together any Ikea furniture. They're the devil    
    
    
    I know everyone is going to be tuning in to the TLC movie tonight. The commentary on twitter is probably going to be interesting    
    
    
    With the last 2 singles Justin Bieber dropped, it looks like he's about to be the one to bring actual R&B back in the game for the youngins    
    
    
    I'm talking about are 'Heartbreaker" and "Hold Tight" in case anyone was confused by last tweet. Black ppl obviously wrote these for him lol    
    
    
    My song "Ah Yeah" will be featured on @MTV's new show "Scrubbing In" Premiering Oct. 24th 10/9C @scrubbinginMTV http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nepXwqSgajo …    
    
    
    Lil Mama seriously nailed Left Eye in this movie. Props to her. She came a long way from showing up on award stages uninvited
#CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    Man I look more like Dallas Austin than this dude. How come no one told me about the auditions? I wanna make out wit Chilli #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    Shit going fast in this TLC movie. Chilli just got pregnant from kissing Dallas Austin #ThatsAFIrst #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    @beautifulrhymes apologies hahaha. You can always go back to my timeline later    
    
    
    Why everyone surprised at a million records sold and being broke? That shit is happening to every rapper right now #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    I bet you TLC recouped their money faster than Rihanna did. She wasn't in the black until like her 3rd album #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    U guys know that @pebbles2day is going to print out her @ mentions to use as slander evidence in court right?Yall better stop #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    Yo Left Eye really pulled a David Ruffin from the Trmptations for a sec..."I Don't Need You"  #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    Had to pull out the record on y'all from my old crates. We played this heavy at every party… http://instagram.com/p/fwRNZTviEt/     
    
    
    Everyone say Happy Birthday to the homie @JustinAnthonyJA You have 5 more minutes unless you're in the Mid West or LA    
    
    
    @shyboi2020 What's up man!! Everything good with ya?    
    
    
    @shyboi2020 been here tweeting. Never went anywhere    
    
    
    @shyboi2020 yeah man did the name change and all that since like Jan. The music has been good man. Can't complain bro    
    
    
    Top 10 Haunted Houses in America http://www.tested.com/inventern/458696-most-high-tech-haunted-houses/ … (Too bad none of these are in NY)    
    
    
    Don't forget to tune in to @MTV's new show @scrubbinginMTV tomorrow at 10/9C You just might hear one of my songs.    
    
    
    @BlendHQ Guys, I never got the invite code. Is the site online yet?    
    
    
    It is much easier to hula hoop with an erection.    
    
    
    @BlendHQ no worries I'm good to go just signed up    
    
    
    People have hit me up about my @NataliaKills remix verse saying it helped them get through certain problems & that means a lot. #Inspiration    
    
    
    I know what it's like to want to give up & feeling indifference toward life. Not sure where I'd be without writing & music #FindYourOutlet    
    
    
    It's all about #Blackfish right now on @CNN    
    
    
    U dont need to see an Orca in a Park to bring awareness. It's 2013. Id smack a kid who didnt know what a Killer Whale was #Blackfish    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo kindle    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo Been great. Honestly I think about it sometimes because I love Aviation but no. There's nothing like fighting for a dream    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo I struggle don't get me wrong but I don't answer to anyone really and it's good. I don't need much to make me happy.    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo Thank You. I cherish having genuine people like u & Mike come into my life though cause that's rare & means a lot more. #truth    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo Right now i wish i was in your weather though. I'm freezing in my apt smh. F***the east coast right now lol    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo yeah it's the "Grass Greener on the other side" complex. I've never heard someone say they miss rain until I went to Cali    
    
    
    Too many suckers for love in this world. We believe in fairy tales way too much. Always go into things with your head    
    
    
    We go together like white girls and cracked IPhone screens...    
    
    
    BBM Life once again: 7B1B6C2C    
    
    
    @thebeatkidz yo you guys are dope. Tryin to get a remix done for my song "Reality Show" if you guys are down    
    
    
    @ChelseyFerri Great first episode by the way    
    
    
    Shout out to you @FifthHarmony. The EP came out really great. Amazing A&R work  @LdotHarman    
    
    
    Hey @melismaticdiva have you heard the @FifthHarmony EP yet? What you think?    
    
    
    Make sure you guys stream my tracks on #Spotify: >>#AhYeah #DanceDruggie #RealityShow<< [All available on ITunes as well]    
    
    
    Is it me or is the new season of Kevin Harts #RHOH not that funny at all?    
    
    
    "Almost every wise saying has an opposite one, no less wise, to balance it." -George Santayana    
    
    
    #BBM Pin: 7B1B6C2C If you're someone I don't know personally or you don't have a pic, let me know who you are so I don't ignore the invite    
    
    
    @mrfingaz what studio is that?    
    
    
    Photo: Work hard sleep hard… http://tmblr.co/Za0yWtyjpreK     
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Funny thats my least favorite track from a production perspective but "Who Are You" is my fav from a writing perspective    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva It's crazy cause I didn't know 4 of them are Bruno Mars' sisters    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva oh maybe that's what it is. I'm mistaken then. Thanks for clearing that up    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva You saw the TLC movie lol It's going to be HARD to see that again but I feel you on the UK statement    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Noone likes being broke for long and the days of selling 10 million are long gone. Except for with Bruno Mars & Eminem    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva NYSNC selling a million in one day had to be part of a grand marketing plan where the label bought a lot of those albums    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Who's the biggest selling Pop group of all time?    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva I just looked it up. Top selling Boy Bands: 1.Backstreet Bys 2. Jackson Five 3. NKOTB 4. The Osmonds 5. Bay City Rollers    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva And your 3 girl groups were exactly right. #4 is Bananarama and #5 is AKB48    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Yup #6 is another J-Pop group "Speed" then the Supremes. Crazy. I can't believe that    
    
    
    If you're on #Spotify, be sure to follow me and add my streams to your playlists--> http://open.spotify.com/artist/03VklqYq5ix8TKgt1il9A1 …    
    
    
    "Music is a means of giving form to our inner feelings, without attaching them to events or objects in the world."    
    
    
    "Love is A Suicide" by Natalia Kills on repeat for right now    
    
    
    "When rich people fight wars with one another, poor people are the ones to die." -Jean-Paul Sartre    
    
    
    "Many a man fails as an original thinker simply because his memory it too good." -Friedrich Nietzsche    
    
    
    Yo 2 Chainz graduated from ASU with a 4.0 GPA. Just thought I'd let the world know. Wow    
    
    
    My #Halloween costume cost $4.99 #AintNoBodyGotTimeForThat #IAintEvenGoingOutTho #NoReally… http://instagram.com/p/gJdc9hviLD/     
    
    
    #Halloween is a whole different thing in Harlem compared to Queens where I grew up. I used to go house to house. These kids go Deli to Deli    
    
    
    Had a productive and fun afternoon with @andrewfennell with _r_a_h_e_l_  and @nakitabanana… http://instagram.com/p/gOigepPiKg/     
    
    
    Shout out to @EstherZysk Amazing singer and Actress. #Follow    
    
    
    If you’re a vegan w a gluten allergy who doesn't own a TV do you put it on a business card or just wait to force it into every conversation?    
    
    
    @EllaRogue Hey thanks for following. GOing to reach out by email and see how we can possibly work on something. Love your voice btw    
    
    
    @Geordaina and I didn't mean that in some subliminal dirty way lol    
    
    
    @EllaRogue Thank You!! I just sent you an email so keep an eye out. :)    
    
    
    "Religion is excellent stuff for keeping common people quiet. Religion is what keeps the poor from murdering the rich." - Napoleon Bonaparte    
    
    
    Just ordered a salted caramel mocha latte at #Starbucks. Does that mean I'm about to be traded to the whites by the @TheRaceDraft ?    
    
    
    #InglishMajors I need a favor. If you're on Hypem, please favorite my "Saturday Night" remix with @NataliaKills -->
http://goo.gl/OwVrW8     
    
    
    Don't listen to country often but I had the the @ladyantebellum "Golden" album jamming this morn and it's really good.    
    
    
    @holisox Appreciate the follow :)    
    
    
    I text people back embarrassingly fast or three days later there is no in between    
    
    
    "Hang out with different people everyday so the only person who knows you've been wearing the same outfit all week is you" - my fashion blog    
    
    
    Let's be real. In his prime, Richard Simmons was, at best, in just okay shape.    
    
    
    Got the @KaceyMusgraves album on repeat today. Her writing is incredible    
    
    
    I can never understand the logic of people who work out all the time but eat the worst foods. Fitness is 90% nutrition people.    
    
    
    @MishaPagano DM me your number wgen you get a chance. Thought I had it    
    
    
    Things I've learned today. Vodka, beer, and Cronuts aren't the best mix....    
    
    
    Happy Birthday 2 one of the best club promoters in NYC @mikemckaynyc. Always supports heavy & for that I say u are an official #InglishMajor    
    
    
    Shoutout to @MishaPagano for bring a great person & for not even attempting to take my picture this weekend. At least not overtly.    
    
    
    If you're interested in casting for #reality #TV or have thought about it, I suggest following the homie -> @MishaPagano<- for that.    
    
    
    @BoRadley_ is that an admission of guilt? Lol    
    
    
    @CiminoTV @CreAjian Great meeting you guys although Asia and I almost had a fist fight over Miley Cyrus in the club    
    
    
    @CoyTiffany @CreAjian yeah we agreed to disagree so noone got hurt lol. Next month we'll def all go party when @MishaPagano comes back    
    
    
    #Food4thought. U remember when @MileyCyrus  did "party in the USA" & said she didnt even know a Jay Z song though she mentioned him in it?    
    
    
    @CreAjian no no never. I was more upset at you kidnapping @MishaPagano then i was at the whole Miley thing actually. Lol    
    
    
    @CreAjian very true    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana wtf? How are you scared sleeping with someone?  #JesusTakeTheWheel    
    
    
    If you're on #Spotify, be sure to follow me and add my streams to your playlists--> http://open.spotify.com/artist/03VklqYq5ix8TKgt1il9A1 …    
    
    
    #CancerAwarness Remember that it all starts with food. What you put in is what u get out. Stay away from processed foods & cut down on meats    
    
    
    #CancerAwareness Stay away from bottled water. The chemical BPA & DEHF found in plastics is linked to high risk of cancer.Buy #Glass bottles    
    
    
    @cassyofLondon It's found in all plastics. It seeps into liquids/foods so it's also good to store left over food in non plastic containers.    
    
    
    "I do." "Same." - wedding vows in 2030    
    
    
    I think Hans Zimmer ran out of ideas cause it sounded like he re used the same music from inception in #12YearsASlave    
    
    
    Not sure I'm ready for the @dallascowboys to embarrass me this Thanksgiving in front of the whole family    
    
    
    Did you guys see the Kanye "Bound 2" video yet? Ummm I'm trying to figure out if this was real or a spoof. http://goo.gl/3510aQ     
    
    
    @VidArroyo lmao or maybe Lamar directed it. That's more believable    
    
    
    @AlreadyFamous10 You're joking right? That video was the worst thing I've seen in a long time lol    
    
    
    @AlreadyFamous10 -_-man i love Ye but wtf??? I can't    
    
    
    #Artists The days of the album are dead.....    
    
    
    @Erene Thanks for the follow hun    
    
    
    My biggest fear is laughing at a joke I didn't understand and someone asks me to explain it to them.    
    
    
    Long day of mixing vocals ahead. It's a love hate relationship i swear but there's nothing like an… http://instagram.com/p/hEUFpXviH0/     
    
    
    #NP #MusicMonday - Banshee (The Relapse) by @pixikill feat @hansinglish [Prod. By @DemitriMedina ]#Retweet http://bit.ly/HXZ2PG     
    
    
    @blacklight_diaz @audiointrusion be sure to follow --> @celebaccountant    
    
    
    #NP #MusicMonday - Banshee (The Relapse) by @pixikill feat @HansInglish [Prod. By @DemitriMedina] #Retweet http://bit.ly/HXZ2PG     
    
    
    Michael just now got sober lol RT @CiminoTV: @CoyTiffany @HansInglish @CreAjian I don't remember anything. #whatelseisnew    
    
    
    #RT @pixikill: New collaboration! Go check it out...its bananas. http://www.soundcloud.com/hansinglish  @hansinglish @demitrimedina pic.twitter.com/iCKzH7XL0D    
    
    
    @kanyewest @cthagod great interview guys. I get both Charlamagne & Ye's points. "Its about guaranteeing you're kids can work at the station"    
    
    
    @MishaPagano: @CreAjian @CiminoTV Cab Driver: " I don't look at every restaurant on the street while I drive. You just better pay." Lmao    
    
    
    @marisaannn man i need to come get some of that creme brulee. I'm hating on your last tweet right now    
    
    
    If u haven't heard it yet, check out my latest collaboration with @pixikill  [Prod. By @DemitriMedina] http://bit.ly/HXZ2PG  #Retweet    
    
    
    @marisaannn I'm always a sucker for good creme brulee. That's a long trip though lol.    
    
    
    #Random I wonder if @YoGottiKOM feels a certain way when white ppl start singin "My Nigga" in the club very comfortably? I nvr kno how 2feel    
    
    
    @Channtiee88 man in the cruise ships they could care less. I've seen 14yr old kids on the slot machines  lol    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving even if u don't celebrate. Luv u guys: @Katy_Batyox @Channtiee88 @melismaticdiva @BoRadley_ @cassyofLondon @HabbGaga    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving!!! Sending love ur way @AlreadyFamous10 @ChelseyFerri @CityOfPastele @SparkleXO @Geordaina @THEmrMEOLA @BChamp_    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving to some inspirational people in my life: @DamienEstreich @blacklight_diaz @DJCoopDaVillain @DjBlackOut @NinaRawz    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving & Thank u for being a genuinely great person: @TheEdenGarden @KatyTizMusic @MishaPagano @2MrNetwork @PrimBELLA    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving & thank you for always supporting: @DJMMMusic @AndrewFennell @ChrisReimers_ @djbengey @LyssV_Xo @EeZeEpEe @mikemckaynyc    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving & Thank u for being so focused & amazing to work with: @MariaVitagliano @EstherZysk @DemitriMedina @EllaRogue @pixikill    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving & Thank you for being so supportive of me through the past 2 years @Dennis_Latos @CandyZack Enjoy the meal and toast up!    
    
    
    I know everyone's stomach is hurting right now. That's what happens when you pray before a meal and then commit gluttony lol    
    
    
    Lorde in an interview said she couldn't relate to anything in Hip Hop because what they were talking about was irrelevant to her?????    
    
    
    Miley couldn't even name a JayZ song 2 years ago and now she "identifies with hood music" and is sipping purp with her J's on?    
    
    
    Thank You  :) RT @TheRealJillyG: I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/wogjo1estzE?a  Natalia Kills feat.Hans Inglish - Saturday Night (Remix)    
    
    
    Your parent's house: a place where even bad photos find their way into frames.    
    
    
    @toscamarleen oh @NakitaBanana drains her battery stalking people on IG and twitter that's why    
    
    
    Thank you RT @TheRealJillyG: @HansInglish @YouTube I LOVE THIS!!!!! HANS AND @NATALIAKILLS YOU GOT THE HEAT!!!!! XO    
    
    
    @DJMMMusic Appreciate the shoutout and support man.    
    
    
    This chick on Instagram posts so many pictures of her boyfriend I feel like I'm dating him smh    
    
    
    Man I swear @sia is one of the best writers in pop & EDM music right now. @britneyspears's song #Perfume is nuts. Shouts to Chris Braide too    
    
    
    @OneMusicPortal Favorite song by Sia? Prob. Hands down She Wolf. Throwback Sia favorite is "Clap Your Hands"    
    
    
    @OneMusicPortal favorite song on the #BritneyJean album then #Perfume and I just found out that's her second single today so no bias there    
    
    
    Another big inspiration of mine as a songwriter is @antonypreston .- Great job with the vocal producing on the #BritneyJean album!    
    
    
    To all my fans who have been waiting for the Inglish 101 EP I promise it will be coming the top of the year.    
    
    
    Really proud of the 3 other songs I've recorded along with #RealityShow and #DanceDruggie but the new tracks will be my best work to date    
    
    
    In the meantime, Ive been songwriting for other artists alongside producers Davenport&Spencer & @djblackout in preparation for 2014    
    
    
    Ive mostly been writing female pop records which is new for me but I'm really excited to shop these records first quarter. #ItsGoingDown    
    
    
    If u havent heard my new collaboration w/ Electro Pop group @pixikill, check it out: https://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/pixikill-feat-hans-inglish … Prod by @demitrimedina & myself    
    
    
    @MrAustinJr No worries the songs are in the proper lanes lol    
    
    
    i wish humans were as excited to meet each other as dogs    
    
    
    So many Pop female artists this year dropped albums this year. My favorite is probably Jessie J's and Ellie Goulding's    
    
    
    HuffPost: @ADL_National "Kanyes comments on were anti-semetic" Jewish ppl in the articlles comments: "its true we have more connects" lol    
    
    
    Anyone want to play my girlfriend on a talk show tomorrow afternoon 12-3pm in NY. Nothing trashy..Straight classy.    
    
    
    @toscamarleen doing my friend who is a TV producer a favor    
    
    
    @MishaPagano I really just hope they don't fuck it up. I'm so picky about scary movies. Not a lot of well made ones lately    
    
    
    #tbt The  first remix verse I ever did over #Cassie "Long Way 2 Go" when I went by #Flawless. Who had… http://instagram.com/p/hj_AlOviKd/     
    
    
    Thoroughly enjoyed watching the live version of "The Sound Of Music" with @carrieunderwood. Few mistakes I caught but overall it was great.    
    
    
    Good morning to my east and west coast homies up and getting it done. #Early    
    
    
    I'm doing my job so you if you're doing yours then naturally we can't lose...    
    
    
    Imma let the new One World Trade Building finish but that's not the greatest architectural design ever. It's just Blahhh    
    
    
    Signed by the legend himself back in '98. #RIP If you haven't read this, you're truly missing out.… http://instagram.com/p/hmDLR3PiGa/     
    
    
    Hahhaha I saw this and thought you'd enjoy this @KatyTizMusic http://www.buzzfeed.com/caraf5/22-naughty-things-the-elf-on-a-shelf-is-doing-whil-eygo …    
    
    
    Whats the point of having a facebook fan page when 1000 people like it but they restrict ur post visibility even to your fans? #DeathToFB    
    
    
    @DJMMMusic & u cant @ your fans either. It sucks. @facebook needs to get that together. I don't want to pay to promote to existing fans    
    
    
    "I Miss Her" by @JessieJ is a powerful song. She absolutely put all her emotions into that. If you haven't heard it go check it out    
    
    
    @RiskOne Appreciate the follow my man    
    
    
    People who decorate their cars for Christmas are in serious need of help.    
    
    
    (L.A.)->RT @MishaPagano: Looking 4 a smart, sexy, hard working, social lady to work as VIP hostess on NYE! Hustlers & quick-learners only! $    
    
    
    #CowboysNation #ThatllBeAll    
    
    
    This is what I always want to text people... #AmIWrongForThat lol #text #chat #funny #hunor #facetime http://instagram.com/p/hwW2jOPiC7/     
    
    
    @toscamarleen you're just not talking to the right people I guess    
    
    
    Research says taking photographs ruins memories:  http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/science-news/10507146/Taking-photographs-ruins-the-memory-research-finds.html?fb …  This article is for u @MishaPagano lol    
    
    
    The white girls were nestled all snug in their beds, while visions of Ugg boots danced in their heads.    
    
    
    Man, speaking of UGG Boots, here is HORRIBLE truth behind how they are made along with wool coats. Narrated by @Pink http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ACl5SI4IjSw …    
    
    
    Man organic milk tastes so much richer than regular milk it's nuts. Never going back    
    
    
    @Geordaina #LactoseIntolerant #SoyMilkWorld 

-Too much soy of no Bueno either. I do Almond Milk. Better choice    
    
    
    @laurafabris77 it's so weird seeing you on twitter lol. How is everything?    
    
    
    @jessdomain Thanks for the follow Jess. Love your music    
    
    
    No joke, all the gifts under my tree say "From Beyonce" ...ummm wtf? lol    
    
    
    @blastmanagement thanks for the follow    
    
    
    The Angel on my tree is turnin up & ALL the gifts under my tree say "From Beyonce"... No lie… http://instagram.com/p/h_lTycPiLd/     
    
    
    YOO, Beyonce sold nearly 600 thousand copies of her album first week with NO PROMO. She smashed every Pop artist in the game. WOW    
    
    
    Life is basically trying to meet better people than the ones you currently know.    
    
    
    Preview: Just finished mixing a new #folk #pop smash. I wrote with @estherzysk (Also singing). Prod.… http://instagram.com/p/iCsFZwviMP/     
    
    
    Imagine going to a theater in 1765 to see Mozart play symphony number 30 but as soon as he starts playing, the bass drops and people go nuts    
    
    
    @trixxbeats Sent you an email homie.    
    
    
    New Music for all my InglishMajors: @britneyspears feat. Hans Inglish #Perfume (Remix) http://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/britney-spears-perfume-remix-feat-hans-inglish …    
    
    
    New #Music#Pheeders: Here's my new remix to "Perfume" by Britney Spears. Download it below for free. Enjoy! #phe...  http://pheed.com/p/43015136     
    
    
    My new remix is out! @britneyspears "Perfume" (Remix) Check it out here https://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/britney-spears-perfume-remix-feat-hans-inglish … #Retweet    
    
    
    My new remix is out! @britneyspears "Perfume" ft. @HansInglish Check it out here https://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/britney-spears-perfume-remix-feat-hans-inglish … … #Retweet    
    
    
    My new remix is out! @britneyspears "Perfume" (Remix) Check it out--> http://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/br … #Retweet    
    
    
    Check out my remix to @britneyspears' single "Perfume" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dD-CptjGCZE&feature=share&list=PLVIL-byuop6DcwihDnQAtS4U3A0SoOdnm … #Retweet    
    
    
    Check out my new remix to @britneyspears' single "Perfume" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dD-CptjGCZE&feature=share&list=PLVIL-byuop6DcwihDnQAtS4U3A0SoOdnm … #Retweet    
    
    
    @ndrewmarin the video might be distracting though while running. Need to send you that mp3 lol    
    
    
    @ndrewmarin got ya. Haha. Glad I could aid in the workout    
    
    
    Seems like my fans predominately use my songs for their workout sessions. Kind of great that I can assist in people's self improvement :)    
    
    
    @peteymajik Hope you enjoyed the Cronut man :)    
    
    
    Merry Christmas to all my #InglishMajors Love you guys!!!    
    
    
    @THEmrMEOLA I really think we should get the song played at Minecon somehow. How can we make that happen?    
    
    
    @TWC is always lying about their internet speeds in their commercials. I wanna know what country they're referring to cause is not the U.S.    
    
    
    @THEmrMEOLA Yeah. I mean I'm sure we can still get it played next year but either way that's amazing    
    
    
    @THEmrMEOLA yeah that would definitely be a great idea. Maybe get them to use it in their ad campaigns.    
    
    
    The smell of u when Im wit her sticks around longer lately. Now she playin detective,different dick,no Warren Beatty https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dD-CptjGCZE …    
    
    
    Did anyone catch that line or did I confuse everyone?    
    
    
    Down. Let's do it RT @MishaPagano: @HansInglish @CreAjian @CoyTiffany @CiminoTV heading into the city today... reunion gathering tonight???    
    
    
    Man I love Ma$e but that new single he just dropped is not good at allllllll.    
    
    
    @CoyTiffany yeah its called "Why Cant We"   http://soundcloud.com/masonbetha-1/why-cant-we-featuring-her …    
    
    
    @MishaPagano @CiminoTV @LucyInTheSky87 @CoyTiffany was I the only 1 who thought somethin was weird about that girl dressed like a Care Bear?    
    
    
    @CoyTiffany The one chick in the pink glitter top and pink leggings who was with that dude    
    
    
    @MishaPagano @CiminoTV #LessonsLearned
Misha is the mischevious gang leader (turn on) Tiff is the shooter.Michael informs the crew whos fake    
    
    
    @Carlitos_Flores thank you man. Glad you liked it.    
    
    
    Notice I haven't tweeted anything for a few days. I was recovering lol    
    
    
    People who actually put that movie theater "butter" on their popcorn should be ineligible for healthcare.    
    
    
    @carlaelyse indeed..which is why i said, "butter"    
    
    
    If you don't learn to master the art of boldness, you will never get what you really want in life.    
    
    
    "I haven't accomplished much but I will harshly judge the hard work of others" -Critics    
    
    
    One of my goals was to get a song feat. on @SHO_HouseOfLies in 2014 & I just got news "Ah Yeah" will be featured in Ep. 6 of the new season!    
    
    
    Set on your mind on something and FUCKING GET IT!! PERIOD!! #ThankYouTvGods    
    
    
    For the first time since I joined @ASCAP in like 2003, I have recieved actual royalties. I'm so Happy right now. #DreamBig    
    
    
    Ny'ers please stop complaining about the snow and saying you'd rather be in LA. You know what snow is? WATER. Something thats imported in LA    
    
    
    @ADADphotography working hard homie. How are things with ya?    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to the greatest friend in the world @PrimBELLA !!! Been Rockin wit ya since like 6 years old. That shit cray. Love you!!!    
    
    
    Who has every remix I've done in their music playlist?    
    
    
    #MusicMonday: @CapitalCities feat. Hans Inglish "Safe and Sound" (Remix) http://snd.sc/185E4X5     
    
    
    @ceesita_ My new remix is out. Enjoy! http://snd.sc/185E4X5     
    
    
    @chrisnycvillage Thanks  for the follow Chris. Would love to collaborate with you on something in the future.    
    
    
    Shout out to you @briecrump :) Thanks for following    
    
    
    My boy got me out here working on his car smh. Thought my mechanic days were over. #MadBoltsLeftOver http://instagram.com/p/cp2O4-PiNe/     
    
    
    #NP: @CapitalCities feat. Hans Inglish "Safe and Sound" (Remix) http://snd.sc/185E4X5  #Retweet    
    
    
    Anyone remember the days when u could be outside playing & everyone went home at 8pm cause it was TGIF on TV? Lol #FamilyMatters #StepByStep    
    
    
    Ludacris' mixtape is bananas....damn    
    
    
    only watch up to two hours of tv a day" oh well i dont have time to watch tv because i stay on the internet all day so im good and healthy    
    
    
    If my entire family died but there was pizza at the wake, a part of me would still be like "yay pizza"    
    
    
    The industry could care less about "talent" really...It's nothing personal just business though right?    
    
    
    @cassyofLondon yup    
    
    
    Drank 1 Sam Adams and I'm swaying. Wtd? Haven't drank in so long my body doesn't know what to do right now. Smh    
    
    
    See...I even misspelled wtf? ......wtf? Lol    
    
    
    @Geordaina Take one from a.neighbor. I mean borrow one    
    
    
    Yo Stephen Colbert is THE MAN ...Seriously. He just gave it to MTV and Viacom for @DaftPunk not appearing on his show lol    
    
    
    Yo thus show Drunk History on Comedy Central is funny as hell. First time seeing this.    
    
    
    @CityOfPastele no prob babe    
    
    
    Photo: #Inspiring others is one of the main reasons I do #music. Messages like these help keep me focused on... http://tmblr.co/Za0yWtrgUkz4     
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe Cheescake is my favorite desert. Creme Brulee is a close second.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I have a slight fear of pigeons    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I learned to fly a plane when I was 13    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I went to a Catholic School for 8 years and I use to be an Alter Boy    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I'm a 80's Pop Fanatic. It was the best era of Pop in my opinion.    
    
    
    @RettaWorldPeace @Geordaina Yall was sippin extra from the Wine huh? lol    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I once performed on 106nPark and Flopped BIG TIME!!    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I use to buy Wu-Tang albums just so I could hear Method Man's verses.    
    
    
    @DJCategory5 Damn all the ex Catholics are in music? lol    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I Consider myself a Deist. Don't know what that is? Well--> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deism     
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I get along with Lesbians extremely well. #Random    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I helped build the first 8 production engines on the Airbus A-380. Largest airplane in the world. PIC: pic.twitter.com/6qtRULQQL0    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I don't realy have a whisper voice. I'm usually always calm but I can yell over anyone. Any challengers?    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I can't perform AT ALL if I'm even slightly drunk or high. I will forget lyrics. It's happened to me    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I like women who are taller than me for some strange reason.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe The first producer I ever worked with was @blacklight_diaz when I attended @FullSail. Our first song was called "NYC Rhythm"    
    
    
    Semi embarrasing footage of me performing my first song ever circa 2004--->http://youtu.be/tO29gzRGqBc  Produced by @blacklight_diaz    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe The first remix verse I ever did was to @CassieSuper's "Long Way To Go" in 2006. Check it out http://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/my-very-first-remix-verse-2006 …    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe When Myspace was poppin, I had 1mil+ plays on a song which got me a deal with now cuurent pres. of @RepublicRecords    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe First love song I wrote was for->@Boogsneffect<- Putting her on blast but she wont care. My boy @izzyspeakslife sang the hook    
    
    
    Actually the song was for my boy's girl but I jacked it and put my verses on it. He was cool with it though. #SuperSappy    
    
    
    @THEREALCHOZN I know exactly why actually. it's the same reason every guy gets stuck watching Telemundo not knowing what they're saying    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe One of my favorite movies is "The Orphanage" by Gullermo Del Torro    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe Favorite Childhood movie is probably Wizard Of Oz. Part 1 and 2. A lot of people don't know there's a part 2.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I played piano at Carnegie Hall in NyC when I was 6. I regret stopping cause I can barely play now. Just enough though.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I have a thing for Middle Eastern women. And I LOVE Middle Eastern Food.    
    
    
    #FactsAboutMe I thrive off competition. I'm still waiting for the day a rapper disses me in a song lol #SeriouslyThough    
    
    
    The biggest lie in America is that hard work ALWAYS pays off. It doesn't. Ask any poor person that works super hard.    
    
    
    #NewMusic @CapitalCities feat. Hans Inglish "Safe and Sound" (Remix) http://snd.sc/185E4X5  #Retweet    
    
    
    New favorite song: Tennis Court by @lordemusic http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D8Ymd-OCucs …    
    
    
    I've been getting subscriptions to Outsiders magazine out of nowhere to my house past 2 months. Someone trying to tell me something? Lol    
    
    
    Obama doesn't think Snowden is a patriot yet what he did is directly leading to the #NSA reforms he's putting out. Sounds patriotic to me.    
    
    
    Anyone at all thought it was funny that the plane at the end of Fast and Furious 6 took like 35min to take off? That's a long runway #smh    
    
    
    Gonna need to remix a One Dirrction song soon. That's overdue    
    
    
    @Zakswfc   lmao. Too funny    
    
    
    @Zakswfc All my latest is on http://www.Soundcloud.com/HansInglish  I have a new project with @pixikills as well coming soon. Check em out    
    
    
    Did you know that Affirmative Action benefits white women the most? Learned something new today    
    
    
    Damn @BonnieMcKee  you did it again. @katyperry 's new single #Roar is dope. You have the golden pen.    
    
    
    Ask me anything @ http://ask.fm/HansInglish     
    
    
    #PSA #AintNoBodyGotTimeForThat #ThatClubLooksPoppin #TheAudioIsGreat #SaidNoOneEver http://instagram.com/p/c41-uTPiL-/     
    
    
    VIDEO: Woooww @DonLemonCNN went in on @UncleRUSH Sheeessh. He made some really great points though I must say http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6cPk5dBxPyo …    
    
    
    @empire_live Thanks for the follow guys. Your stuff is great. If you ever need a feature verse or something don't hesitate to hit me up :)    
    
    
    Elon Musk just dropped his plans for the Hyperloop today which got me thinking. He is definitely the real life Iron Man. #Undisputed    
    
    
    Good morning #InglishMajors. At this time of the morn, the only thing I can think to say is something cliche sooo, "Rise & Grind" people!!!    
    
    
    @djrossone lmao off at your Kendrick comment    
    
    
    NICE!! Lorde Becomes The First Woman To Top The Alternative Chart In 17 Years http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/08/12/lorde-first-woman-alternative-chart-17-years-royals_n_3745113.html …    
    
    
    Imma let Kendrick Lamar finish but @LupeFiasco had the best verse of 2013 on 'Bad Decisions"    
    
    
    @emanuelhouse  thanks for the tweets E.    
    
    
    Big shout out to @sheenasakai. Super talented singer. Check  her out guys    
    
    
    @IM_YOUNG_D Appreciate the follow homie    
    
    
    I've said this before and I'll say it again. @DawnRichard's album "GoldenHeart" is the sh**    
    
    
    @deejaymig  Appreciate the love man    
    
    
    Much Love to all my #Greeks. Always supporting hard.    
    
    
    Just wrapped up the mix for an exclusive track I have coming with @pixikill Get excited #InglishMajors Coming Sooon! #electropop at its best    
    
    
    Patiently explaining to a 5yr old that night lights only mean u will SEE the monster as it rips u apart..sometimes not knowing is better    
    
    
    Best Kendrick Lamar response is definitely Papoose's. Check it out. DAMN!! https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=wF6p58cl5A4#at=142 …    
    
    
    @OMGitsShateezy lol very good way of putting it.    
    
    
    Watching @jasonderulo live right now. Gotta support my Haitian brothers-> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WqjXN5RRYsw …    
    
    
    This music industry will suck the life out of you... seriously.    
    
    
    @Bethliliani Hey Beth. Como Esta?    
    
    
    @juliane115 for sure :)    
    
    
    Quick shoutout to a few Top of the class #InglishMajors who mean a lot to me @channtiee88 @katy_batyox @theduchessv79 @Geordaina #Love    
    
    
    @AlyxCullen Nice blog btw    
    
    
    Gottta show @YourMusicRadar major love for always supporting my remixes.    
    
    
    #KeepCalm & #SpeakInglish http://instagram.com/p/dHp7z6viNN/     
    
    
    Watching House Party 2 thinking why can't parties be like that again? Now everyone just stands around mean mugging each other    
    
    
    Every time I watch #Catfish I can't help but think education has failed these ppl since all they needed to do was a simple Google search.    
    
    
    In 2013 you SHOULD NOT be getting catfished...seriously. If you had real sex instead of phone sex, you wouldn't be in those situations.    
    
    
    Follow me on Instagram People. I post the most beautiful pictures of Subway sandwiches and add the hastag #foodart & #foodporn @HansInglish    
    
    
    The video to my single #RealityShow is actually a compilation of videos I've taken at clubs etc. over the years http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W9hP6loboXE&feature=share&list=PLVIL-byuop6A1Ng44Wr6hFft-0uMjzXJe …    
    
    
    #FunFact I recorded Reality Show with Johnny Nice who was an engineer & producer on Rihanna's first 2 albums    
    
    
    @nilesG Hey Niles. Would love for you to take a look at some of my material if you get some time. Have a great Sunday and thanks in advance.    
    
    
    #FunFact It took 48 different mixes of my song #DanceDruggie before I was completely satisfied. @blacklight_diaz was executive producer    
    
    
    #FunFact I recorded the idea for #DanceDruggie in 2009 and never released it till early this year. I didn't like it's original production    
    
    
    #FunFact I did my first "Hip-House" track in 2004 and A&R's at record labels straight shitted on me saying it woud never work #GoFigure    
    
    
    @kacee_cox Yeah so what... :)    
    
    
    #ProducersToWatch --> @DemitriMedina @blacklight_diaz @CapBeatz    
    
    
    #StraightUpTellSomeoneTheyreHot @mishapagano #JustSaying    
    
    
    Maybe I shouldn't partcipate in this #StraightUpTellSomeoneTheyreHot T.T.. I know some ppl are gonna catch feelings if I dont mention them    
    
    
    #FunFact My video for #RealityShow is a compilation of personal videos Ive taken at clubs etc. over the years http://goo.gl/SXBAOw     
    
    
    @carlaelyse lmao...save the energy for when I shoot official video ;)    
    
    
    @freemagz Appreciate you guys adding me to your Soundcloud.    
    
    
    I really only produce for myself but if any Pop or EDM artists need a remix or original done for a good price, hit me up.    
    
    
    Are you a vocalist and live in NY? Looking for a singer to reference songs for major label Pop artists. Great exposure opportunity. Hit me    
    
    
    Agree RT @toscamarleen: The 'fat' twin has a nicer body. Why does the other twin think its ok that i can see her chest plate @nicoleandbri    
    
    
    @toscamarleen no but i knew who you were talking about because that show is on right now l lol    
    
    
    @toscamarleen Yeah they are really good on WWE but the show is not for me. Can't deal    
    
    
    Intimidation of journalists by the US & British Gov't is not ok Mr. @BarackObama #RIP Investigative Journalism    
    
    
    @Katy_Batyox lol It would be slightly if I didn't see it an hour late    
    
    
    Just touched down at @PattyLaurent's Pre VMA myxer with @RSVPLifestyle . Looking sexy in here.    
    
    
    Ladies, if you want to see Jason Derulo perform tonight come out to Finale on 199 Bowery St. NYC Drinks on me. Hit me up if you're coming    
    
    
    Honestly @martinsolveig's - The Night Out sounds so crazy in the club. Love that song http://goo.gl/LDnr55     
    
    
    Ok....@360ismusic ...SOB's..... Queens is in the building end of story. #Crazy    
    
    
    @Mackey_Memo Do what you do homie. Appreciate the love.    
    
    
    Got a remix to Bruno Mars' Treasure coming in the next day or 2 for all my #InglishMajors    
    
    
    If you have the Palladia channel turn to it now. This is giving me life    
    
    
    @Katy_Batyox nah I meant like the actual audio quality of the microphones etc. at live shows in the past.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @ShesRYAN ..Enjoy your day even though it's shitty outside.    
    
    
    Someone needs to tell attractive people that their stories are boring.    
    
    
    I bet the Al Qaeda recruiting video is just footage of Americans waiting in line 3 hours for Cronuts.    
    
    
    Been working on a song with someone in Paris for like 2 months & Ive already done like 6 different versions. Still not where it needs to be.    
    
    
    Right about now I need like 4 shots of Tequila    
    
    
    Been working since this morning and I'm just now remembering to eat dinner. Smh I can't be doing this anymore.    
    
    
    @Geordaina Oh I need that lol.    
    
    
    Man vs. Nature  #UpperEastSide #NYC http://instagram.com/p/dXIsLQviFD/     
    
    
    @NinaRawz wait you in NY?    
    
    
    @NinaRawz smh and you aint hit me up? Really? -_-'how long are you here?    
    
    
    @NinaRawz ahhhh man. Worst time. I'm working till late on a project right now. You leave tomorrow what time?    
    
    
    Some people say waaay too much on twitter I swear. Certain things are better kept to yourself    
    
    
    Ok people get excited because this @pixikill  x @HansInglish collaboration just rounded 3rd base. Release date TBA...    
    
    
    @NinaRawz lmao well I DM'd you so just hit me tomorrow whenever    
    
    
    Got an early surprise for you guys. Go to my Soundcloud page--> http://www.soundcloud.com/HansInglish  #Retweet    
    
    
    Just linked up with @NinaRawz while she's visiting NYC. Super cool peoples. Been supporting me on radio & social media for 3 years plus.    
    
    
    Always dope how twitter can bring people together. I've met some of the best people on here. Thankful    
    
    
    @Marcus_Pepe  Appreciate the tweet Marcus    
    
    
    #MusicMonday Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  #Retweet    
    
    
    #MusicMonday Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  #Retweet ..    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva true. That song is def. Not a good as treasure.    
    
    
    #MusicMonday @BrunoMars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  #Retweet    
    
    
    Have you heard my new Bruno Mars "Treasure" Remix? Check it out!! http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  #Retweet    
    
    
    @Geordaina Maybe it is. You just never know hahaha    
    
    
    @Akin9603 @minnely101 Check out the Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. @HansInglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  Think you'll like it :)    
    
    
    @M0weezyANA @sbrem71 Check out the Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. @HansInglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp  Think you'll like it :)    
    
    
    Someone care to tell me the point of decaf coffee? It's like smoking a fake cigarette.    
    
    
    Need some listening material on your way to work? Check out my Bruno Mars #Treasure (Remix) on Soundcloud http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    @j_buzzi Happy Birthday homie    
    
    
    Need some listening material on your way to work? Check out my @BrunoMars #Treasure (Remix) on @Soundcloud http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    So I just saw Miley Cyrus' VMA perforce and....wow, can you say black culture exploitation at it's finest. Who are the people on her team?    
    
    
    Why do white people want to be "ratchet" so bad? And why are they abusing the word 6 years after Hurricane Chris sadly introduced it?    
    
    
    Can we leave the twerking to @Ciara? PLEAAASSSEEEE!!!    
    
    
    I just saw someone by themselves not looking at a phone. Hope they're ok.    
    
    
    Lmao .true RT @Geordaina: @HansInglish should have lent them your charger....    
    
    
    Met the group @pixikill 3 weeks ago on Instagram...Yes Instagram and we decided this needed to happen.… http://instagram.com/p/diIuZwPiGU/     
    
    
    "To be interested in the changing seasons is a happier state of mind than to be hopelessly in love with spring." -George Santayana    
    
    
    Let's set the record straight. Twerking has been around since the 90's. Why is it such a new phenomenon all of a sudden?    
    
    
    I guess @diplo is probably responsible for making twerking popular on a National and if not an international level    
    
    
    "No problem can withstand the assault of sustained thinking." -Voltaire    
    
    
    #InglishMajors I need sime inspiration right now. Send me a link to song that really gets you motivated to take on the world. Anything...    
    
    
    @Zakswfc Always good to catch em by surprise ...thanks homie    
    
    
    Honestly these motivational songs everyone's sending my way are giving me life right now. Keep em coming...    
    
    
    @DJMMMusic didn't forget you man. Will have your drop tomorrow    
    
    
    @meghna_sangwan Good Morning buddy. Have you heard my Bruno Mars #Treasure (REMIX) ? -> let me know what you think http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    @KittyCavas Happy Birthday homie. Hope all is well and you're enjoying yourself :)    
    
    
    Meet me on the corner of...umm, what street is this? #NYC #Me http://instagram.com/p/dpuwrNviN7/     
    
    
    Chick asks me where she can get the D. I paused for a second & just had to laugh. I was like "oohhh the D TRAIN? U can get it at the corner    
    
    
    #Retweet Bruno Mars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    There's nothing that leaves you more fatigued than an unfinished task    
    
    
    @darcieGNO congrats that's huge!!    
    
    
    @DJMMMusic yeah i sent it yesterday    
    
    
    @DJMMMusic Going to check in a few when I get back to the crib    
    
    
    @MishaPagano ask jokes aside though, coffee table books are aleays good. Try "The Creativity of Ditko" "The New Erotic Photography 2"    
    
    
    @MishaPagano and there is always this one which is popular for select audiences http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/0767917537 …    
    
    
    You really think the US cares about 500 children dying in a chemical attack? The 1st Gulf War we killed 500,000 children w/out blinking    
    
    
    Big shout out to @iamkingdeco #Talent    
    
    
    I'm urging everyone to write to their Congressman and protest @BarackObama striking against Syria. All my NY'ers contact @cbrangel    
    
    
    #NowPLaying @BrunoMars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    Well since @ElectricZooNY is canceled, everyone can just go to the Bronx Zoo    
    
    
    @BrideOfChucky__ yeah    
    
    
    OH man I had the Fig & Mascarpone Cronut and that s*** is POPPING. Best flavor yet.    
    
    
    Via @Gawker: Dear Khary (An Autobiography of Gentrification) http://goo.gl/hRLWKg 

-Wow this was such a great read I just had to share it.    
    
    
    If you think that the U.S. morally cares about 1,400 people dying in a chemical attack in #Syria, I have a bridge to sell you #JustSaying    
    
    
    is there anything more capitalist than a peanut with a top hat, cane, and monocle selling you other peanuts to eat    
    
    
    @iGetMuzik Appreciate the follow guys    
    
    
    Back on it!!! I'm live at #SullivanRoom, #NYC Wednesday 9.4.13 for a college end of the summer party… http://instagram.com/p/dxn6MfviLi/     
    
    
    If you want exclusive content and news sign up for my email list here: http://bit.ly/Q8gLab     
    
    
    So apparently the girl who died at EZoo took 6 hits of Molly. WHY would anyone do such a thing? 6? Really?    
    
    
    Oh BTW, I'm live at #SullivanRoom, #NYC tomorrow 9.4.13 for a college end of the summer party 18+ http://Instagram.com/p/dxn6MfviLi/ ”    
    
    
    @ezralevant @carney @teapartyorg @loudobbsnews Wait, u guys realize that a lot of Presidents have been photographed w/ feet on desk right?    
    
    
    Sara Bareilles said there was no beef but Katy Perry's "Roar" sounds so much like "Brave". In the hood thats like someone stealing ur chain    
    
    
    TONIGHT:  live at #SullivanRoom, #NYC Wednesday 9.4.13 for a college end of the summer party… http://Instagram.com/p/dxn6MfviLi/ ”    
    
    
    Good morning everyone!!! Just want to thank all the fans that came out to my show at Sullivan Room and showed love. It was crazy    
    
    
    Much love to @thedreamlab Robots for performing with me and much love to their whole crew. Hopefully we can do it again at some point    
    
    
    Shout out to all the #InglishMajors who showed love last night at #SullivanRoom, #NYC. #live #show… http://instagram.com/p/d4qOKnviKU/     
    
    
    Rocking out @ Sullivan Room with The Dream Lab Robots. 
#pheeders #electro #photography #pop #edm #hiphop ... © 2013 http://pheed.com/p/33177464     
    
    
    @Channtiee88 cause you're a boss. We all know that    
    
    
    Another dope shot of my performance at #SullivanRoom taken by @mikemckay24 http://instagram.com/p/d9hle4PiNF/     
    
    
    "Smooth Criminal" #photography #pheed #pheeders #fashion http://pheed.com/p/33475899     
    
    
    @Channtiee88 like you're new avatar btw    
    
    
    Is Breaking Bad delaying tasks in anyone else's life like it is mine?    
    
    
    Hands down @923NowFM plays the best music on Sat. Night I swear    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana Tired from all the sex drugs and rock n roll . Mostly all the drugs...'.........in "Breaking Bad"    
    
    
    Cowboys ALL day. Goodnight...    
    
    
    Oh, hey @justinbieber... http://instagram.com/p/eC1qz2PiHf/     
    
    
    Yesterday was crazy. Got to meet Justin Bieber, Paris Hilton and Miguel at Dream Hotel    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva lol not sure he would take the advice but he was cool enough to stop, say hi and take a pic so some credit due    
    
    
    Love my city!! Rooftop #DreamHotel #PHD #NYC @ Dream Downtown http://instagram.com/p/eDZphaviIx/     
    
    
    9 out of 10 men prefer a girl with a big butt. The 10th man prefers the other 9 men.    
    
    
    I'm thinking the saddest thing about this whole Gucci Man beef on twitter is the complete disrespect of the English language    
    
    
    Just voted on a really old voting machine. Starred at it for 5 min before I knew what to do. Now I know how older ppl feel at digital polls    
    
    
    Naked girls and Disco Balls...    
    
    
    @NataliaKills  album "Trouble" on repeat...    
    
    
    Yo @ADreamOfficial is killing it in the game right now. @ladygaga 's song "Swine" is CRAZY! That beat is so sick man    
    
    
    Is Flo Rida serious with this new Beamz product he is selling? WTF???https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=vVQpaGeW3xo …    
    
    
    Good morning everyone!!! Hope your day started off on a positive note    
    
    
    Damn @real_mistercee is resigning from hot 97. Crazy that it's his last day today. Been listening to thus dude since like 1999    
    
    
    #tbt coming off stage at Highline Ballroom and got mobbed by a group of girls from the UK. Thoughts in… http://instagram.com/p/eK9XLpPiEh/     
    
    
    Maybe teenagers just aren't strong enough yet to remove the sticker from their hat    
    
    
    Have we worked together in the past or recently? Add me to your connections on linked in here: http://lnkd.in/bEZD5Um     
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Man I'm jealous. Save me a slice    
    
    
    #LoneyGirl Exhibition @ #MartosGallery..Who wants to roll with me tonight 6pm? http://instagram.com/p/eNkWirPiAO/     
    
    
    @colortheory Hey Brian appreciate the follow. Loving your stuff. Would love to collaborate on something in the future if you'd be down    
    
    
    RT  “@patbits: “What are the specs on those pecs?” My dream girl says to me at the E3 Square Enix booth.”

-Who? Sasha Grey?    
    
    
    @toscamarleen does that mean you in the area?    
    
    
    @colortheory no problem man. Good music is good music    
    
    
    Summertime Sadness...    
    
    
    If you live in NY and you're not listening to @DJYONNY on Friday nights @923NowFM somethings wrong with you. #justsaying    
    
    
    Shout out to @BChamp_ & @MariaVitagliano ..Been a while since I've meet such hard working and humble people like you guys. #Salute    
    
    
    @BChamp_ @MariaVitagliano man I can't get "Ambiance" out of my head #wtf  lol    
    
    
    The homie @TravieMcCoy is filming a video right across the street from me. Watching the action with my binoculars lol    
    
    
    Spent the day getting the "What are you doing with your life speech" from my parents...Happens once every few months    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of "Giving Away Tons of Personal Data to Corporations and Government Agencies Because I'm an Idiot" on FourSquare!    
    
    
    @_1337_x3_ Hey thanks for the follow btw :-)    
    
    
    @DJCoopDaVillain Yo you dipped out already?    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to my cuzzo @RonAustinJr !! Hope you enjoy all the lube and condoms bestowed upon you by the family lol    
    
    
    Watch "Maejor Ali - Lolly ft. Juicy J, Justin Bieber" on YouTube http://goo.gl/K1Bq7J 

-Justin spittin verses now? He kinda killed it    
    
    
    #tbt Fashion week 2011 with my cousin @nakitabanana http://instagram.com/p/edF_UqPiBg/     
    
    
    Songwriting, Songwriting and more songwriting    
    
    
    Newest TV Show addiction is "Suits"...Really good show    
    
    
    Big shout out to singer @SitaraKmusic Her voice is amazing. Be sure to follow her people.    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana Did @RonAustinJr win an award? Did he do a speech? I'm mad I'm missing it but there was a situation. #HeavyFlow    
    
    
    Do everything with the thought process that your character may just be getting tested...    
    
    
    Quick look at my #SullivanRoom #show 2 weeks ago with @thedreamlab Robots. Head to my YouTube page for… http://instagram.com/p/ek0B1DPiK_/     
    
    
    Artists still think they can get record deals by doing demos? lol that's funny...    
    
    
    Best new Jersey in the NFL has to go to the Miami Dolphins hands down. #tough    
    
    
    With that said, what's up with the new two tone Garbage Man Green Jets uniform?    
    
    
    Video: Some footage of me live at the Sullivan Room, NYC. Amazing all the love these kids showed.  http://tmblr.co/Za0yWtvpu7fl     
    
    
    Is it national post a baby pic on Facebook day?    
    
    
    Girls heres how to tell if a guy wants you for sex: 

1) He does    
    
    
    Shout out to @louddigital for the great event last night. Had a lot of fun. @wale and @myfabolouslife killed it http://thbs.co/p/BPGGIP?ref=ipad …    
    
    
    Attention everyone: When you Shazam a song, you don't have to hold your phone up in the air becuase it's a song and sound goes everywhere!    
    
    
    There's a haunted house in Philly where you go through it completely naked. I really wanna do that    
    
    
    @toscamarleen would you do it?    
    
    
    Why is Chelsea Clinton wearing one of Shaba Rank's jackets on @TheDailyShow ?    
    
    
    Grand Theft Auto reminds me of Florida. Except one lets you shoot people without consequence and the other is a video game.    
    
    
    Cowboys Nation #ThatllBeAll #NFL    
    
    
    I need some leather jogging pants. Just want to see how that works out ..for jogging    
    
    
    @MishaPagano lol I actually would do it. That would be truly overcoming your fears. I think it's a great idea.    
    
    
    @MishaPagano Lmmfao Oh that's why you're on haunted house boycott.Got it. Have you ever been to the ones in Orlando at Islands Of Adventure?    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana Williamsburg is being gingerbreaded too.Don't do it    
    
    
    #GoodByeBreakingBad I might get emotional    
    
    
    Beware drinking from plastic water bottles. The chemicals used to make them are linked with infertility, birth defects & cancer    
    
    
    @HabbGaga  thank you so much. I really appreciate that. Where did you hear the remix if you don't mind me asking?    
    
    
    @HabbGaga Wow. So crazy how people discover new artists. That's dope. I love Natalia Kills. Been a fan since she was "Verbz" on Myspace lol    
    
    
    @HabbGaga yeah she used to be a rapper and was really good actually. She changed her whole image up.    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana true    
    
    
    #Soundcloud @BrunoMars - #Treasure (REMIX) feat. Hans Inglish http://snd.sc/19HMTYp     
    
    
    "I've realized that business and being polite DON'T match. You can be fair but me being polite is me not being fair to myself."    
    
    
    @nakitabanana . http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pt8VYOfr8To&sns … #WorkBxxch #Yup    
    
    
    Excuse me while I watch this Britney #WorkBitch Video http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pt8VYOfr8To&sns … ..Who thinks I should remix this?    
    
    
    Sometimes I hate that I can't have too much of an opinion being in the music industry. Everyone gets offended so easily    
    
    
    Evev better though---> RT @arcadefire: Here Comes the Night Time http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_fFAKrIntzY …    
    
    
    New Yorkers, please stop damaging our covering up new Banksy pieces before i get to see them. Thank You -MGMT    
    
    
    Fact: The ACA was signed into LAW through a constitutional process and deemed by the Supreme Court to be Constitutional so WTF is the prob?    
    
    
    Man this Reflektor album from @arcadefire is going to be BANANAS    
    
    
    @arcadefire has six Haitian percussionists featured on the album. That's the first thing I thought when I heard #HereComesTheNight    
    
    
    @RealRageJunkie I recommend checking out newcomer @blacklight_diaz https://soundcloud.com/blacklightdiaz  #DopeEDMProducer    
    
    
    Hppay Birthday to the homie @elenikaterina !!!    
    
    
    Big shout out to @SitaraKmusic who is working on a song I wrote right now. You are beyond incredible and immensely appreciated. Thank You    
    
    
    @Channtiee88 Your avatar looks like you were in my "Ah Yeah" video lol Did you see it?    
    
    
    I hear @thedoctorluke needs songwriters.... #ILikeToDream but seriously I can write u some smashes. Just 1 song #IChallngeYourWriters    
    
    
    @Channtiee88 lol yeah but i get to place the hand prints on the re-do :)    
    
    
    #tbt Interviewing Joe Jackson a few months after MJ died. #BestMomentOfMyLife #WishEdHardyDiedInstead… http://instagram.com/p/fA415BPiN0/     
    
    
    #InglishMajors: Be sure to check out this great Non For Profit >>@tpscommunity. They fund small projects in impoverished countries worldwide    
    
    
    @tpscommunity is a new Org. run by some great people that I had the pleasure meeting. What they are doing is great. Check them out!!    
    
    
    @sold_inc    
    
    
    C'mon Tony Romo.WHYYYYY!!!###    
    
    
    @mlebean You're seriously a big inspiration to me as a songwriter/engineer. Not enough females in the game doing what u do. Love it #Talent    
    
    
    The government basically un-friended us.    
    
    
    @Katy_Batyox it's a little late but I wanted to wish you a Happy Birthday. Keep being the positive spirited person u are & enjoy ur night!!    
    
    
    Spent the last few weeks studying mixing & vocal arranging techniques on some of my favorite songs. Learned some great things. #growthweek    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @TarynPapa !!! Sending love your way :)    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Ok not a prob. Let's go to @CityOfPastele 's show tomorrow :)    
    
    
    @CityOfPastele What time is your show? Looks like I'm performing tonight as well but much later at Stash    
    
    
    Tonight I'm making an appearance at Stash, NYC for a college 18 plus party if anyone wants to come give me a hug cause I need one lol    
    
    
    @RheaPasricha I know you're always looking for writers & since you're going to be in NY, I would love to possibly meet with you when ur here    
    
    
    @cassyofLondon It's so cloudy over there everyone needs one. I might be out there early next year actually    
    
    
    How to make a relationship run smooth: Break up with the person then continue seeing them like nothing ever happened. Arguments over.    
    
    
    @CityOfPastele sorry i couldn't make your show. My soundcheck was at 10:30. How was it?    
    
    
    @CityOfPastele good. I hate missing your shows. I always live hearing ur new stuff. You know, the songs you keep a secret from everyone :)    
    
    
    Great session today with mariavitagliano. She absolutely killed this song I wrote. #ManListen… http://instagram.com/p/fbQLubPiBw/     
    
    
    @DJMMMusic I don't even know. My phone tweeted that on it's own    
    
    
    Geek Tweet: For any of you engineers looking for a DOPE compressor to add to ur arsenal, check out the @fabfilter Pro-C. DOES IT ALL & WELL!    
    
    
    @JMCPrinting Got you locked in    
    
    
    @fabfilter Thank u for your incredible plugin visualizations. Makes.my life that much easier and helps me really understand what's happening    
    
    
    C'Mon #NYPD. He actually raising property values. Let him live. http://instagram.com/p/fkqe-rviF5/     
    
    
    #tbt Me and my cuzzo @ronaustinjr been daper since the age of 5 lol http://instagram.com/p/flBMHjviG2/     
    
    
    @AkaashSingh great meeting you man. Let me know when your next show is    
    
    
    On a set playing a doctor cause you know, f*** it why not? Anyone need a prescription? http://instagram.com/p/flxeymviAs/     
    
    
    Its really ironic that we had a Govt shutdown that cost a total of $24 Billion all over Obamacare which would cost an estimated $1.1 Billion    
    
    
    My song "Ah Yeah will be featured on @MTV's new show "Scrubbing In" Premiering Oct. 24th!! @scrubbinginMTV Tune In http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nepXwqSgajo …    
    
    
    Just had an awkward moment of telling someone they left their shoes under my bed and then having them say they don't own them. Yikes    
    
    
    Ultimate trap RT @JustinRosePHC: @HansInglish lmao that's happened to me too many times    
    
    
    Everyone in my family who works in the corporate world always comes home telling stories about something racist thei co-workers said lol    
    
    
    @ChelseyFerri Not sure cause they're keeping me in the dark on that but thanks. I think it will be a great show despite controversy    
    
    
    Its full blown summertime again out here in NY. Damn!!    
    
    
    Tell me how my cousin @patbits had coffee with @NataliaKills and didn't tell me smh. I'm hurt lol    
    
    
    @Dhaniscorp THANK YOU for tweeting the Minecraft Parody :)    
    
    
    @patbits Yo have you seen this? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UiiS-TSuE1M&feature=youtu.be … I'm in minecraft history now lol    
    
    
    Why is the beat for @Krewella's "Live For The Night" so damn EPIC. Man @omgRainMan really did his thing on that. I wanna jump on couches now    
    
    
    Thug Prolly,Yo come Polly,He wanna f* a bad Dolly,Pop Molly. I hope ur mothaf** pockets got a pot belly or is it dat u neva ball,John Salley    
    
    
    Nicki Minaj Minaj Killed that vere on Chris Brown's 'Love More" woooo    
    
    
    Is @Zendaya the new Cassie? Oh shit...    
    
    
    Who's at the #AES Convention right now?    
    
    
    Have yall heard my @drake "The Motion" Remix?  Download it and blast it on the way to the club tonight https://soundcloud.com/hansinglish/drake-feat-hans-inglish-sampha …    
    
    
    While you're at it you might as well download my J Cole Villuminati Freestyle too http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PvLPm-jDIgM&list=PLVIL-byuop6DcwihDnQAtS4U3A0SoOdnm&index=6 …    
    
    
    If you're out and about in the city tonight, come join me at Suite 36 Free to get in and drinks on us. 11:30pm List: @RSVPLifestyle    
    
    
    @IncredibleLAGO Wish you were you at #AES this weekend? They definitely needed a talented female engineer to be present and give tips    
    
    
    @MasonBetha Has a new album coming called #NowWeEven. Interested to see what he does lyrically on this one.    
    
    
    Thank god I have the newest, fastest phone so I can mindlessly check the same three apps 500 times a day.    
    
    
    @THEmrMEOLA lol I'm sure everyone can    
    
    
    @J_Grys Don't ask me to help you put together any Ikea furniture. They're the devil    
    
    
    I know everyone is going to be tuning in to the TLC movie tonight. The commentary on twitter is probably going to be interesting    
    
    
    With the last 2 singles Justin Bieber dropped, it looks like he's about to be the one to bring actual R&B back in the game for the youngins    
    
    
    I'm talking about are 'Heartbreaker" and "Hold Tight" in case anyone was confused by last tweet. Black ppl obviously wrote these for him lol    
    
    
    My song "Ah Yeah" will be featured on @MTV's new show "Scrubbing In" Premiering Oct. 24th 10/9C @scrubbinginMTV http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nepXwqSgajo …    
    
    
    Lil Mama seriously nailed Left Eye in this movie. Props to her. She came a long way from showing up on award stages uninvited
#CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    Man I look more like Dallas Austin than this dude. How come no one told me about the auditions? I wanna make out wit Chilli #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    Shit going fast in this TLC movie. Chilli just got pregnant from kissing Dallas Austin #ThatsAFIrst #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    @beautifulrhymes apologies hahaha. You can always go back to my timeline later    
    
    
    Why everyone surprised at a million records sold and being broke? That shit is happening to every rapper right now #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    I bet you TLC recouped their money faster than Rihanna did. She wasn't in the black until like her 3rd album #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    U guys know that @pebbles2day is going to print out her @ mentions to use as slander evidence in court right?Yall better stop #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    Yo Left Eye really pulled a David Ruffin from the Trmptations for a sec..."I Don't Need You"  #CrazySexyCool    
    
    
    Had to pull out the record on y'all from my old crates. We played this heavy at every party… http://instagram.com/p/fwRNZTviEt/     
    
    
    Everyone say Happy Birthday to the homie @JustinAnthonyJA You have 5 more minutes unless you're in the Mid West or LA    
    
    
    @shyboi2020 What's up man!! Everything good with ya?    
    
    
    @shyboi2020 been here tweeting. Never went anywhere    
    
    
    @shyboi2020 yeah man did the name change and all that since like Jan. The music has been good man. Can't complain bro    
    
    
    Top 10 Haunted Houses in America http://www.tested.com/inventern/458696-most-high-tech-haunted-houses/ … (Too bad none of these are in NY)    
    
    
    Don't forget to tune in to @MTV's new show @scrubbinginMTV tomorrow at 10/9C You just might hear one of my songs.    
    
    
    @BlendHQ Guys, I never got the invite code. Is the site online yet?    
    
    
    It is much easier to hula hoop with an erection.    
    
    
    @BlendHQ no worries I'm good to go just signed up    
    
    
    People have hit me up about my @NataliaKills remix verse saying it helped them get through certain problems & that means a lot. #Inspiration    
    
    
    I know what it's like to want to give up & feeling indifference toward life. Not sure where I'd be without writing & music #FindYourOutlet    
    
    
    It's all about #Blackfish right now on @CNN    
    
    
    U dont need to see an Orca in a Park to bring awareness. It's 2013. Id smack a kid who didnt know what a Killer Whale was #Blackfish    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo kindle    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo Been great. Honestly I think about it sometimes because I love Aviation but no. There's nothing like fighting for a dream    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo I struggle don't get me wrong but I don't answer to anyone really and it's good. I don't need much to make me happy.    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo Thank You. I cherish having genuine people like u & Mike come into my life though cause that's rare & means a lot more. #truth    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo Right now i wish i was in your weather though. I'm freezing in my apt smh. F***the east coast right now lol    
    
    
    @LyssV_Xo yeah it's the "Grass Greener on the other side" complex. I've never heard someone say they miss rain until I went to Cali    
    
    
    Too many suckers for love in this world. We believe in fairy tales way too much. Always go into things with your head    
    
    
    We go together like white girls and cracked IPhone screens...    
    
    
    BBM Life once again: 7B1B6C2C    
    
    
    @thebeatkidz yo you guys are dope. Tryin to get a remix done for my song "Reality Show" if you guys are down    
    
    
    @ChelseyFerri Great first episode by the way    
    
    
    Shout out to you @FifthHarmony. The EP came out really great. Amazing A&R work  @LdotHarman    
    
    
    Hey @melismaticdiva have you heard the @FifthHarmony EP yet? What you think?    
    
    
    Make sure you guys stream my tracks on #Spotify: >>#AhYeah #DanceDruggie #RealityShow<< [All available on ITunes as well]    
    
    
    Is it me or is the new season of Kevin Harts #RHOH not that funny at all?    
    
    
    "Almost every wise saying has an opposite one, no less wise, to balance it." -George Santayana    
    
    
    #BBM Pin: 7B1B6C2C If you're someone I don't know personally or you don't have a pic, let me know who you are so I don't ignore the invite    
    
    
    @mrfingaz what studio is that?    
    
    
    Photo: Work hard sleep hard… http://tmblr.co/Za0yWtyjpreK     
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Funny thats my least favorite track from a production perspective but "Who Are You" is my fav from a writing perspective    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva It's crazy cause I didn't know 4 of them are Bruno Mars' sisters    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva oh maybe that's what it is. I'm mistaken then. Thanks for clearing that up    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva You saw the TLC movie lol It's going to be HARD to see that again but I feel you on the UK statement    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Noone likes being broke for long and the days of selling 10 million are long gone. Except for with Bruno Mars & Eminem    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva NYSNC selling a million in one day had to be part of a grand marketing plan where the label bought a lot of those albums    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Who's the biggest selling Pop group of all time?    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva I just looked it up. Top selling Boy Bands: 1.Backstreet Bys 2. Jackson Five 3. NKOTB 4. The Osmonds 5. Bay City Rollers    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva And your 3 girl groups were exactly right. #4 is Bananarama and #5 is AKB48    
    
    
    @melismaticdiva Yup #6 is another J-Pop group "Speed" then the Supremes. Crazy. I can't believe that    
    
    
    If you're on #Spotify, be sure to follow me and add my streams to your playlists--> http://open.spotify.com/artist/03VklqYq5ix8TKgt1il9A1 …    
    
    
    "Music is a means of giving form to our inner feelings, without attaching them to events or objects in the world."    
    
    
    "Love is A Suicide" by Natalia Kills on repeat for right now    
    
    
    "When rich people fight wars with one another, poor people are the ones to die." -Jean-Paul Sartre    
    
    
    "Many a man fails as an original thinker simply because his memory it too good." -Friedrich Nietzsche    
    
    
    Yo 2 Chainz graduated from ASU with a 4.0 GPA. Just thought I'd let the world know. Wow    
    
    
    My #Halloween costume cost $4.99 #AintNoBodyGotTimeForThat #IAintEvenGoingOutTho #NoReally… http://instagram.com/p/gJdc9hviLD/     
    
    
    #Halloween is a whole different thing in Harlem compared to Queens where I grew up. I used to go house to house. These kids go Deli to Deli    
    
    
    Had a productive and fun afternoon with @andrewfennell with _r_a_h_e_l_  and @nakitabanana… http://instagram.com/p/gOigepPiKg/     
    
    
    Shout out to @EstherZysk Amazing singer and Actress. #Follow    
    
    
    If you’re a vegan w a gluten allergy who doesn't own a TV do you put it on a business card or just wait to force it into every conversation?    
    
    
    @EllaRogue Hey thanks for following. GOing to reach out by email and see how we can possibly work on something. Love your voice btw    
    
    
    @Geordaina and I didn't mean that in some subliminal dirty way lol    
    
    
    @EllaRogue Thank You!! I just sent you an email so keep an eye out. :)    
    
    
    "Religion is excellent stuff for keeping common people quiet. Religion is what keeps the poor from murdering the rich." - Napoleon Bonaparte    
    
    
    Just ordered a salted caramel mocha latte at #Starbucks. Does that mean I'm about to be traded to the whites by the @TheRaceDraft ?    
    
    
    #InglishMajors I need a favor. If you're on Hypem, please favorite my "Saturday Night" remix with @NataliaKills -->
http://goo.gl/OwVrW8     
    
    
    Don't listen to country often but I had the the @ladyantebellum "Golden" album jamming this morn and it's really good.    
    
    
    @holisox Appreciate the follow :)    
    
    
    I text people back embarrassingly fast or three days later there is no in between    
    
    
    "Hang out with different people everyday so the only person who knows you've been wearing the same outfit all week is you" - my fashion blog    
    
    
    Let's be real. In his prime, Richard Simmons was, at best, in just okay shape.    
    
    
    Got the @KaceyMusgraves album on repeat today. Her writing is incredible    
    
    
    I can never understand the logic of people who work out all the time but eat the worst foods. Fitness is 90% nutrition people.    
    
    
    @MishaPagano DM me your number wgen you get a chance. Thought I had it    
    
    
    Things I've learned today. Vodka, beer, and Cronuts aren't the best mix....    
    
    
    Happy Birthday 2 one of the best club promoters in NYC @mikemckaynyc. Always supports heavy & for that I say u are an official #InglishMajor    
    
    
    Shoutout to @MishaPagano for bring a great person & for not even attempting to take my picture this weekend. At least not overtly.    
    
    
    If you're interested in casting for #reality #TV or have thought about it, I suggest following the homie -> @MishaPagano<- for that.    
    
    
    @BoRadley_ is that an admission of guilt? Lol    
    
    
    @CiminoTV @CreAjian Great meeting you guys although Asia and I almost had a fist fight over Miley Cyrus in the club    
    
    
    @CoyTiffany @CreAjian yeah we agreed to disagree so noone got hurt lol. Next month we'll def all go party when @MishaPagano comes back    
    
    
    #Food4thought. U remember when @MileyCyrus  did "party in the USA" & said she didnt even know a Jay Z song though she mentioned him in it?    
    
    
    @CreAjian no no never. I was more upset at you kidnapping @MishaPagano then i was at the whole Miley thing actually. Lol    
    
    
    @CreAjian very true    
    
    
    @NakitaBanana wtf? How are you scared sleeping with someone?  #JesusTakeTheWheel    
    
    
    If you're on #Spotify, be sure to follow me and add my streams to your playlists--> http://open.spotify.com/artist/03VklqYq5ix8TKgt1il9A1 …    
    
    
    #CancerAwarness Remember that it all starts with food. What you put in is what u get out. Stay away from processed foods & cut down on meats    
    
    
    #CancerAwareness Stay away from bottled water. The chemical BPA & DEHF found in plastics is linked to high risk of cancer.Buy #Glass bottles    
    
    
    @cassyofLondon It's found in all plastics. It seeps into liquids/foods so it's also good to store left over food in non plastic containers.    
    
    
    "I do." "Same." - wedding vows in 2030    
    
    
    I think Hans Zimmer ran out of ideas cause it sounded like he re used the same music from inception in #12YearsASlave    
    
    
    Not sure I'm ready for the @dallascowboys to embarrass me this Thanksgiving in front of the whole family    
    
    
    Did you guys see the Kanye "Bound 2" video yet? Ummm I'm trying to figure out if this was real or a spoof. http://goo.gl/3510aQ     
    
    
    @VidArroyo lmao or maybe Lamar directed it. That's more believable    
    
    
    @AlreadyFamous10 You're joking right? That video was the worst thing I've seen in a long time lol    
    
    
    @AlreadyFamous10 -_-man i love Ye but wtf??? I can't    
    
    
    #Artists The days of the album are dead.....    
    
    
    @Erene Thanks for the follow hun    
    
    
    My biggest fear is laughing at a joke I didn't understand and someone asks me to explain it to them.    
    
    
    Long day of mixing vocals ahead. It's a love hate relationship i swear but there's nothing like an… http://instagram.com/p/hEUFpXviH0/     
    
    
    #NP #MusicMonday - Banshee (The Relapse) by @pixikill feat @hansinglish [Prod. By @DemitriMedina ]#Retweet http://bit.ly/HXZ2PG     
    
    
    @blacklight_diaz @audiointrusion be sure to follow --> @celebaccountant    
    
    
    #NP #MusicMonday - Banshee (The Relapse) by @pixikill feat @HansInglish [Prod. By @DemitriMedina] #Retweet http://bit.ly/HXZ2PG     
    
    
    Michael just now got sober lol RT @CiminoTV: @CoyTiffany @HansInglish @CreAjian I don't remember anything. #whatelseisnew    
    
    
    #RT @pixikill: New collaboration! Go check it out...its bananas. http://www.soundcloud.com/hansinglish  @hansinglish @demitrimedina pic.twitter.com/iCKzH7XL0D    
    
    
    @kanyewest @cthagod great interview guys. I get both Charlamagne & Ye's points. "Its about guaranteeing you're kids can work at the station"    
    
    
    @MishaPagano: @CreAjian @CiminoTV Cab Driver: " I don't look at every restaurant on the street while I drive. You just better pay." Lmao    
    
    
    @marisaannn man i need to come get some of that creme brulee. I'm hating on your last tweet right now    
    
    
    If u haven't heard it yet, check out my latest collaboration with @pixikill  [Prod. By @DemitriMedina] http://bit.ly/HXZ2PG  #Retweet    
    
    
    @marisaannn I'm always a sucker for good creme brulee. That's a long trip though lol.    
    
    
    #Random I wonder if @YoGottiKOM feels a certain way when white ppl start singin "My Nigga" in the club very comfortably? I nvr kno how 2feel    
    
    
    @Channtiee88 man in the cruise ships they could care less. I've seen 14yr old kids on the slot machines  lol    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving even if u don't celebrate. Luv u guys: @Katy_Batyox @Channtiee88 @melismaticdiva @BoRadley_ @cassyofLondon @HabbGaga    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving!!! Sending love ur way @AlreadyFamous10 @ChelseyFerri @CityOfPastele @SparkleXO @Geordaina @THEmrMEOLA @BChamp_    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving to some inspirational people in my life: @DamienEstreich @blacklight_diaz @DJCoopDaVillain @DjBlackOut @NinaRawz    
    
    
    