This is a must watch for fans of Final Fight and Valkyrie Profile: http://youtu.be/ce9J-J30B3o    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair does that count Planet of the Apes?    
    
    
    Nothing like a packed train going out of service right at West Oakland.    
    
    
    I'll deal with more GDC stuff tomorrow. Now to "play" some FF13.    
    
    
    @jasonbertrand I hope it really was black and white.    
    
    
    Deus Ex's triangular art style just makes me think the artists forgot to smooth out the models.    
    
    
    A few hours behind, but heading to GDC now.    
    
    
    @iocat hey I'm following you one here now. Got my GDC stuff so maybe I'll run into you.    
    
    
    I don't know what's worse, the flying machine controlled by an iphone or the human hamster ball.    
    
    
    Ah late night GDC bart. I look up and see two badass Backbone designer friends standing over me.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen I was wondering where you were. Yellow to Red some other day.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa The show just needs more NBA Jam music. Seriously that stuff is frontier epic.    
    
    
    @The_Katbot That video reminded me that Probotector was a real game and not some black market Contra knock-off    
    
    
    Damn, chapter 8 of Final Fantasy 13 went from childish to fucking dark in minutes.    
    
    
    FF13's 360 "Extras" menu is a nice touch.    
    
    
    Final boss of FF13's chapter 11 is freaking intense. It could top my list of all FF fights.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen I leave the hacked turret around a corner and lure guards into it. Also Icarus slam China.    
    
    
    Didn't really expect Final Fantasy 13's ending. First thing I did was look at the logo on the game box.    
    
    
    Wow, the new Wacom Inkling looks impressive: http://youtu.be/fXbBA1DRE84     
    
    
    For those that had problems with the third boss in Deus Ex HR, this glitch is amazing: http://youtu.be/4v1X5F0d58I     
    
    
    Nerf Heavy Lifting Augmentations http://youtu.be/0l3wOT9cSg4 ?    
    
    
    @pkollar  Could have been worse. Could have tasted like Black Eyed Peas. And I don't mean soul food.    
    
    
    @gamespite SOUND. It finally exists.    
    
    
    @nsuttner I'd be more worried if they were "on par".    
    
    
    My cab driver ranted about the President, German History, and then stopped to repair his shoe. Worth it as I got a giant sized Gears 3.    
    
    
    Want to work at GameSpot's Guides department? http://tinyurl.com/3utpfqb     
    
    
    The GameSpot News Team is also hiring http://bit.ly/nc2SBY     
    
    
    Damn you FF14, not getting in Alpha but still having a MMO craving has made me start up FF11 again.    
    
    
    Time to try Dark Souls as a meager Cleric. Hope From Software invades.    
    
    
    I wrote a little about Dark Souls, but mostly rant about Temple of Elemental Evil and GOG http://l.gamespot.com/pzEYcb     
    
    
    @pkollar @jamesmielke I gave up on both the Cleric and Sorcerer. Rocking a great sword Warrior and breezing for now.    
    
    
    @CTWatters I decided to call it a day after fighting three giants that dropped "dung pies".    
    
    
    @jasonschreier @kobunheat if it's not Ivalice related, it damaged the brand.    
    
    
    Linking a Square Enix I.D. to PlayOnline Seems more of a nuisance than actually helpful.    
    
    
    Got invaded for the first time in Dark Souls. He dropped 11000 Souls. Next time try rolling.    
    
    
    @pkollar the one in the alley? Just walk up the stairs and drop on him. Or do you fight him twice!?    
    
    
    @pkollar run up the stairs and onto the ledge. Then drop down and he'll chase you in a loop. Run fast and drop on him.    
    
    
    @pkollar aren't you strong enough that the dogs are one hit KO?    
    
    
    @pkollar time to make an Intelligence GREATSWORD.    
    
    
    @pkollar probably not, but that would kick ass. I'm still hunting for more crafting items passed +6    
    
    
    @pkollar get a weapon to +5 and you can start modify it towards elements, magic, stats and others. You can undo upgrades but loose the mats.    
    
    
    Welp, blue phantoms can't use Estus flasks. Sorry host dude.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub what's passed Ceaseless Discharge? These Capras and Tuarus are getting annoying.    
    
    
    @vanjnguyen the Parish is quicker and cheaper.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub ok, so giving up was the right choice for now. Also being summoned with little health blows.    
    
    
    @pkollar how much life do you have? Only did half a bar at 800.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk yikes I'm level 59 after that Sen's Fortress boss. Too much grinding and dying.    
    
    
    @pkollar downed an Estus+2 after every firewave then hit him twice. Won after 16 club slams.    
    
    
    @pkollar nope, think you have to beat the dragon knight and fatty first for the item.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub I could take Sen's Fortress and Anor Londo, but Demon Ruins' bosses as normal enemies is too much.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk did anyone fight the painting boss? I just walked away so I didn't lose 40k souls.    
    
    
    @pkollar any clue how to reach the catacombs black smith? I warped out after finding the princess.    
    
    
    @pkollar those skelewheels cornered me near a wall that had a hammer clanking. Assuming it's a smith.    
    
    
    @pkollar well all the Lord Soul areas are crazy. One is pitch black, while another has invisible bridges.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub I'm cringing getting to the Lord Souls. Let me know if you beat one.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub where the heck am I going after the centipede? If it's into the lava I'll be peeved.    
    
    
    @larrrk joined the Gravelords, had to kill Nito anyway.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk found any of the second embers for Normal/Divine/Fire? I can't get above +10/+5    
    
    
    @Larrrk switch in basement with the wheel skelies. I found it as a phantom. As a human I glitched the dragon with a strong attack.    
    
    
    @Gamespot Dark Souls user: "Will there be a walkthrough on how to get beards? Seriously, I couldn't find the option anywhere. Disappointed."    
    
    
    The news mainly makes want to rewatch Pirates of Silicon Valley. The Windows unboxing is so great, even if  Jobs and Gates had lines fliped.    
    
    
    @larrrk Sparky the crow in Undead Asylum will trade each moss for 4 Twinkling Titanite total.    
    
    
    @Larrrk @vanjnguyen Asylum Sparky will also trade Skull Lantern for Forest Hunter ring.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk @vanjnguyen Two bosses left.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk Finished Dark Souls. Also spoiled the ending for @vanjnguyen    
    
    
    @pkollar you're getting a little too kinky for Twitter there.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk @vanjnguyen wow I read my time wrong, it was only 68 hours long.    
    
    
    @vanjnguyen eagle shield or any tower shield blocked them really well.    
    
    
    @jamesmielke you'll love the cats and mushrooms.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle @fiddlecub conundrum: how long would Batman survive in Lordran? I'd say until Darkroot.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub if this Soul Calibur 5 rumor is true, you might have a "hidden" interest in the game http://aol.it/qAU2j0     
    
    
    @fiddlecub time to pay Oswald in the Parish 4562783 billion souls to make everything normal.    
    
    
    Dear lord, Dark Souls random face generator: http://youtu.be/-mCb8nZxg2M     
    
    
    @pkollar complexly naked sounds awesome.    
    
    
    Just ate bbq ribs on top of spaghetti. My body (and brain) is confused.    
    
    
    Random lyrics is really what Air Man's theme was missing: http://www.ocremix.org/remix/OCR01687/    
    
    
    RE5 spoilers: http://tinyurl.com/auya4b There is a link to here on there. Blue Portal?    
    
    
    Is it bad that I knew about "Innerspace" before "Fantastic Voyage"? http://tinyurl.com/d3uews    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair are the $4 fake?    
    
    
    @jasonschreier oh god the hand to hand combat was so clunky. I loved it!    
    
    
    @jasonschreier also Drake hasn't saved the world with a comb, jar of old mayo, and half an eaten sandwich.    
    
    
    @gamespite I hope he makes Wright is a masochist anyway.    
    
    
    Wow, MTV might be on track again. Beavis and Butt-Head season 8 premiered tonight. 14 years later and it's th… (cont) http://deck.ly/~qGXyA     
    
    
    @jason_wilson I can think of a few corporations that poop.    
    
    
    @smcinnis is 80% of the city comprised of cheese and/or steak?    
    
    
    @fiddlecub can they steel-cut the parfait? I'd go yogurt anyway.    
    
    
    Got to the BART station just as I realized I left my work at home. That was a fun dash back.    
    
    
    @jeffgerstmann @jamesmielke Is it bad that I hummed "Part-Time Lover" instead?    
    
    
    TF2 Scouts got nerfed again. Way to kill your last update, Valve.    
    
    
    I just played Phantasy Star Online followed by Diablo 2. Must have fallen in a timewarp.    
    
    
    @compellingpixel If those terrible photos of me came out ok, send them my way. I think it's time for a new lowbrow profile picture.    
    
    
    FFXIV dev team reorganised, more free months and the PS3 version delayed for who knows how long.    
    
    
    Updating Linkedin crap. It still linked to "My Website" which has been dead for almost a year.    
    
    
    @compellingpixel I'm pretty sure I had more like 12 red bulls. Now for a new pic goal: http://tinyurl.com/df6kf5    
    
    
    Time to see how well i can make fried chicken    
    
    
    @omgmorejade Damn right it was awesome! Here's to crazy techno anime theme songs!    
    
    
    I need the DuckTales song (Get the Money) from this show http://tinyurl.com/abq8rw    
    
    
    @Chufmoney I was disappointed that the the story did not in fact contain a Laser Wolf.    
    
    
    Starting Walking Dead thanks to @prettytony    
    
    
    Finished Book One of Walking Dead. Hope that Hershel guy gets fucked up later.    
    
    
    @twittch sexy robot vote: Guri from Shadows of the Empire. Though, no regular actress portrayed her/was an illustration.    
    
    
    @EddieMakuch typical weekend then?    
    
    
    @mikecruz_at1UP Good to know that I still use that hospital.    
    
    
    My name is Ted, and one day I'll be dead, yo, yo, yo http://tinyurl.com/227ewa    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle at least we're breaking even.    
    
    
    Touching the pilot light while cleaning the stove: not fun.    
    
    
    @omgmorejade Well, nothing enhances a dish’s aroma better than the souls of the living    
    
    
    After cleaning my apartment, it just looks barren. Had I been living in trash?    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa Your latest avatar is intense in the best way possible. Scanner battle?    
    
    
    Most of the CNET office I'd huddled in the lobby to get free cookies.    
    
    
    Starting on Omega the Unknown #1 while listening to Kraftwerk http://tinyurl.com/6699w4    
    
    
    Just finished Omega the Unknown (WTF!?) while listening to some April Wine http://tinyurl.com/bcsmmt    
    
    
    Retro/Grade info on 1up's FreeLoader blog http://tinyurl.com/d9rnzs    
    
    
    Latest episode of Lost, and then The Pitt.    
    
    
    Just got done knowing half the battle with @pkollar and @omgmorejade    
    
    
    The Old Republic's Flashpoints have amazing troll potential when you disagree and out roll your teammates during dialogue.    
    
    
    Jedi ally "We'll do this peacefully", seconds before my Commando vetos and opens the air lock.    
    
    
    A little too much Goose and Juice, but home in one piece.    
    
    
    Molyneux talk was underwhelming.    
    
    
    They're finally tearing down the crack motel...Or planning to rebuild it as a super mutant-ultra mecha crack motel.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa HP/MP restored, but you're still hungry.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen I think I should feel bad for reading "Duplicity" as "Multiplicity"    
    
    
    Walking Dead Book Three finished. The Governor is one fucked up bastard.    
    
    
    Morning walk, followed by WATCHMEN: Under the Hood    
    
    
    San Pablo, to 40th, to Adeline, to MLK Way, to 51st, to Piedmont, to W MacArthur and back may have been more than a jog.    
    
    
    Losing a hour of progress in To the Moon due to clipping bugs is annoying. Walking on pure light is kind of neat, though.    
    
    
    At&T strikes again. I'll be out of home internet service from their crud hardware.    
    
    
    Getting equipped with Day of the Tentacle and Full Throttle.    
    
    
    My Motorola has finally died...Because my BlackBerry has gone Connor MacLeod on its ass.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa Good, buy more Chevron Texaco. http://www.spoke.com/info/pCkJ8o1/JimSeid    
    
    
    @gamespite Who's like us!? Damn few!    
    
    
    @retronauts Looks like we need more lysergic acid diethylamide.    
    
    
    Riot cops at MacArthur station, ready to beat down some protesters.    
    
    
    My fridge is now equipped with 8 more pounds of ribs than it previously had    
    
    
    @aliceingameland says that if she was a man she'd be gay for girly men    
    
    
    @teanah and @aliceingameland discuss @exxy 's soulpatch dilema    
    
    
    @aliceingameland molests @capnsmak and @teanah for twitter power    
    
    
    @bigolaf knows his ebonics grammar, bitches    
    
    
    @mikecruz_at1UP nah i talked to @compellingpixel a few days ago. Or at least I think I did!    
    
    
    @mikecruz_at1up damn you and your repeated mention of Jarritos. *Drinks cool refreshing Jamaica Hibiscus flavour*    
    
    
    @Teanah I eat a lot of weird shit, but most of that is flat out vile. Ok, I'd eat the Horseshoe Sandwich.    
    
    
    @bigolaf is drinking for once    
    
    
    Thank god the low lights hide my asian glow    
    
    
    Platinum working on Metal Gear Rising? Sounds interesting. Also "REVENGEANCE".    
    
    
    When people  stop dreaming they become stagnant. Even if the goal is unrealistic or insane,  I'll still fight for it.    
    
    
    This VGA item joke is so damn terrible.    
    
    
    Seriously how can GOTY not also win on a console? #VGAsarestupidyahdayahda    
    
    
    REVENGEANCE #vgas    
    
    
    Fun times partying last night with @CesarQuintero @jasonbertrand @Chufmoney @demian_linn @nsuttner @loquats @talkingorange and others.    
    
    
    My sunday basketball debut was fun. Now to not be terrible at the game.    
    
    
    Listening to Geekbox made me start filling out an old OKcupid profile out of boredom. Possible blog later.    
    
    
    @nsuttner Great GDC blog. Hope your finger feels better. That sure was an interesting first time sunday basketball.    
    
    
    I'm a little weirded out that people have started adding my name to the various 1UP wikipedia pages.    
    
    
    New 1UP party nick name "The Red Man" (Who breaks iPhones).    
    
    
    @prettytony @omgmorejade so was there a grand maiden voyage through the lobby? Or did security continue to waggle their fingers?    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen its all about mini burgers and crab cakes.    
    
    
    Home safe from the clutches of EA thanks to @pkollar and @AmandaOchsner    
    
    
    Hell yeah, my first 1UP top story, Wheelman review http://tinyurl.com/c6greu    
    
    
    HE SHOT HIM RIGHT IN THE GROCERIES    
    
    
    @fiddlecub I'll be on Nar Shadaa, Imperial side. Name is Sulfurmustard. See you in pvp.    
    
    
    Watching Gozu. May never look at a ladle in the same way.    
    
    
    Starting konami event right- vodka and orange juice    
    
    
    Konami keeping @aliceingameland down    
    
    
    Konami Dinner with @rdb_aaa @compellingpixel @gamespite @chufmoney @teanah @bigolaf and @aliceingameland. Leone wants more salt.    
    
    
    @gamespite @aliceingameland and @chufmoney are blowing while waiting for silent hill    
    
    
    @prettytony starts the fire.    
    
    
    @compellingpixel fights going deaf    
    
    
    Awesome time partying with @omgmorejade @CesarQuintero @SeanaLyn @compellingpixel Richard Li and Shirk at @prettytony 's show. Now sleep.    
    
    
    Woke up smelling of spilled beer and Konami beef. What a night.    
    
    
    @pkollar @twittch @rdb_aaa I loves me some terrible movies. It'll be a life altering experience!    
    
    
    Oh shit bird tornado at telegraph/tamescal. Whyd I leave my good camera?    
    
    
    Landlady and construction crew are setting down new floors in a few apartments. Whole building smells like Bamboo.    
    
    
    @pkollar yeah you can try out that green coaster on my desk.    
    
    
    Taxes filed. Getting a return of $556    
    
    
    @sophiatong at least it's a balanced meal.    
    
    
    @aliceingameland try to take running slow first. Here's the route I've been doing since GDC http://tiny.cc/8z3Dp (Though Oakland is flatter)    
    
    
    @The_Grind The main thing is I don't want to wait for another screen to load. Chrono Trigger did random battles right.    
    
    
    Christmas is a time to wear clothes with tags still on them. I am large, $35, and sueded for softness.    
    
    
    Time for a traditional Jewish Christmas day dinner: Chinese food.    
    
    
    Actually, chow mein stuffed in a lobster covered with pork is the antithesis of kosher.    
    
    
    My grandma is teaching me an important holiday skill: pai gow poker.    
    
    
    Food molded to resemble something inedible typically spooks me, but I'll make an exception for a wooden log filled with ice cream.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub I love how that To the Moon topic starts discussing the grease fire.    
    
    
    @compellingpixel @aliceingameland Tazo Earl Grey and Calm over at @Mycheats . Take that Bigelow!    
    
    
    Why can't I find pictures of Final Fantasy 5 Monks!?    
    
    
    Morning remix: polysics, queen, deerhoof, falco, bush, real mccoy, rx bandits, dvda, judas priest, william shatner, men without hats...    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa must be the new office quailudes    
    
    
    You can't get to some places in Star Wars the Old Republic if you decided to be muscular or fat. Bioware hating on wide people.    
    
    
    40 minute Jawa Ballon ride ahoy. The rest of the @gamespot office is awe struck.    
    
    
    Thought process 20 minutes ago: I haven't had chicken strips in a long while. Currently: Good Lord, why did I just eat chicken strips!?    
    
    
    How did I not realize that Polysics did a Sergeant Keroro opening? Worlds colliding! http://tinyurl.com/dyk9cm    
    
    
    Tired as hell but still feel like moving. Sometimes the pain feels good.    
    
    
    After running around for three hours, I need a nap. But when I rise from my grave: Dragonball with @pkollar, @amandaochsner and @twittch    
    
    
    Reading old 1UP news is odd, especially with old glimpses of @prettytony @rdb_aaa @aliceingameland and others http://tinyurl.com/cs78xm    
    
    
    Dragonball Evolution made my brain bleed a little.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa @pkollar probably better than "Seven rings in hand, nights with feet in sand"...Which will most likely be a future blockbuster.    
    
    
    Keamy, Charlie, Van Wilder, and the guy from The Black Eyed Peas make a great BTeam.    
    
    
    Off to sf sakura fest in japantown. Never realised how many gospel churchs I live near    
    
    
    Right, ice tea at a soul food diner is gonna be full of sugar. At least I walked from Rockridge to Emeryville to get here.    
    
    
    @pkollar I ended up two-manning that fight. Saw the story play out two ways as the mission needs to be done for each Agent in the party.    
    
    
    @pkollar what's also neat is that you can talk down the boss by straight demanding him to kill you.    
    
    
    Old Republic's Voss is a planet with PvP Cantinas. Bet that Jedi Shadow was looking for a "Rest Area", not a "Rest in Peace Area".    
    
    
    @gamespite I take it that means I'm going second to last...Or talking about the series in reverse order.    
    
    
    My first time on Retronauts http://podcast.1upnetwork.net/flat/Retronauts/R042309.mp3    
    
    
    Nothing like the thieves at AT&T wasting a hour of my time and try to steal $200.    
    
    
    90 minutes to LA.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen I sat in the nose bleed seats and couldn't see what was goning on. I think I took a panther or cougar.    
    
    
    G.I. Joe Resolute is amazing! Thanks to The Geekbox for informing me about it. http://tinyurl.com/c2rfyk    
    
    
    Oh boy, the same Xbox games I saw last night, but no crazy Euro dancers climbing rocks.    
    
    
        
    
    
    E3 Monopoly Community Chest: Error in your favor, recieve Miscrosoft badge. Better get this fixed...    
    
    
    Someone needs to remind Ubisoft that E3 is for videogames, not 80's throwbacks.    
    
    
    @twittch is stealing the show! Makes me want to go sober    
    
    
    Was @bigolaf a no show? Or is his cloaking device too perfect?    
    
    
    The epic battle between @cesarquintero and @rob_bowen    
    
    
    Wow I come back to the hotel and my bathroom has a huge xbox ad in it. Go marriott.    
    
    
    Glad I'm watching the Nintendo conference from GS' booth, cuss I'm gonna dart over to South Hall ASAP.    
    
    
    I'd still enjoy if Zelda forced people to play left handed. Or shield main hand.    
    
    
    @at1uptwit travis and a can of lighter fluid. Safety hazard?    
    
    
    Epic kirby tank. Awesome    
    
    
    Yes mgs3DS    
    
    
    Tron logo looks great. http://twitpic.com/1x1oco    
    
    
    Shirk is enjoying the spicy duck. Now for "feral boar" and "30% rusk".    
    
    
    Awesome goobbues in ff14. Also classic main theme    
    
    
    Travis broke his horseshoe weiner    
    
    
    @at1uptwit term of the night for travis and shirk: "turd flauta"    
    
    
    Dragon quest 9 is great. I failed at power leveling though and dragged my warrior's corpse in an immaculate coffin.    
    
    
    Krillin is really fantastic (cheap) in Dragon Ball Raging Blast 2    
    
    
    With @lauralovescake fighting robots and commiting crimes at Sega...looking at Phantasy Star and Yakuza would be good too.    
    
    
    @at1uptwit headed home after a post Travis party- Shirk adventure.    
    
    
    The demo levels of LittleBigPlanet 2 are a bit simple, but I really want to try its level editor.    
    
    
    I know that most beat-em ups are bound to become repetitive after time, but the Yakuza 4 demo is great.    
    
    
    While I'd love to check out the 3DS, I don't have the spare hours to sit in a line.    
    
    
    Time to Test Drive Witcher Kittens at Atari    
    
    
    Just got a very unexpected intro to our Dreamcatcher footage. Models in LA will jump at any chance to get in front of the camera.    
    
    
    @pkollar  There needs to be a GS-GI pow wow/stand off.    
    
    
    @pkollar  Those extra O's are the mark of authority. Hopefully I can, my lord.    
    
    
    Confusingly ran into @gamespite while scurrying back to the hotel. You're just skin and bones, hard to recognize.    
    
    
    @iocat you should DM me the details and some how get me in    
    
    
    @iocat ill head there after my liquid "dinner"    
    
    
    Reunion with the great chums at @1up . Good luck to @gamespot 's mortal rivals.    
    
    
    Free beer the halo team. Good times.    
    
    
    Excellent talk with the LucasArts guys about monkey island and full throttle ideas. No, nothing official.    
    
    
    Just as I'm about to go back to the hotel and sleep @Area5_Coop 's @jasonbertrand and @CesarQuintero drag me back.    
    
    
    Hearing some awesome kinect info from the microsoft guys.    
    
    
    I've been informed by @LattMeone that I need to harass @smcinnis about some sweet waffles.    
    
    
    Big props to the dudes at @Foundation9 , @1up , and @Area5_Coop for making my night. A blast to see old friends.    
    
    
    Just got my first taste of Playstation Move with Sports Champions. I really need to brush up on table tennis.    
    
    
    I really hope another party makes use of the Babysitting Mama baby. One game isn't nearly enough.    
    
    
    Just got a chance to talk to Shinichi Kasahara, a producer at  Hudson behind the upcoming Lost in Shadow. He wouldn't tell me any spoilers.    
    
    
    Tearing down the @gamespot booth as E3 comes to a close.    
    
    
    Reading Larry Hama's G.I. Joe Marvel Comic #1-#155 while the Star Trek OST plays. Epic.    
    
    
    I'm eating a fried wiener, @capnsmak is choking the chicken and @bigolaf is licking donuts.    
    
    
    @kromestudios PR rep was apparently @gamespot 's old GameBoy Color editor. Crazy how things come full circle.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa Whelp, I'm mortified. Thanks.    
    
    
    @gamespite they first need to shoehorn in 3D Radical Dreamers. The text will fly off the screen!    
    
    
    I don’t know what’s worse: Finding peoples’ old abandoned MySpace pages, or their currently activate and updated MySpace pages.    
    
    
    @gamespite Onions are awesome BECAUSE they smell like BO    
    
    
    My MGS Peace Walker team just developed Tortilla Chips. That's R&D to good use.    
    
    
    Health + Mana + Konami Blood vile + Peet's Loose Leave Tea = Feeling Groovy    
    
    
    Kurtis 4, @compellingpixel 0. Did he throw the fight? http://tinyurl.com/dfdm97    
    
    
    @The_Katbot Of course you've been a great influence! But remember, we didn't meet until Game Night http://gamevideos.1up.com/video/id/23648    
    
    
    Great, 2 AT&T PVC circuits are down. Likely won't have home internet for most of the day. And with their record, maybe never.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa Yeah, Dairy Queen and Rocket Propelled Grenades are a bad combination.    
    
    
    I like how 2Wire suggests going online to their website to fix your modem.    
    
    
    The CNet  Wi-Fi yielded a Pharmacist/Nurse for the MGS Peace Walker team.    
    
    
    Nisa beef has nothing on konami beef. But nisa shrimp? Oh shit, son!    
    
    
    2013 will be the year of black and white silent films in 3D.    
    
    
    Downloading/installing Crackdown 2 now thanks to @fiddlecub and @msgamestudios    
    
    
    I don't remember everything that happened last night, but Sharkey has one nice bungalow.    
    
    
    Star Trek might be one of the best movies I've ever seen.    
    
    
    Was feeling tired running, but seeing good friends gave me my second wind. Also, humming Enterprising Young Men helped http://tiny.cc/dMoOr    
    
    
    I'll be playing Mass Effect 3 live for @gamespot on Tuesday the 6th from 12am-8am.Tune if you don't sleep!
http://www.gamespot.com/shows/gamespot-live/?event=mass_effect_3_marathon20120305 …    
    
    
    Reformatting to deal with bad spyware reunites me with the horrors of Vista.    
    
    
    Lamb chops, pot pie, crab hush puppies, and a bottle of babycham. Dinner looks good.    
    
    
    @guycocker hates on Styx. Good thing the rest of @gamespot lknows what's up.    
    
    
    I wrote why the very different games TF2 and APB both wound up costing nothing http://www.gamespot.com/features/free-for-all-why-both-a-sucess-and-a-failure-went-free-6365699 …    
    
    
    Just spent about 15 minutes battling Microsoft's 360 Content Licenses transfer.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @tommcshea I liked the part where you help Aeris stalk her estranged son.    
    
    
    I'm fine with the fact that your choices didn't really effect ME3's endings. It's not like it mattered in the last two games.    
    
    
    Alright, a real ME3 spoiler: why does Harbinger have no lines and just leave Shepard alive? Doesn't this contradict its actions from ME2?    
    
    
    Bioware needs to add scenes explaining Joker on the Normandy. Why did he leave Earth? When did he pickup the crew? Why is he using a relay?    
    
    
    No suprise that the Oakland 24 hour fitness on webster is a junk show.    
    
    
    Riot cops keeping a cop killer protest in check. Jury duty is a blast already.    
    
    
    I'd support this change to the ME3 ending http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5kqVB15Yab4 … #gamespotme3    
    
    
    @pkollar for some reason I always get Gabriel Knight confused with Broken Sword.    
    
    
    @pkollar the lask GK is about the Knights Templar, which is Broken Swords' shtick. But the first game was about voodoo.    
    
    
    I hope they call me into the jury box so I can make an ass of myself.    
    
    
    A two year old @bioware social thread that predicted ME3's ending, and hated the idea http://social.bioware.com/forum/1/topic/105/index/970146/1 …    
    
    
    @The_Katbot I don't remember that Grandia 2 boss being very hard. Roan is like crazy overpowered when he rejoins.    
    
    
    @fakeimmigrant I've been a resident of CA for 26 years. It never gets better.    
    
    
    @Synthia_GS summon feral dire kitten?    
    
    
    @ThereVanGoes this is how hoarding starts, pack rat.    
    
    
    I'm a bit disturbed that Pandora picked out The Black Mages despite me having no video game stations. FF6 theme during jury duty break.    
    
    
    I just drank 3 Vitasoys and think I got the Betis now. Damn this courthouse being next to Chinatown.    
    
    
    Breakfast of champions: grilled porkchops and bacon out of a plastic bag.    
    
    
    @smcinnis there is still enough fat to grease up a small child.    
    
    
    Adult Swim's prank of broadcasting Toonami just makes me sad that Big O didn't get a third season.    
    
    
    Overall goal of today's gym workout: to not feel bad about the cheap CAL berkeley spaghetti I'll eat later.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen @The_Katbot It still freaks me out when the towns people go from real actors to lifeless pixels.    
    
    
    Listening to Ice Cube. When Keith David intros I just assume it's Anderson from Mass Effect. Or maybe Goliath.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier One day they will merge into one super bad company. Oh God!    
    
    
    Tomatoes in clam chowder are pretty damn good. Suck on that New Englanders.    
    
    
    @TimOfLegend Shaft and Bath? Can you dig it?    
    
    
    The first Fallout is free on http://GOG.com  right now: http://www.gog.com/en/gamecard/fallout/ …    
    
    
    @gamespot I sure do hope so. Doubt it, though.    
    
    
    The Phantasy Star Online 2 Character Creator and PC Benchmark are live of Sega's Japanese site: http://download.pso2.jp/PSO2_CC.zip     
    
    
    @pkollar @timturi is it strictly lifting and eating corndogs?    
    
    
    @pkollar @timturi Got to doublefist those wieners everyday!    
    
    
    @pkollar @justinmcelroy @polygon Replace white background with rainbow or star cutout.    
    
    
    I'm not sick of ham yet, but I soon will be. 11 lbs shank for $10 obtained!    
    
    
    @sophiatong @KiMBa161 Bruce Lee was fit and he enjoyed steak. Typically raw, bleneded with eggs and milk.    
    
    
    @sophiatong Standing rib roast for one. Got it.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier this is how romance starts.    
    
    
    Legend of Grimrock obtained. Time to make a stealthy Minotaur and Lizard Wizard.    
    
    
    I probably heard this on Food Network too, but fancy European cheeses taste great from likely containing veal stomachs http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rennet     
    
    
    I swear the checkpoints in Trials Evolution have a slight brown note frequency.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier It's a harsh ocean.    
    
    
    Last bart train out of the city. But where can I get food in Berkeley/Rockridge this late? Or I could cook at 2:00 am like a peasant.    
    
    
    19 st freak show is in full circle. Everyone is loud & drunk, driver is getting surly, & a guy was hauling ass with a fist full of puppies.    
    
    
    @EddieMakuch in his case is it short for Murderhands?    
    
    
    At&t continues to be the most incompetent company. They are trying to steal $150 of my money on an account that doesn't exist.    
    
    
    @ATT is comprised completely of fucktards.    
    
    
    The fire department is rescuing my neighbors trapped in the elevator. I think I'll take the stairs for the next week.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle let's hope that Latex Babes of Estros becomes a real full game.    
    
    
    Almost a full hour on the phone with criminal organization AT&T. Nothing but run arounds and flatout lies.    
    
    
    If John Carpenter's The Thing was about cats, made out of clay. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BG33zECv8dc …    
    
    
    Takeru Kobayashi Maru: where Starfleet cadets must eat Nathan's hotdogs against impossible odds.    
    
    
    @taswell Only if it also meant slammers.    
    
    
    Sweet, Tactics  Ogre remake for PSP http://bit.ly/bDitHR    
    
    
    The line for takoyaki is absurd. I'll get BBQ ribs first.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen  We got at least three copies over here and can't install. I just want to play the Campaign, too.    
    
    
    @pkollar I just spent $1200 to PC Game again. Conclusion: pretty dead, I'd say.    
    
    
    @pkollar But dude, I'm getting a Dell.    
    
    
    Unlike most everyone else, I think I'll just wait for the digital Starcraft 2 unlock tomorrow morning. I do have a retail box, though.    
    
    
    SC2 name: GSFragSeid, friend code: 487    
    
    
    32 marines + 16 medics may have been overkill for mission 2.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen @pkollar I got to appreciate a game that stores save games as sleeping people.    
    
    
    I think SC2 installed faster on my home PC than here at the GameSpot office.    
    
    
    Well, glad I didn't get stuck in this Starcraft 2 queue. http://twitpic.com/29754c    
    
    
    Oh, Starcraft 2's built in screenshot button even picks up Fraps' FPS counter. Better turn that off.    
    
    
    Neat, a campaign mission where I can pick sides. I chose the Protoss option, though guess it means I'll have to play the mission twice.    
    
    
    Grabbed the @eastbayexpress on my way to bart. One of the articles is about @robertashley . It's like worlds colliding.    
    
    
    According to an irate e-mail CBSi and GameSpot published Dungeon Siege 3 and "The way it is your game sucks!"    
    
    
    Didn't get any "Maw of the Void" achievements due to a Battle.net error. Will now proceed to beat Starcraft 2 without having "Played" it.    
    
    
    $478 glasses. Thank god for eye insurance.    
    
    
    I'll be giving out Torchlight 2 Beta codes on Twitter later today. Tell your friends, or hoard them for yourself.    
    
    
    @NormalMode @pkollar Is Phil gonna be in the background of http://kink.com ?    
    
    
    I have 16 Torchlight 2 Beta keys. Here's two: 3AC2-D2C1-C6AF-4AF7 and 8FB0-84F1-94C2-46EB. Redeem them at https://secure.runicgames.com/signup     
    
    
    Here's the third #Torchlight2 beta code: 6B49-8E11-5E38-4E39    
    
    
    @vcharette1 it appears @Skadavr had the fastest trigger finger.    
    
    
    Use this #Torchlight2 Beta key to become a steam powered choo choo train Engineer:  6540-277F-6780-4061    
    
    
    @EyTay I Think I saw your followers go from 47 to 190, and then back down to 90.    
    
    
    The missing digits of this #Torchlight2 beta code are delicious flavors of hepatitis: 4E53-?9?8-32?4-4D45    
    
    
    I don't think you want to admit that about hep. RT @NathanChatham: @KurtisSeid Got it, thanks!    
    
    
    The missing digits of this #Torchlight2 beta code stand for the company that brought the Avengers to arcades: 94BF-55??-BAFE-439E    
    
    
    This beta key is backwards, so you’ll need to type it out instead of just copypasta: 2364-A1C4-3868-75E7    
    
    
    Both these codes have mixed-up sections, but if you solve either you’ll have TWO keys: 82C1-0FD4-8163-4A6B | 6E6E-17AA-EE9E-4A7B    
    
    
    Nothing creative about these next two Torchlight 2 Beta keys. Just take 'em: 5B20-7764-5930-4D48 and 81BF-3D61-1CA7-43E4.    
    
    
    @CTWatters Is it the one docked in Alameda harbor?    
    
    
    @Vinkel176 Thanks for the offer, but I'm already in!    
    
    
    Now for an infuriating one, 14 digits of this beta key are scrambled (Only the first 0 and 3 are in the right place): 0011-2234-489B-BDDE    
    
    
    Alright that last puzzle was absurd, so here's a free Torchlight 2 beta key: C40F-B6F2-C662-40C8    
    
    
    These lost digits are for the Final Fantasy game that informed me that I had been playing for MORE than 200 days: ??36-E817-687B-41B3    
    
    
    The missing digits of this #Torchlight2 beta key are how old I’ll be tomorrow (Hint: I’m not 80): 45C8-BF9B-AB0?-44?E    
    
    
    Surprise fools. #Torchlight2 Beta key for the insomniacs and duders in shit timezones: C7F4-4AF4-9758-4F56    
    
    
    I'll be streaming old diablo games until midnight: http://www.gamespot.com/shows/gamespot-live/?event=diablo_live_marathon20120514 …    
    
    
    Also we are giving out six free copies of Diablo 3 during this stream.    
    
    
    Racing against EBMUD, BART, OPD, Clorox, and Kaiser in Oakland's Jack London Square  Saturday morning.    
    
    
    Diablo 317002: Error of Destruction    
    
    
    GameSpot is streaming old Metal Gear games, and I'll be joining in for MGS3 (maybe MGS2 as well) http://www.gamespot.com/shows/gamespot-live/?event=mgs_vghm_051612 …    
    
    
    @jasonschreier Should have gone Monk. And if you did, what's wrong with you?    
    
    
    Diablo 3's version of the cow level: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-BgOeK72jSs&feature=related …    
    
    
    Why did Dragons Dogma's English theme song retool lines about television and phone calls? It could probably work in a high fantasy setting.    
    
    
    I'll be streaming classic Zelda games along with @TomMcShea at 11 am PST: http://www.gamespot.com/shows/gamespot-live/?event=zelda_live_marathon20120523 …    
    
    
    I'm soaked and groady after racing in Jack London's Paddle for Life fund raiser www.paddleforlife.org    
    
    
    @fakeimmigrant I like to think of him as the Red White and Blue Goblin.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle at least you're about relevant topics. Most of my tweets will be about spaghetti.    
    
    
    I might have played Diablo 3 some more if my account didn't get hacked. Guess I'll try Nightmare with no equipment or money.    
    
    
    @EyTay I'm trying the recovering thing first. Besides, it's a pretty boring game.    
    
    
    @smcinnis the secret is that's what @Larrrk 's desk is like all the time.    
    
    
    Laundry, dishes, packing, laser tag. Sounds like standard E3 prep.    
    
    
    A large group of 5 year olds just screamed about much they love Call of Duty.    
    
    
    This Old Spaghetti [from a] Factory will fuel me for the rest of my packing.    
    
    
    Now to eat all the perishable food in my fridge. Milk-Apple Sauce-Teriyaki Chicken Wings are go.    
    
    
    The plane has landed. I'm wearing too many layers and kind of deaf.    
    
    
    @smcinnis @Synthia_GS you are now fold out soulmates.    
    
    
    E3 is getting in the way of Game of Thrones and Mad Men. Time to amend this problem.    
    
    
    @randolphramsay does that stage conduct lightning?    
    
    
    So does Resident Evil 6 not have Kinect support? I wanted to order Chris Redfield to punch boulders.    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair It's Games Pote 3, thank you very much.    
    
    
    They probably made Gears 4 a prequel so they won't have to deal with Baird's beard. It would have been beefy and made of bees.    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair just had a Canadian melt down.    
    
    
    @pkollar if a sport has feet, it's football. See: kick boxing.    
    
    
    Need for Speed: Prodigy. Most importantly it's about an old web service.    
    
    
    @randolphramsay Someone with rabies?    
    
    
    Ubisoft trainwreck is go!    
    
    
    Tigers, tits, explosions, TV fire traps, and bows. Ubisoft is doing some mondo shit with Far Cry 3    
    
    
    @guycocker It's the circle of life.    
    
    
    And so Ubisoft closes on a shit burger called Shootmania.    
    
    
    Watch Dogs looks pretty badass. I love the multiplayer idea of each person taking a different part in the story.    
    
    
    Wait, the Vita now includes free Crystal Light? Lemonade sounds great.    
    
    
    Sony: "Children today are stupid and don't understand books."    
    
    
    @fiddlecub teach your kids how to blast off faces with the power of books.    
    
    
    @EddieMakuch I don't recommend eating the wraps at E3, though. #GamespotE3    
    
    
    Got around to watching Mad Men. HOLY SHIT. And it's not even the season finale.    
    
    
    So does the Wii U have games? #GameSpote3    
    
    
    Hell yeah we can grief new friends over Super Mario Wii U..    
    
    
    Of course P3 and P4 get shafted with Toads. #GameSpotE3    
    
    
    Oh but P5 gets to be the touchscreen bitch #GameSpotE3    
    
    
    I hope Scribblenauts Unlimited is as tedious as the last game.    
    
    
    @gamespite It's good to hate kids, though.    
    
    
    Reggie is self aware! #GameSpotE3    
    
    
    Wii U: Play games with your ass. #GameSpotE3    
    
    
    @fakeimmigrant I don't know, if it's like Wii Fit we might be playing with our anuses.    
    
    
    @marcowhereru @gamespot evolving...into epic yarn!?!?!    
    
    
    Is this Lego Watch Dogs? #GameSpotE3    
    
    
    Well nintendo is dead. Good Night #E3    
    
    
    Played some Crysis 3, heard the crazy plot. Writing my impressions now #GameSpotE3    
    
    
    Took a break for dinner, but got around to writting my impressions of Crysis 3 http://e3.gamespot.com/story/6380791/crysis-3-doesnt-reinvent-the-wheel-nor-will-it-probably-need-to …    
    
    
    @JamieRG91 It would seem that you need to do research on something called "humor", fucktard.    
    
    
    Played the second episode of The Walking Dead game. Wrote some words
http://e3.gamespot.com/story/6381337/the-walking-dead-episode-2-gets-extra-crispy-extra-spicy …    
    
    
    Reggie is checking out Dust 514 over at the Playstation 3 booth. He looks stern even on the show room floor.    
    
    
    My memory is a bit hazy now, but I think @PCBrown and I spent 15 minutes explaining how Merican school grades work to @DanChiappini    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle @TomMcShea Those are some strong friendships.    
    
    
    My personal top 5 games of E3 2012: Project P-100, Watch Dogs, Dust 514, The Walking Dead Episode 2, Assassin's Creed 3    
    
    
    Reading about Mad Men, listening to Super Castlevania 4 music, drinking tea with cream. This morning is odd.    
    
    
    @MrToffee Next time get lamb chops.    
    
    
    Woke up in LA, hopped on a plane to NorCal, dropped off bags at home, watched Prometheus IMAX 3D in a packed theatre, now for sleep.    
    
    
    I've been stuck in BART limbo for almost an hour, and it's gonna get worse.    
    
    
    I should have stayed at home when the bay bridge traffic clogged all the way to Rockridge.    
    
    
    It took 2 hours to get to the office. For my coworkers that decided to stay home, you made the right choice.    
    
    
    Hell yeah, Worlds of Ultima 1 and 2 are free on http://GOG.com : http://www.gog.com/news/free_releases_worlds_of_ultima_1_2 …    
    
    
    This Gary's Mod riff on EA's business model is amazing http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e-LE0ycgkBQ …    
    
    
    GameSpot's Civ 5 Expansion review has been on YouTube for less than a hour and it's already become a religious debate http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jjEpgCGWK98&list …    
    
    
    Went to Oddball Films last night http://www.oddballfilm.com/  The Archer theme was playing during a Delta Airlines promo http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lVyMiYYyiWs&feature=fvwrel …    
    
    
    10 year old PS2 game? 2013 expansion (not on PS2): http://www.playonline.com/ff11us/adoulin/index.html …    
    
    
    Valve's Source Filmmaker looks amazing http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zri1c_If6Ic …    
    
    
    @Larrrk That is a very articulate way to talk about pornography.    
    
    
    This Casio keyboard demo is incredibly nostalgic. I also never noticed that it changed instruments on each verse http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rHlRmKAPFt0 …    
    
    
    Screw civil service. At least the Hayward juror room is less of a cluisterfuck than Oakland.    
    
    
    Judge: half of you give me excuses why you shouldn't be on the jury. The rest of you do nothing for 2 1/2 hours.    
    
    
    Just ordered a LG Nitro HD. All you smart phone nerds can harass me about how good or bad this idea was.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle I think this con is for the funnies section of the local pap. Li'l Abner, Dick Tracy, and the like.    
    
    
    Dark Souls PC comes out next month. Time to watch this again and again http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T3d94pxVRQU&feature=related …    
    
    
    Oh great, there is a Steam Summer Sale. Time to waste a bunch of money http://store.steampowered.com/     
    
    
    AT&T remains a terrible company. They deactivated my old BlackBerry without activating my new Nitro. I have no phone for who knows how long.    
    
    
    The Mass Effect "Anime" looks terrible http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Af6tA206Y6Q&feature=player_embedded …    
    
    
    It took a hour at the AT&T store (and also a customer rep dude that was way too friendly), but it appears my phone is working.    
    
    
    @pkollar robot limbs!    
    
    
    SFMOMA has some batshit insane exhibits. I love it!    
    
    
    It's my last day with cbs. Thanks to everyone for a great two+ years!    
    
    
    Watching Bruce Lee's Fists of Fury and Jet Li's Fist of Legend back-to-back. Now I just need that crappy Jackie Chan version.    
    
    
    Ten hours into my day and only now do I realize my socks are mismatched.    
    
    
    Oakland Obama protest. pic.twitter.com/arFtducE    
    
    
    California Extreme in Santa Clara is this weekend. A huge amount of old arcade games for a flat fee http://www.caextreme.org/     
    
    
    Ah California Extreme, it's as if all the fat of Bakersfield was compressed into a single convention hall.    
    
    
    My best pinball score of the day. pic.twitter.com/SHLIaFc1    
    
    
    Worst thing in Final Fantasy 14 so far are quests that are not won by combat or fetching items, but by emoting randomly.    
    
    
    Got my toenails sliced off at Kaiser. Time to eat unagi at Geta while I'm nearby.    
    
    
    I'm not sure if I'm sleepy at 4:30pm or if PGA golf is just the most boring shit known to man.    
    
    
    Though John Daly has pants that would blind God.    
    
    
    My bad cholesterol is 30 points lower than reccomended for healthy people. Now I'll break even if I ever get heart problems.    
    
    
    Just installed the "new" AIM. This is a violation on the eyes.    
    
    
    This Milton and Smalls "Arabian Night'' white Russian tastes like fruity pebbles.    
    
    
    Bart is delayed and hot as hell. At least it may keep my rice warm.    
    
    
    Pork pineapple Risotto cooking in cast iron. pic.twitter.com/hIg0x8cq    
    
    
    For transport across the bay pic.twitter.com/HP5HBii2    
    
    
    @fiddlecub the main thing is that you should start depraved.    
    
    
    I just added fried eggs to leftover Risotto and it exponentially improved the flavors of both. Crazy.    
    
    
    KOTOR 2 is live on Steam: http://store.steampowered.com/app/208580/     
    
    
    Thank you gringo bandito. pic.twitter.com/oDqG68qq    
    
    
    @tacticsogregame has some "updated" translations I really don't care for. "Walister"? "Galgastani"!? Well, War of the Lions did the same...    
    
    
    @The_Katbot I feel bad for people who weren't already into RPGs by the SNES or even NES era.    
    
    
    @The_Katbot What!? FF4 and CT already had me hooked. At least once I realized I could heal my party...    
    
    
    @The_Katbot I played the hell out of Falcom PC games back then too. Though, Y's and Xanadu were more action RPGs.    
    
    
    Bad close captions are great: the Republican debate with "TDiane Swerenson" and "George Stefonopolis".    
    
    
    @gamespite it better be from a box.    
    
    
    @iocat grats on a new gig. Gonna have to harass you till you announce where.    
    
    
    Bart police will not allow the doors to open "for safety".    
    
    
    I'm drinking wine infused with garlic. It could use less grapes and more cloves.    
    
    
    Prawn garlic Bacon chili pasta from the Stinking Rose. pic.twitter.com/wFhhkLJm    
    
    
    @EpicNameBro saw your DkS easy mode video. They could make some items assessable sooner (Soapstones, Smithbox) without touching combat.    
    
    
    Nachos are too real at this time of night. Also who puts lettuce on this?!    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle I hope its "Cyron Hinids".    
    
    
    Hey people on Meetup, stop taking 2 (4 total) limited rsvp spots for two different events at the same time.    
    
    
    Bread stuffing is just a means to consume large amounts of gizzards.    
    
    
    The best Dark Souls PvP is when you pretend to be a NPC http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FI3T-xSUnVE&feature=plcp …    
    
    
    Waiting on the 21 muni. The streets reek of piss and the air is scented with weed. Perfect for a San Francisco picnic.    
    
    
    Buffets will be the death of me. But at least i'll go out with cheesecake.    
    
    
    Chili fries make my problems melt away.    
    
    
    @pkollar amazon shipped my copy already. No turning back now.    
    
    
    Using a comma instead of a period can be a pretty bad typo. But I'd gladly accept  2,500,000 worth of CBS stock into my 401k.    
    
    
    @jamesmielke sounds like a metaphor for life in general. Just keep paying to survive.    
    
    
    @pkollar made my ffxiv character on kashuan. May switch to selbina if my ffxi ls goes there.    
    
    
    Taking a break from playing a busted debug game by playing the working retail version of exact same game.    
    
    
    Isn't an Arnold Palmer meant to be half and half, instead of lemonade splashed with tea?    
    
    
    On that note I want to watch that ESPN documentary that focuses more on the drink than the golf player.    
    
    
    Nothing as humbling as when depression forms into acceptance.    
    
    
    China's tourism board should use Jeff Daniels' soundbite "I'm from the future, go to China."    
    
    
    Is something wrong with my phone? No. It's just Rob Base and DJ E-Z Rock.    
    
    
    Banana cream whey is the new Mountain Dew.    
    
    
    @pkollar dude, you get stronger by making orange juice in a frying pan. Brilliant.    
    
    
    Sometimes I wish I wasn't so content and could remember what the fuck sadness really feels like.    
    
    
    @pkollar are you saying its 3 hours long?    
    
    
    Why is gangnam style even on CNN? Must be a slow news day.    
    
    
    Got a craving for OB town chicken but they don't open for another 2 hours. I might actually wait that long.    
    
    
    Jwipo tastes good but it's a pain to eat. Who would think to fry jerky?    
    
    
    @EpicNameBro I've gotten so used to mid-rolling (and fat rolling) that I can't handle the speed of fast movement.    
    
    
    @EpicNameBro The first build I beat DkS with was 40 strength, Large Club, Full Stone Knight Set & Eagle Shield. Sometimes I couldn't roll.    
    
    
    So I did end up going to OB Town. If you're in Berkeley they have an absurd happy deal; four huge dishes at $20 before 7pm    
    
    
    This Snoop Dog HotPockets ad is beyond surreal http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qr22iCGxDBo …    
    
    
    Downloading games to my PSP keeps failing. I think this was a ploy by Sony to make me download Media Go.    
    
    
    Why does a British appliance commercial have the music to Robocop on Gameboy? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YUVs7vXNZiw …    
    
    
    Another great bit by Aziz Ansari http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WFR4PPxp2z8 …    
    
    
    I ate barbequed Bacon and deep fried grits for dinner; I'm good to skip the assortment of pie, thanks.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @fiddlecub ffxiv has a huge level spike compared to ffxi. On average you'd be 6 levels higher in xi from xiv's skill point totals.    
    
    
    The makeup in Cloud Atlas is insane. I wouldn't have guessed who Huge Grant was playing at times.    
    
    
    Damn these Richmond harlots clogging the Pittsburgh/Baypoint. Just learn to swim or wait for a weekday morning.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub pepperoni is kind of grossly processed. Next time get pizza with a ribeye steak on top.    
    
    
    Hello fellow tenants, when there are only two washing machines STOP doing 4+ loads at once.    
    
    
    Got to wonder if people are in costume before Halloween or just have terrible fashion sense.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle the main thing to reflect on is that Hugo Weaving is always evil.    
    
    
    @TomMcShea NG+, see everything you didn't do before.    
    
    
    Les Mis makes for interesting weight lifting music. Maybe a little too appropriate.    
    
    
    A 24 hour fitness locker is an interesting place to temporarily store spare ribs.    
    
    
    Screw this Democrat vs Republican non-sense. I'll continue to "throw my vote away" on Green and Libertarian as I please.    
    
    
    Spotify radio keeps playing the same song every 30 minutes. At least it's excellent at simulating a real radio station.    
    
    
    The first episode the the Battlestar Galactica prequel is out http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pT79x4qM4FE&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Final Fantasy 14 Online shutdown for 2-4 months. Ending/Trailer for the re-release http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sqL3-n2-3J4 …    
    
    
    It's just not Bond without product placement http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t8aSIjSQzAo …    
    
    
    Twinkies are dead, Hostess files Chapter 11 http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052970204257504577154402317896574.html …    
    
    
    PBS Inventors: The coffin that screws into the ground. Also comes in clear resin so you can "wave goodbye" http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=CBtRSOm7gpY …    
    
    
    Sega brings together its classics such as TF2, Wreck-It Ralph and Danica Patrick in HotWheels (turn off annotations) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EFAJ-G1h2UE&hd=1 …    
    
    
    Picky eaters at restaurants where the servers don't have great English are the worst.    
    
    
    An amazing comic generator http://pandyland.net/random/?comicid=627513209 …    
    
    
    @EvilSharkey Wow, that really blows man. What happened?    
    
    
    @pkollar Looks like a retail 360 for sure.    
    
    
    11 pounds of Ham, 13 pounds of Turkey. Hopefully enough for a meal or two.    
    
    
    If you're a fan of Mega Man or Doom you should try out Mega Man 8-bit Deathmatch: http://bit.ly/cvfDzt    
    
    
    @pkollar @gamespite If Game Informer counted, GameSpot is so indy that we never even printed a zine in real meat space.    
    
    
    @twittch @pkollar try replacing it with something else. Like chewing gum or crack cocaine.    
    
    
    Lack of content prompts Square Enix to extend FFXIV's free trial period; http://bit.ly/bQ6LNo    
    
    
    An American branch of a Spanish company is closed for Dia de la Constitucion. Interesting to know.    
    
    
    Old crazy man on Shattuck yelling about 1950s ice cream and how we should boycott it.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub did you get Shadow? Better do it again if you don't have Shadow.    
    
    
    Played the BSG board game. Cylons Adama and I (Tyrol) kept Roslin in the brig, tricked Starbuck & stranded Galactica with no fuel.    
    
    
    The Hobbit in 48 FPM http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ao8NOsYwyYI …    
    
    
    Touhou Project meets Beastie Boys!? http://viotex.matrix.jp/muzik/saigetsu.mp3    
    
    
    These hops look like a throw pillow. pic.twitter.com/tpjWFFYf    
    
    
    In an attempt to light fireworks, the guests have lit the lawn on fire.    
    
    
    An old women just gave a couple misinformation and caused them to miss their transfer point.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen aren't they both about 'Fookin prawns?'    
    
    
    @pkollar did you not play witch hunt or leliana's song? Those have even worse members.    
    
    
    I'm still hammering out all the little details, but my new job is sending me to Spain right away.    
    
    
    I've been playing @GuildWars2 a bunch lately. I'm on Fort Aspenwood with @Spirit_of_Faith [HOPE]. Crystal Desert can suck it.    
    
    
    My opinion of Fable 3 just greatly improved. It's the ultimate griefing multiplayer when you can jump into a random game and ruin someone.    
    
    
    @The_Katbot it straight up hurts my eyes looking at it.    
    
    
    Looks like I'll be a bit north of Dreta de l'Eixample. The info states "it is a safe and quite neighbourhood".    
    
    
    Hopefully all this turkey and bread will knock me out. Flying United economy sucks.    
    
    
    "Why is it painted white everywhere?" "Oh, that's snow."    
    
    
    I want to just sleep eat and bathe for the rest of time.    
    
    
    Been stuck on BART for nearly a hour. Way to not prepare for this Giants horse shit, transit system.    
    
    
    The office meditation room. pic.twitter.com/nbwSwOOw    
    
    
    Mint soap is insane. My whole body feels winter fresh.    
    
    
    Why is everyone scheduling BBQs and Super Bowl parties at 10pm!?...Oh right, time zone difference.    
    
    
    View from the 16th floor break room. pic.twitter.com/Wema7yrV    
    
    
    @fiddlecub use the free weights over the machines. They are way more efficient.    
    
    
    @sophiatong some kind of interpreted dance?    
    
    
    Had a -12°C cocktail over at Icebarcelona http://WWW.Icebarcelona.com  pic.twitter.com/pA2YO2SJ    
    
    
    All day meetings means my breakfast is fistfuls of Frit Ravich.    
    
    
    @pkollar you telling me to ignore them wants me look harder.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle I was almosting expecting a moment out of Un Chien Andalou.    
    
    
    United is still fucking terrible. Gonna arrive back in San Francisco 5 hours behind and an extra connecting flight.    
    
    
    Yup 49ers are officially dead.    
    
    
    Blackout time out. 49ers got desperate.    
    
    
    Ironmangotofacebookplease    
    
    
    The Super Bowl party I'm at is arguing about Star Trek.    
    
    
    Great Jack in the Box Super Bowl ad.    
    
    
    Alright better not go into San Fran for a bit.    
    
    
    6 cookies and milk was a bad idea.    
    
    
    @Larrrk do you mean I should have gone to 8?    
    
    
    @Larrrk cookies are always personal. Unless you're one of THOSE guys.    
    
    
    @Larrrk sure you can have them. I could use a nap anyway.    
    
    
    @TomMcShea is it about two naked eight year olds who are married?    
    
    
    Eastbay residents/workers help support @OaklandBakes and @KitchenerOak by eating a bunch of free stuff wednesday http://www.facebook.com/events/429296863816626/ …    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair sorry for living under a rock but only now -4 months late- did I realize that you fled the country.    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair don't worry. Now you can FedEx me hot poutine and bagged milk.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub which 24 hour fitness do you go to? I'm either at the California St or Van Ness big ones, or the Berkeley one on weekends.    
    
    
    Great the transbay is on time for once...time to hustle to BART instead.    
    
    
    Gotta love when a company/venue doesn't give you their area code and it isn't an obvious local one.    
    
    
    Play queue: Warren G, Cardigans, Donald Fagen, Kamelot, Lionel Richie+Tim McGraw, Robyn, Strokes, Link 80, Nat King Cole. Wtf mix is that?    
    
    
    I do appreciate Christopher Cross followed by Kris Kross, though.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle only cents to the uh. Whus are still a premium.    
    
    
    Cyndi Laupher is the way to rock out an evening. pic.twitter.com/G4xBL1yw    
    
    
    Bell Biv Devoe looks different than I remember. pic.twitter.com/Z1Gse3Vc    
    
    
    REO Speedwagon ruins the night again.    
    
    
    I reviewed Potatoman Seeks the Troof. Go download and play it! …http://potatoman-seeks-the-troof.en.softonic.com/     
    
    
    Like exploring? I wrote a review for an awesome game called Proteus http://proteus.en.softonic.com/     
    
    
    Time to introduce some San Francisco geeks to Estrella Damm.    
    
    
    @vaderbabe87 I said San Francisco. Maybe if they don't drink it all or there is a place that sells it east of the tunnel.    
    
    
    My Spotify is going for all the good years: Smashing Pumpkins (1979), Van Halen (1984), Prince (1999)    
    
    
    Note to self: braised soda smells like corn syrup.    
    
    
    In my professional and mature opionion the PS4 controller looks goofy.    
    
    
    Is the PS4 backwards compatible!? Screw new features, I'm just going to use it to play Final Fantasy Tactics.    
    
    
    @TheMoronMike @McBiggitty @TheAlanJohnson @littleman00 I probably would have been some kind of hippie otherwise. Gross.    
    
    
    #1upmemories getting the shake down from @pkollar @nsuttner and @ShaneWatch on my very first 1UP FM podcast.    
    
    
    #1upmemories My first week was Halloween. I just assumed that how the staff always dressed.    
    
    
    #1upmemories @gamespite upgrades from desk to storage closet.    
    
    
    Main street is just filled with parked lunar new year parade floats.    
    
    
    @gamespite @jasonschreier @jason_wilson They better just deploy a FF7 remake now. I can't think of what else can help them at all.    
    
    
    If you use Chrome you should install the Great Suspender extension and save lots of memory: http://the-great-suspender.en.softonic.com/     
    
    
    @fiddlecub Heartless name: Nexvik Doxnarv    
    
    
    @jasonschreier I spent the last week playing PS1 games. I don't think I'm hyped for new releases.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier at least that's somewhat recent. I'm going through Front Mission 3 and Final Fantasy Tactics for like the tenth time.    
    
    
    @Pseudobread I refuse to believe that's a real thing. Nope. Never.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub Galerians claimed 50 hours of gameplay, but it was like a 6 hour survival horror http://i2.listal.com/image/1109884/600full-galerians-cover.jpg …    
    
    
    I spent almost a hour trying to remember a Royksopp song, only to realize it was actually Show Me by Mint Royale. Close enough.    
    
    
    If you are using Windows 8 try OblyTile to make custom tiles http://oblytile.en.softonic.com/     
    
    
    I love that most of my film friends have pure green avatars, while most of my video game friends have creative jokey green avatars.    
    
    
    @MintRoyale I assumed they really love plugs in Norway.    
    
    
    This is the first time ive ordered English Breakfast and they give me hot frothed cappuccino milk on the side.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub That fast even?    
    
    
    Can't find detachable gym pant leg? Time for shorts over Dockers.    
    
    
    Middle aged couple on the BART just quoted Gurren Lagann. What the!?    
    
    
    @gamespite Even better if it was actually a Thin Mint.    
    
    
    @The_Katbot I hope the main product was the jerky.    
    
    
    @fakeimmigrant Blasphemy.    
    
    
    There is something mesmerizing about watching a front loader toss around traffic barriers like beach balls.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle @fiddlecub I was 2 when that show ended.    
    
    
    @Larrrk It's short for Carlwinslow.    
    
    
    Trying to figure out if a young lady dyed her hair grey, or if an old woman just looks great.    
    
    
    Stand Back by Stevie Knicks sounds like it's from NBA Jam TE.    
    
    
    Got Windows 8 and want to edit some photos? In this blog I teach you how to use Aviary Photo Editor http://onsoftware.en.softonic.com/how-to-use-aviary-photo-editor-for-windows-8 …    
    
    
    @pkollar taxes do make me think about horrible ways to die.    
    
    
    Ok Marvel...So Peter Parker is dead and now a reformed Dr Octopus is Spider-Man in Parker's body? Whuuu!?    
    
    
    Stumbled into a drag queen bachelorette party at AsiaSF.    
    
    
    A night is pretty successful when the thought "I'm exhausted" quickly leads to "I need fried chicken".    
    
    
    @MikeJMika let me clarify: I didn't know there was a bachelorette party. The drag queens were supposed to be for everyone.    
    
    
    "The reason you are no longer working for the above employer is: STILL WORKING FOR EMPLOYER"    
    
    
    Time to be in the b-roll on a Spanish show about my employer.    
    
    
    @Larrrk see your problem is you're eating wings by themselves. Real men eat the whole bird as a snack.    
    
    
    @Larrrk when it's cooked well enough it debones itself.    
    
    
    @McBiggitty The main thing I want to know about Dark Souls 2 is if the Guilty Still Pay the Price. I want to keep invading invaders.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier Top or bottom? Left or right? Candy shell or creamy center?    
    
    
    Painkillers + cough medicine + inhaler + Mimosas will make this day disorienting.    
    
    
    Softonic NL interviewed the makers of Candy Crush Saga (I localized it to EN): http://onsoftware.en.softonic.com/candy-crush-saga-publisher-talks-sweet-success …    
    
    
    Twitter music is out and it "suggested" this song. Hmmm... #NowPlaying @neontrees - Everybody Talks ♪ https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/everybody-talks/id513802949?i=513803062&uo=4 …    
    
    
    Oblivion was "satisfying". I wasn't displeased, nor was I blown away. It's like a filling meal that lacks zest.    
    
    
    @pkollar when? Where? How!?    
    
    
    Mad Men, Game of Thrones, and This American Life in my queue? From WBEZ Chicago I'm Peggy Olson.and Winter is coming.    
    
    
    Misread "Community Yoga" as "Community Yogurt". I was confused and excited.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier I'm more interested in the argument about the dwarf. Has there been a sexualized male character that isn't a power fantasy?    
    
    
    @iocat Why not just log into LIVE? DLC serials only matter when you're off line.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa but it's like a calling card. Let's one know "Barnholt is in the wind."    
    
    
    @Larrrk putting it between cookies will make it a true lunch sandwich.    
    
    
    Lunch consisted of BBQ ribs and sweet potato pie at Delancy Street Restaurant. Time to not eat anything else for the rest of the day.    
    
    
    A few drinks, some carnitas, a donut, and cookies - pertfect gym fuel.    
    
    
    Me logging into Instagram is just for a Softonic "How To" blog post. I'll be damned if I use it for real.    
    
    
    1985 (born), 1991, 1996, 2002, and 2013 - all of my birth/mother's days. Means my siblings get to pickup the check tonight.    
    
    
    I've added hamburger to fried rice and am contemplating Cheddar cheese too. I may have gone too far in some places.    
    
    
    @pkollar but I don't have anything else to contribute to society!    
    
    
    Large amounts of Mexican food (and booze) keeps motivating me to go to the gym.    
    
    
    I know the bottle is designed to prevent this, but one day I'll probably swallow a Ramune marble.    
    
    
    Pen and paper RPGing: Enlarged, enraged level 2 Barbarian (25 strength), 24 damage in a full round attack against the final boss.    
    
    
    @Joygirl007 I haven't talked to you in a few years, but could you dm me your email/contact info?    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @hbearlover my eyes just go to the gray hairs.    
    
    
    @E3HamDuet I don't miss the slimy sandwich, mealy apple, or warm cheese. Wasnt there a "classic" roast beef for a few years?    
    
    
    Dead Rising 3: AW MAN, AW CRAP, WINDOWS ERROR SOUND    
    
    
    Booing on the set of MS Conference.    
    
    
    A preview of Gameloft's E3 lineup: http://features.en.softonic.com/e3-2013-gamelofts-mobile-games-lineup …    
    
    
    Even when I don't mean to, I occasionlly keep typing the Xbox One as "Xbone". It's just second nature.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub I recall chugging a whole bottle of Dayquil and pissing a lot last year. Actually, that might have been every E3.    
    
    
    iOS 7: Everything you need to know http://features.en.softonic.com/ios-7-everything-you-need-to-know …    
    
    
    I played around with the iOS 7 beta http://features.en.softonic.com/hands-on-with-ios-7-beta …    
    
    
    @LaDigitalDame @CTWatters I feel there is a Vine coming soon.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier complete with disc scratches and notes in the back of the manual.    
    
    
    @jennatar @pattheflip I thankfully don't neg, instead I just insult people by my general presence.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub sounds like voyeurism.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle why get coffee around 7? It's booze time.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle that's why you ask people "want to grab a cup of whiskey?"    
    
    
    Hamburger, cheddar, fried eggs, Grammy Smith apples, corn tortilla chips. Not a bad combination. pic.twitter.com/tZNL5FWAZI    
    
    
    Saturday: I still got six days to pack, I'll take my time. Thursday: Oh shit, why didn't I pack yet!?    
    
    
    @fiddlecub permanent body paint.    
    
    
    Brunch buffet will be the death of me.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle @EdmondTran I mainly want to know if the California characters will be a major part, or if its like being written out.    
    
    
    4th of July from America's heartland: Europe. Free damm?    
    
    
    @chr1sa @gilberttangjr a few days late, but thanks for checking out my article.    
    
    
    Celebrate July 4th, Dark Souls PC style http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JrLMzCehLV8 …    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle you'll have fond memories of how tame S2 is if you manage to watch how much grimmer S3 gets.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier even better if it was also available on PS2.    
    
    
    A Santa like old man is watching K-on! On his iPhone.    
    
    
    I believe I've entered the Mission when I see a guy with a parrot and a bunch of baguettes.    
    
    
    Police "situation" on Bart probably means me standing for another 15 minutes.    
    
    
    Some really neat content cut from Dark Souls http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5RkLstvjmUk …    
    
    
    My quest for spicy stew has surprising resulted in vegeterian meals all day. Guess it makes up for eating two steaks yesterday.    
    
    
    Line for the men's locker? Wtf..    
    
    
    @fiddlecub a hot mess?    
    
    
    Argh adablargh long Dolores Park bathroom lines.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub started watching your FF14 Twitch stream. Did you not import your 1.0 character? I started as a level 30 PUG right away.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub I guess it did kind of cheapen things being able to do all the low level content with a mount, retainer, and overpowered gear.    
    
    
    Sweet, Apple is finally releasing the Gameboy Color.    
    
    
    Infinity Blade 3 on Apple Super Gameboy Color Gold with Blast Processing.    
    
    
    @pkollar as a Bard I am constantly switching dps, support, flipping switches, and kiting adds (when the tank is bad).    
    
    
    Too much unagi.. but not nearly enough tamago!    
    
    
    @pkollar wait how is your warrior new? Did you grind 5 levels real quick or were you a MRD past 30?    
    
    
    @pkollar ah. LNC was 15 and PUG was 30 when I got monk and bard. Go 1.0 grinding.    
    
    
    @jasonventer yes means no and no means banana.    
    
    
    @pkollar @jaykaypea MAGNETS.    
    
    
    The world is a vampire.    
    
    
    @pkollar where's the Realm Reborn review, Lebowski? We want that review, Lebowski. Bunny said you were good for it.    
    
    
    @pkollar wondering how much of the PS3 version you played. Fates are awful as it loads PCs/pets before mobs - who often spawn dead.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @fiddlecub curious if you got to Titan or Qarn. Those really upped the craziness of combat.    
    
    
    Wow, that's quite a start to making Gameling games. Guess I'm getting this Game Dev Tycoon ting. pic.twitter.com/vuSZJTB5QW    
    
    
    I really need to stop leaving my best umbrella at the office. Hello flimsy hooded raincoat!    
    
    
    A great in-depth article by @jasonschreier about the death of LucasArts http://kotaku.com/how-lucasarts-fell-apart-1401731043 …    
    
    
    Cool video about indie games going mainstream featuring my old boss @iocat http://www.polygon.com/2013/10/4/4768148/the-next-generation-of-indies …    
    
    
    I should have tried out LinkedIn professional portfolios before. pic.twitter.com/wMRirOvXeo    
    
    
    I'll be disappointed if I fall asleep during Gravity. Coffee and tension better bet exhaustion!    
    
    
    Crazy loud people gambling on the BART Fremont-Richmond line. Good old hobo hustling.    
    
    
    I know comics have to update character origin stories with the times, but the Fantastic Four at a rave is going too far.    
    
    
    Bulletstorm really doesn't seem like the kind of game that needs PS3 user locked saves.    
    
    
    Is Dragon's Dogma Dark Arisen on sale? It is? Black Friday shopping complete.    
    
    
    Reading the @gamespot Tactics Ogre forums makes me aware that people can't tell the difference between freedom and evil.    
    
    
    Emery-go-round "stop requested" sounds like" stop requesting".    
    
    
    @gamespot instant office groan: describe anything as "Dynasty Warriors-ish".    
    
    
    Is @tacticsogregame cutting into my @dragonage time, or is it the other way around? At least I've beaten one of them.    
    
    
    @lauralovescake that pretty much describes most of the Bay Area    
    
    
    Lunch with the boys at Maxis. Good times.    
    
    
    15 @gamespot editors out at Buca Di Beppo, yet we order for 30+.    
    
    
    @Larrrk trust me I feel gross. Worth it to see @smcinnis shove balls (of meat) into his mouth.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub truly understanding the complex maze that @TMag_GS weaves with the graceful swan dance called life.    
    
    
    Great, if anything happens I have a career as @smcinnis 's adopted man child.    
    
    
    Dragon Age 2's Black Emporium is kind of weird if you wait until Act 3 to install it. SUDDENLY: A DOG IN MY MANSION EATING CRIMINALS.    
    
    
    @guycocker @MaxwellMcGee @gs_rt I feel gross thinking about that meal. Time for some Italian abstinence.    
    
    
    Another fine CBS program that @gamespot can attest is very accurate to modern PC gaming: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FRhGPVYRsOY    
    
    
    @pkollar that's where most of the replay comes from. So much can go down in the Deep roads based on your party. Who did you take?    
    
    
    @pkollar if you play through a second time try switching out Fenris for your sibling.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier I'm sure the codes themselves will be 3D. Or you will need 3 codes--1 per each D.    
    
    
    My laptop breaks and the PS3 doesn't support Flash 10. This must be some joint Dell-Sony anti-Hulu coup d'etat.    
    
    
    Super Dodge Ball is annoying to find via the Xbox Marketplace Dashboard. Better to get it in a browser  http://mkidz.jp/dsd/    
    
    
    @fiddlecub Lego Paul Harvey, Lego 60 Minutes with Andy Rooney, Lego Johnnie Walker Black, Lego Mavis Beacon, Lego Debbie Does Dallas.    
    
    
    @justicecovert seems my Worgen got hacked, leaving a free month of a game I don't play. Must have really wanted in the empty guild vault.    
    
    
    According to my blackberry, the last time I checked twitter was 111 days ago. I'll try to keep that up.    
    
    
    @justicecovert they are both cutting into Texas Instruments' profits.    
    
    
    Main advantage of the early shift: snagging Dragon Age 3+ hours before the normal rush.    
    
    
    @gamespite DW even came with an out right plea from Enix to buy the sequel.    
    
    
    Hello Dragon Age! Goodbye social interaction. Like I even did that!    
    
    
    @The_Katbot going dwarf noble rogue. Royal backstabbing for all. Still undecided about sex.    
    
    
    Ugh the Fade is brutal and confusing as a Rogue archer. Also, minced pies! #dragonage    
    
    
    @aliceingameland thanks for the mental image. Sounds like a gangrape wendsday.    
    
    
    Wuh? Even Dragon Age has plot battles you're meant to lose? I always hate that design.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I wonder how many people are here to listen about this soon to be canceled Fox show, or are just getting an early seat for Thundercats.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle make sure to also "star", "coin" and "red power fist" strangers when you can.    
    
    
    @pkollar Hmmm guess I should check this podcast out considering I beat Dragon Age like 15 minutes ago.    
    
    
    Took about ~30 hours to beat Dragon Age without side quests (except getting Shale). The ending I got was rather lacking.    
    
    
    This took me close to 90 minutes to build. Hopefully I'll put it to good use. http://twitpic.com/4hgqhi    
    
    
    @pkollar it would have come up sooner if Homefront also had some kind of BBQ product placement.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa better start injecting coffee directly into your blood stream.    
    
    
    @gamespot @EddieMakuch doesn't 'going gold' typically mean when they send the game to the manufacture? It would be a little late.    
    
    
    @iocat Tales of the Abyss, Tactics Ogre, Grandia 2, Growlanser, Suikoden 3 and 5, Valkyrie Profile, Chrono Trigger.    
    
    
    Ah man, only one DA:O Ranger can summon at a time? There goes my plan for a Bear army.    
    
    
    @pkollar I can't keep the seasons straight. Which one was 3? I'm trying to avoid spoiling EVERYTHING.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @smcinnis I'll go ahead and be a weirdo and say Portable Ops. That is an absurd package for a PSP game.    
    
    
    @pkollar honestly that's probably my least favorite as it's sandwiched between two even more amazing seasons. Though 3 does have Romo.    
    
    
    @gamespite you better also be playing them all at once.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @garylu they really need to accept Elvish or Klingon as well.    
    
    
    @The_Katbot Shep's gender is one thing. But clearly that impostor is some Paragon Spacer War Hero blow hard.    
    
    
    GameSpot is hiring a sports game editor: http://bit.ly/fEJf2G    
    
    
    @jasonschreier I think that would mainly just annoy copy edit.    
    
    
    @dimortuisunt you can attempt to, but I'd assume knowing sports is required.    
    
    
    @JayFrechette reserve the nudity for sweeps. Or be nonchalant about no pants.    
    
    
    First piece of free Sega swag: A Phantasy Star Zero Rappy shirt.    
    
    
    I rant with @fiddlecub and @carolynmichelle about Dragon Age 2 funk in this Spoilercast http://tinyurl.com/3lwj9c2    
    
    
    @jasonschreier Tetris. That ending left me hanging for more.    
    
    
    Dragon Age actually makes me want to listen to Jared Leto. What a strange turn of events.    
    
    
    @smcinnis the official term is Atmosphere Bonanzas.    
    
    
    Warden's Keep really wasn't worth the MS points. 560 for something way too short.    
    
    
    Alright, the Kryptonian sword and the Kents made Dragon Age dlc kind of worth it.    
    
    
    @aliceingameland it's entertaining enough, and the moments of nerd rage are well worth it.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub you make that sound like an HR violation.    
    
    
    @pkollar for a twist my money is that it's Neve Campbell this time.    
    
    
    Well, Last.Fm on Xbox reaffirms my eclectic music taste by recomending both Chris Cross and Kriss Kross.    
    
    
    @nsuttner special snow cones for orphans.    
    
    
    Listening to the old 1994 Mortal Kombat 1 soundtrack. Nice to know most sites have the lyric "Warrior" listed as "Why you wear?".    
    
    
    Not sure if I actually like Gyromancer yet, but there is something addictive to it.    
    
    
    Oh right, debug and retail Live are on different planes of existance. That will teach me to try and get Vandal Hearts for free.    
    
    
    "Fountain Sandwich Special" just makes me think they have grilled cheese on tap.    
    
    
    @The_Katbot I'm just glad there is an excuse to blare the terrible 1994 MK soundtrack.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier depending on how far you are that could be a spoiler.    
    
    
    I love dumb reader comments: "GameSpot doesn't know about games. Portal 2 doesn't have multiplayer, only Co-Op."    
    
    
    @gamespite Chill, Spark, Armored, Launch, Boomer, Sting, Storm, and last Flame.    
    
    
    I just realized Buckaroo Banzai and the Get It Shawty music video were filmed in the same location. Those would make a weird crossover.    
    
    
    @pkollar news flash: stupid people exist.    
    
    
    I can't tell if this Sony conference stream is lagging, or if they are pausing to think.    
    
    
    @pkollar a Kollar Koran? Khrist.    
    
    
    @gamespite @ferricide @EvilSharkey you're gonna get Rangda Bangda'd.    
    
    
    Hell yeah to bbe's binary solo at umloud with no doubt's just a girl!    
    
    
    The lego band is musically terrible, but the showmanship makes up for it two fold.    
    
    
    @sophiatong out the latter and into the former.    
    
    
    @pkollar my body is ready. My sanity...not so good.    
    
    
    I am shocked that VGMusic.com is still kicking, and using the same n64/MMX3 logo. Follow them: @vgmusic    
    
    
    @EvilSharkey now is a good a time as any to make bathtub moonshine.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier I'm looking forward to the day we can play CoD via text messaging.    
    
    
    Got reminded about the old 1UP PSU Cup (http://tinyurl.com/yky5ksv) Why is Shane a robot that wants feathers? http://tinyurl.com/yjubqf4    
    
    
    Got to about pit stop 6 before burning out. Great for fist bay to breakers at least.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub you're working some kind of voodoo. I'm about to eat mashed potatoes, and I don't normally like them!    
    
    
    @fiddlecub don't know if you've tried it, but some QTEs are broken with a gamepad. I couldn't block during fist fights.    
    
    
    Had too much English breakfast, so I jogged from Collins-Geary to Powell-Market. Probably not enough.    
    
    
    Also both the Japan Town mall and Westfield are janky these days.    
    
    
    @pkollar_live Sell every piece of loot (Except Teleport stones). It's what they are designed for.    
    
    
    @pkollar_live the chests are in Lowtown near Dalan's, the two in the palace cellar, a few in the prison stash, and the ones in Phon coast.    
    
    
    @pkollar_live It's in the Henne Mines, but the drop rate is REALLY low. Also the best great sword and katana are nearly as good.    
    
    
    @iocat sounds like food poisoning in the wake.    
    
    
    heading down to LA for the craziness that is E3.    
    
    
    Something is up with my E3 hotel room when I can shower and watch tv at the same time.    
    
    
    Now you can say in real time "I'm Commander Shepard and this my favorite store on the Citadel."    
    
    
    Yes Ghost Recon jazz hands.    
    
    
    Can we just call it Fourza for simplification?    
    
    
    @pkollar "Dropped on your head with Kinect"    
    
    
    @jasonschreier we really got to ration those nerd snarky comments. Otherwise we risk a famine.    
    
    
    With Ninja Gaiden 3 I can Ryu on WiiU with you in a multiplayer slew.    
    
    
    Just did four on camera interviews with the good people at Sega. Aliens looks great!    
    
    
    I talked to the producer behind Aliens: Colonial Marines http://l.gamespot.com/kVLHy4    
    
    
    I interviewed the Brand Manager with Sonic Generations: http://l.gamespot.com/l85ooc    
    
    
    I talked with a producer about Anarchy Reigns: http://l.gamespot.com/jhdvwJ    
    
    
    My interview with a producer of The Sims 3 Pets: http://l.gamespot.com/jrHbrr    
    
    
    I literally sat down and talked with the dev behind Payday: The Heist http://l.gamespot.com/ll53rw    
    
    
    Yes, one more interview. This time looking at Binary Domain http://l.gamespot.com/jgTWUj    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair just explained the motivations of the Golden Axe gnomes and their need for magic potions.    
    
    
    I've lost the following in LA: My voice. Please let me know if you find it.    
    
    
    Welp, 2 hours early for my flight and southwest won't let me transfer.    
    
    
    @Larrrk head east to Vegas.    
    
    
    @Larrrk go to Andersons pea soup. It sucks ass.    
    
    
    @Aussie_Kozy @Larrrk I don't advise driving back to Australia. Might be a little too wet.    
    
    
    Looks like my flight is delayed 9 whole hours. Time for a shady airport hotel.    
    
    
    I interviewed the devs about the new Star Trek game: http://l.gamespot.com/lLpcY6    
    
    
    It's looking like @GSJody might be the last of the @gamespot crew stuck in LA.    
    
    
    @smcinnis @noreentahir consider this concept: whole watermelon pan fried  in batter.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle it gets even crazier when you see a colleuge interview a dev you know, but they clearly don't know each other.    
    
    
    @gamespite did the food taste like him though?    
    
    
        
    
    
    A little AvP with a few reviewers. I think I team killed someone from Game Informer.    
    
    
    I must be getting old. My black friday shopping was linens and luggage. Not a single game or software.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    I too keep getting this crash in Mass Effect 2: http://tiny.cc/NtAEi . Made the Horizon battle a real pain.    
    
    
    Damn, +45 Renagade for getting the secret 12th squadmate in Mass Effect 2. It was a pretty F'd up scene, too.    
    
    
    @randolphramsay @sophiatong we didn't wait long enough for the waiter to bring it back. It's an IOU from Mortons now.    
    
    
    @randolphramsay @sophiatong on the flip side I had a The Standard steak first thing in the morning.    
    
    
    After how cool, funny and interesting Shale was in Dragon Age, Zaeed from Mass Effect 2 is kind of a let down DLC character. Useful at least    
    
    
    @The_Katbot Nintendo EU got us a SUPER English build of what I've branded Soulatouroubou.    
    
    
    In my game of Mass Effect 2, both Shepard and Garrus have solved diplomatic arguments with headbutts. I hope Tali gets the same option.    
    
    
    Figures Loghain and Morrigan are Quarians. Their suits are even the same colors.    
    
    
    Time to start loading the Kindle with stuff. First up, Patriot Games or The Hunt for Red October? I've read neither before.    
    
    
    Keep crashing on the IFF misson, so time to start Mass Effect 2 again on Xbox.    
    
    
    One international plug adapter packed, but 5 separate plugs for my phone, camera, kindle, psp, and ipod. Hope I won't need most of those.    
    
    
    LHR has some terrible wi-fi. Time to start the day right by tracking down a steak and ale pie with HP sauce.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Since Cape Town I've been on planes for 26+ hours. It's 9pm in California too, right?    
    
    
    I kind of want to play NES World Cup now, but Japan is always an early minor opponent. Also the last boss being West Germany.    
    
    
    @eddie_not_eddy maybe if it includes Surf Ninjas and Spy Hard.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier @pkollar I hope the next book is a prequel of James just being a dick.    
    
    
    Still have slight jet lag insomnia. Woke up and felt the urge to try TF2 crafting. What is up with that?    
    
    
    Updating the @gamespot OoT guide. Thinking of stopping at the Water Temple. #rainierwolfcastlestandup    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair I like to think that they just accidentally deleted the code for those items    
    
    
    PHantasy Star Online 2 looks amazing: http://youtu.be/BLWcqxmPGHI    
    
    
    It's probably bad that Terraria keeps making me think of Crackdown 2 for god knows why.    
    
    
    Phantasy Star Online 2's character creation is absurd: http://youtu.be/z89_Tg1ggRg    
    
    
    I think I made one of the most counter productive drinks: whey protein shake meets Bailey's Irish cream.    
    
    
    Terraria character file: 100 KBs. Terraria world file: several 100 MBs.    
    
    
    @EvilSharkey but what if you need to spread some poo on a shit sandwich?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jasonschreier @DHGFMarkB @pkollar give John Madden tits. Think about that sales explosion.    
    
    
    @jasonschreier @MaxwellMcGee Skyrim does not appear to have a "smartass" slider. #herpderpingonforums    
    
    
    This is a must watch for fans of Final Fight and Valkyrie Profile: http://youtu.be/ce9J-J30B3o    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair does that count Planet of the Apes?    
    
    
    Nothing like a packed train going out of service right at West Oakland.    
    
    
    I'll deal with more GDC stuff tomorrow. Now to "play" some FF13.    
    
    
    @jasonbertrand I hope it really was black and white.    
    
    
    Deus Ex's triangular art style just makes me think the artists forgot to smooth out the models.    
    
    
    A few hours behind, but heading to GDC now.    
    
    
    @iocat hey I'm following you one here now. Got my GDC stuff so maybe I'll run into you.    
    
    
    I don't know what's worse, the flying machine controlled by an iphone or the human hamster ball.    
    
    
    Ah late night GDC bart. I look up and see two badass Backbone designer friends standing over me.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen I was wondering where you were. Yellow to Red some other day.    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa The show just needs more NBA Jam music. Seriously that stuff is frontier epic.    
    
    
    @The_Katbot That video reminded me that Probotector was a real game and not some black market Contra knock-off    
    
    
    Damn, chapter 8 of Final Fantasy 13 went from childish to fucking dark in minutes.    
    
    
    FF13's 360 "Extras" menu is a nice touch.    
    
    
    Final boss of FF13's chapter 11 is freaking intense. It could top my list of all FF fights.    
    
    
    @ThierryNguyen I leave the hacked turret around a corner and lure guards into it. Also Icarus slam China.    
    
    
    Didn't really expect Final Fantasy 13's ending. First thing I did was look at the logo on the game box.    
    
    
    Wow, the new Wacom Inkling looks impressive: http://youtu.be/fXbBA1DRE84     
    
    
    For those that had problems with the third boss in Deus Ex HR, this glitch is amazing: http://youtu.be/4v1X5F0d58I     
    
    
    Nerf Heavy Lifting Augmentations http://youtu.be/0l3wOT9cSg4 ?    
    
    
    @pkollar  Could have been worse. Could have tasted like Black Eyed Peas. And I don't mean soul food.    
    
    
    @gamespite SOUND. It finally exists.    
    
    
    @nsuttner I'd be more worried if they were "on par".    
    
    
    My cab driver ranted about the President, German History, and then stopped to repair his shoe. Worth it as I got a giant sized Gears 3.    
    
    
    Want to work at GameSpot's Guides department? http://tinyurl.com/3utpfqb     
    
    
    The GameSpot News Team is also hiring http://bit.ly/nc2SBY     
    
    
    Damn you FF14, not getting in Alpha but still having a MMO craving has made me start up FF11 again.    
    
    
    Time to try Dark Souls as a meager Cleric. Hope From Software invades.    
    
    
    I wrote a little about Dark Souls, but mostly rant about Temple of Elemental Evil and GOG http://l.gamespot.com/pzEYcb     
    
    
    @pkollar @jamesmielke I gave up on both the Cleric and Sorcerer. Rocking a great sword Warrior and breezing for now.    
    
    
    @CTWatters I decided to call it a day after fighting three giants that dropped "dung pies".    
    
    
    @jasonschreier @kobunheat if it's not Ivalice related, it damaged the brand.    
    
    
    Linking a Square Enix I.D. to PlayOnline Seems more of a nuisance than actually helpful.    
    
    
    Got invaded for the first time in Dark Souls. He dropped 11000 Souls. Next time try rolling.    
    
    
    @pkollar the one in the alley? Just walk up the stairs and drop on him. Or do you fight him twice!?    
    
    
    @pkollar run up the stairs and onto the ledge. Then drop down and he'll chase you in a loop. Run fast and drop on him.    
    
    
    @pkollar aren't you strong enough that the dogs are one hit KO?    
    
    
    @pkollar time to make an Intelligence GREATSWORD.    
    
    
    @pkollar probably not, but that would kick ass. I'm still hunting for more crafting items passed +6    
    
    
    @pkollar get a weapon to +5 and you can start modify it towards elements, magic, stats and others. You can undo upgrades but loose the mats.    
    
    
    Welp, blue phantoms can't use Estus flasks. Sorry host dude.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub what's passed Ceaseless Discharge? These Capras and Tuarus are getting annoying.    
    
    
    @vanjnguyen the Parish is quicker and cheaper.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub ok, so giving up was the right choice for now. Also being summoned with little health blows.    
    
    
    @pkollar how much life do you have? Only did half a bar at 800.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk yikes I'm level 59 after that Sen's Fortress boss. Too much grinding and dying.    
    
    
    @pkollar downed an Estus+2 after every firewave then hit him twice. Won after 16 club slams.    
    
    
    @pkollar nope, think you have to beat the dragon knight and fatty first for the item.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub I could take Sen's Fortress and Anor Londo, but Demon Ruins' bosses as normal enemies is too much.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk did anyone fight the painting boss? I just walked away so I didn't lose 40k souls.    
    
    
    @pkollar any clue how to reach the catacombs black smith? I warped out after finding the princess.    
    
    
    @pkollar those skelewheels cornered me near a wall that had a hammer clanking. Assuming it's a smith.    
    
    
    @pkollar well all the Lord Soul areas are crazy. One is pitch black, while another has invisible bridges.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub I'm cringing getting to the Lord Souls. Let me know if you beat one.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub where the heck am I going after the centipede? If it's into the lava I'll be peeved.    
    
    
    @larrrk joined the Gravelords, had to kill Nito anyway.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk found any of the second embers for Normal/Divine/Fire? I can't get above +10/+5    
    
    
    @Larrrk switch in basement with the wheel skelies. I found it as a phantom. As a human I glitched the dragon with a strong attack.    
    
    
    @Gamespot Dark Souls user: "Will there be a walkthrough on how to get beards? Seriously, I couldn't find the option anywhere. Disappointed."    
    
    
    The news mainly makes want to rewatch Pirates of Silicon Valley. The Windows unboxing is so great, even if  Jobs and Gates had lines fliped.    
    
    
    @larrrk Sparky the crow in Undead Asylum will trade each moss for 4 Twinkling Titanite total.    
    
    
    @Larrrk @vanjnguyen Asylum Sparky will also trade Skull Lantern for Forest Hunter ring.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk @vanjnguyen Two bosses left.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk Finished Dark Souls. Also spoiled the ending for @vanjnguyen    
    
    
    @pkollar you're getting a little too kinky for Twitter there.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub @Larrrk @vanjnguyen wow I read my time wrong, it was only 68 hours long.    
    
    
    @vanjnguyen eagle shield or any tower shield blocked them really well.    
    
    
    @jamesmielke you'll love the cats and mushrooms.    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle @fiddlecub conundrum: how long would Batman survive in Lordran? I'd say until Darkroot.    
    
    
    @fiddlecub if this Soul Calibur 5 rumor is true, you might have a "hidden" interest in the game http://aol.it/qAU2j0     
    
    
    @fiddlecub time to pay Oswald in the Parish 4562783 billion souls to make everything normal.    
    
    
    Dear lord, Dark Souls random face generator: http://youtu.be/-mCb8nZxg2M     
    
    
    @pkollar complexly naked sounds awesome.    
    
    
    Just ate bbq ribs on top of spaghetti. My body (and brain) is confused.    
    
    
    Random lyrics is really what Air Man's theme was missing: http://www.ocremix.org/remix/OCR01687/    
    
    
    RE5 spoilers: http://tinyurl.com/auya4b There is a link to here on there. Blue Portal?    
    
    
    Is it bad that I knew about "Innerspace" before "Fantastic Voyage"? http://tinyurl.com/d3uews    
    
    
    @BrendanSinclair are the $4 fake?    
    
    
    @jasonschreier oh god the hand to hand combat was so clunky. I loved it!    
    
    
    @jasonschreier also Drake hasn't saved the world with a comb, jar of old mayo, and half an eaten sandwich.    
    
    
    @gamespite I hope he makes Wright is a masochist anyway.    
    
    
    Wow, MTV might be on track again. Beavis and Butt-Head season 8 premiered tonight. 14 years later and it's th… (cont) http://deck.ly/~qGXyA     
    
    
    @jason_wilson I can think of a few corporations that poop.    
    
    
    @smcinnis is 80% of the city comprised of cheese and/or steak?    
    
    
    @fiddlecub can they steel-cut the parfait? I'd go yogurt anyway.    
    
    
    Got to the BART station just as I realized I left my work at home. That was a fun dash back.    
    
    
    @jeffgerstmann @jamesmielke Is it bad that I hummed "Part-Time Lover" instead?    
    
    
    TF2 Scouts got nerfed again. Way to kill your last update, Valve.    
    
    
    I just played Phantasy Star Online followed by Diablo 2. Must have fallen in a timewarp.    
    
    
    @compellingpixel If those terrible photos of me came out ok, send them my way. I think it's time for a new lowbrow profile picture.    
    
    
    FFXIV dev team reorganised, more free months and the PS3 version delayed for who knows how long.    
    
    
    Updating Linkedin crap. It still linked to "My Website" which has been dead for almost a year.    
    
    
    @compellingpixel I'm pretty sure I had more like 12 red bulls. Now for a new pic goal: http://tinyurl.com/df6kf5    
    
    
    Time to see how well i can make fried chicken    
    
    
    @omgmorejade Damn right it was awesome! Here's to crazy techno anime theme songs!    
    
    
    I need the DuckTales song (Get the Money) from this show http://tinyurl.com/abq8rw    
    
    
    @Chufmoney I was disappointed that the the story did not in fact contain a Laser Wolf.    
    
    
    Starting Walking Dead thanks to @prettytony    
    
    
    Finished Book One of Walking Dead. Hope that Hershel guy gets fucked up later.    
    
    
    @twittch sexy robot vote: Guri from Shadows of the Empire. Though, no regular actress portrayed her/was an illustration.    
    
    
    @EddieMakuch typical weekend then?    
    
    
    @mikecruz_at1UP Good to know that I still use that hospital.    
    
    
    My name is Ted, and one day I'll be dead, yo, yo, yo http://tinyurl.com/227ewa    
    
    
    @carolynmichelle at least we're breaking even.    
    
    
    Touching the pilot light while cleaning the stove: not fun.    
    
    
    @omgmorejade Well, nothing enhances a dish’s aroma better than the souls of the living    
    
    
    After cleaning my apartment, it just looks barren. Had I been living in trash?    
    
    
    @rdb_aaa Your latest avatar is intense in the best way possible. Scanner battle?    
    
    
    Most of the CNET office I'd huddled in the lobby to get free cookies.    
    
    
    Starting on Omega the Unknown #1 while listening to Kraftwerk http://tinyurl.com/6699w4    
    
    
    Just finished Omega the Unknown (WTF!?) while listening to some April Wine http://tinyurl.com/bcsmmt    
    
    
    Retro/Grade info on 1up's FreeLoader blog http://tinyurl.com/d9rnzs    
    
    
    Latest episode of Lost, and then The Pitt.    
    
    
    Just got done knowing half the battle with @pkollar and @omgmorejade    
    
    
    The Old Republic's Flashpoints have amazing troll potential when you disagree and out roll your teammates during dialogue.    
    
    
    Jedi ally "We'll do this peacefully", seconds before my Commando vetos and opens the air lock.    
    
    
    A little too much Goose and Juice, but home in one piece.    
    
    
    Molyneux talk was underwhelming.    
    
    
    They're finally tearing down the crack motel...Or planning to rebuild it as a super mutant-ultra mecha crack motel.    
    
    
    