Social Influencers Who Are Changing The World Through Twitter http://www.fastcompany.com/node/3004155  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    Lift a glass of water to the New Year and celebrate!    
    
    
    10 Things Extraordinary People Say Every Day http://www.inc.com/jeff-haden/10-things-extraordinary-people-say-every-day.html … via @Inc    
    
    
    This is a great article!
Starting a new business and life from the groundup: Fearless http://ebrianschneider.blogspot.com/2013/01/fearless.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    At Davos Investing in Women Emerges as a Business Strategy http://thebea.st/10GpShM  via @thedailybeast    
    
    
    SMU's Economic Outlook Meeting was super!  Thanks Dan Foster, Dr. Bruce Yandle and Colleen Keith for a great presentation.    
    
    
    2013 will be the Year of the Woman Entrepreneur and will grow their businesses through social media.  Let's celebrate! http://ow.ly/hNA5b     
    
    
    A wonderful article - worth your time.
http://www.huffingtonpost.com/john-r-talbott/things-my-mother-taught-m_b_2881505.html …    
    
    
    Just signed up for #Nestivity, reserve yours now http://nestivity.com/  via @Nestivity    
    
    
    6 Secrets of Women Entrepreneurs Who Built $10 Million Companies - Forbes http://onforb.es/YSJQZl .    Great advice for all women in business.    
    
    
    Women In the World: 125 Women Of Impact  http://thebea.st/10XHPM2  via @thedailybeast
An introduction to amazing women!    
    
    
    Hillary Clinton: Helping Women Isn't Just a 'Nice' Thing to Do http://thebea.st/YXtwGB  via @thedailybeast. Seize the Moment!    
    
    
    Handwritten Notes Are a Rare Commodity. They're Also More Important Than Ever. - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/04/handwritten_notes_are_a_rare_c.html …  Personalizing matters    
    
    
    Women In Business Discouraged By Ethical Dilemmas, Study Suggests http://huff.to/14HxeYO  via @HuffPostWomen Ethical behavior matters    
    
    
    Climbing the career ladder!
She’s the boss: Women in business [infographic] http://holykaw.alltop.com/shes-the-boss-women-in-business-infographic … via @GuyKawasaki    
    
    
    She’s the boss: Women in business [infographic] http://holykaw.alltop.com/shes-the-boss-women-in-business-infographic … via @GuyKawasaki    
    
    
    Equal Pay Day Advice for All Women   http://ow.ly/jY1r7     
    
    
    We need to get comfortable with powerful women.  http://ow.ly/jY3sE     
    
    
    We need more women on Boards.  Vince Cable: There is a chronic shortage of women in top jobs http://gu.com/p/3f6j7/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Let's call "bossy" girls and women what they are: leaders!  The "B" Word http://huff.to/17xhdSt  via @HuffPostWomen    
    
    
    This is a great trend for nonprofits!  http://ow.ly/kgVgk     
    
    
    Thanks to all of my terrific co-workers who volunteered at the Spartanburg Water Day of Service last Saturday. http://ow.ly/i/222yE     
    
    
    I love this article!  Warren Buffett is bullish ... on women http://cnnmon.ie/1205jil  via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    Without Water, Revolution http://nyti.ms/18T46yi     
    
    
    @Inc MidYear Check-up    
    
    
    Thanks to my fellow Board members and the outstanding staff at United Way of the Piedmont.  http://ow.ly/mDmIP     
    
    
    @americanrivers @outsidemagazine  Craft Beer Teams Up for Clean Water    
    
    
    Great Article, Great Advice! How To Get Everything You Want In Life http://flip.it/rHiJW     
    
    
    Great series, do you agree with this pillar? https://twitter.com/forbeswoman/status/351808395084435457 …    
    
    
    Learn from the best!  RANKED: The 30 Most Creative People In Social Media Marketing http://www.businessinsider.com/the-30-most-creative-social-media-marketers-ranked-2013-7 … via @BI_Advertising    
    
    
    This article asks an important question about your leadership style - are you a Hill-Finder or a Hill-Taker? http://lnkd.in/z2i5Y8     
    
    
    How do you define success for yourself?   Do your agree with this article?     http://ow.ly/mMatf     
    
    
    It's great to see the glass ceiling broken at the largest U.S. Utility.  Duke Energy names new CEO http://usat.ly/16fb9ih  via @USATODAY    
    
    
    Glad to see Microsoft recognizing women in technology.  Let's cross the Digital Divide!   http://bit.ly/13Hv6Sh     
    
    
    Sometimes the most powerful voices are the youngest among us. Malala will not be silenced by Taliban attack http://flip.it/2FTdi     
    
    
    Reach for the stars!   Half of NASA's New Class of Astronauts Are Women http://flip.it/WYVN7     
    
    
    Water impacts the world.  This is a great map of global water risks. http://lnkd.in/c8BGQn     
    
    
    An Incredibly Detailed Map Shows The Potential Of Global Water Risks http://lnkd.in/c8BGQn     
    
    
    Phoenix has done a lot to prepare for water scarcity, but will it be enough with climate changes?
 http://m.usatoday.com/article/news/2439191 …    
    
    
    Wonderful leadership advice for everyone.  http://www.forbes.com/sites/jennagoudreau/2013/03/21/eight-leadership-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-powerful-women/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    It's great to see her progress with Yahoo.  How CEO Marissa Mayer turned around Yahoo http://usat.ly/12D3VFC  via @USATODAY    
    
    
    Great article on the impact of weather volatility to global commerce.  How do we manage uncertainty?  http://linkd.in/14iRaSr     
    
    
    Climate volatility and the impact to water in the Midwest will affect food production.  What does the future hold? http://bit.ly/13ZD0p1     
    
    
    Phoenix, Arizona has planned for climate change but future impacts are uncertain. http://usat.ly/16hftxy     
    
    
    Spartanburg Water has implemented strategies for resilience during climate uncertainty.  How resilient are you? http://ow.ly/1ZDycT     
    
    
    Coming to the conclusion that conservation and reuse may nor be enough.  What's next for the Colorado River? http://ow.ly/1ZDByF     
    
    
        
    
    
    Maryland suburb faces economic impact of fixing aging water infrastructure during heat wave.  http://ow.ly/1ZEgXg     
    
    
    We need Game Changers to get our economy moving.  Do you agree with this list? http://ow.ly/1ZKt0h     
    
    
    Congratulations to my co-workers at Spartanburg Water for another successful Paddlefest event at Lake Blalock today! http://ow.ly/1ZKuVv     
    
    
    Leading your team through great questions.  What do you ask to solve problems? http://ow.ly/nceiJ     
    
    
    Have you used these 5 powers to launch your ideas?  http://ow.ly/ncgnA     
    
    
    An effective water strategy ensures business continuity.  Have you considered how your organization is positioned? http://ow.ly/1ZPqO6     
    
    
    Will the glass ceiling finally be broken at the Fed?  Will Janet Yellen succeed Bernanke? http://ow.ly/1ZPuQA     
    
    
    Just imagine the quality of apps, technology and games that will improve as the number of women increase in tech.  http://ow.ly/1ZUX4v     
    
    
    Unbelievable video of a young man who refuses to allow himself to have any limits- what holds you back?  http://ow.ly/1ZVen7     
    
    
    Lt. Andrew Kinard, of Spartanburg, continues to inspire and lead.  A wonderful video well worth your time. http://fplus.me/2ytT     
    
    
    Thank you so much!    
    
    
    I hope to see you at the Women in Business Conference next week!  Great speakers! Great women!  See you there! http://ow.ly/20xaww     
    
    
    South Carolina is a leader in automotive and aerospace, check out this article! http://industrytoday.com/article_view.asp?ArticleID=we571&goback=.gde_2482866_member_260213838 …    
    
    
    Water: China's Worst Economic Crisis http://blogs.marketwatch.com/thetell/2013/07/31/china-faces-its-worst-economic-crisis-water/?mod=mw_share_linkedin&goback=%2Egde_2751785_member_262129603 …    
    
    
    Over 126 million women entrepreneurs/business owners are growing their businesses worldwide.  Are you one of them?
http://ow.ly/20D8t6     
    
    
    Great sources for all women!  Do you follow? RT @projecteve1: Top 13 Sites for Women to Follow http://flip.it/f8rUT  http://flip.it/f8rUT     
    
    
    Is Higher Ed doing enough to protect women?  RT @HuffingtonPost: Yale's huge failure punishing sexual assault http://flip.it/Y917g     
    
    
    Great advice from some talented entrepreneurs.  http://ow.ly/nBEhU     
    
    
    This is an issue in sewer lines everywhere.  Please don't flush wipes or pour grease down the drain.  It matters.  http://ow.ly/nH8hZ     
    
    
    @LeanInOrg   Always try what others say can't be done!    
    
    
    Follow@ecalschnei    
    
    
    Got Water?  http://pinterest.com/pin/195062227583719219/ …    
    
    
    http://m.motherjones.com/tom-philpott/2013/08/gulf-of-mexico-dead-zone-growth …    
    
    
    http://www.thestate.com/2013/08/13/2916226/feds-fining-city-15-million-for.html …    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/21mucU     
    
    
    So much rain this year in the Southeast, but the facts are rolling in that the West has reached its peak water.  http://ow.ly/21mzhk     
    
    
    Will Silicon Valley be on rationing water next year? http://www.mercurynews.com/science/ci_23881247/san-luis-reservoir-17-percent-full-causing-silicon …    
    
    
    What happens when there are more claims for water than exists with current capacity?  What's the future in the West?  http://ow.ly/21nwiw     
    
    
    A future water crisis on the horizon.  The photos of shrinking reservoirs are very revealing. http://ow.ly/21pL01     
    
    
    These women have something to say!  Technology IS a women's game.    http://ow.ly/21pMEY     
    
    
    Busting water myths about the Great Lakes.  http://ow.ly/21yyZu     
    
    
    http://ow.ly/21ACig     
    
    
    China is struggling with the demand for energy in water stressed regions.  Are their plans making it worse? http://ow.ly/21KfhC     
    
    
    Are you listening to these 25 women?  Join the conversation! http://ow.ly/oi5aW     
    
    
    Bringing water and sanitation to those most in need.  http://ow.ly/21TwI5     
    
    
    Drought is making its impact on the Midwest.  http://ow.ly/21WSlX     
    
    
    This western wildfire is different and why we should be concerned about it.  http://ow.ly/21Yzf9     
    
    
    Whether you believe our climate is changing or not, the sea level is rising.  Check out this list.  http://ow.ly/21YAGk     
    
    
    This is an article that makes you think.  Would this idea launch more female owned businesses? http://ow.ly/21YCra     
    
    
    Global politics involves water - those with resources and those needing more.  http://ow.ly/orTlj     
    
    
    Will clean water be compromised by clear cutting forests in Oregon?http://ow.ly/221AWg     
    
    
    The nexus between drought and funding aging infrastructure.  Are new pricing strategies needed? http://qz.com/118025     
    
    
    A great article on how the thriving Salton Sea in California is now a toxic mess.  Have we learned any lessons? http://ow.ly/221Dfa     
    
    
    This is an interesting case on the the future of Nestle's bottled water in Maine.  http://ow.ly/227uTY     
    
    
    http://ow.ly/227xbq     
    
    
    http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/water-hazard-how-the-un-plans-to-provide-clean-drinking-water-for-everyone-in-rwanda-8788693.html …    
    
    
    Great tool to track any stream. http://ow.ly/227FjN     
    
    
    A lighter look at "Water Wars".  Have you tried this craft beer? http://ow.ly/227GH5     
    
    
    A new day in North Carolina as the state supports New reservoirs.  http://ow.ly/227H4v     
    
    
    How important is economically to the US to dredge the Mississippi? http://ow.ly/227HTa     
    
    
    An increase in wetter decades contributes to the woes of Detroit's aging infrastructure.  http://ow.ly/22baLj     
    
    
    China's continual pollution problems.  http://ow.ly/22ex5d     
    
    
    Mexico is the largest per capita consumer of bottled water.  How does it stack up against soft drinks? http://ow.ly/22eRRV     
    
    
    Ever hear of an ATM that dispenses water?  http://ow.ly/22eSaN     
    
    
    http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2013-09-06/mesh-rising-energy-demand-with-world-water-needs-un-envoy-says.html …    
    
    
    The State Dept predicts water demands will exceed supply by 40% in 2030.  Should we be focusing scarcity issues now? http://ow.ly/22o2zK     
    
    
    Did the decade long drought intensify the tension in Syria? http://ow.ly/22pOeX     
    
    
    Collaboration could ease water tensions. http://ow.ly/22pPZo     
    
    
    Creating a sustainable future through water and energy conservation practices. http://ow.ly/22pRGi     
    
    
    The Great Lakes are truly great, see these photos. http://ow.ly/22sItc     
    
    
    Great advice!  Share it with a friend.  http://ow.ly/oNdKH     
    
    
    Never released DOE report predicts water and energy conflicts.  http://ow.ly/22Vub0     
    
    
        
    
    
    Making a kitchen-table case for massive water bill http://flip.it/KL4Gc     
    
    
    Janet Yellen could be the next Fed Chair.  http://ow.ly/22ZxTU     
    
    
    Whois@username    
    
    
    Whois@womennetwork    
    
    
    Whois@ewomennetwork    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/23jn4t     
    
    
    http://ow.ly/23jntG     
    
    
    Congratulations to the 300 volunteers from the colleges and community who participated in the Spartanburg Water 25th Annual Lake Sweep!    
    
    
    @LeanInOrg @DrMayaAngelou    
    
    
        
    
    
    Listening to a CEO panel on the importance of the early childhood investment. PNC, Michelin NA, Home Depot and Aflac CEOs make the case.    
    
    
    http://www.sacbee.com/2013/09/22/5756636/southern-california-water-users.html …    
    
    
    http://www.washingtonpost.com/business/capitalbusiness/women-influencing-corporate-boards-despite-shortage-of-numbers/2013/09/22/8fa9ad10-16f4-11e3-804b-d3a1a3a18f2c_story.html …    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://www.ydr.com/nation-world/ci_24132000/13-500-gallons-oil-spill-along-colorado-river …    
    
    
    http://www.waterworld.com/topics/device/mobile/t/81052663/industrial-water-day-now-less-than-two-weeks-away.htm?m_n=true …    
    
    
    http://blogs.hbr.org/2013/07/surprises-are-the-new-normal-r/ …    
    
    
    http://www.forbes.com/sites/heatherclancy/2013/09/19/with-annual-losses-estimated-at-14-billion-its-time-to-get-smarter-about-water/ …    
    
    
    http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_24153355/colorado-launching-massive-emergency-dam-inspection-progam …    
    
    
    Alcoa continues fight over hydro license | http://CharlotteObserver.com  http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2013/09/26/4344889/alcoa-continues-fight-over-hydro.html#.UkTwunllApQ.twitter …    
    
    
    Five Great takeaways on global warming.  http://ow.ly/23Zpaa     
    
    
    This report certainly is direct in how it is evaluating the impact of climate change.  What do you think? http://ow.ly/piAGz     
    
    
    Who should pay for our future water? http://touch.latimes.com/#section/-1/article/p2p-77592700/ …    
    
    
    The rains have revived the Rio Grande this fall.  http://ow.ly/24c25W     
    
    
    Do you know the Value of Water?  http://thevalueofwater.org/     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    The nexus between water and energy continues to grow. http://ow.ly/24WR4W     
    
    
    Weather extremes continue to challenge our communities with too much or too little water. http://ow.ly/24WS87     
    
    
    http://ow.ly/24WUrY     
    
    
    Should coastal ares continue to be rebuilt after extreme weather? http://ow.ly/24WVpQ     
    
    
    This is an amazing list!  http://ow.ly/pJTbT     
    
    
    Northern China's water use is unsustainable.  How damaging will the fixes be? http://ow.ly/2572oP     
    
    
    http://ow.ly/2574md     
    
    
    http://ow.ly/2574CJ     
    
    
    http://ow.ly/2574OR     
    
    
    http://ow.ly/2576xb     
    
    
    The damming of the Nile River by Ethiopia could cause war with Egypt.  Is this the beginning of more "Water Wars"?  http://ow.ly/25j0iJ     
    
    
    Geography in the News: Oil Spills http://flip.it/Re6bq     
    
    
    How stressed is your water basin?  http://ow.ly/25jxnH     
    
    
    A very funny, thoughtful article worth your time to read and share.  http://ow.ly/pP0rB     
    
    
    Great tips that we can all do to maintain clean water. http://ow.ly/25m5Ia     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://ow.ly/25sFwh     
    
    
    Extreme weather affecting crops.   http://finance.yahoo.com/news/iowa-scientists-climate-change-affecting-193357996.html …    
    
    
    Great new water research center in Milwaukee.   http://www.jsonline.com/news/opinion/global-water-center-a-big-step-for-milwaukee-b9994351z1-223050131.html?ipad=y …    
    
    
    Colorado business leaders leading groundswell support for water conservation.   http://www.denverpost.com/breakingnews/ci_24340930/business-water-summit-stirs-economic-support-water-conservation …    
    
    
    Today is the 41st anniversary of the Clean Water Act.  Should the CWA be updated?  #water    
    
    
    We need to change the way we think about water.  Infrastructure matters.  http://ow.ly/25EvDB     
    
    
    Most Texans say they support $2B for water infrastructure projects.  Do you support water infrastructure? http://ow.ly/25EwL1     
    
    
    The bottled water industry continues to evolve to flavored products at a premium price.  Do you value your tap water? http://ow.ly/26dMPE     
    
    
    In a discussion on how to convey the value of water to our communities with >150 water leaders at AMWA Conference.  http://ow.ly/i/3yTyp     
    
    
    This article provides inspiration to solving water stress, not just reports about it. Worth your time to read. http://ow.ly/26fQBg     
    
    
    The House overwhelmingly passed a mammoth water bill last week.  It's time to  finish the job with the Senate. http://ow.ly/26fRfH     
    
    
    Do you go with the flow or engineer the water back into place? A dilemma for the experts. http://ow.ly/26fSAV     
    
    
    Inspirational women water warriors!  http://ow.ly/26fTfc     
    
    
    Do you know the source of your drinking water?  The Upstate has wonderful source waters.  http://ow.ly/26xyz3     
    
    
    How are you encouraging women and minorities to enter STEM careers? http://usat.ly/1bMXQb1     
    
    
    Will water scarcity in the Arabian Gulf contribute to political unrest? 
http://ow.ly/26V2eK     
    
    
    China will soon be home to the first 50 M person city.  'Smart' tech will increase future water sustainability. http://ow.ly/27dRy7     
    
    
        
    
    
    China is failing to protecting its source water and its $62 B water transfer project won't meet water scarcity needs. http://ow.ly/28bXC9     
    
    
    Thanks to all the water professionals who are working on this holiday to bring us clean water to our homes.  Let's raise a glass to them.    
    
    
    Tomorrow is the busiest day of the year for plumbers.  Please don't put grease from your holiday dinner down the kitchen drain.    
    
    
    Did you know that access to clean water and sanitation is also a problem in the USA? http://ow.ly/28El3S     
    
    
    Rethinking Waste Water http://bigthink.com/in-their-own-words/rethinking-waste-water?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A%20bigthink%2Fmain%20%28Big%20Think%20Main%29#.UqO_QCSG2Ng.twitter …    
    
    
    What if Congress had listened to the idea of organizing the boundaries of western states around watersheds? 
http://ow.ly/28H76m     
    
    
    Detroit's decline causing abandoned pipes to leak for years.  http://ow.ly/28OQVt     
    
    
    Water stress continues to increase around the world.  http://ow.ly/28Uh1v     
    
    
    Crack!  Do hear the glass ceiling breaking open? Congrats to Mary Barra, the new CEO of General Motors. http://ow.ly/28YKbe     
    
    
    What would a day without water be like? Simply submitting a photo will help build a well and provide sanitation. http://ow.ly/29aT4l     
    
    
    During our busy holidays don't forget to drink...water!  Stay healthy and hydrated. http://ow.ly/29ofn3     
    
    
        
    
    
    San Francisco May Be First Major City to Ban Plastic Water Bottles http://flip.it/013IS     
    
    
        
    
    
    How Inspiring!  http://ow.ly/29vQEF     
    
    
    After a year of dysfunction, both parties can agree on water infrastructure projects.  Water is the unifier.  http://ow.ly/29yRT8     
    
    
    The City of Spartanburg opened 24 new businesses downtown in 2013!  Spartanburg is The Place to locate!  http://ow.ly/29JLIH     
    
    
    Wow, You need to see this list! Bing celebrates courageous women who showed us what the human spirit can achieve. http://ow.ly/29JNYQ     
    
    
    Are you feeling under the weather? Here are some suggestions to help you feel better? http://ow.ly/29TN9S     
    
    
    