@LuxuryTravelMom How old is your teen girl? 
 #tmom    
    
    
    Congrats! RT @CindyRichards: Woo-hoo Anne!Way to go! RT @travelingmoms: Congrats to our $25 iTunes gift card winner @annewassociates!  #tmom    
    
    
    @network_outcast What? They did't leave you a list? :) #tmom    
    
    
    Sweet! RT @TibsTravel: @slstaffo FOR THE FAMILY = your reason to be a biz traveler. Good mantra for all of us. Thanks. @travelingmoms #tmom    
    
    
    @network_outcast Well, good luck! #tmom    
    
    
    Enjoyed chatting with you all! #tmom    
    
    
    If you have teens, please follow me @collegevisit , too, where I tweet about colleges, visits, admissions, & more! #tmom    
    
    
    @akilbello You're welcome.    
    
    
    @doctornayaka My new fav power accessory: PowerRocks http://ht.ly/chBgu  #TMOM    
    
    
    @ramblingstump Ouch! Her school should get http://www.becomealum.com/  so students can plan ahead & see when classes are offered.    
    
    
    @ramblingstump Hate when that happens. An unforeseen glitch in the plan! #tmom    
    
    
    Join our fans! Like-minded travel lovers unite on TravelingMom FaceBook page http://bit.ly/9n8LT5 . #TMOM #traveltuesday    
    
    
    Working #TravelingMom, @teresashaw shares her best packing tips for solo travel: http://bit.ly/MsCUyc  #TMOM    
    
    
    Join me tonight on #CampusChat: Pros and cons of living on/off campus! The best and worst of both worlds! Join us at 9PM ET!    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @nancyberk: I'm at the #NSTweetup w/ @WeekendInParis @thedailybasics @12MeterCharters Love Newport & my BFTweeps    
    
    
    #CampusChat makes me happy.    
    
    
    @JohnLusher @TEDxMacUni @iggypintado Congrats, John!    
    
    
    @zrosen88 @JJustinB @GailatSCV Modern sounds great! We hit the road Sunday morning!  #ontheroadagain    
    
    
    “@travelingmoms: There are rules & regs to flying w/ a pet in cabin - get the scoop from Memories #TMOM, @heartblog! http://bit.ly/LHZ7Hg ”    
    
    
    Seeking to interview any college students who have participated in a code-a-thon. Please let me know if you know of anyone.    
    
    
    @CathyWebSavvyPR Cathy, that would be great! Hope you can make it!    
    
    
    Seeking an html to #pdf converter. Anyone have any recommendations?    
    
    
    Find out where folks are coming from to move to Blacksburg RT @bburglodging: American Migration-Forbes http://fb.me/11CjcZPrg  via @stuartmease    
    
    
    @zrosen88 Back in #Blacksburg. Loved touring @unewhaven campus & state of art classrooms--thanks for showing us around your lovely campus!    
    
    
    Congrats to @handshake20 on your 4yr anniversary - coming up on Sunday! Love these the #top10 facts http://ht.ly/cwUor     
    
    
    Hi, Kelly Queijo here/been following chat 2nite. May be of interest: Secret Lives of Teenagers (Biz Insider) http://read.bi/O38rmq  #emchat    
    
    
    @AlexMWilliams_  Hi, Alex! I finally made it! #emchat    
    
    
    Given time/ppl constraints, rec using tweet schedulers & alert notifications to keep active & informed. #emchat    
    
    
    @AlexMWilliams_ Sweet! College visits are my favorite subject! #emchat    
    
    
    @AlexMWilliams_ Thanks! I'll add to my calendar! #emchat    
    
    
    @AlexMWilliams_  Hope you have a wonderful birthday, Alex! #emchat    
    
    
    Beautiful campus! RT @collegevisit: College Visit Video: Quinnipiac University http://bit.ly/OldkJR     
    
    
    #CampusChat inspired a blog by @zach_richards RT @collegevisit: Student Reflections: College Tours & College Decisions http://bit.ly/LYbGtv     
    
    
    Great advice for #startups: Start-up Therapy  http://ht.ly/cCREG  (appreciate @GailatSCV influence at SmartCollegeVisit)    
    
    
    Clearwater Cocktail: Blending Family, Work, & College Tours  http://ht.ly/cDNdR  #TMOM    
    
    
    Great travel tips on saving money on vacation #travel from #TMOM http://ht.ly/cIglM     
    
    
    Sweet! RT @debmomof3: My 6yo's dream come true - meeting Minnie Mouse! #disney #tmom   @ Camp Minnie-Mickey http://instagr.am/p/N31QNmu_mw/     
    
    
    Have you been to #Clearwater Beach? Was your experience as much fun as mine? http://ht.ly/cJHe2  #TMOM    
    
    
    @wyndhamwomen Yes, #unplug to get the most out of #familytime.    
    
    
    Go for the gold and join the Olympics themed #TMOM Twitter party 9 pm EDT 7/6. RSVP for prizes: http://bit.ly/M6HZqm     
    
    
    Fun, fun! RT @pircy23: Go for the gold and join the Olympics themed #TMOM Twitter party 9 pm EDT 7/6. RSVP for prizes: http://bit.ly/M6HZqm     
    
    
    @stewartbuzz Thanks so much for the RT!    
    
    
    A1 Gymnastics! Daughter was competitive gymnast for years. Still love watching the sport! Any other gym moms in #TMOM?    
    
    
    Agree!! RT @mommytravels: A2 Portland, Oregon its an awesome place #tmom    
    
    
    Now that would be fun! RT @CindyRichards: And if Chicago won the Olympics, you could all come and stay with me. #tmom    
    
    
    @DebMomOf3 Love #Atlanta. Wonder if the Olympic athletes got to drink all the sweet tea they wanted when they were there? #tmom    
    
    
    A4 London? Everything! #tmom    
    
    
    @AskWifey Flipping back and forth between Olympics and Lost on Netflix (of course they are time traveling right now-a diff journey!) #tmom    
    
    
    A5 A hat and a pack of gum! #tmom    
    
    
    @CindyRichards My kids love gum. Doesn't everyone?  #tmom    
    
    
    Me too! RT @twinlins: Im all about gymnastics! Q1: WHAT SPORT IS WORTH TRAVELING TO SEE? #tmom    
    
    
    @cindyrichards You'll be shipping it in goody boxes to your son!    
    
    
    @askwifey Hi, So glad to know someone else in Atlanta!    
    
    
    Looking forward to tonight! RT @alexmwilliams_: Campus Tour Guest: Z. Kelly Queijo http://wp.me/p22c3K-c3  via #EMchat - ... Thurs at 9PM EST!    
    
    
    @emjennielle Hi! Looking forward to #EMchat !!    
    
    
    Watching my fav show on TV: #SharkTank --  #alwayslearning    
    
    
    @alexmwilliams_ Thanks for inviting me, Alex. #EMChat was a blast!    
    
    
    @nancyberk Back to school is Tuesday for my high schooler in #Blacksburg! #shortsummer    
    
    
    @nancyberk That reminds me, I'd better go wake him up now. #nomoresleepingin    
    
    
    Love #VA entrepreneurial culture! RT @handshake20: 10 Stats About Virginia Entrepreneurs http://bit.ly/MGEIEk     
    
    
    @mygola Sure thing. Follow me back and let's DM    
    
    
    @intractvachvmnt Thanks! Have always admired your work. Nice to connect on Twitter.    
    
    
    @mygola Thanks so much!    
    
    
    Yay! RT @handshake20: RT @CITGAPFunds: Congrats to Brian Putt, Co-founder of @lujuremedia and a #GAP50 finalist. #Hokies    
    
    
    Way to go, Caroline! RT @citgapfunds: Congrats to @Caroline_Pugh, COO of VirtualU, for becoming a #GAP50 finalist.  #VTech    
    
    
    Had fun setting up a "Recently Published' board on @Pinterest. Nice way to create a visual portfolio. http://ht.ly/d3Owh     
    
    
    @mygola No problem - kelly at smart college visit dot com    
    
    
    #TMOM Twitter Party 8/20, 9pm ET – we’re talking about sustainable travel. RSVP for fun & prizes: http://bit.ly/NvIrCR     
    
    
    Beautiful building! RT @collegevisit: Focal Points: see Wayne State University's @waynestate most photographed building http://bit.ly/PSaJJL     
    
    
    Moving into #VaTech dorms? Go to YToss in McComas for $8 fans & more! #blacksburg pic.twitter.com/4950fhBP    
    
    
    YToss has hutches too- McComas Hall #VaTech #Blacksburg pic.twitter.com/BYsZgw7k    
    
    
    Inspired by the students at #VTKWGlobal RT @collegevisit: The Real ROI of a College Education  http://tinyurl.com/9lb2mfp     
    
    
    @HBCU_Lifestyle thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    @dtcav Happy, #FF Donna & @NancyBerk !!    
    
    
    Can you guess the top Twitter hashtags from the past 12 months? How many of these did you tweet? http://ht.ly/doW0x     
    
    
    Thank you so much! RT @hbcu_lifestyle: @zkellyq NP! <3 what you all are doing. #KeepUpTheGreatWork    
    
    
    @mygola Thanks. I will read and respond! No problem.    
    
    
    @boydjane What tools do you like for curation? #blogchat    
    
    
    @boydjane Thanks, I'll check it out! #blogchat    
    
    
    @JTDabbagian Are your Pinterest pins linked back to your blog. P will drive traffic to your site.  #blogchat    
    
    
    Using Reddit & liking it but also use the other 2. RT @profkrg: What about Stumble and Tumblr? Users? #blogchat    
    
    
    @NickKellet We publish CollegeMomMinute podcast weekly http://www.smartcollegevisit.com/college-mom-minute/ … #blogchat    
    
    
    @recessionista Thanks, have been very impressed by amt of traffic Reddit is sending to http://SmartCollegeVisit.com . #blogchat    
    
    
    @Recessionista Good SEO = Good content, keywords and tagging. Repeat in the tools used to promote. #blogchat    
    
    
    @recessionista It never ends, does it?  #blogchat    
    
    
    Agree! RT @BruceSallan: Tweet Chats are a much more economical way for many brands to really reach AND connect with consumers!  #blogchat    
    
    
    @profkrg I think of it as similar to Stumble/a content aggregator (post what you've read). Similar to Digg. #blogchat    
    
    
    @profkrg According to http://Compete.com , @reddit gets more web traffic than the Stumble or Digg (recently anyway) check it out #blogchat    
    
    
    @audaciouslady High schools are teaching social media, too! #blogchat    
    
    
    @recessionista Have to become addicted to ur data. Review top 10posts w/most traffic/look for keywords that are driving those hits #blogchat    
    
    
    @audaciouslady I host #campuschat Wed 9pm. Topic: branding for teens. Hope u can join us! Hoping to have a HS class ! http://ht.ly/dpIAh     
    
    
    @audaciouslady Hope they do! I was surprised and pleased to hear it mentioned at 9th grade orientation for my teen.    
    
    
    @MirandaSman Google #1. Twitter is #2, then FB & FB mobile #blogchat    
    
    
    @MackCollier Enjoyed #blogchat tonight. It's been a while - nice to be back!    
    
    
    @MirandaSman Search. Need to do more with + #blogchat    
    
    
    @MackCollier Thanks, Mack!! Ditto! #blogchat    
    
    
    Save money with a one-tank trip! Join the #TMOM Twitter party 9pm EDT 9/3. RSVP: http://bit.ly/MWUppN     
    
    
    Save money with a one-tank trip! Join the #TMOM Twitter party 9pm EDT 9/3. RSVP: http://bit.ly/MWUppN     
    
    
    Thanks for the great advice for HS teens! RT @askjohnabout: Happy to be writing for @collegevisit. Who are your people? http://ht.ly/drbTp     
    
    
    Love this! RT @weekendinparis: It's "Take Your Flight Attendant Out To Dinner in Paris" Day http://bit.ly/NIKBPj  #oldpost #Paris    
    
    
    Great tips! Please share w/high schools RT @collegevisit: Advice on writing the best #college application essay http://ht.ly/dvktI     
    
    
    At #VaCIT waiting for @Lujure big announcement! #entrepreneurs    
    
    
    Hey, hey, @heyo !!    
    
    
    @CITGAPFunds Awesome! Honored to be in this group #GAP50    
    
    
    University of Tampa: Florida Vacation and Campus Visit http://bit.ly/OghHUS     
    
    
    More fun than packing! RT @jhiscock: Pre-travel rituals: Filling iPod with podcasts and new songs.I'm getting my head ready for travel now..    
    
    
    @jhiscock It's unpacking once I'm back home that I really don't like.    
    
    
    It's important to know who you are writing for. Try visualizing your ideal reader, give him/her a name. Makes it easier to write. #blogchat    
    
    
    @robpetersen We've done this at http://SmartCollegeVisit.com . Have a trusted blogger resource list is wonderful.  #blogchat    
    
    
    @sandee_jackson Yes, "personas" !! Could not think of the word. #needcoffee    
    
    
    @shannonbelew Thanks, Shannon. I find it helpful.    
    
    
    This is by a professional journalist & English prof on writing tight. Tips are great for bloggers, too! http://ht.ly/dA7J1  #blogchat    
    
    
    @davedelaney What tool do you like for keeping email lists/contacts? 
 #blogchat    
    
    
    @katmtaylor Thanks, I like Mailchimp, too. #blogchat    
    
    
    @rwardlow7 I had forgotten about them. Thanks for mentioning! #blogchat    
    
    
    @davedelaney Thanks! Agree about Gmail. #blogchat    
    
    
    @sandee_jackson Thanks, you, too! #blogchat    
    
    
    @davedelaney Nice chattin' #blogchat    
    
    
    Fine Tuning Your Social Media Strategy w/ #CampusChat guest @JasonFalls Wed 9PM ET, hosted by @collegevisit. Join us! #highered    
    
    
    Some Mondays are so much better than others. Hope you're having a good one!    
    
    
    A1 To make everyone jealous they're not with me, of course!  #tmom    
    
    
    @TibsTravel That's a great idea. I'm feeling "duh" -- why didn't I think of that -- research FB for travel destinations! #tmom    
    
    
    Agree! RT @CiaoMom: @travelingmoms I love 2 share postiive aspects by tagging. Things that were not great I would rather send an email #tmom    
    
    
    @CarmelLeeMooney Do you post your articles on your page? If so, tag the destination, then they will see it. #goodvibes #tmom    
    
    
    @CarmelLeeMooney Agree w/you about tagging #tmom    
    
    
    @travelingmoms Awesome! Thanks so much! Will DM! #tmom    
    
    
    Great chat! RT @kimorlando: Thanks to @chilihead for sharing her Facebook knowledge and for writing a tek book I want to read! #tmom    
    
    
    @kimorlando Most of it. Audio prob at beginning + off/on during chat. Enjoyed spreecast. Enjoyed #TMOM. Alot to keep up with at once tho.    
    
    
    @kimorlando Was it challenging for you to keep up?    
    
    
    @kimorlando Good to know! I plan on trying spreecast but have not decided on which chat!    
    
    
    @chilihead Thank you! Looking forward the book! Enjoyed the chat! Thanks for being with #TMOM tonight.    
    
    
    Hope you all can join me via @collegevisit: Fine Tuning Your Social Media Strategy w/ #CampusChat guest @JasonFalls Wed 9PM ET  #tmom    
    
    
    Fine Tuning Your Social Media Strategy with Jason Falls http://bit.ly/RBvKJt     
    
    
    @johntlawlor Looking forward to your findings re: males & #highered.    
    
    
    @johntlawlor When do you expect to release the overview?    
    
    
    @johntlawlor Thanks, pls follow so I can reply via dm.    
    
    
    @Handshake20 @aciwebs Thought you'd like this: Ranking The Top Social Media Outlets, Fantasy Football Style http://ht.ly/dDEwi     
    
    
    @carmelleemooney You got it! Now following :)    
    
    
    @jasonfalls Known you online for a while, was nice to meet in person at #blogworld. Thanks again for being on #campuschat    
    
    
    Congrats, Eric! RT @citgapfunds: Congrats to the newest #GAP50 finalist: Eric Collins, President of @SansSeriph Design http://ow.ly/dzm0h     
    
    
    Looking forward to being on #TMOM panel tonight 9pm: Parents Day at College http://ht.ly/dLwgA     
    
    
    @tvparrot Thanks so much! #TMOM will be so much fun tonight (but then it always is)!    
    
    
    @CollegeChat Great topic! I hope to make it!    
    
    
    @orderoochaos can't wait for #campuschat tomorrow night! So happy to have you as my guest!    
    
    
    @handshake20 Congrats!    
    
    
    Learn how to tell your story via @GSBrownABC http://ht.ly/e7ivh  at the Family Travel Conf #FTCDallas w/ @travelingmoms #tmom    
    
    
    @GSBrownABC Looking forward to meeting you at the Family Travel Con in Nov! #FTCDallas #TMOM    
    
    
    Get insider tips for traveling like a local on the Oct. 1 #TMOM Twitter party with #RIThrival. RSVP for prizes: http://bit.ly/NPh5IU     
    
    
    On college visits, always ask the students where to get the best whatever (burger, pizza, veggies, etc.) #tmom    
    
    
    A3 Ask for restaurant recs on Twitter of course.  #tmom    
    
    
    @mygola Yes, looking forward to it.    
    
    
    Have u registered 4 Family Travel Conference in Dallas? Focus=video. Speakers @wendyperrin @GSBrownABC + #FTCDallas http://bit.ly/OvW96O     
    
    
    Only at the Family Travel Conf: How to Use Social Media to Grow Your Brand w/Conde Nast @wendyperrin Nov 9-11 http://ht.ly/e7jlS     
    
    
    @donnadilley Thanks, Donna! Excited to be among so many fine VA companies! #GAP50    
    
    
    @handshake20 Thank you -- what a week for @collegevisit!    
    
    
    Join me at the Family #Travel Conf: How to Use Social Media to Grow Your Brand w/Conde Nast @wendyperrin Nov 9-11 http://ht.ly/ediKR     
    
    
    Have u registered 4 Family Travel Conference? Focus is on video! Speakers @wendyperrin @GSBrownABC + #FTCDallas http://bit.ly/OvW96O     
    
    
    Click here http://ht.ly/e7jtj  for the complete list of #FTCDallas workshops -Family Travel Conference Nov 9-11 #TMOM    
    
    
    Join us: Family Travel Conf Nov 9-11 in Dallas w/@ChristiMcNeill @GSBrownABC @KimOrlando @newmediatravel & many more! #FTCDallas #TMOM    
    
    
    Family Travel Conference is coming up! Nov 9-12 Get hands on experience in video production!  #FTCDallas #TMOM http://ht.ly/ehHBO     
    
    
    Here's just 1 of the cool travel peeps you'll meet at #FTCDallas @newmediatravel, Travel editor for @technoriti http://ht.ly/ehKk1     
    
    
    Only at the Family Travel Conf: How to Use Social Media to Grow Your Brand w/Conde Nast @wendyperrin Nov 9-11 http://ht.ly/e7jow     
    
    
    Get schooled on educational travel on the #TMOM Twitter party 10/8. RSVP: http://bit.ly/Sl3sE5     
    
    
    Agree! RT @DebMomOf3: RT @chickadeeprints: Q1: offer to chaperone, its puts both of your fears to rest.  #tmom    
    
    
    A1 Don't fear the school bus. They have high visibility on the road.  #tmom    
    
    
    If you can, offer to pay for a kid who may not get to go.  #tmom    
    
    
    A2 Chaperoned 2nd grade zoo trip. Kind of like herding cats! #tmom    
    
    
    Oops, zoo trip was not overnight - thankfully! #tmom    
    
    
    Have them make a field trip passport book they can update after each trip #tmom    
    
    
    @FirstClassKris Wish I had thought of it when my kids were young! #tmom    
    
    
    Family. Travel. Conference. Fun. Join me Nov 9-12 #Dallas http://ht.ly/elwkA  # @FamTravConf #FTCDallas #travel #TMOM    
    
    
    Family travel video workshop  Nov 9-12 #Dallas http://ht.ly/elwwc  # @FamTravConf #FTCDallas #travel #TMOM    
    
    
    Share w/your fav mom blogger: Family Travel Conference video workshop, Nov 9-12 in Dallas! #FTCDallas #TMOM http://bit.ly/R4doQj     
    
    
    Starting to gather gear for the Family Travel Conf #FTCDallas http://ht.ly/elQ1y     
    
    
    @jodigrundig Ditto!! Meeting other moms and writers is the best! #FTCDallas    
    
    
    What I hope to learn about #video at the Family Travel Conf #FTCDallas http://ht.ly/elQ4o     
    
    
    Innovation in America is alive and well at #DCDI2012. Amazing ideas and pitches! #entrepreneurs    
    
    
    "speed to market is critical" - #DCDI2012    
    
    
    @heyo Go Nathan! pic.twitter.com/vnQg3VUK    
    
    
    Can't wait to learn #video tips  at the Family Travel Conf #FTCDallas http://ht.ly/elQ4o     
    
    
    Just set up a stream in @HootSuite to follow all of the awesome #FTCDallas speakers I will meet in Nov! http://ht.ly/esxyW  #TMOM    
    
    
    @handshake20 @kenmaready @heyo @hutchlaw #DCDI2012 was terrific! Thanks for all the shoutouts!    
    
    
    @wanderingtastes @jodigrundig Looking forward to #FTCDallas with you!    
    
    
    @pauleisenberg Truth: have always wanted to attend #comiccon. Don't think my kids approve of my #innergeek.    
    
    
    @chilihead Have you tried @Hootsuite? Desktop and iphone - both good.    
    
    
    @TravelingMom, @TakingtheKids, @FamilyTravelForum
& @TMShowcase present #FTCDallas - November 9-11, 2012    
    
    
    @dianarowe Diana, can't wait to see you at the #FTCDallas conf in Nov! Disney was a long time ago!    
    
    
    Ciao #TMOM @ElenaSonnino shares how relaxing travel during her chemo made things better http://bit.ly/QjrwBh  via @TravelingMoms    
    
    
    Ditto! RT @chaotic_barb: I *might* be shopping for a new pair of cowboy boots for when I @visit_dallas #FTCDallas    
    
    
    @kstraw No doubt! Looking forward to #FTCDallas @visit_dallas next month!    
    
    
    Thanks @nancyberk for another great #podcast! RT @collegevisit: College Mom Minute: Insurance Policies http://bit.ly/RYBlZL     
    
    
    Now this is totally awesome! RT @judy511: Traveling Mom Named Top Travel Blog @kimorlando @CindyRichards http://bit.ly/PDfKqH     
    
    
    Wow! RT @tmshowcase: 13 days until Family Travel Conference in Dallas produced by Travel Media Showcase.  http://bit.ly/OvW96O  #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Hurricane Sandy Alert Tracking resource list & tips #travel & #college #application updates http://ht.ly/eQoca  via @CollegeVisit    
    
    
    Good luck to all the #TMOM s in the northeast tonight! #travelingmom    
    
    
    Congrats on the new vid! RT @thetechpad: Our new site is live! Check out our sweet promo video. http://fb.me/22yBWT6o5     
    
    
    @thetechpad Sorry to miss all fun! Off-site meetings today are keeping us away today. Hope you get lots of visitors!    
    
    
    Countdown to Family Travel Conference http://bit.ly/TF6Rwm     
    
    
    Countdown to Family Travel Conference http://bit.ly/TF6Rwm  #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Share your holiday traditions on the #TMOM Twitter party 9pm EDT 11/5. RSVP for prizes: http://bit.ly/sonyholiday     
    
    
    Holiday travel: Where, What, Why, and How. Join the convo at the @travelingmoms FB page. http://ht.ly/eY3h7  #TMOM    
    
    
    Tonight: Share your holiday traditions on the #TMOM Twitter party 9pm EDT 11/5. RSVP for prizes: http://bit.ly/sonyholiday     
    
    
    Happy Thursday! Feels like a Friday to me -- traveling to #FTCDallas tomorrow! #TMOM    
    
    
    Hungry right now in #blacksburg? Ceratano's is yummy! Italian buffet! Best pizza ever!    
    
    
    @debmomof3 Hope your flight was sweet. Can't wait to see you again! #FTCDallas    
    
    
    @CindyRichards Ditto! Missed each other in Chicago, but not in Dallas! #FTCDallas    
    
    
    All my flights to #Dallas for #FTCDallas smooth and w/early arrival! TY #USAIRWAYS    
    
    
    #FTCDallas is about to begin! Pluggin in and loggin on!    
    
    
    #FTCDallas Beautiful welcome from #OmniDallas @FamTRavConf, more details to come!    
    
    
    Every guest-room has tv in bathroom mirror, now that's a wow! #FTCDallas    
    
    
    "Create a bond of trust" most important In all uses of social media via @WendyPerrin #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Write about what you wish you'd known before the trip - that's what your audience wants via @KristaParry #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Authentic content is a must via @Takingthekids & @KristaParry #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Be passionate about helping others #blogging @KristaParry #FTCDallas #snowmamas    
    
    
    Health focus/food allergies need to be addressed more in travel blogging #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Multi-gen travel info needed. "We're all more active" via @dianarowe #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Homeschooling and travel go together #FTCDallas    
    
    
    "So many different types of traveling kids. Let's keep them in mind too." #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Just one of the events during #ftcdallas #Dallas http://www.medievaltimes.com/dallas.aspx     
    
    
    Thank you #omnidallas #ftcdallas !!! pic.twitter.com/1Cgo3xTP    
    
    
    Delicious evening at @dallaszoo #FTCDallas pic.twitter.com/HXKfnCKv    
    
    
    Good morning #FTCDallas !    
    
    
    Workshop starting: What's the story: Captivate Your Audience @gsbrownABC @NewMediaTravel @travelwithval @PaulEisenberg #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Always ask "What's the takeaway." via @gsbrownABC #FTCDallas    
    
    
    " Not every story needs a video" #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Pitching a TV segment? Be prepared to produce it. #FTCDallas    
    
    
        
    
    
    Mobile booking apps can save bucks on hotel rooms! @gsbrownABC #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Kaleel Sakakeeny shares his know how about creating video content. #ftcdallas pic.twitter.com/xm99bfsQ    
    
    
    "The video post card lets the content be king." @NewMediaTravel #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Draw me into the essence of "chef-ness @NewMediaTravel #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Your video is about the experience #FTCDallas @NewMediaTravel    
    
    
    You need stills in video via @NewMediaTravel #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Now up @travelwithval #ftcdallas pic.twitter.com/8BPC04h5    
    
    
    Val and her video camera - that's @travelwithval #FTCDallas "think like a reporter"    
    
    
    Keep your ears open for "nat-sound" via @travelwithval #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Different approaches to creating video @gsbrownABC @NewMediaTravel @travelwithval #FTCDallas What can you do?    
    
    
    Happiness and lunch with #Disney #FTCDisney pic.twitter.com/1vFNQmlu    
    
    
    Road trip to #GalleriaDallasHoliday. 1st Xmas tree for me this yr: largest indoor Xmas tree! #FTCDallas    
    
    
    @kstraw The skating was Awesome! #GalleriaDallasHoliday Did not expect to see ice skating in #Dallas #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Good morning #FTCDallas! Kicking off today with @ChiliHead & great tips for using Facebook. 1. Start with goals    
    
    
    Make goals measurable, specific, and relevant via @ChiliHead #FTCDallas    
    
    
    You #FB cover photo is YOUR BRAND! @ChiliHead #FTCDallas    
    
    
    #FB engagement do you solve, educate or entertain? #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Make it easy to complete the call to action #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Experiment w/ text and images/track what works via @ChiliHead #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Invitation to share great form of engagement but follow up, pay attention per @ChiliHead #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Note to self: look at interest lists to organize what I want to keep with #FTCDallas #Facebook    
    
    
    Pinterest can be used as a bookmarking site for your audience per @ChiliHead #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Who would of thought? #Pinterest for resumes! #FTCDallas    
    
    
    @chilihead Thanks for all the great #FB & #Pinterest tips! #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Welcome @SouthwestAir to #FTCDallas !!    
    
    
    For @SouthwestAir short messages and photos rule! #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Good idea: test social media channel personally first. If it works, try w/your brand. @SouthwestAir #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Pinning when really Relevant and dynamic--nice, not everything needs to be posted #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Follow an editorial calendar, but be flexible! Great tip from @SouthwestAir (@gailAtSCV loves this!) #FTCDallas    
    
    
        
    
    
    @graceduffy Nice. I pin content relevant to @collegevisit. #FTCDallas    
    
    
    @SheldonWordNerd can you email me?    
    
    
    Spectacular Chihuly glass sculpture at @DallasArboretum pic.twitter.com/og6WqQol    
    
    
    Moms wear many hats. In Dallas, I got to wear 3. #ftcdallas #visitdallas pic.twitter.com/Bzq0IrEZ    
    
    
    @kimorlando Gee, do I have to wait til 11/19 to say I'm thankful for #TMOM and @FamTravConf? #FTCDallas rocked!    
    
    
    #ThankfulFor All the fabulous parents I met at #FTCDallas, #travel, #TMOM and my family.    
    
    
    TY!  RT @handshake20: Internet co founded in #Blacksburg make the list http://bit.ly/TLiIa5  @skillcapped @collegevisit @VirtualUFashion    
    
    
    Good article! RT @jogebauer: Burn Your Corporate Blog And Get Published http://bit.ly/QIQqLo  via @JasonFalls    
    
    
    I'm reading, 'The KISS Method to Digital Marketing Success' by @NetBase @JasonFalls. Get a free copy: http://bit.ly/PuJeSv     
    
    
    "we can give you guidance and guardrails" @dharrisindc @Startup_VA    
    
    
    @thetechpad What a week! Tech Pad is hoppin:  @Startup_VA @aneeshchopra @dharrisindc @MarkWarner all in the same week!    
    
    
    Rekindling Romance: Even Entrepreneurs need to Getaway http://bit.ly/UZayvx     
    
    
    You know you live in a small town when you get teary about a fav postal worker retiring: http://ht.ly/fDWF4  lady of letters #Blacksburg    
    
    
    Ever feel this way: Even Entrepreneurs need to Getaway http://bit.ly/UZayvx  #TMOM    
    
    
    Mary Miller introduces @markwarner at #vacrowdfunding event @techpad pic.twitter.com/r4NgmcIr    
    
    
    80% of all new jobs in past 20 years  have come from startups @markwarner #vacrowdfunding #BVA #blacksburg    
    
    
    You should not have to leave your hometown to create a world class business via @markwarner #vacrowdfunding #BVA    
    
    
    @MarkWarner we're working on making @collegevisit one of those world class companies #BVA #startup    
    
    
    'twas the Night Before SATs  http://bit.ly/TwEeOH     
    
    
    Did u see @HopeSprings? Share yr fave rekindling romance tips on #TMOM Twitter 12/3 9pm ET #TMOMHope. RSVP http://bit.ly/hopespring     
    
    
    10 questions to ask on a college visit http://ht.ly/fK7bC  -- my new post for @USATODAYcollege. Who's visiting colleges this weekend?    
    
    
    Join #TMOM Twitter to talk romantic #travel on 12/3 9pm ET #TMOMHope. RSVP for prizes http://bit.ly/hopespring     
    
    
    Did u see @HopeSprings? Share yr fave rekindling romance tips on #TMOM Twitter 12/3 9pm ET #TMOMHope. RSVP http://bit.ly/hopespring     
    
    
        
    
    
    Have you ever felt like Meryl Streep in the move "Hope Springs" ? Then join #TMOM at 9PM ET ! http://ht.ly/fMklw     
    
    
    Truth! RT @twinlins: Cool prizes! Join @travelingmoms to talk romantic travel 9pm ET tonight! http://ow.ly/fJtlw  #TMOM #TMOMHope    
    
    
    Woohoo!  RT @ConnieFoggles: @MaryHeston @FamilyTravel4um @RachelFerrucci @zkellyq #TMOM #TMOMHope #tmom    
    
    
    @maryheston Are you having trouble remembering, too? #TMOMHope #tmom    
    
    
    Q1:  Now this is sad: I can't remember where!  #TMOM #HOPESPRINGS    
    
    
    @maryheston Of course - that works! #tmom    
    
    
    Sweet! RT @ConnieFoggles: @DebMomOf3 Thats a sign of real love - you dont remember and it doesnt matter! #tmom    
    
    
    So true! RT @kimorlando: Movies like @HopeSprings bring all the memories flooding back! #TMOM #TMOMHope #tmom    
    
    
    I could use a trip like that right now! RT @ConnieFoggles: A2. Going away alone and leaving all the stress behind. Ahh! #tmom    
    
    
    Q2: Travel is magic - makes day to day distractions disappear! #TMOM #HOPESPRINGS    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mimitravelz Same here - #tmom #tmomhope But now I'm curious - what would that trip look like? May need to drop some hints!    
    
    
    @mummadear Agree!! #tmom TMOMHOPE    
    
    
    Q3: Here's hoping!  #TMOM #HOPESPRINGS    
    
    
    @maryheston @ramblingstump We have a #yurt dealer in Floyd, VA: http://www.blueridgeyurts.com/  #TMOMHOPE #tmom    
    
    
    @dianarowe Had to stay a cheap hotel once & the lights & TV were on when we came in. That was creepy. #TMOMHOPE #tmom    
    
    
    @ramblingstump Tiny houses (built by elves?) :) Would love to see pics. #TMOM #TMOMHOPE    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @ramblingstump: @zkellyq I have a whole Pinterest board of Tiny Houses- think a fort for grown ups. #TMOM #TMOMHope    
    
    
    @wanderingtastes Easier to clean!  #TMOM #TMOMHope    
    
    
    Q5: Least fav gift: jumper cables. #TMOM #HOPESPRINGS    
    
    
    LOL! RT @CarmelLeeMooney: @ConnieFoggles Renew by sea phone? #tmomhope #tmom    
    
    
    Q6: A mountain resort would be lovely!  #TMOM #HOPESPRINGS    
    
    
    Great fun tonight, y'all! #TMOMHOPE #tmom    
    
    
    Happy Wednesday, everyone! Make it an awesome day!    
    
    
    Milk and Cookies at the Magnolia http://ht.ly/fQd7o  #visitdallas #FTCDallas #TMOM    
    
    
    Ooo! Another cool #CollegeMomMinute parenting tip from @NancyBerk http://bit.ly/11St4JF     
    
    
    Off to a great morning with #BVA Startup Blacksburg @TechPad    
    
    
    @aneeshchopra We're in @Startup_VA @collegevisit !    
    
    
    The funnest (that's a word, right?), fastest hour you'll spend online http://ht.ly/fWNOx  Join #TMOM Twitter party Mon night! RSVP/Prizes!    
    
    
    Big thanks to @conniefoggles for sharing her parent / college visit tip on SmartCollegeVisit today: http://ht.ly/fYbIx  via @collegevisit    
    
    
    A few reasons why I fell in love w/ Dallas: Growing & Learning @dallasarboretum http://bit.ly/QYw1Go  @visit_dallas #TMOM #FTCDallas    
    
    
    Teachers: The First Heroes We Know via Smart College Visit #education http://tinyurl.com/cbazzxu  via @collegevisit    
    
    
    @Delta Just got a txt msg from you re: E-boarding pass for someone I don't know. Perhaps a typo by the user re: ph #?  Can we DM?    
    
    
    @deltaassist Yes and a qr code    
    
    
    @deltaassist 00623174935194    
    
    
    @deltaassist Yes will do.    
    
    
    @deltaassist Thanks for all your help. I appreciate the quick response and hand-holding to figure this out.    
    
    
    Anybody else working on site updates instead of shopping? :)    
    
    
    @nancyberk So jealous! Great view from @MBhotelCT !!    
    
    
    Still searching for the perfect gift? Try this: Crowdfunding Shopping Guide for the Gift-Challenged via @handshake20 http://bit.ly/V14v9t     
    
    
    @karenafull Ha! I know how that goes! Looking forward to catching up in Jan! Hope your holidays are merry and bright!    
    
    
    @akilbello Happy Christmas!    
    
    
    #Crowdfunding sites - a great place to find the #thenextbigthing for Xmas! http://bit.ly/V14v9t     
    
    
        
    
    
    4all my #startup friends @RBTC @TechPad @StartupVA Need last-minute, ubercool gift? Shop on #crowdfunding sites http://bit.ly/V14v9t     
    
    
    @katiepritchard Way to relax !! Merry Christmas!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @healthtechhatch Thanks for sharing the link! #crowdfunding shopping guide!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I always new my focus on medieval lit in #college would be useful! Fun times at @MedievalTimes http://ht.ly/grSxU  #TMOM #FTCDallas    
    
    
    CampusChat 2013 Begins Tonight at 9PM ET http://bit.ly/Vj58eJ     
    
    
    @weekendinparis Travel is an awesome way to begin the new year. Make that "Ahhhhhsome" since there's a spa involved! Have fun!    
    
    
    @weekendinparis Great! Getting into college means everyone celebrates!    
    
    
    Startup Metrics and Data http://tech.co/startup-metrics-data-2012-12 … via @techcocktail    
    
    
    Top 10 questions to ask about Study Abroad while on your #collegevisit http://ht.ly/gyWZc     
    
    
    Area jobs lists on our #TrailingSpouse site http://www.trailing-spouse.com/  #Blacksburg #Christiansburg #Radford #NRV    
    
    
    @dtcav Loved your blogtalk radio interview with your mom and @NancyBerk!    
    
    
    How Do You Begin Your College Search? http://bit.ly/VVVxKI     
    
    
    All you ever need to know about SAT and ACT - Download Free! http://bit.ly/WRcvZg     
    
    
    Why We Are Asking You to Contribute to Cognichoice's Crowdfunding Campaign:  http://bit.ly/SCCrgt  via @handshake20    
    
    
    @handshake20 Your #crowdfunding project is off to a great start! Congrats, Anne! I just posted the link to #LinkedIn. http://ht.ly/gQ1wV     
    
    
    Got #flushot? College Mom Minute @nancyberk calls for "Medical Reinforcements" for your college kid http://ht.ly/gMWsN     
    
    
    @aneeshchopra RT @handshake20: Our #crowdfunding campaign4 #mhealth app @cognichoice is live on @healthtechhatch! http://bit.ly/SDGBEF  #BVA    
    
    
    The A-B-Cs of Applying to College - SCV Workshop http://bit.ly/UQw0lg     
    
    
    I'm attending Montgomery County Regional Tourism Strategic Planning Session 2 http://conta.cc/UkvNvU  #constantcontact    
    
    
    Congrats! RT @elenasonnino: Excited to announce & be a part of the launch of the #HiltonMomVoyage site! http://ow.ly/gUEie  #TMOM    
    
    
    Nancy & her celebs - Gr8t stuff! RT @nancyberk: My Whine At 9 audio podcast is free on iTunes. #Celebrity Conversations http://ow.ly/gVB7m     
    
    
    @cvlkulow Fabulous to meet you #IRL!! Love having a @collegevisit buddy in Cville!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just learned #MCVA has 3 wineries!    
    
    
    Cool swag from tourism mtg Montgomery County #VA Yay!! pic.twitter.com/7Ly5qao3    
    
    
    Fab! RT @nancyberk: Loved this wk's episode of @WhineAt9 w/ the brilliant @chriscerf http://ow.ly/h6XoJ  #SesameStreet #NationalLampoon    
    
    
    We had fun with this! RT @collegevisit: New SCV Video: Going On  College Tours  http://bit.ly/10S4smD     
    
    
    Want to make changes in your life? There's an app for that in development: http://ht.ly/h7I62  #behavioralhealth app by @cognichoice    
    
    
    Now this is a great place to chill after visiting colleges in #Dallas: Omni Dallas: High Tech, High Touch http://ht.ly/h7KQI     
    
    
    The Bike Barn Wall in downtown #Blacksburg!! pic.twitter.com/lliZXI2P    
    
    
    @visitblacksburg The murals in #Blacksburg are awesome!    
    
    
    @thetechpad Thanks for sharing the @collegevisit story!    
    
    
    @loisgeller Lois, I've been watching your @YouTube videos and loving them!  #branding    
    
    
    Wise words from @NancyBerk for the #Harbaugh parents before the #superbowl game begins http://ht.ly/hkzjN     
    
    
    This year the game is better than the commercials! #sb49    
    
    
        
    
    
    Q2 Craziest thing-not in a good way-was someone driving in the wrong direction on the highway! #roadtrip #TMOM    
    
    
    Q3 I've always loved packing for & heading to the beach or lake or camping. #Roadtrip #TMOM    
    
    
    Q4 Doesn't matter. Passenger becomes navigator, climate control mgr, and car DJ. Driving is easier! #Roadtrip #TMOM    
    
    
    @kimorlando Q4 I left out snack hostess    
    
    
    @mimitravelz @cindyrichards Agree! Love scenic roads. a welcome relief from driving the daily routine! #tmom    
    
    
    Q5 Daily use. Sometimes better (& exciting) to rent a car for #roadtrips. #TMOM    
    
    
    @kimorlando Always fun to rent and drive a variety of car types #TMOM    
    
    
    Q6 #Roadtrip playlist what ever daughter has mixed or the usual: #Beatles, Steely Dan, Yes #TMOM    
    
    
    Happiness is a Mobile App or Two http://bit.ly/11N6EMN     
    
    
    Love this! RT @suzanneshaffer: Q7 Have heard some parents text a "word of the day" and use it in a sentence. #campuschat    
    
    
    Mobile apps make me happy. Making them via @collegevisit makes me happy, too. http://ht.ly/hvqA5     
    
    
    Great Google Search tip!! RT @collegevisit: Love Tip #10 from Scholarship Mom @AidScholarship on how to "Search Smart"  http://ht.ly/hxgeN     
    
    
    Looking a job in #Blacksburg or #Roanoke? Check out http://Trailing-Spouse.com  for a list of job links: http://ht.ly/hEpVZ     
    
    
    Booking travel to visit college #TravelTip: Book flight & hotel together to save $$ http://bit.ly/XEtUZN  #campustour    
    
    
    Listening to @nancyberk 's interview with @DevonAllman. Touching, insightful...can't wait to listen to his music! http://ht.ly/hYYsW     
    
    
    Is a mobile app part of your #college #recruitment strategy next FY? It should be. Here's why: http://www.scvmobile.me/     
    
    
    You were right! RT @nancyberk: @zkellyq You'll love #TurquoiseAlbum by @devonallman Great musician and writer!    
    
    
    Everybody needs a little @prezi on a Friday! Here's one from @GailatSCV Golf & Campus Visits: Of Course http://ht.ly/ial5H     
    
    
    @nancyberk Agree! Perfect timing @RedWidowABC.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Adding a round of golf to your college visit? RT @collegevisit: Golf & Campus Visits: Of Course  http://ht.ly/iajXr  #collegegolf    
    
    
        
    
    
    Scholarship Mom Tip #14: Always Ask a Business http://bit.ly/Xsn36E     
    
    
    Enjoyed talking tourism, #NRV, #Blacksburg #MontCo and more with @MCVLisa this morning!    
    
    
    Does your dorm room look like this? Time for a switcheroo! http://bit.ly/ZbyDkA     
    
    
    Car Tech. Traveling back from #nyc & Pace U @CollegeVisit #tmom pic.twitter.com/fZTLaFOgOm    
    
    
    What Do You Want in a Hotel on your College Visit? http://bit.ly/13SXfUL     
    
    
    To all my #collegebound #tmom friends: New survey: What Do You Want in a Hotel on your #CollegeVisit? http://bit.ly/13SXfUL     
    
    
    @frederickcook Congrats on @Moveline successes, Fred!    
    
    
    How to get the word out from @AidScholarship RT @collegevisit: Scholarship Mom Tip #16: Tell Everyone http://bit.ly/14eOYeh     
    
    
    Watching #livestream of #CrowdTilt founders in #Blacksburg http://ht.ly/jlRbt  "Become numb to failure and move as fast as you can"    
    
    
    #crowdtilt founders: "startup love at first sight" @thetechpad    
    
    
    I use the front ashtray for parking meter $, but that little ashtray in the backseat is totally useless. #tmom    
    
    
        
    
    
    A computer workstation would be nice on the road #tmom pic.twitter.com/VPJahppx1T    
    
    
    @ramblingstump I remember my old Toyota had that. I think I hauled 2x4s #tmom    
    
    
    Auto ashtray = Tollbooth piggy bank! #tmom    
    
    
    @LuxuryTravelMom gotta haul stuff! #tmom    
    
    
    Booking It to The Library Hotel in #NYC http://ht.ly/jD7gK  #hotelreview #TMOM    
    
    
    As founder of @collegevisit, I'm looking forward to being part of @radfordu women's leadership panel next week! http://ht.ly/jHP8s     
    
    
    My fav #gmailtip RT @aidscholarship: Gmail Undo Send – Saving You from Your Mistakes http://goo.gl/bIyzV  via @wonderoftech    
    
    
    Scholarship Mom Tip #18 Deadlines Change!!  http://www.smartcollegevisit.com/2013/04/scholarship-mom-tip-18.html …    
    
    
    Clear skies in #pa Heading to #blacksburg #va and to snow!    
    
    
    only 206 miles to go! #longestdayever    
    
    
    @vtktorg @gailatscv is driving. I get to tweet! Clear and open road in WV can't stop now!    
    
    
    @vtktorg Hope she made home ok! We are in #va now, just drove into rain. Heard it was melting in #blacksburg    
    
    
    @Mike_TheBurgs Hi Mike! Is is still snowing in #blacksburg? Hoping to make it home tonight    
    
    
    @mike_theburgs We did! Long day/late night, but good to be back in #blacksburg (snow and all!). Traffic was light which made the drive go...    
    
    
    Aww, @jasonpinter should have been on  #CampusChat Wed night! RT @collegeologist: Hysterical but see what I mean? 
http://www.huffingtonpost.com/mobileweb/jason-pinter/why-i-a-straight-guy-shou_b_2999275.html?icid=hp_college_featured_art …    
    
    
    Listening to a podcast on my TV. Which one? @Whineat9 by @nancyberk !!    
    
    
    Scholarship Mom Tip #20: Share Your Story http://bit.ly/15omOxO     
    
    
    Mom: My First Mentor http://bit.ly/YxhAbP     
    
    
    Excited when son said he would like to read "The Iliad." I told him I had a copy. He replied:"No, I mean if it was required for a class."    
    
    
    When I need inspiration, I go to @TedTalks. Even better when I know the speaker: http://ht.ly/kBadr  Inspired today by @hesonwheels    
    
    
    @goingmobo Looking forward to talking with you tomorrow!    
    
    
    Smart College Visit Nominated for Rising Star http://bit.ly/12ZEk8Z     
    
    
    Excited to share: Co-founder of @Cognichoice Will Be Guest on mHealth Zone Live by @Happtique #mHealthZone Th 5/2 http://bit.ly/Ziyz1G     
    
    
    @akilbello Thanks!! So excited to be nominated!    
    
    
    Can't wait for #CampusChat tonight!! 9PM ET -- only 1 hour to go!    
    
    
    HootUpROA today! RT @dhatfield: So proud to have you! RT @collegevisit: Looking forward to being part of #HootUpRoa! http://ht.ly/kBuQQ     
    
    
    Getting some #hootlove at #HootUpRoa !!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hootin' it up at #hootuproa with @dhatfield and @brandonpierce pic.twitter.com/34JHagb8Y9    
    
    
    Let the #HootUpRoa begin with @dhatfield pic.twitter.com/HsxCOnOQUi    
    
    
    The count is now up to having met 4 ppl named "Brandon" in the past 24 hours. Lovely name, lovely people, too!    
    
    
    Love the advice Danielle shared! RT @collegevisit: Social media advice for teens! Video interview w/ @dhatfield #HootUpRoa    
    
    
    @keegan4delegate Great to see at #HootUpRoa last night!    
    
    
    Interview with @dhatfield at #HootUpROA RT @collegevisit: Teen Tip Social Media 101: What Goes Online Stays Online http://bit.ly/11xYN7i     
    
    
    Q3Voice activated radio station tuner that works would be nice #tmom    
    
    
    @yourcollegekid Join us tonight on #campuschat for study tips with smartphones from @goingmobo #mobobrain    
    
    
    Another great Scholarship Mom Tip- #24: Note Dollars and Dates (pls RT!) http://bit.ly/10ZwXJx     
    
    
    Congrats! RT @thetechcouncil: Congrats to @MiserWare for the Rising Star Award! Glad to have you on board in the #RBTC ! #TechNite    
    
    
    Love that I can ask another #tmom about a place I am going and one of them will have been there!    
    
    
    @DebMomOf3 Deb, so glad you shared the hurricane app link! Thanks! #tmom    
    
    
    @vtktorg An awesome @collegevisit 
breakfast awaits with some truly awesome people!    
    
    
    Have not decided, but getting some great ideas from you all! #tmom    
    
    
    A2 A little of both! Some planning/ some winging (more winging).  #tmom    
    
    
    @kimorlando I love it when the kids plan!  #tmom    
    
    
    Agree! RT @runitbymom: @travelingmoms Q3 going in the middle of the week.. steer clear of weekend  #tmom    
    
    
    @Kimberredneck There's also an app called "iExit" with that type of info #tmom    
    
    
    @Kimberredneck Perfect! #tmom    
    
    
    Agree! RT @runitbymom: #tmom q6 we eat out less and save the money for vacay #tmom    
    
    
    Had a friend once who had a swear jar - anyone who said a bad word had to put money in the jar. They were saving for Disney.  #tmom    
    
    
    Great idea! RT @TinaSeitzinger: @kimorlando A6: I have a vacation acct that I put money into throughout the year. Really helps!  #tmom    
    
    
    @newstipps "decision"? What exactly was decided? Seems like a suggestion was made, not a decision?    
    
    
    Talking startups with @aneeshchopra in #Blacksburg pic.twitter.com/kLkdn6XRnH    
    
    
        
    
    
    Suggestion from attendee re: needs in #VA "Leave women's rights alone; create more jobs" @aneeshchopra    
    
    
    Jobs talk now w/ education. "Education is our seed corn...pays dividends in the future" @aneeshchopra    
    
    
    @NewsTipps thanks for the info!    
    
    
    Off-line fun! RT @handshake20: Throquet: The World's First New Lawn Game http://bit.ly/1aVmfd8     
    
    
    @us_ignite Let's discuss. Follow me @zkellyq or @collegevisit and we can DM    
    
    
    9PM ET !! RT @cindyrichards: Where will you #roadtrip this summer? Share on #tmom tonite. Starts in 90 min!    
    
    
    Parents of Freshmen -> RT @collegevisit: College Travel: Make Hotel Reservations Now  http://bit.ly/18LeYNK     
    
    
        
    
    
    This "What is your ideal vacay?" question seems like it should be asked while dating! #factfindingmission #tmom    
    
    
    @kimorlando Now we need to raise our kids to ask these questions when they find love! #tmom    
    
    
    @cindyrichards Let me know if you come south for #Dollywood. It's not that far from me! #tmom    
    
    
    A3 Not assigned exactly, but I prefer to pack the car #tmom    
    
    
    @bbpinktaz #emptynest - kinda like a new home! #tmom    
    
    
    A morning without rain? A bright start in #Blacksburg today!    
    
    
    Bacon? A 1st for hotel recs?! RT @haroldbanks2: @sheratonhotels @travelingmoms I love your bacon!  #SheratonClub & #TMOM @sheratonhotels    
    
    
    Agree! RT @delovely_m0mma2: @travelingmoms Q3 - Once in a lifetime experiences! #TMOM #SHERATONCLUB #ad    
    
    
    A4 A very quiet AC - heating/cooling system. Can't stand loud fans in a hotel room #tmom    
    
    
    A4 power outlets by the bed at nightstand level for charging phones at night. #musthave #tmom #sheratonclub    
    
    
    @delovely_m0mma2 Exactly! #TMOM #SHERATONCLUB    
    
    
    @kimorlando Never tried Club Level, will have to soon! #tmom #sheratonclub    
    
    
    Also, prefer: instant email confirmations after booking a room + reminders/welcome message day of travel. #tmom #sheratonclub    
    
    
    Yep! RT @kimorlando: A6 I have never regretted a spa treatment. Like pizza - even bad ones are pretty good! #SheratonClub #ad #TMOM    
    
    
    Gr8t! RT @travelingmoms:Thx to our panelists! @kimorlando @DebMomOf3 @CindyRichards @ramblingstump @techmama @maryheston #TMOM #SheratonClub    
    
    
    Great #traveltips on #TMOM tonight! #sheratonclub    
    
    
    @TeresaShaw Congrats!! #tmom #sheratonclub    
    
    
    Tech: The growth vitamin women entrepreneurs need http://www.techpageone.com/business/tech-the-growth-vitamin-that-women-entrepreneurs-need/#.UcAmZKp5okp.twitter …    
    
    
    How to make the most of your #mobobrain http://ht.ly/mbJd8  via @goingmobo    
    
    
    Now this is a great #traveltip! RT @robynsworld: @kimorlando @techmama Always upgrade yourself on vacation - you're worth it!    
    
    
    Sun is shining, slight breeze, cats sleep while hummingbirds flit back and forth. Hope your day=Beautiful too.    
    
    
    Scholarship Mom Tip #30: Don't forget the Resume http://bit.ly/19xtXyH     
    
    
    Excite to be at #LinedInLive #Blacksburg !!    
    
    
    LinkedIn earliest adaptor Alec Siegel in #Blacksburg #LinedInLive    
    
    
    The #RBTC #LI company page rocks! #LinedInLive    
    
    
    Awesome @modea in top area companies followed on #li #LinedInLive !    
    
    
    #linkedinlive #blacksburg awesome panel! pic.twitter.com/TQTKBGTujC    
    
    
    No endorsements I #LI? You may get overlooked by investors #linkedinlive    
    
    
    Are you in the #nrv #blacksburg? You should follow @YesMontgomeryVA for all the good news about our region    
    
    
    Your Travel Bill of Rights: The Video http://bit.ly/19IlhlN     
    
    
        
    
    
    Lunch specials, too! RT @bburglodging: To see what's going on in the #NRV, check out the #nextthreedays calendar on...    
    
    
    Happy Independence Day, Everyone!    
    
    
    @CollegeRiding Do you have a link for the tour? Will you be in #blacksburg?    
    
    
    @CollegeRiding Darn. I used to help with the tour when it came here. Sorry I can't crash the tour and say hi in person! Have fun!    
    
    
    Scholarship Mom Tip #31: Requirements ARE the reviewers' checklist http://bit.ly/1cYmxRm     
    
    
    Hopping on the #VZWBuzz chat today! Join me and RSVP here: http://bit.ly/qvlEV0     
    
    
    Agree. RT @jamal_tknox: @RobynsWorld setting up all email accounts #vzwbuzz    
    
    
    1st timers:  #musthave these goodies: screen protector, portable charger, car charger & case (if tablet) #VZWBuzz    
    
    
        
    
    
    Good to know! RT @robynsworld: TIP: Verizon Wireless offers FREE Wireless Workshops in store & online. http://vz.to/16chl8K  #VZWBuzz    
    
    
    @robynsworld I use mine as a level when I need to and just because it's cool to do so! #VZWBuzz    
    
    
    A #mustread RT @thetechdad: How to find a lost smartphone http://tinyurl.com/mrhghdw  #VZWBuzz    
    
    
        
    
    
    Love the @hootsuite app! #VZWBuzz    
    
    
    @thetechdad I will have to look at Verizon Cloud. Had not considered this before. #VZWBuzz    
    
    
    @verizoninsider Ziplock bags - great for protecting phone at the beach! #VZWBuzz    
    
    
    Great tips on #VZWBuzz. I've favorited a bunch of tweets today!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I use dropbox. RT @love2lovemykids: Q8: @RobynsWorld Is there an easy way to transfer video from a smartphone to my computer? #VZWBuzz    
    
    
    Enjoyed it! TY #VerizonWireless! RT @robynsworld: FIRST LET'S THANK our sponsor, Verizon Wireless, for the great prizes as always! #VZWBuzz    
    
    
    @thetechdad Thanks for following! Had a great time on #VZWBuzz today!    
    
    
    So excited about our new state series on colleges! RT @collegevisit: State Snapshot: Visit Alabama's Colleges & Universities...    
    
    
    @debrawellis Hi Debra, all is good! Busy and good! How are things with you? Sorry to have been MIA. Missed tweeting with you!    
    
    
    Good info for @thetechcouncil members & @thetechpad RT @jeanpetersray: Top Seed Venture Capital Investors http://www.cbinsights.com/blog/trends/top-seed-venture-capital-investors … via...    
    
    
    @vtktorg Come back to #VA!    
    
    
    @CindyRichards All excellent reasons to #VisitCA ! #tmom I'll add cuz my BFF lives there!    
    
    
    @suzanneshaffer Have a great time at #BlogHer13 !!    
    
    
    @dhatfield Good morning, Danielle! Saw these at a store. Reminded me of meeting you at #hootuproa! http://ht.ly/ngYwo     
    
    
    @jodiokun Thank you! Love the #collegefinancialplanningtip!    
    
    
    @dhatfield Wonderful now that it's not raining every single day! #cravesunshine :) How are you?    
    
    
    @dhatfield No, but I'll put it on my list. Been reading Platform by @MichaelHyatt. Have you read it?    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @nancyberk: Tomorrow it's all about #tonight. As in @jayleno    
    
    
    Happy to tell this story! RT @handshake20: Blacksburg Startup UIU Link @UIULink Off to a Great Start http://bit.ly/19wKl1V     
    
    
    @uiulink You're off to a great start! #findonlineclasses    
    
    
    #Facebooktip RT @rjfrasca: Facebook sizes and dimensions cheat sheet 2013 http://feedly.com/k/13AnXRo     
    
    
    It's true. I ♥ #hashtags RT @handshake20: Awesome post by @zkellyq on Facebook and hashtags: I Heart Hashtags http://bit.ly/11OkAVU     
    
    
    I really like #OrangeIsTheNewBlack but I sure hope @OITNB does not come out with cooking show spinoff.    
    
    
    Do You Know Your #CreditScore? http://ht.ly/o3eWd  #goodtoknow    
    
    
    Meeting a need - #1 reason to start a business. #Mompreneur @MomStillCares gets it.  http://ht.ly/o3gcG     
    
    
    TY! RT @handshake20: 4 Quick Tips on How to Plan a #Conference from Lindsey Eversole of @VTKW by @zkellyq http://bit.ly/1cXb0qR     
    
    
    @maryheston What year is dd?    
    
    
    @abcsharktank Hooked! Can't wait for season 5! #sharktank    
    
    
    The @VTKW Global Partnership Student Challenge is live-streaming now! #vtkwglobal http://ht.ly/oa1PS     
    
    
    Hi, folks! Made it to #emchat!    
    
    
    @AlexMWilliams_ I know! Too long , happy to be with you all tonight #emchat    
    
    
    @BethWhiteBU Thanks, Beth! #emchat    
    
    
    @AlexMWilliams_ @ChasingAcademe Agree! Challenging topic. #emchat    
    
    
    @AdamCastroEdu what % of families make college decisions this that way? #emchat    
    
    
    Thanks @plaidavenger for making this vid: RT @collegevisit: Why College Students Should Be On #LinkedIn http://bit.ly/1aCcDs8     
    
    
    Wow! Congrats! RT @handshake20: Thanks @TheTechCouncil! Job posted 9/1, filled 9/5! #RBTC    
    
    
    Looking forward to being #Toronto for #NACAC13 next week!    
    
    
    @meghdale Looking forward to meeting #IRL at NACAC13 !    
    
    
    Happy to speak to students in #VirginiaTech Professional Writing classes today & talk about the @collegevisit blog    
    
    
    #Scholarship Mom @AidScholarship has a great tip for you this week: http://ht.ly/oNR0j     
    
    
    #Blacksburg #BrewDo Tomorrow. Yes!    
    
    
    How connected on #LinkedIn are you? As much as these folks? http://ht.ly/oRETJ     
    
    
    Trying something new today: volunteering at @BburgBrewDo. Come see me at the Chef's tent: Cooking with Beer!    
    
    
        
    
    
    What I learned at the #Blacksburg #LinkedInLive @thetechcouncil http://ht.ly/oU6eU     
    
    
    How I will hire a #salesrep @collegevisit: Wow me online 1st. By phone 2nd. Then in person. http://ht.ly/pemqP     
    
    
    How to Write a Professional E-mail that Gets a Reply : @ProBlogger http://ht.ly/pemUx     
    
    
    Love the links in this @handshake20 post. Was totally absorbed reading about #MarissaMayer http://ht.ly/plQLd     
    
    
    Please share: RT @collegevisit: Wanted: Independent Sales Rep #highered http://bit.ly/GzIIVl     
    
    
    Looking forward to speaking to the #NRV Writers Group tonight!    
    
    
    @TheTechCouncil Paul Grossman was great! Thanks for having him speak at TechNToast!    
    
    
    Parents in #Blacksburg #Christiansburg #NRV Tips about #scholarships at our lunch & learn 10/29/13. Sign up here http://ht.ly/pPD15     
    
    
    Just checking out #VirginiaTech's campus on the Visit VT mobile app. Great for #gameday #gohokies !    
    
    
    See you there! RT @vtktorg: Game day boys and girls. Let's hope this meeting I'm in ends by noon! #Hokies #StartJumping    
    
    
    @Vidocq_CC Thank you for the shoutout! I'm so glad you came to the workshop. I'm working on the next event via @CollegeVisit    
    
    
    Joining us on #CampusChat at 9PM ET? Share some early like w/our guest @UIULink on #FB http://ht.ly/qyTuj  -help them reach their goal!    
    
    
    Scholarship Mom Tip #48: Make it a Party http://bit.ly/1a9HGJx     
    
    
    @vtktorg Oops meant to send from zkellyq: Just saw your tweet. Hope FIL is improving.    
    
    
    Hey, Hey... RT @nancyberk: Catch up w/ @TheMickyDolenz1 in my Showbiz Analysis column for @ParadeMagazine http://ow.ly/qBhtS  #Monkees    
    
    
    #SethGodin on Embracing skeptics http://ht.ly/qGScg  good #startup advice via @ThisIsSethsBlog    
    
    
    Whew! I did not forget to register for @thetechcouncil Tech n Toast on Thursday!    
    
    
    My interview with Jeff Pearson on @mentorimpact is live today - check it out at http://thementorimpact.com     
    
    
    @MentorImpact Jeff, it was a pleasure to be on your podcast show. Thank you for inviting me!    
    
    
    With @collegevisit So glad you came to #virginiatech @alexisohanian pic.twitter.com/2Rbo68POOy    
    
    
        
    
    
    @vtktorg I know what you mean! It's a beautiful stage still!    
    
    
    Loved mass media class in college! RT @UIULink: Searching for an accredited #onlinecourse in Contemporary Mass Media? http://ow.ly/qSZzZ     
    
    
    At this same time tomorrow, @AidScholarship will be on #CampusChat to answer Qs about aplying for #scholarships. Join us on Wed 9PM ET!    
    
    
    Happy to represent @collegevisit at #VACollegeAppWeek! pic.twitter.com/hABl6WwgjS    
    
    
    VA College Application Day   at EMHS! pic.twitter.com/LfKy7kDy8A    
    
    
    At #BHS for Growing The Future talent show! Thank you #Shelor for supporting #NRV kids & schools! #Blacksburg    
    
    
    The #NRV sure has a lot of talented kids! #talentshow    
    
    
    #goosebumps throughout the whole song "My Girl" Christiansburg Acapella Group!! #NRV #talentshow    
    
    
    Which town is your fav? RT @collegevisit: The Top 20 College Towns via Smart College Visit #education #CollegeVisits http://tinyurl.com/p45zdxj     
    
    
    We're tweaking our new site. Would love to know if Focal Points Gallery displays w/links in your browser http://ht.ly/rBUjp   Like it?    
    
    
    @JohnLusher @dhatfield @Hootsuite Does the world need another tweet scheduler? We're working on 1 at @collegevisit. We felt the need!    
    
    
    @JohnLusher Happy to get your input. Could not find what I needed/decided to create it.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @dhatfield Oops, meant to tweet from this acct. :)    
    
    
    @JodiOkun Always loved that quote!    
    
    
    Heads up #startups!  http://blog.startupprofessionals.com/2013/12/8-key-questions-to-expect-in-investor.html?m=1 …    
    
    
    TY! RT @handshake20: Smart College Visit @collegevisit Wins Outstanding Technology Business Award from @MontgChamber http://bit.ly/1jkWj4f     
    
    
    Enjoyed meeting the nice folks at the Library Hotel in NYC http://ow.ly/i/4ahVc  http://ht.ly/sab2z  #TMOM    
    
    
    