3 Days to Race Day! http://bit.ly/c5VdTB    
    
    
        
    
    
    We now have elevation profiles for trail segments!  For now it works only for non-Internet Explorer browsers.  We... http://bit.ly/cOzd7B    
    
    
    Check out our trail segment elevation profiles! www.trailguide411.php.    
    
    
    What features would you like to see in an online trail guide?  Pictures, routing, ratings, comments?  C/O http://trailguide411.com  and tell us.    
    
    
    What would you like to see in an online trail guide?  Pictures, routing, comments, ratings?  Checkout http://trailguide411.com  and let us know!    
    
    
    We new have elevation profiles for Internet Explorer! http://bit.ly/bMhdh7    
    
    
    Back on the trails today!  Slow, steady progress.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Working on bringing the trail maps to your mobile phone.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Still in awe of clouds of Lady Bugs in flight at Laurel Dell on Mt Tam.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just bought a new GPS unit so we can finish capturing Marin trail data.    
    
    
    Tonight in San Francisco!    
    
    
    Just posted new East Bay Shoreline Virtual Tour:  www.ultimatetrailguide.com/videos/Shoreline.wmv    
    
    
    Just sent out our Newsletter www.ultimatetrailguide.com/newsletters/Jun09.html    
    
    
    Great 8 mile Golden Gate Bridge run with SF Fit today!    
    
    
    Looking for feedback on our new mobile map web site.  If you have an iPhone, Nokia, Palm, Android or Driod mobile... http://fb.me/xCMuqf7X    
    
    
    getting ready for book signings tonight and tomorrow.  http://www.ultimatetrailguide.com/newsletters/flyers/JuneSignings.html    
    
    
    Successfully tested new GIS program to capture GPS data!  Knocked out Dimond Canyon Park yesterday!    
    
    
    Celebrating that we were finally able to capture the Steep Ravine Trail in Mt Tam State Park!    
    
    
    Looking forward to nicer weather so we can complete the data capture for the North Bay.  With the North Bay, we... http://fb.me/vxrqOdfQ    
    
    
    Do you have a plan?  Remember:  Loma Prieta on Saturday, October 17th at 3 pm: www.ultimatetrailguide.com/newsletters/flyers/LomaPrieta.pdf.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    I posted 6 photos on Facebook in the album "Mt Tam Kent, Rocky Ridge and Berry Trails" http://bit.ly/3OZxXX    
    
    
    I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "Lake Merrit/Lakeside Park" http://bit.ly/2qhT7y    
    
    
        
    
    
    I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "Memorial Park" http://bit.ly/14S7oy    
    
    
    I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "Alameda Shoreline" http://bit.ly/38MEs6    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hi everyone, Sue and I are running 55 minutes this Saturday.  Please help us to decide where to run:  choices are ... http://bit.ly/dCWO0    
    
    
    I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "Eastshore State Park" http://bit.ly/07iB8rN    
    
    
    I would like to get your feedback.  We have beta map page that shows our trails on Google maps.  Take a look and... http://bit.ly/08wp0ty    
    
    
    Try our new beta trail map:  www.ultimatetrailguide.com/mapdata/TrailKML.php.  Let us know what you think!    
    
    
    Ran 65 minutes this morning at Balboa Park in LA.  Great run -- it was cool and easy to get into the zone.  Sorry,... http://bit.ly/5pS00T    
    
    
    I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "San Francisco Bay Trail Along the Embaradaro" http://bit.ly/57YLyQ    
    
    
    I posted 8 photos on Facebook in the album "Golden Gate Bridge Run" http://bit.ly/5m1T0e    
    
    
    Trying to get Google to include our trail data organically in their basemaps    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    I posted 5 photos on Facebook in the album "Golden Gate Park" http://bit.ly/8VVzhe    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Mobile Revolution -- have you looked at your company's website on a mobile device?  Attached is my presentation to the Handcrafted Soap…    
    
    
    We just updated our trail map page to include data from San Francisco
and Marin Counties.  We have also improved... http://bit.ly/6j3hjm    
    
    
    We just updated our www.trailguide411.com map page to include trails in Marin and San Francisco Counties!  This adds 500+ miles of trails.    
    
    
    It was a great 70 minute run yesterday at Martin Luther King Jr Shoreline in Oakland yesterday!  As Claire and I... http://bit.ly/5I6MYz    
    
    
    Looking forward to a break in the rain this weekend!  The trails will be too muddy to use so we will look to one of... http://bit.ly/7Lbyf2    
    
    
    Now a days when I talk about the trails I talk about running.  But remember, you don't have to run to enjoy the... http://bit.ly/5QEUD2    
    
    
    I posted 6 photos on Facebook in the album "The Outdoors" http://bit.ly/7lu2Ge    
    
    
    Come to "Romance Inside and Out" Thursday, February 11 from 5:30 pm to 8:30 pm. Be DIFFERENT! Be BOLD! Go... http://bit.ly/6ILgHi    
    
    
    Ultimate Trail Guide January 2010 Newsletter http://bit.ly/5K3nfX    
    
    
        
    
    
    Inspiration Point Hiking Plan, Tilden Regional Park http://bit.ly/5BHYxP    
    
    
    Ivan Dickson Loop Hiking Plan, Briones Regional Park http://bit.ly/8mCSNd    
    
    
    View Hikes in San Francisco East Bay Regional Parks http://bit.ly/75uoI1    
    
    
    Getting back out on the the trails today!    
    
    
    Finally, good weather for hiking!  Finishing the North Bay is in our sights!    
    
    
    Ran an 85 minute run this weekend.  Conquered the McDowell Hill in Fort Mason -- anyone who has run from Marina... http://bit.ly/62xgTv    
    
    
    I posted 5 photos on Facebook in the album "Nimitz Way Trail" http://bit.ly/4IDV5V    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "SF Bay Trail" http://bit.ly/c2XwHB    
    
    
    I posted 10 photos on Facebook in the album "Cascade Canyon Open Space" http://fb.me/Jq9hJV3C    
    
    
    Trying to decide what to do for Valentine's Day this year?  Join us as Susan Kaymon talks about romantic places for... http://bit.ly/cQ6Dk9    
    
    
    Great turnout last night at Abigail's of Alameda for the Romance Inside and Outside Event.  Follow the link below... http://bit.ly/axNAZR    
    
    
    Recovering from slightly more then 7 mile run on the Lafayette-Moraga trail yesterday.  It was a beautiful day with... http://bit.ly/b1Bxjr    
    
    
    Does anyone know where there is a running track in or around Oakland that is available in the late afternoon early evening?    
    
    
    I posted 7 photos on Facebook in the album "White Hill Open Space" http://fb.me/Lr4tvkIZ    
    
    
    Great 9 mile run yesterday -- despite the rain!  Did you know you can plan your own runs using trailguide411?  We... http://bit.ly/aWT7Fa    
    
    
    King Mountain Open Space is done!  Barring the Boy Scouts, we will finish data capture of SF North Bay Trails next... http://fb.me/MTb1TvG6    
    
    
    I posted 5 photos on Facebook in the album "King Mountain Open Space" http://fb.me/S3XAiJpI    
    
    
    