The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @tulsashock @brian_agler @espnrachel @sportnewsjunkie @basketmeter    
    
    
    One of my favorite people in the whole world: @TSDIVADANI Check out her blog! http://vsb.li/Anhm0S  http://vsb.li/y5jxEX  via @pinterest    
    
    
    Word of the day: Explore    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @thesportsbrain @peoplesfinance @mrquacker @texs2424    
    
    
    Word of the day: Tutor    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @bagbroadcaster @arispie @coachd96 @lifestyle_ent    
    
    
    I'm watching The Finder (920 others checked-in) http://vsb.li/l2nYzW  @GetGlue @TheFinderonFOX    
    
    
    Big sigh of relief. It's the weekend!    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @theunclehood @briman3    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @mkdb3000k    
    
    
    We are having meatloaf for dinner! pic.twitter.com/ZHiHvqhR    
    
    
    @shashib For sure! Recipe is at http://bit.ly/8RgQDF     
    
    
    Word of the day: Polish    
    
    
    Have an existing SkyDrive account? Go to it today & claim the 25G currently available to you. Unclaimed accounts are being reduced to 7G!    
    
    
    @tdhurst Started as web only, but it has expanded as of today. Check out this article from a fellow MVP for more info: http://bit.ly/JslWNH     
    
    
    @PPTWiz Thought you might want to know that I am @callkathy not @kathyjacobs - Think you are following the wrong one of us :)    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 4 retweets received, 12 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: swamped    
    
    
    Feeling quite disconnected from my Twitter peeps. Hard to follow conversations when working on a single monitor.    
    
    
    Wondering what is up with my peeps - esp. @QueenofSpain @BlondeByDesign @bschorr @Kinchie @CharJTF and @spiderwebwoman Missing you all!    
    
    
    @CharJTF When is your surgery date? Late summer, right?    
    
    
    @bschorr You lucky dog. I miss warm.    
    
    
    @perricollins It would be easier to work on one monitor if I were at it more of the time here in Rockford.    
    
    
    @spiderwebwoman Rockford is cold. Unseasonably cold. Getting adjusted to life here. Healing (bodily). re-connecting with the network.    
    
    
    @BlondeByDesign Doing a bit better. Feeling human. Missing you. Glad you are well enough to keep busy. my frog misses your frog!    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @theunclehood @r8derpool @dirtyharry16 @peoplesfinance    
    
    
    Having a very nice evening. Lots of awesome phone conversations. The future is looking up tonight!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Options    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @gtrnews @esportfemeni @basketmeter    
    
    
    Next change in our lives: Drive to LA starting May 21st :)    
    
    
    @Kinchie Glad to hear my good news helped make your day too. Miss you!!!    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @geekandsundry http://vsb.li/YndX77  The Guild: I'm the One That's Cool Directed by    
    
    
    http://vsb.li/51w4r5  Current xkcd explained. Check the comments for discussion on what things mean.    
    
    
    Taking my mom to lunch :D (@ Panera Bread) http://4sq.com/IbKMSa     
    
    
    Word of the day: Leaves    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @thewallnba @hoopfeed @brandonmellor @yellowfeverzgz    
    
    
    http://vsb.li/xBEcpO  OneNote tip from John Guin's blog - gotta admit it was new to me :)    
    
    
    http://vsb.li/wFD1lZ  Jeremiah was a bullfrog.... ribbit ribbit ribbit    
    
    
    Word of the day: Trek    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @purple1029 @wnbajones    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @wbbdaily @swishappeal @markremme    
    
    
    Today's plan: pancake breakfast, church, church social/potluck. Gonna eat good food all day!    
    
    
    Was great to see @bowman1's mom at church this morning. Guess he hadn't seen the tweet that we are here this weekend :P    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz     
    
    
    Change in plans. Staying an extra night in Iowa    
    
    
    Word of the day: Tooth    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @wbbdaily @fox59larry    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 retweets received, 4 new followers, 28 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: Cover    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @jovanybz @rucoachnew @jaydaevans @ktdouglas_blog    
    
    
    Made it back to Rockford    
    
    
    My @klout score is 56. Sign up to find out yours! http://vsb.li/tWEh2S     
    
    
    Word of the day: Distracted    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @ap_slush24 @cre8molew @thekk23 @b3burch @kac044    
    
    
    Check out my profile on Recmnd.Me (http://bit.ly/JW6oSB ) Check ur ranking too! @RecmndMe    
    
    
    Word of the day: Tense    
    
    
    @jpalnau Will that make people use the right tenses in their writing too?    
    
    
    Just out of the oven.  Too hot to eat yet.  Melts in your mouth.  I have cooked this outside before but it is... http://fb.me/1DtItIjE5     
    
    
    http://vsb.li/Vha4RN  Bruce's Mom's Egg Custard - SOOO good!    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @midwaymadness    
    
    
    For my PPT friends - MVP and other wise :) http://vsb.li/9nd9nv     
    
    
    Learned that those receiving last #FedExtenForUnemployment in IL will no longer get it after mid-May. #Thankful for job after 5/29    
    
    
    North IL peeps: Get jewelry for Mother's Day, grad, wedding gifts at the Craft Show in Roscoe, IL this weekend! 5454 Bridge Street    
    
    
    North IL peeps: Sis is selling her jewelry at the Craft Show in Roscoe, IL F/S/S! 5454 Bridge Street Great for Mother's Day, grad, wedding    
    
    
    Word of the day: Archway    
    
    
    History of encryption and password protection. (I hope anyway. So many images on the page I wasn't s http://vsb.li/m1wYgZ     
    
    
    @MarkSheppard Oh yum - lemon archways. Haven't had them in quite a while. @mindlessfluff may need to buy me some.    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz     
    
    
    Off to get the mail then on to the craft show in Roscoe.    
    
    
    Why Online Organizing Is Changing Politics: 'It's the Network, Stupid' http://vsb.li/AwgRY4  via @mashable (Attn:  @adrielhampton)    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @richardcohen1 @foe23 @basketfem    
    
    
    Murano Glass 40mm Blown Glass Swirl Bead - Amber (PS - I want one too!) http://vsb.li/twnn1H     
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @nhrjimfuller @anderssonand    
    
    
    Geekery+Music/GraduationFun=RoarsOfLaughter http://pinterest.com/pin/50524827039888714/ …    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @ignitephoenix http://vsb.li/yJFkfA  Ignite Phoenix #12 - Hanging Out With Hackers,    
    
    
    @ElectricOctopi Looks like it went well. Proud of you!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Drizzle    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @gtrnews @ktdouglas_blog @ndeportes    
    
    
    Every Major's Terrible: http://vsb.li/fKpeBN  via @youtube (For everyone who loved this morning's #xkcd    
    
    
    One of 10 games that look like office work -- HT to Mashable for posting the list. http://vsb.li/5N6wxl     
    
    
    Sorry that Holly is really dead. Looking forward to tonight's new episode http://vsb.li/pkFwoY  @GetGlue @_S_A_R_A_H_    
    
    
    I unlocked the Eureka: Jo Lupo sticker on @GetGlue! http://vsb.li/nVKs3f     
    
    
    So... Are things really back to normal??? http://vsb.li/rJjFMv  @GetGlue @_S_A_R_A_H_    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 5 retweets received, 2 new listings, 2 new followers, 11 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @dishnswish @nhrjimfuller    
    
    
    Word of the day: Picturesque    
    
    
    Who wanted to be Howard Carter when they were growing up? Count me in that list! http://vsb.li/bGopyF     
    
    
    Word of the day: Minimum    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @basketfem @cskyeh @azc_domingo @thesportsbrain    
    
    
    Word of the day: treat    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @ktdouglas_blog @triadtrust @sdmattpotter    
    
    
    Word of the day: week    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @minnesotalynx @basketfem @jaltavilla    
    
    
    How you learned about the geek world says a lot about you! http://vsb.li/StJdSQ     
    
    
    Busy afternoon planned. @TechPhx meeting via Skype at 11 PHX time, then a Skype presentation to #ASCIiUG on Blogs 90 minutes later.    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @quickdeuce @swishappeal    
    
    
    ASCIi User group presentation on blogs http://vsb.li/BoQyDm     
    
    
    Presentation done now for a bit of down time :D    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @wnbajones @lynxradio @carminjc    
    
    
    @SGBmedia thanks for the +K!    
    
    
    Mother's Day dinner with hubby, sister, bro in law, and my mom (@ Hawk's View Family Restaurant) http://4sq.com/KexdxN     
    
    
    Word of the day: Bead    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @basketfem    
    
    
    Map by the National Low Income Housing Coalition shows how many hours you need to work at minimum wa http://vsb.li/rPPK2P     
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 retweets received, 8 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: Bike    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @iballunited @4seasonstylemgt @madhvimewar @jaydaevans @wbbdaily    
    
    
    Word of the day: Case    
    
    
    @VisioMVP yes i AM    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz     
    
    
    The Dilbert Strip for May 17, 2012 - This applies in so many ways to parts of my life!!! http://vsb.li/2EqO50     
    
    
    @jack_daniel But why not?????? :)    
    
    
    Word of the day: grocery    
    
    
    The #wnba Daily is out! http://bit.ly/jzu0vz  ▸ Top stories today via @jwfocke @wbbdaily @madhvimewar @christywscott51 @stephenlitel    
    
    
    For those curious about my new job: This article shows exactly why I am so eager for the new job to start http://vsb.li/ZlSX3h     
    
    
    Help @UNICEF spread the word about #SahelNOW! 1 Million+ children are suffering from severe malnutrition! #KloutForGood http://vsb.li/rEFj7C     
    
    
    Discover a new way to shop w/ #LittleBlackBag! Shop, swap & share on @LBBag & get a little extra with your @Klout! http://vsb.li/mcGwD1     
    
    
    Off we go! Next real stop: Galesburg Il then in to Urbana    
    
    
    @Bowman1 we will. FYI we are driving to Story City on our way west Monday. You have been warned :D    
    
    
    Lunch with Bruce and Nathan Johlas. Then on to Urbana (@ Steak N Shake) http://4sq.com/KYOVrl     
    
    
    Word of the day: Tomorrow    
    
    
    Here! (@ Ramada Limited Urbana) http://4sq.com/KKm7mU     
    
    
    In the road, but not moving far... Stuck in road construction    
    
    
    Iowa <3    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 3 retweets received, 1 new listings, 1 new followers, 10 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: Road    
    
    
    Nebraska    
    
    
    Home for the night. B making mac and cheese here in the room in a bit. (@ Days Inn Lexington NE) http://4sq.com/KypBqB     
    
    
    Colorado - and phone service reappears    
    
    
    Word  of the day: mile    
    
    
    Here for the night and glad of it. (@ Econo Lodge) http://4sq.com/JyCghu     
    
    
    NationBuilder in our nation's capitol - Changing the world http://vsb.li/X8Ogfd     
    
    
    Once again CA UI screws me up. So close to getting out of hole. Last UI check hasn't come. Worried about covering 1st week's expenses in CA.    
    
    
    Word if the day: sign    
    
    
    Made it to Las Vegas - Las Vegas, New Mexico that is   :D    
    
    
    Here for the night. Tomorrow Flagstaff then Phoenix. Glad to be out of the car a bit. (@ Super 8) http://4sq.com/KYbLh6     
    
    
    @haroldwong things going good. On our way to PHX for the weekend. My new job starts Tuesday. B says hi back!    
    
    
    Things look much better today. Have a plan to make to LA and new job    
    
    
    Word of the day: Stem    
    
    
    Arizona    
    
    
    @haroldwong New job is in LA. Company is @NationBuilder. Start Tuesday. In PHX for long weekend.    
    
    
    Having a nice afternoon with the grandkids :D    
    
    
    Time to head to PHX. Good times with kids    
    
    
    Meeting Patricia and Al for lunch - we are early (@ Mimi's Cafe) http://4sq.com/LnX0Xt     
    
    
    Trying to find a motel in the LA area for our temporary home. Looking for somewhere fairly inexpensive, with a micro/fridge and wifi. Ideas?    
    
    
    @sherrierohde Love the beach house idea, but doubt we can afford one!    
    
    
    @sherrierohde Do you have a link or other such for the beach house rental idea? Would love to find a way to make it work!    
    
    
    @sherrierohde Will do! Thanks for the leads!    
    
    
    Sweating Bullets - Someone please tell @mindlessfluff that I want this book.... http://vsb.li/AwzJSP     
    
    
    Getting ready to pack the car for the last leg of the trip to LA    
    
    
    @ehorley My new job with @NationBuilder which starts tomorrow :)    
    
    
    @ehorley office is in Pershing Square downtown. Will be motel/hoteling it until we find an apartment    
    
    
    @ehorley Eventually @Mindlessfluff will need work out there too.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Leg    
    
    
    @ehorley I know. @Mindlessfluff will definitely be going to meetings and u will when I can. Same goes for @SoCalitpros cc @ubergeekgirl    
    
    
    California! Two and a half hours to the hotel!    
    
    
    Moving along nicely now. Fingers crossed the traffic keeps going at this speed    
    
    
    Home for the next few days (at least) (@ Days Inn Ontario Airport) http://4sq.com/LyW7vj     
    
    
    My week on twitter: 6 new followers, 15 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    On our way to work. Will be glad to glad to move to a closer place Thursday    
    
    
    First morning done - lunch next!    
    
    
    Word of the day: orientation    
    
    
    On bus heading to motel. Great first day at @NationBuilder    
    
    
    I just ousted @vivalaserdisc as the mayor of Days Inn Ontario Airport on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bDdHU9     
    
    
    On the bus finally    
    
    
    Day two commences    
    
    
    Word of the day: Commence    
    
    
    I promise... Updates will get more interesting as I adjust to schedule. Too busy to post much right now!!    
    
    
    Last night here. Motel for next week (at least) is in West Covinia (@ Days Inn Ontario Airport) http://4sq.com/KKll8q     
    
    
    Word of the day: Shadow    
    
    
    Mac peeps: I need a way to do offline diffs on my Macbook Air. Can't  remember tool I used to use. Recommendations?    
    
    
    @trishussey know an online tool to do them, need a way to do them when not online    
    
    
    @trishussey pretty much - need to find problems with text files/csv files.    
    
    
    @CatherineOmega thanks for the tip - will check it out    
    
    
    On the bus to our new temp location - Rodeway Inn West Covina.    
    
    
    Dinner with my sweetie. <3 :D (@ Chili's Grill & Bar) http://4sq.com/L22Af2     
    
    
    Word of the day: Wonder    
    
    
    @azentrepreneurs New job started last Tues. with @NationBuilder in LA. Support Organizer on @AdrielHampton's team. Loving it.    
    
    
    @azentrepreneurs yes. Moteling it in West Covina right now while @mindlessfluff finds an apartment (and a job for himself).    
    
    
    Nice quiet weekend. Ready for whatever Monday throws at me    
    
    
    Word of the day: Hip    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 4 retweets received, 15 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word if the day: Explain    
    
    
    "How many times must a man beeee texted before he learns to call back?" sung to the tune of "How many roads"  cc @mindlessfluff    
    
    
    I wonder if @tdhurst has seen today's xkcd yet    
    
    
    Word if the day: Bandanna    
    
    
    This could be a long bus ride. Bus keeps stalling. Aren't even on freeway yet    
    
    
    Early morning today. Any guesses whether I will make it to the office by 8?    
    
    
    Word of the day: Stay    
    
    
    Hit the sweet spot this morning. Little traffic so far. Emptyish bus. Nice driver. Makes up for being up and moving at thus hour.    
    
    
    Word of the day: request    
    
    
    Dinner with @mindlessfluff (@ Baileys) http://4sq.com/Le8YQv     
    
    
    @TSDivaDani If you want me for anything during the meeting, I am here online - both twitter and Skype :)    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://vsb.li/SY1shD  Mister Rogers Remixed | Garden of Your Mind | PBS Digital Studi    
    
    
    Laundry time (@ Wash 'n' Dry Coin Laundry) http://4sq.com/Ly7vsG     
    
    
    We went to Ikea and spent less than $50!! (Checked in at IKEA Covina) http://vsb.li/o12m5c     
    
    
    @TSDivaDani we miss you all too!    
    
    
    In for the night .. Don't we live an exciting life. :) (@ Rodeway Inn West Covina) http://4sq.com/LFN7Ei     
    
    
    On a fairly full bus heading in for a 10 to 7 shift. That extra hour was nice. Hope everyone's Monday is going well!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Racecar    
    
    
    We bought a crockpot over the weekend. Guess who made dinner so it would be waiting for me?    
    
    
    @perricollins he used to. Now he just posts recipes once in awhile.    
    
    
    @VisioMVP I've missed your humor lately sire!    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 new listings, 16 new followers, 3 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word if the day: conductor    
    
    
    Word of the day: Popsicle    
    
    
    Just looked at an apartment that is big enough and cheap enough for the next year. Thinking about it overnight.    
    
    
    Fingers crossed we get the place we looked at last night in Baldwin Park.    
    
    
    Word of the day: ahead    
    
    
    No word on apartment yet. Hope to know more today.    
    
    
    @vendettamit so true! If we get this place, it will be great. If not, we'll find another. It is just the waiting that gets to me ;)    
    
    
    Word of the day: Story    
    
    
    Getting ready to present "Social Media for the rest of us" to the Brookdale Computer User Group via Skype. Care to say hi?    
    
    
    Presentation done. Had blast doing it. Another tomorrow morning to Verde Valley group    
    
    
    @gio1110 thanks!!!    
    
    
    On the bus to the @nationbuilder office. Presentation to vvcc then work. Happy day!    
    
    
    @NationBuilder presentation may be a no go. Tech problems on other end    
    
    
    @alternatecloud blogs and blogging. Just finished    
    
    
    Presentation in blogs done. Work day now cinnencubg    
    
    
    Poll: word of the day my work days (Tuesday to Saturday) or your work days (Monday to Friday)?    
    
    
    Just finished my first solo shift at @NationBuilder support. Proud to say I helped people today!    
    
    
    Decided to pass on Baldwin Park apartment. Couldn't get in touch with the manager of the place all weekend long. Back to looking.    
    
    
    Chinese for dinner (@ Kirin House) http://4sq.com/MXLWxN     
    
    
    Yum. Added bonus: eating with Cry's and Sean (@ In-N-Out Burger) http://4sq.com/MisqyM     
    
    
    Word of the day: Undecided    
    
    
    Food for Bruce (@ Subway) http://4sq.com/NKXs4i     
    
    
    I'm at Edwards El Monte 8 (El Monte, CA) http://4sq.com/MjiJ33     
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 retweets received, 6 new followers, 17 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Just saw someone board the bus in El Monte headed to work at Disney. Hope for their sake they work at the hall, not the park.    
    
    
    Word of the day: If    
    
    
    Riding the bus back to the motel. Rumor has it dinner is waiting for me in the crock-pot    
    
    
    Waiting on the bus.... Two going the other direction. Oh wait - here they come!!!    
    
    
    Working... Working... Working    
    
    
    Word of day: Then    
    
    
    Bumpy bus ride tonight. On the flip side, we are moving right along...    
    
    
    Morning status: stiff knee. Early bus. Lots to do when I get in to work.    
    
    
    @UberGeekGirl liking public transport. Foothills silver streak to work. Metro silver line home. Tap and go both ways    
    
    
    Word of the day: Latitude    
    
    
    Hello friends - here's hoping your Friday is a fine day!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Unusual    
    
    
    Have I mentioned lately how much I love working at @NationBuilder? Great people making a difference.    
    
    
    @Karoli you would love this crew. Next time you are in LA let me know so I can introduce you around    
    
    
    Dinner - pasta and goodness (@ Di Pillas Italian Restaurant) http://4sq.com/LH5vMc     
    
    
    Working Saturdays us fun and fulfilling - right up until I hit the dead zone at about 3 pm.    
    
    
    Almost "home". Long day. Food waits at the other end of this bus ride    
    
    
    Getting to watch the last quarter of the @phoenixmercury game. Awesomeness (even if they are down 17 right now)    
    
    
    Join #REDRUSH with @joinRED & @Klout! 1,000 babies are born w/HIV every day. By 2015 that can be near 0. #KloutForGood http://vsb.li/WkmHS9     
    
    
    Here's hoping Brave is as good as I've heard... (Checked in at Edwards El Monte 8) http://vsb.li/WDCV0P     
    
    
    I'm watching Eureka (5185 others checked-in) http://vsb.li/hVDdky  @GetGlue @_S_A_R_A_H_    
    
    
    I unlocked the Eureka: Global Dynamics sticker on @GetGlue! http://vsb.li/vdNTlq     
    
    
    My week on twitter: 1 retweets received, 15 new followers, 6 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: archaic    
    
    
    Mexican for dinner. Camarones for me. Pollo for Bruce. Plus margarita wine to wash mine down [pic]: http://4sq.com/LOO78i     
    
    
    Urgent care opens at 8:30. Hopefully I can get a breathing treatment and get out of here by ... Noon http://4sq.com/NN6NaS     
    
    
    "A suite of easy-to-use campaign software designed by rock-ribbed Democrats is about to be deployed  http://vsb.li/hrd8vQ     
    
    
    Woke to good news today. Healthcare bill upheld!    
    
    
    On a more personal note: heading to work. Feeling tired but much better than yesterday. Much to do at @NationBuilder today    
    
    
    Word of the day: Upheld    
    
    
    Good morning everyone! How's your Friday looking?    
    
    
    Word of the day: Shadow    
    
    
    I have now been at @NationBuilder for a full month. Feels good. Still love the work, the people, and the product - it is all good!    
    
    
    Finally on a bus to work. Good thing I didn't need to be there at my normal time.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Survey    
    
    
    Dinner with a side of tiki kitsch (@ Bahooka Ribs & Grog) http://4sq.com/N1gyRN     
    
    
    I just pushed @Klout 2.5 meters towards the finish in the @AIDSWalkSF. Use your #KloutForGood & help us reach the goal. http://vsb.li/b01FxG     
    
    
    We have an apartment. Details to come. Yay    
    
    
    Burgers and cheese fries (@ Original Tommy's Hamburgers) [pic]: http://4sq.com/MEQs8L     
    
    
    My week on twitter: 1 retweets received, 7 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: normalize    
    
    
    Nice things about having an apartment: setting home button in GPS. Picking furniture. Grocery shopping.  Putting things away.  A closet.    
    
    
    @gavindeschutter That's what the crisper drawer in the fridge is for!    
    
    
    Drive from apartment to bus: 5 minutes. So nice!    
    
    
    Three Startups Defending Democracy In America: Votizen, Memeorandum, and NationBuilder http://vsb.li/gcJhYY  via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    Three Startups Defending Democracy In America: Votizen, Memeorandum, and NationBuilder http://tcrn.ch/NaPpfo  via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    Just realized I forgot to do a word today. Maybe I will do two tomorrow    
    
    
    @mulka good    
    
    
    Word of the day: forgotten    
    
    
    Word of the day: Liquid    
    
    
    Long day at work today. 2+ hours on support calls. 2+ hours on a data project. Rest of the time email after email. Glad I love my job :)    
    
    
    Heading off for work in just a few. Going to be another great day at NationBuilder support!    
    
    
    Such a huge difference between "quiet day" and "quite a day" - second one describes today.    
    
    
    Which state do you live in? http://vsb.li/k85emd     
    
    
    I am off to get scratches on my arms... allergist here I come. Eager to have this started and over with.    
    
    
    It could have been much worse...    
    
    
    Word of the day: Bumps    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 retweets received, 4 new followers, 13 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Bad start to the day. Knee aches and the bus is late. Just now leaving El Monte station for work.    
    
    
    Word of the day: phone    
    
    
    Front seats in a bus are for elderly and disabled. Being young and rude is not in that list. #justsayin    
    
    
    @bschorr    
    
    
    @bschorr for sure. Not giving up a seat for me with my cane is one thing. Dirty looks at the 75yr old w a cane a whole different thing.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Baseboard    
    
    
    Dinner with Bruce. (@ Nick's Burgers) http://4sq.com/MjSR4D     
    
    
    Word of the day: overcast    
    
    
    @VisioMVP possibly. That morning's crew didn't have pregnancies to worry about for sure    
    
    
    Dinner and an appletini. @Hewie Poplock should try this! (@ Ish New Asian Kitchen w/ 2 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/Nl1Gyy     
    
    
    Awesome place to eat. Loving our food and the attentive service! http://vsb.li/PEfJoh     
    
    
    Word of the day: Away    
    
    
    http://vsb.li/QZphbm  Marie Vesta Kicks Off APCUG / CAMUG Regional Computer and Technology Conference    
    
    
    Word of the day: Furniture    
    
    
    Bruce's turn. (@ Kaiser Permanente Baldwin Park Medical Center) http://4sq.com/MtI39q     
    
    
    Word of the day: Leap    
    
    
    Hey #Excel MVPs: Need to split 300+M Excel file into chunks. Know an automated way? @mrexcel @mrexceleast @ddalgleish @Jon_Peltier    
    
    
    @mrexcel and @mathews_p I need it split into files by size. 20M per file max.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Server    
    
    
    Word of the day: wait    
    
    
    Word of the day: Import    
    
    
    Word of the day: Genus    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 new followers, 8 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Wfh today. Now using three machines at once. One for general support tasks and two for data work. Yay for multitasking    
    
    
    Hubby dear is making something new and amazing for dinner. Really good stuff.    
    
    
    Ham and Cheese French Fry Bake - tonight's deliciousness pic.twitter.com/xnhVUxTd    
    
    
    And the same dinner on the plate :) pic.twitter.com/s6oKU8yW    
    
    
    Time to see the doc about my knee. Bet the answer is referral to Ortho.. Which will mean another two week wait... http://4sq.com/OjiwvW     
    
    
    @RichirOutreach Saw your tweet about Salsa exports saving as jsp file. Did you by chance ever blog this? If so, link?    
    
    
    Word of the day: Format    
    
    
    Word of the day: helpless    
    
    
    Word of the day: Image    
    
    
    Long bus ride home today.    
    
    
    Bus ride should be better this morning. Less crowded. Plus, I made the early one.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Slam    
    
    
    Mr Excel shares how to turn any table on your site into an interactive Excel spreadsheet. Check it o http://vsb.li/bcj8m6     
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 new followers, 4 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: Display    
    
    
    Sunday appointments rock. (@ Kaiser Permanente Baldwin Park Medical Center) http://4sq.com/OvUOwD     
    
    
    I entered for a chance to have my rent or mortgage paid for a FULL YEAR! Thanks, @nbcLA! Enter Here --> http://vsb.li/6VeGmv     
    
    
    @MarkSheppard @callkathy It is a nice dream, but not likely. :)    
    
    
    Word of the day: Shambolic    
    
    
    Need a new router (@ Fry's Electronics) http://4sq.com/NEldvz     
    
    
    Time to get chopped - hair is to long to stand anymore. (@ Supercuts) http://4sq.com/Q6sLGR     
    
    
    Hair? Check. Router? Check. Groceries? Check. Super productive day? Check!    
    
    
    Beauty and the Werewolf (Five Hundred Kingdoms Series #6) - Mercedes Lackey http://vsb.li/Sf8Nvl     
    
    
    The Glasswrights' Master - Mindy Klasky http://vsb.li/aY9jEQ     
    
    
    Inheritance (Inheritance Cycle Series #4) - Christopher Paolini http://vsb.li/GG2gle     
    
    
    Word of the day: Orthopedist    
    
    
    Ortho appointment at the top of the hour. (@ Kaiser Permanente) http://4sq.com/MhStcw     
    
    
    It's not my knee. It might be my back. Next step: appointment with physical medicine (and surviving the pain from the exam tonight).    
    
    
    From@spellwight - Great advice on how men can prevent rapes. http://vsb.li/m38OP1     
    
    
    Word of the day: august    
    
    
    Word of the day: Plate    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 1 retweets received, 7 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Another great Saturday at NationBuilder support!    
    
    
    @socialupheaval welcome to @nationbuilder support! Eager to meet you! (Hope you love the job as much as I do!!!)    
    
    
    #Curiosity made it! Way to go!    
    
    
    @bluemilker Wish I were there. Settling for watching it on @ustream!    
    
    
    @bschorr 6.5. Kilometers and dropping    
    
    
    @epstudios #Curiosity is much more interesting than the Olympics tonight.    
    
    
    @spellwight Who needs champagne? They have all the geeks in the world spellbound. That's gonna make them drunk enough!    
    
    
    As of this writing the NASA/JPL websites are still overloaded. Trying CURIOSITY-REAR-CAM_[256px_x_25 http://vsb.li/eNp3CF     
    
    
    Word of the day: Curiosity    
    
    
    Trip to Fry's (@ Fry's Electronics) http://4sq.com/QG4kmi     
    
    
    Bringing treats to work this morning. @NationBuilder team finally gets brownies    
    
    
    Back again. This time to see the physical medicine doc (@ Kaiser Permanente) http://4sq.com/MudG2Q     
    
    
    Word of the day: spine    
    
    
    Earthquake here in LA. First one we have felt since moving here.    
    
    
    @adrielhampton Felt it here too...    
    
    
    Word of the day: spinning    
    
    
    Win Tickets and On Field Passes for the Packers vs. Bears Game Sept 13, 2012 http://vsb.li/k62qdA  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Word of the day: Comma    
    
    
    @Bowman1 that is one use of the word!    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 retweets received, 1 new listings, 16 new followers, 7 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: Domain    
    
    
    This should almost be captioned "This I believe" http://vsb.li/n8rs3M     
    
    
    I know this crew. I know this event. Wish I had the time to go this year. http://vsb.li/dzeMHf     
    
    
    Hey, before you go, can you explain to me what job I now have? http://vsb.li/AyEM4F     
    
    
    Word of the day: Eyes    
    
    
    Word of the day: Seismic    
    
    
    The Oatmeal is asking for your help to buy Tesla's land and lab. Can you help? http://vsb.li/p6EDXF     
    
    
    Going to be a long day. It has started with me having to stand most of the bus ride in.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Patience    
    
    
    @Kinchie thanks my friend. One bad day once in a while is much better than life a few months ago. I just have to keep going.    
    
    
    Sour Cream and Bacon Crockpot Chicken - This sounds really good. Need Bruce to make it for me one da http://vsb.li/kVNfgQ     
    
    
    Pain level way down today. Plus, I snagged a seat. Much better start than yesterday.    
    
    
    Word of the day: puzzle    
    
    
    @Toby_Metcalf thanks for the mention! Hope you are having a great day!    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 1 retweets received, 12 new followers, 5 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: Takeaway    
    
    
    Sharing in OneNote 2013 - Engineering OneNote Blog - Site Home - MSDN Blogs http://vsb.li/8Wgdlw     
    
    
    Ghostbuster's Theme on eight floppy drives: http://vsb.li/9dgr9M  via @youtube There's a ghost in this machine. HT @Mashable    
    
    
    SkyDrive has been redesigned and colored. What do you think of it? http://vsb.li/vNVVak     
    
    
    Word of the day: distract    
    
    
    Hoping everyone has a great Wed. - I know I plan to!    
    
    
    Word of the day: element    
    
    
    Jerry Brown visits NationBuilder! Emily Schwartz, Kevin Berry and Gov. Jerry Brown http://vsb.li/x99Vsx     
    
    
    Please retweet this! Sign up FREE to enter for a trip to the Democratic National Convention: http://vsb.li/7vs50j     
    
    
    Word of the day: Caffeine    
    
    
    Word of the day: Crowd    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 5 retweets received, 7 new followers, 1 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: Talk    
    
    
    You have me intrigued. Pleasantly so. Call me Monday afternoon. Have a checkup Monday morning.    
    
    
    That was a total DM fail....    
    
    
    Neil Armstrong's family wants you to look at the moon ... and give a wink - Cosmic Log http://vsb.li/TreN4Z     
    
    
    Word of the day: County    
    
    
    I love my dasKeyboard! Have used it for over two years and no problems what-so-ever. Only thing is.. http://vsb.li/J8j7M7     
    
    
    Word of the day: Picnic    
    
    
    Word of the day: Echelon    
    
    
    I just signed up to speak at @TechPHX this November: Using Technology to Organize for Good    
    
    
    Word of the day: Field    
    
    
    @TechPhx yes we are both coming for the weekend. :D    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 1 retweets received, 5 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: Labor    
    
    
    ’Green Mile’ actor Michael Clarke Duncan dead at 54 http://vsb.li/gXna0h  via @NBCNewsEnt    
    
    
    Very much appreciate @mindlessfluff driving me to work this morning    
    
    
    Word of the day: panorama    
    
    
    Word of the day: Relaxation    
    
    
    Off to see paranorman. Very silly, but something we can both agree on. (@ Edwards El Monte 8) http://4sq.com/P0BXfX     
    
    
    "Don't boo....vote." Great quote.    
    
    
    sushi for me... Teriyaki for Bruce  (Checked in at The Sakura) http://vsb.li/aJoQQk     
    
    
    Word of the day: Throwaways    
    
    
    That was exciting. Someone ran into our bus. No one hurt.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Empty    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Filmmakers Aim to Set the Record Straight About Nikola Tesla [VIDEO] http://vsb.li/vesseJ  via @mashable (Wonder if @oatmeal is helping?)    
    
    
    My first post on the NationBuilder blog is live. Let me know what you think! http://vsb.li/vKxHa4     
    
    
    The link to my UTF-8 blog piece: http://vsb.li/JQTYvm  (A bit of computer history for @JoeConte)    
    
    
    @JoeConte No worries - wanted an excuse to tweet it directly anyway :)    
    
    
    Finale. I will miss this show... http://vsb.li/qwzMlH  #GetGlueHD @ArmyWives    
    
    
    Word of the day: Remember    
    
    
    What a morning. Stuck in traffic on I10 westbound to LA. Good thing I made the early bus.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Eye    
    
    
    Working hard today-New awesomeness released by @NationBuilder -Verify your voter info now! Read more: http://vsb.li/TQsw93     
    
    
    Word of the day: Claim    
    
    
    Rock the Red: Erin Kotecki Vest on Katie Couric's New Show http://vsb.li/eSWEqN     
    
    
    Busy day made better by brownies baked by @mindlessfluff for the @NationBuilder team    
    
    
    Word of the day: Queue    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 1 retweets received, 4 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word if the day: Compute    
    
    
    Wireless wooden keyboard made from one board. I WANT! http://vsb.li/C6Ce4K     
    
    
    Does anyone else find themselves thinking he is Nehemiah Scudder come to life?
http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/09/15/rick-santorum-smart-peopl_n_1886684.html …    
    
    
    The Science of Social Timing http://vsb.li/FOltXj     
    
    
    I want this engraved on my tombstone like the Epitaph of Stevinus. http://vsb.li/eHh5MV     
    
    
    More press for NationBuilder's Election Center. Are you claiming your voter record? http://vsb.li/lH0BYL     
    
    
    More press for NationBuilder's Election Center. Are you claiming your voter record? http://techcrunc http://vsb.li/TTQJ3o     
    
    
    Word of the day: Pending    
    
    
    Click and drag. Be sure not to give up just because the scene changes. There is much more to see tha http://pinterest.com/pin/50524827040739027/ …    
    
    
    Check out AZ Cactus Pine GS on Chase Community Giving, & vote to help it share in $5MM in grants! http://vsb.li/Sw8JL1  #InOnTheGiving    
    
    
    Interesting read from @Hardaway about a new way to look at entitlement.

http://blog.stealthmode.com/a-new-twist-on-entitlement …    
    
    
    @Meetup See the site is down. Any info available RE: When it will be back up?    
    
    
    Word of the day: Tilde    
    
    
    @perricollins import files with funky characters including tildes    
    
    
    IgNobel 2012 prize winners announced including a SpeechJammer demonstration http://vsb.li/wKlrgr     
    
    
    Election Center Apps - We need your ideas! : Volunteer Capacity Planner http://vsb.li/c1Lqc7     
    
    
    Word of the day: Speechless    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 3 retweets received, 15 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    This is the great iOS6 mapping app? http://vsb.li/pxQ6VM     
    
    
    Word of the day: Reaction    
    
    
    Not fair @timewarner - taking away our HD during @FaceOff!!!    
    
    
    Word of the day: parrot    
    
    
    Onetastic adds Macros for OneNote - Engineering OneNote Blog - Site Home - MSDN Blogs http://vsb.li/Rr8qB5     
    
    
    Getting @mindlessfluff's right eye checked. Not the one zapped last night, the other one. More when I know more http://4sq.com/P9BeWg     
    
    
    Word of the day: patch    
    
    
    Optho appt. For B's rt eye. (@ Kaiser Permanente Baldwin Park Medical Center) http://4sq.com/QrWo6v     
    
    
    My Job - Obama for America TV Ad: http://vsb.li/KcB5ls  via @youtube    
    
    
    Speakers list for @TechPHX this year. Will you be there? http://pinterest.com/pin/50524827040800112/ …    
    
    
    Word of the day: Overload    
    
    
    I could use an injection of see's chocolate about now. #justsayin    
    
    
    Decided to splurge. After this week, we both needed it. (@ Elephant Bar) http://4sq.com/P1364t     
    
    
    My week on twitter: 9 new followers, 4 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    Word of the day: extended    
    
    
    First set of downs in the @packer game equals 6 points. That's the way it is done!!!!    
    
    
    50 career TDs by Jennings. Congrats @packers!    
    
    
    Thanks again @packers!    
    
    
    Ok. Rodgers' must be ok. That was a pretty set of downs with the right result.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Skittish    
    
    
    Word of the day: license    
    
    
    @wanichan @spiderwebwoman @visiomvp Definitely - good morning!!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Consult    
    
    
    Word of the day: Hautboy    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 1 retweets received, 5 mentions. Via: http://goo.gl/j9ORw     
    
    
    @adrielhampton Luckily @mindlessfluff didn't see this yesterday. Haven't told him about the latest addition to the office yet.    
    
    
    Working on how-to scripts for @nationbuilder videos today. #lovemyjob    
    
    
    Boy Scouts: Don't let your anti-gay policy deny my son his Eagle award http://vsb.li/7c21nM  via @change    
    
    
    Cake Wrecks - Home - Sunday Sweets: Rainbow Connection http://vsb.li/oT29N1     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/EvjOz2QmD9Y?a  The Boy with Tape on His Face Comedy Rocks Ep 1.    
    
    
    Word of the day: prose    
    
    
    Trying out a new Chinese restaurant. Hoping it tastes as good as it smells (@ Mandarin Chef) http://4sq.com/R5MCUe     
    
    
    Infographic   86 Percent of Users May Leave a Website When Asked to Create an Account http://vsb.li/j0ge5v     
    
    
    Word of the day: Bacon    
    
    
    It's been too long since I shared this. Perfect week to do so: If you use #PPT, check out the #PPTFAQ at http://vsb.li/EbSvWk     
    
    
    Word of the day: transcribe    
    
    
    Thunder and lightning and rain... Oh my!    
    
    
    Announcing the Microsoft Community Video Tips Sweepstakes Winners! : http://vsb.li/MWPxLy  (cc @MrExcel)    
    
    
    Word of the day: Chirp    
    
    
    Check out the #TundraEndeavour, the story of a half-ton truck's mission to tow Space Shuttle Endeavour. http://vsb.li/LFxX2Z     
    
    
    Toyota Tundra tows Space Shuttle Endeavour. Tweet to raise $ for @CAScienceCenter at http://vsb.li/Ny1VVF . 48 days left. #TundraEndeavour    
    
    
    Word of the day: Render    
    
    
    Field 101 webinar: Political Campaigning with NationBuilder http://vsb.li/kvlEQ0  via @NationBuilder    
    
    
    I just volunteered for the Abe for Prez campaign and you should too! http://vsb.li/w1GArT  http://vsb.li/h28yHH     
    
    
    No white guy who's been mentioned on Twitter has gone on to win. (Take the time to read it all) http://vsb.li/ae5qCL     
    
    
    Word of the day: Five    
    
    
    To whom ever designed the new El Monte bus station: I hope you have to walk the station with limited mobility someday. The new design sucks!    
    
    
    word of the day: cane    
    
    
    Word of the day: why    
    
    
    Word of the day: company    
    
    
    Maple. Bacon. Donut. You may all now drool.    
    
    
    The @TechPhx schedule is live! I speak 11/10 at 11 on Using Technology to Organize for Good (rm 204) http://vsb.li/MblRDV     
    
    
    Japanese steak and shrimp (@ Miyabi Japanese Steakhouse & Sushi) http://4sq.com/Uunk80     
    
    
    Word of the day: Resistance    
    
    
    Word of the day: Marketplace    
    
    
    How can I split files too big to import? http://vsb.li/LYxnXV  via @NationBuilder With thanks to @MrExcel!    
    
    
    Tell me something good    
    
    
    Health woes hurt workers two ways http://vsb.li/7jHrez   via @NBCNewsBusiness (been there - lived through it)    
    
    
    Word of the day: exuberant    
    
    
    Word of the day: Obvious    
    
    
    For the political wonks and history geeks in my life: xkcd breaks down the make up of congress http: http://vsb.li/adxlFH     
    
    
    Do good. Learn some stuff. See old friends. Maybe win a prize. Food Drive For United Food Bank - http://vsb.li/6cztgZ     
    
    
    I unlocked the Happy Halloween 2012 sticker on #GetGlue! http://is.gd/cvQCdr     
    
    
    Word of the day: Appearance    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://vsb.li/Br8VZb  Whedon On Romney    
    
    
    Word of the day: Snowball    
    
    
    Word of the day: Tag    
    
    
    If you missed it, here's the NationBuilder team getting into the Halloween spirit on NationBuilder Live http://vsb.li/E7m1mP     
    
    
    Word of the day: concrete    
    
    
    Waiting for @mindlessfluff to get here and take me home. Hear there is traffic on I-10 slowing his progress. :S    
    
    
    Is it possible that I am almost caught up at work? Just in time to take time off later this week for @techphx!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Predict a winner: Battleground states - 2012 election - Data Desk - Los Angeles Times http://vsb.li/N3XX6G     
    
    
    #Ivoted for #Obama. Would have posted that at polling place, but no connection there.    
    
    
    Word of the day: VOTE    
    
    
    @ClimateHiJinx Vote Obama! :)    
    
    
    It's party time at @nationbuilder    
    
    
    Congratulations to our president on his reelection!    
    
    
    Word of the day: shoulder    
    
    
    Word of the day: Book    
    
    
    Our home for the weekend. Though I am guessing we will spend more waking hours over at UAT (@ Candlewood Suites) http://4sq.com/TQozwI     
    
    
    Pre @techphx set up. Traffic on Baseline is worse than I remembered today. (@ University of Advancing Technology) http://4sq.com/WN7cAO     
    
    
    #evfn and @techphx together - awesome times!    
    
    
    I'm at University of Advancing Technology (Phoenix, AZ) http://4sq.com/SL8UMp     
    
    
    #techphx opening by @tsdivadani happening now!    
    
    
    The #techphx sessions are being streamed? From the schedule page of the site, click the room # for the session you want to watch!    
    
    
    looking to create a great timeline cover page? #techphx http://vsb.li/wjMk7t     
    
    
    @BKPapp your presentation is going to be awesome!    
    
    
    listening to @AprilHolle talk community and technology at #techphx    
    
    
    @EileenMKane thanks! Glad you are getting good stuff out of today!    
    
    
    Great examples from @aprilholle during her @techphx presentation http://vsb.li/kAOAmq     
    
    
    Do you know these two? I do! Talking @evernote and small businesses. (yes I use it and #OneNote too) http://vsb.li/dmEPqD     
    
    
    ...@CjPhx thanks for having me on the show! One of the best parts of #techphx, as always!!!    
    
    
    Noticing that lots of people using @prezi for their #techphx presentations. Something to think about for next year.    
    
    
    Hoping @mindlessfluff is watching the #techphx closing for the day. He has our raffle tix.    
    
    
    @aprilholle great to see you today too!    
    
    
    Love the shirts @techsmith sent for #techphx! Wonder if @betsyweber would send me one? http://vsb.li/BrHZx0     
    
    
    #techphx opening starring @tsdivadani starts in 10mins. Are you here?    
    
    
    I'm at Room 201 @ UAT (Tempe, AZ) http://4sq.com/TpnGJG     
    
    
    @paulvalach that would be a great presentation for next year! Sign up!!!    
    
    
    Great to have been back in Phoenix for the weekend, but time to head back home now.    
    
    
    California time. 200 miles more.    
    
    
    Home. Stiff. Sore. Tired. Happy    
    
    
    @imkilo you are ripping thru them. By the time I get home from work tonight will there be any left to do? (kidding)    
    
    
    Word if the day: Nation    
    
    
    Word of the day: Organizer    
    
    
    Some thoughts and musings about making things for the web - The Oatmeal http://vsb.li/BG8kLS  via @Oatmeal    
    
    
    @BradMarston Thanks for being such an awesome customer!    
    
    
    @redptstrategies @BradMarston Suggest you try getting them to watch  our YouTube videos. http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL-B1wk591JeKDzUejM6oVI-cQ0-bXy_47 … Shorter and more lively    
    
    
    Have I said lately how much I love working at @NationBuilder? It rocks! And we are hiring!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Community    
    
    
    @imkilo @transmatrix I haven't even had the energy to start my part yet. How am I supposed to catch up now? :) Glad you are able to do them!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Gadfly    
    
    
    Word of the day: Definition    
    
    
    Word of the day: Manor    
    
    
    @VisioMVP good one. Have missed your comments lately!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Events    
    
    
    About to see Lincoln with @mindlessfluff and some @NationBuilder folks (@ Regal LA LIVE Stadium 14 w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/UKBTPQ     
    
    
    Word of the day: everything    
    
    
    Thanks to @betsyweber & @techsmith I have two new t-shirts. Great to be able to wear something that promotes one of my fav companies!    
    
    
    To the real couple behind xkcd - Your awesomeness never ceases to amaze me. http://pinterest.com/pin/50524827041208134/ …    
    
    
    The Ultimate Night In: Seamless and UrbanDaddy are giving away three prizes of $1,000 worth of delivery and spirits. http://vsb.li/kLTZm9     
    
    
    Checked in. Have my preboard pass. Now for food for the flight. (@ Terminal 1) http://4sq.com/YnzCC6     
    
    
    @ianpatrickhines thanks!    
    
    
    made it this far. Next up... Get luggage and car, then drive to Rockford http://4sq.com/SAkjRN     
    
    
    Waiting room... Waiting for my mom's surgery to finish. (@ Swedish American Hospital) http://4sq.com/UBJYdq     
    
    
    @FreddywithaY it went very well. She is home and resting.    
    
    
    Here 2.5 hours early for a wide variety of reasons. Hoping computer and midi have enough charge (@ Alterra Coffee) http://4sq.com/XrFWY2     
    
    
    No idea why foursquare checked me in at the coffee place. I am st my gate in Milwaukee    
    
    
    Word of the day: Hiatus    
    
    
    Santa Santa Santa.. Everywhere I look near Pershing square in LA there are Santa's!    
    
    
    The @packers need to get something going. Down by two touchdowns    
    
    
    Word of the day: Rails    
    
    
    @gkirkpatrick Both!    
    
    
    Word of the day: cold    
    
    
    Word of the day: IF    
    
    
    Work day done. Heading home through traffic. Looking forward to some sleep tonight.    
    
    
    @FreddywithaY that would make for a great sb    
    
    
    Word of the day: butterscotch    
    
    
    @randyknob do you have her recipe?    
    
    
    Word of the day: exceptional    
    
    
    Word of the day: light    
    
    
    Word of the day: End    
    
    
    Word of the day: Blurry    
    
    
    Hoping this is as good as it smells (@ Rolling Rice) http://4sq.com/UhJ05H     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://vsb.li/X7vPay  HALLELUJAH - Covered Live by Espen Lind, Kurt Nilsen, Alejandro Fuentes and Holm    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube playlist http://vsb.li/heLqTW  A tribute to    
    
    
    Waiting in line to see Les Miz :) (Checked in at Edwards West Covina 18) http://vsb.li/KpNoDx     
    
    
    Watching "cave of forgotten dreams" on History Channel - so inspiring    
    
    
    Word of the year: KNOW    
    
    
    @JoeConte I like it!!!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Cross-purposes    
    
    
    Word of the day: headset    
    
    
    Regarding the Westboro Baptist (so-called) Church | Telling it like I see it http://vsb.li/xaBXKs     
    
    
    Hey @Walgreens selling a month old weekly magazine as it were new is definitely #notcool - wish I had noticed b4 I bought it.    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @nmanewsdirect http://shrd.by/BfK328  Futuristic highways in the Netherlands glow in the dark    
    
    
    Futuristic highways in the Netherlands glow in the dark: http://shrd.by/Asrp6m  via @youtube    
    
    
    Great dinner with Brent and Michelle Spore (and Cadie of course)!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Chrome    
    
    
    I nominate @WinObs for a Shorty Award in #blogger because... he makes Windows make sense for everyone! http://shrd.by/B3rtff     
    
    
    Word of the day: Optimize    
    
    
    Nice guy on the train gave me his seat. Awfully nice of him.    
    
    
    Word of the day: juggle    
    
    
    Word of the day: albeit    
    
    
    Back at Kaiser Baldwin Park for visit with B's eye doc. Serious case of deja vu    
    
    
    Word of the day: Blow    
    
    
    With+my+support%2C+the+Latin+American+Coalition+is+making+our+community+a+more+welcoming+place. http://shrd.by/LtYJll  via @la_coalicion    
    
    
    Got a #brooksideperk from @Klout & @Brookside_Choc - Choc coated pomegranate pieces. Yum to the max! Got me through the sick.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Saturday    
    
    
    Word if the day: fulgurous    
    
    
    Just realized the word of the day didn't post. It was WET    
    
    
    @A_StrausGarcia Thanks! Glad to help any time I can. Love helping @NationBuilder's customers!    
    
    
    @srikavuru You deserve a bunch of the thanks for today too!    
    
    
    Social Media Strategy in 8 Steps http://www.convinceandconvert.com/social-media-strategy/social-media-strategy-in-8-steps/ … via @jaybaer (Wonder if @dvpwjr has seen this?)    
    
    
    I’m on the waitlist to get an advance copy of #OzReimagined from 47North & @Klout! Check out the book here:  http://shrd.by/pxDqc0     
    
    
    @adrielhampton Great idea! Thinking my network needs to know this too!    
    
    
    This afternoon on NationBuilder Live, let's talk Events. Join me and @adrielhampton at 4 p.m. http://easternnationbuilder.com/live  #nptech    
    
    
    This afternoon on NationBuilder Live, let's talk Events. Join me and  @adrielhampton at 4 p.m. eastern http://shrd.by/H3XLEC  #nptech    
    
    
    @FreddywithaY Yes they are!    
    
    
    Word of the day: penguin    
    
    
    Word of the day: Exceed    
    
    
    Thinking about opening a nation? Do it today and make a difference in this world! https://3dna.nationbuilder.com/startnow     
    
    
    February first already? That month went by fast!    
    
    
    @WinObs got any big plans for this month?    
    
    
    @WinObs Sure am. But Summit 2013 will be my last one :/    
    
    
    @WinObs By choice. @Nationbuilder job is awesome, but keeps me way busy - no time for other stuff right now.    
    
    
    Word of the day: hack    
    
    
    @randyknob Yup. Mine might have been one. Changed my password just in case. Thanks for watching out for me!    
    
    
    For those wondering, word of the day wasn't related to the Twitter hack. It was bcse it was Hack Day at @Nationbuilder today    
    
    
    Word of the day: Camaraderie    
    
    
    Word of the day: propagate    
    
    
    I know there are events peeps in my network looking for jobs - @NationBuilder needs an event organizer http://shrd.by/R7gpOj     
    
    
    Want to expand your video skills? @NationBuilder is looking for a live video intern http://shrd.by/7fXNbV     
    
    
    Word of the day: patience    
    
    
    Word of the day; Hair    
    
    
    Just finished an @NationBuilder improve session! Thanks to Dan for leading it!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hurray! I have one of the top 5% most viewed @LinkedIn profiles for 2012. http://shrd.by/bYpC45     
    
    
    Word of the day: Song    
    
    
    word of the day: call    
    
    
    word of the day: quayage    
    
    
    Really wish I had this option: How to Download Your Twitter Archive http://shrd.by/gd6FPR  via @support    
    
    
    @randyknob @Support - I want it because it would be a great way to see my word of the day list from over the years.    
    
    
    What is your Social Media Personality? http://pinterest.com/pin/50524827041695921/ …    
    
    
    Word of the day: forget    
    
    
    Background Checks-Who Should Be Prevented From Buying Firearms? http://shrd.by/88NC5l  via @mindlessfluff    
    
    
    One year of Treehouse's Gold Plan for $49 http://shrd.by/tmaGmZ  via @appsumo    
    
    
    Missed my train by less than a minute. Glad it is a nice day - can sit and enjoy the sun while waiting.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Happiness    
    
    
    Word of the day: increase    
    
    
    Word of the day: Assemble    
    
    
    Word of the day: valuable    
    
    
    OH: It is not really a good idea to schedule a shift by yrslf right before a trip (So true - especially when the trip is #Summit2013)    
    
    
    @jodijodijodi how about lunch tomorrow?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jodijodijodi not tonight. Poss. Tomorrow coffee. Let me see how today goes    
    
    
    Word of the day: SUMMIT    
    
    
    Unexpected break between sessions. Staying here in bldg. 31. Join me! #msmvp13    
    
    
    Seeing so many of my fav keeps tonight!    
    
    
    Hoping @jodijodijodi feels better soon!!!!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Chatter    
    
    
    OneNote session w/ Daniel Escapa... 2 of four OneNote MVPs are in the room with many other MVPs    
    
    
    @A_StrausGarcia mostly aesthetic right now. Much more on backend in work. Will update you more next week when back from vacation    
    
    
    Word of the day: Notes    
    
    
    New guest blog post from @cstreet: Practical online tools to improve government http://shrd.by/BH3LdQ  via @NationBuilder    
    
    
    @WinObs @bschorr Daniel did the #OneNote presentation yesterday. IT was great. #mvp13    
    
    
    Great closing party. Time for me to call it a summit. Heading back to the hotel #mvp13    
    
    
    Moved to an earlier flight for Oakland to LAX. Glad it worked since my planned flight is 30 minutes late.    
    
    
    Yes it is silly, but I am hungry. (Checked in at Encounter Restaurant (LAX Tower)) http://shrd.by/smVcCq     
    
    
    Word of the day: Home    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://shrd.by/OLbFj1  Ellen's Great Adventure    
    
    
    Word of the day: Up    
    
    
    Word of the day: Sprint    
    
    
    Word of the day: Gather    
    
    
    Word of the day: interface    
    
    
    Lots of happy peeps at @NationBuilder tonight. Launch of  new control panel went well. Small party for us all at office. Great end to day!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Thursday    
    
    
    Word of the day: Strange    
    
    
    @doctordns yes!    
    
    
    @mmcallen true    
    
    
    @BradMarston @NationBuilder We are here here to help however we can!    
    
    
    Watch "Founding Your Nation" to get up and running quickly on NationBuilder http://shrd.by/rD1q7X     
    
    
    Word of the day: Yoga    
    
    
    Rain. Yuck. No wonder my knee was complaining. Slept in a bit because of it. On train to work now.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: remix    
    
    
    Word of the day: Donation    
    
    
    Ignore this share please :) http://fb.me/2144F9Bz2     
    
    
    Word of the day: echolocation    
    
    
    Celebrate International #WomensDay with @Kiva and #KloutforGood. Change a woman's life with a $25 loan on Kiva today. http://klout.com/s/forgood/kiva?n=tw&v=kiva&i=1718 …    
    
    
    Word of the day: Trade    
    
    
    word of the day: pi    
    
    
    Word of the day: dogmatic    
    
    
    Use NationBuilder and need help? Check out the newly designed support area on the site at: http://shrd.by/5wybqg     
    
    
    Word of the day: Rejuvenate    
    
    
    Word of the day: meeting    
    
    
    Word of the day: Exhausted    
    
    
    Word of the day: send    
    
    
    Shut up and listen: women, sexism, and tech http://shrd.by/S17wbe     
    
    
    Word of the day: loud    
    
    
    Word of the day: boolean    
    
    
    Just made a donation to VitaminCH http://shrd.by/KJTQXR     
    
    
    Word of the day: takeout    
    
    
    @wanichan @spiderwebwoman @JoliBallew @VisioMVP @tromboneforhire We will still stay in touch even though neither of us are MVPs any more.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Bank    
    
    
    See @callkathy speak at the@CompTechConf April 5th. (PS: I'll be there Thurs/Fri next week. Come up and see me!) http://nationbuilder.com/computer_technology_conference?recruiter_id=200780 …    
    
    
    Constantly amazed at who will/ won't offer seat on train. Nice guy who prob needs seat almost as much as me gave his up. Healthy peeps? Nope    
    
    
    Word of the day: finances    
    
    
    @brianshaler could have been worse... Could have been taxes. (run away!!!!)    
    
    
        
    
    
    testing something for an @NationBuilder customer. Will this link go through? http://shrd.by/Fs3Vce     
    
    
    Word of the day: spoof    
    
    
    another customer test.... http:/www.edshadid.com    
    
    
    Looking for pictures of user group meetings, awards, etc. I can use for the sample nation for @Comptechconf this week. Got any to share?    
    
    
    Word of the day: Arise    
    
    
    Bad end to the work day. Just got rear ended. Ok. But glad Bruce was driving.    
    
    
    Word of day: empress    
    
    
    Ah Sky Harbor.. You really never change. Waiting on my @Supershuttle up @comptechconf    
    
    
    @twinklergirl is @odasnor coming or going?    
    
    
    @twinklergirl only here until tomorrow evening. Presenting at a conference at Fort McDowell. Wish we could get together    
    
    
    @twinklergirl Definitely!    
    
    
    Word of the day: participate    
    
    
    Presenting on Social Media starting at 9:15 Phoenix time. Plz reply with your top tips!    
    
    
    Word of the day: institution    
    
    
    vintage social networking http://shrd.by/4E9pFd     
    
    
    Presentations? Done. Hugs? Got 'em! Resting at the conference center? On it!    
    
    
    Still at the fort waiting for @supershuttle which was supposed to be here 30 mins ago. Drvr called to say he was past Shea and Scottsdale    
    
    
    Word of the day: Bruise    
    
    
    Word of the day: Silence    
    
    
    @randyknob  Please - can we silence them?    
    
    
    @SuperShuttle Sent in the report. Have full eval email at home. Haven't found a way to be polite enough in my comments to submit it.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Socks    
    
    
    @BlondeByDesign I hope you are having an absolutely sparkly wonderful birthday!!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Spike    
    
    
    Tattle Monster - for all the parents in my life! http://shrd.by/90AGyZ     
    
    
    We're off to see the wizard, finally! Oz better be worth the ticket price!    
    
    
    Now for movie number two: Hunger Games via Amazon Prime    
    
    
    Word of the day: Chill    
    
    
    Dinner out with my honey (@ California Pizza Kitchen - @calpizzakitchen) [pic]: http://4sq.com/115IbhT     
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: Frazzle    
    
    
    Word of the day: Smell    
    
    
    Word of the day: Quiz    
    
    
    Wow - gas today was only 3.83 a gallon in El Monte. Been awhile since it was that low    
    
    
    Word of the day: Clear    
    
    
    Word of the day: geocode    
    
    
    Word of the day: Migration    
    
    
    Word of the day: Choice    
    
    
    I've just entered to win a @Surface RT, from @consumercamp. You can enter, too. http://shrd.by/CZR2Qz     
    
    
    Excel Book Moving Sale: http://shrd.by/xQScDz  via @youtube and @mrexcel    
    
    
    Word of the day: Formula    
    
    
    Two of my favorite @NationBuilder team members here at work with me today: @srikavuru and @melinda_amato They need followers :)    
    
    
    Steak! Always a good thing (@ Clearman's Galley "The Boat") http://4sq.com/10ktmFO     
    
    
    Word of the day: marked    
    
    
        
    
    
    No train this morning. Being driven to work. Hope the day gets better.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Pipe    
    
    
    Word of the day: Wait    
    
    
        
    
    
    Not much more time to wait!    
    
    
    #TornadoWeek Would love to hear what is going on in the room!Maybe the wind is too much for the mics.. Learn more at http://shrd.by/QXw7rH     
    
    
    Great piece on the value of a work-life balance (and what part of it whe shouldn't ignore) from my friend @timheuer http://shrd.by/y1aBV7     
    
    
    Lunch (@ Fruit Tree Cafe) http://4sq.com/100SK7K     
    
    
    Word of the day: punctilious    
    
    
    Word of day: anosognosic    
    
    
    word of the day: sketch    
    
    
    @OutdoorCookCom So glad the testing is going well for the new Twitter API!    
    
    
    Word of the day: water    
    
    
    I just got Perk'd with a One-Day Pass to the @AmericanAir #AdmiralsClub lounge! See if you can too at    
    
    
    Please reply to this tweet #testingwhenishouldbeasleep    
    
    
    Best times to post on social media infgoraphic http://shrd.by/nWtDw7     
    
    
    Word of the day: Hammer    
    
    
    Word of the day: maternal    
    
    
    Excel on the Mac really doesn't like me today #justsayin    
    
    
    Word of the day: pasta    
    
    
    Word of the day: candor    
    
    
    Word of the day: alone    
    
    
    Word of the day: Again    
    
    
    Word of the day: suggestion    
    
    
    Sumo Sleepover in Seattle http://shrd.by/gRH3hT  via @appsumo    
    
    
    Word of the day: History    
    
    
    Word of the day: hippopotomonstrosesquipedaliophobia    
    
    
    @JustSomeAntics Glad to be connected! You should check in with @mindlessfluff too - he's my hubby - will be an expert some day    
    
    
    Just learned that my friend @twistedbarbie shares strange facts of the day. If you like interesting facts - follow her!    
    
    
    @twistedbarbie How well I know it!    
    
    
    I have a dream http://shrd.by/1LB451  testing...testing...testing    
    
    
    Word of the day: baize    
    
    
    Please RSVP: Join us for a drink at THE PARISH http://shrd.by/w6fpax     
    
    
    Word of the day: scattered    
    
    
    Word of the day: mapping    
    
    
    Bruce just saved me. I left my purse at our happy hour and he ran up the stairs and got it for me. He rocks.    
    
    
    Word of the day: Year    
    
    
    @twistedbarbie LOL    
    
    
    @twistedbarbie @karameredith Neither of you told me this was for Girl Scouts!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Count    
    
    
    The tech team at @NationBuilder rocks. #justsayin    
    
    
    Word of the day: Telecommute    
    
    
        
    
    
    Had a blast at the beach. Expect to be sore tomorrow but it was well worth it. Pics to come if any are good enough. :D    
    
    
        
    
    
    Social Media crisis infographic from @JFouts http://shrd.by/LPG1RH     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://shrd.by/QWxfpm  Memory-a spoof by Pam Peterson    
    
    
    Word of the day: found    
    
    
    Word of the day: curvature    
    
    
    NationBuilder raises $8M round to show community organizing can be big business http://shrd.by/Mj51cY  via @pandodaily    
    
    
    Word of the day: Submitted    
    
    
    Word of the day: scalability    
    
    
    @SolitaireBlitz Got my deck of cards and the extra surprise. Thanks!!!    
    
    
    Word of the day; Harvest    
    
    
    Word of the day: assurance    
    
    
    Word of the day: Nap    
    
    
    Word of the day: orthogonal    
    
    
    Word of the day: Father    
    
    
    @VisioMVP Missed this on Friday... But that would work. Or, would work if I had time to take one :)    
    
    
    If you do front end engineering or any Javascript programming... Read this. A page of great tips! http://shrd.by/rZLBon     
    
    
    Word of the day: querulous    
    
    
    Word of the day: track    
    
    
    Word of the day: duplicate    
    
    
    Burgers... Yum... (@ Nick's Burgers) http://4sq.com/16kgYer     
    
    
    Word of the day: interview    
    
    
    Word of the day: achievement    
    
    
    Word of the day: Keyboard    
    
    
    Word of the day: magniloquent    
    
    
    @FreddywithaY You could. I know that. Apply!!! Apply!!! Apply!!!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Mattress    
    
    
    Word of the day: purpose    
    
    
    Word of the day: Air    
    
    
    Dinner out. Smells good! (@ Yes Sushi) http://4sq.com/17PG9Xr     
    
    
    Word of the day: Return    
    
    
    Word of the day: defenestrate    
    
    
    @roger_lee Sorry to hear you have to shut down Job Change Notifier. Have used it for years and will miss it greatly!    
    
    
    Word of the day: converse    
    
    
    finished Aliens Ate My Pickup by Mercedes Lackey http://amzn.to/QPdKJ9     
    
    
    Smells great (@ Ish New Asian Kitchen) http://4sq.com/133DjNr     
    
    
    @JoeConte @gavindeschutter I love his work! If you like Excel based art, check out this app: http://www.boydevlin.co.uk/excelart/excelart.php …    
    
    
    Word of the day: Convoluted    
    
    
    Chop chop (@ Supercuts) http://4sq.com/12yIVj6     
    
    
    Word of the day: worry    
    
    
    Don't believe the latest rumor that Android 5.0 is delayed. (From http://shrd.by/OwFB0d  - one of my favo http://shrd.by/MtvKyf     
    
    
    Word of the day: ferschimmeled    
    
    
    Word of the day: long    
    
    
    Word of the day: indulgence    
    
    
    Word of the day: Card    
    
    
    Word of the day: break    
    
    
    Word of the day: French    
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: pulchritudinous    
    
    
    @SueOnTheWeb Exactly!    
    
    
    Word of the day: Jaw    
    
    
        
    
    
    Had a great time at #xLSoCal - Great to see @MrExcel too! First time that he, @mindlessfluff  & I have been in same place at same time!    
    
    
    If you are looking for another great Excel resource (and bio), check out @xszil    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MrExcel That's kinda brilliant....    
    
    
    Word of the day: tab    
    
    
    @AOSoCalI I want to learn more about what's been covered in your past events. Looking for software test in agile environment    
    
    
    @AOSoCal  Have attended several. Know all about both Open Space and the Unconference movement. . Thanks for the infol    
    
    
    Word of the day: Skeuomorphism    
    
    
    Going out to pick up my order from @GrubHub and hoping I find not just dinner, but myself as well. #Namaste http://shrd.by/183gAK     
    
    
    Word of the day: Radiculitis    
    
    
    Word of the day: Penguin    
    
    
    Word of the day: dinosaur    
    
    
    @redtimmy Thanks for being so great to @nationbuilder and its customers!    
    
    
    Word of the day: garlic    
    
    
    @randyknobloch  I did and I love it!!!    
    
    
    Thinking that Google missed a beat on today's doodle - clicking it should take you to a random cat video....    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: Adventure    
    
    
    Word of the day: sleep    
    
    
    Word of the day: Coach    
    
    
    Word of the day: migraine    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: international    
    
    
    Word of the day: Magnetic    
    
    
    Word of the day: Screen    
    
    
    Word of the day: Gig    
    
    
    Word of the day: Virtualization    
    
    
    Word of the day: sophomore    
    
    
    Word of the day: Drill    
    
    
    I think @NationBuilder HQ needs one of these :) http://shrd.by/WqD1hM     
    
    
    Word of the day: Hundred    
    
    
    Word of the day: adapter    
    
    
    Word of the day: Demonym    
    
    
    Take The New Episode SurvHeyyyyy http://shrd.by/mA27Ag     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://shrd.by/x5eRde  Monty Python and the Holy Grail Modern Trailer    
    
    
    Word of the day: pandemonium    
    
    
    Word of the day: wonder    
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: Bruise    
    
    
    Word of the day:  Title    
    
    
    Word of the day: Permission    
    
    
    Word of the day: Guacamole    
    
    
    Word of the day: comic    
    
    
    Word of the day: card    
    
    
    Word of the day: perhaps    
    
    
    Dear @GOP -  shutting down the government to prevent Obamacare is petty and irresponsible.  http://shrd.by/Tv09ol     
    
    
    Word of the day: Intern    
    
    
    Please follow and welcome @biancaNBTest - She's a new intern here in the @nationbuilder test team!    
    
    
    Word of the day: impediment    
    
    
    Tall Infographics - The wave of the future according to xkcd! http://shrd.by/z024OT     
    
    
    Word if the day: noisiness    
    
    
    Word of the day: Feathers    
    
    
    Open Letter http://pinterest.com/pin/50524827042999964/ …    
    
    
    Hippopotomonstrosesquipedaliophobia    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Not just a geeky tech dream: one month of UK political conferences  http://nationbuilder.com/nationbuilder_uk_splash … via @NationBuilder    
    
    
    Word of the day: typical    
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: Name    
    
    
        
    
    
    From @Janet Fouts Love Your Content - History of Content Marketing World http://pinterest.com/pin/50524827043055157/ …    
    
    
    @VisioMVP I knew someone would say that. Also expecting a reply of the breakfast type.(answered from wrong account afraid you didn't see it)    
    
    
    Word of the day: example    
    
    
    I am speaking at @TechPHX! 2013 Speaker: Kathy Jacobs - http://s.shr.lc/1gsUKzu     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/lnG3MKos87A?a  Children's Hospital at Dartmouth-Hitchcock performs Katy Perry's Roar    
    
    
    Word if the day: Closed    
    
    
    Word of the day: instantaneous    
    
    
        
    
    
    just posting test posts, not much else right now    
    
    
    They say not to get testy but I can not help it    
    
    
    Word of the day: Giraffe    
    
    
    @sherrierohde and @WinObs That is the word of the day on FB - and those photos are what inspired it! Hope it made your day!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: Kinemortophobia    
    
    
    @OutdoorCookCom and @mindlessfluff You need to post some new recipes soon    
    
    
    Please welcome @BiancaNBtest @thewesternkid23 to social media. Just introduced them to LinkedIn and the dos and don'ts of Twitter    
    
    
    Word of the day: turnout    
    
    
    word of the day: list    
    
    
    @bennettscience Need to Dm you a question about the chrome beta email you sent me earlier this week. Can you follow me so I can ask?    
    
    
    Word of the day: add    
    
    
    Check this out: Win Great Prizes And Do A Good Deed! - http://shrd.by/Tw4DKn     
    
    
    I see...Two little dogs facing away from each other
#RorschachDoodle http://shrd.by/CKbENn     
    
    
    Word of the day: improvisational    
    
    
    @jkc137  Sure seems that way some weeks. (this one included)    
    
    
    I just signed up to become an Alpha Tester for 'Motiif. Sign up now - http://shrd.by/Nhx7wZ , @MotiifIsUS http://shrd.by/S4pzEG     
    
    
    Word of the day: Drama    
    
    
    Word of the day: vacation    
    
    
    Thank you for the 51derful birthday greetings! They made a good day great!    
    
    
    Foursquare check-in at 'TechPhx': Check-in at TechPhx on Foursquare:    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just listened to @thefabulousone talk about #howsocialmediastolemykidney at #techphx    
    
    
        
    
    
    #techphx after party (@ Main Event Entertainment w/ @spellwight) http://4sq.com/1dFTnZe     
    
    
    Day 2 - more great presentations, more great people! (at @TechPhx w/ @twinklergirl @spellwight) http://4sq.com/1dIMvdD     
    
    
    Hotel check out commencing. Ready to head back to LA. Great time here, but miss my bed!    
    
    
    @Camping4Foodies @Linda_Esposito Great meeting both of you too!    
    
    
    @stephliebold Just saw your great summary of my talk from @TechPhx Very glad you got so much out of it!    
    
    
    Word of the day: image    
    
    
    Word of the day: Water    
    
    
    Word of the day: minion    
    
    
    Word of the day: Jeopardy    
    
    
    Foursquare check-in at 'Edwards El Monte 8': Check-in at Edwards El Monte 8 on Foursquare:    
    
    
    Word of the day: Killer    
    
    
        
    
    
    Word of the day: search    
    
    
    Word of the day: Visit    
    
    
    @VisioMVP Thanks for the daily groan :)    
    
    
    Awesome food. Attentive service. Handled our allergies with no problems (@ Happy Family Restaurant) http://4sq.com/1gOJ1YT     
    
    
    . @NanceLarson I know that @NationBuilder is hiring too - learn more at http://shrd.by/qnp409     
    
    
    Car's land! (@ Flo's V8 Café - @disneyland w/ 2 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/19xdkOE     
    
    
        
    
    
    Looking for work in organizing or tech? Check out NationBuilder! Learn more about our philosophy: http://shrd.by/C2GSq6     
    
    
        
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://shrd.by/fa4AHJ  WestJet Christmas Miracle: real-time giving    
    
    
    Word of the day: Graduation    
    
    
    @VisioMVP  Only if the lines are growing or shrinking in size :)    
    
    
    Word of the day: fourteen    
    
    
    