Leapfrog names 65 best hospitals in the country for 2010 | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/fRIyz1    
    
    
    RSNA: Agfa HealthCare spotlights meaningful use | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/g5FOu7    
    
    
    Colorado Technical University addresses 'changing workforce needs' | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/i8pL0d    
    
    
    I just signed up for the Xobni for iPhone Alpha. You should too. http://www.xobni.com/waitinglist/iphonealpha …    
    
    
    Accountant (Plains, PA) - http://catsone.com/j?428j #jobs #catsjobs    
    
    
    Business Development Manager (Plains, PA) - http://catsone.com/j?3vli #jobs #catsjobs    
    
    
    Project Manger (National Position) (Plains, PA) - http://catsone.com/j?3vkq #jobs #catsjobs    
    
    
    HIMSS Survey: Meaningful Use is Driver of Health IT Spending http://bit.ly/aUYsCK    
    
    
    University of Iowa Hospitals and Clinics patients support online records | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/eZ4Vjq    
    
    
    Healthcare Job Postings Up in November http://bit.ly/gzjUOp    
    
    
    EMR Implementation: How Do You Stack Up Against Your Peers? http://bit.ly/ee0ZqX    
    
    
    John Brebbia: Surgeon™s Work Honors Fallen Friend http://bit.ly/dLGtGY    
    
    
    RSNA: Fate of ailing car mechanic illustrates healthcare's woes http://bit.ly/frTpqE    
    
    
    Retirees need more than $100K to cover health costs - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/fkGM9P    
    
    
    Barriers to Meaningful Use with Modular Certification | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/fejjrj    
    
    
    Nuns, a dying breed fade from leadership roles at Catholic hospitals http://bit.ly/npHv9I     
    
    
    10 ACO Blunders You Can Avoid http://bit.ly/qWdUPo     
    
    
    VA will test cloud-based collaboration tools for physicians http://bit.ly/r4yJdI     
    
    
    Single vocab standard for each EHR reporting domain seen as 'momentous' http://bit.ly/qWsSVi     
    
    
    Healthcare IT News zeroes in on best places to work | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/o4DNfP     
    
    
    Contest seeks development of Facebook app for emergencies | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ndK6em     
    
    
    Obama's new rural jobs initiative includes health IT http://bit.ly/r75q5b     
    
    
    Cloud Connect: NIST Prepares 'Use Case' Site -- Cloud computing -- InformationWeek http://bit.ly/dmMUpx    
    
    
    Check out this site: http://fcgadgets.blogspot.com/2009/04/friend-connect-gadget-share-this.html    
    
    
    Mar 17, 2010 -- Healthcare IT Consultant Blog - powered by FeedBurner http://bit.ly/adSIkM 

Fifty-eight percent of... http://bit.ly/cgBroo    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/admWN8    
    
    
    Can Broadband Really Save Healthcare?  http://bit.ly/9LutNW    
    
    
    SHSMD: 10 Tips for Strategic Planning http://bit.ly/peRb1O     
    
    
    EHR incentive program ramps up to 90K providers http://bit.ly/r1oXF4     
    
    
    Walked into a lamppost? Hurt while crocheting? Help is on the way http://bit.ly/r4EARc     
    
    
    Health Affairs: Real benefit will come later for meaningful use, CPOE http://bit.ly/nX2R85     
    
    
    CFO Exchange: Weighing Expenses Against Quality Mandates http://bit.ly/q9u3fU     
    
    
    Healthcare IT: On the Road to Reform, Regardless of What Happens in Court | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/qKQJ4l     
    
    
    Huntzinger Management Group - Job Opportunities http://bit.ly/ifRxNR     
    
    
    Senate passes bill to exempt docs from FTC's Red Flags Rule | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/fgMnWd    
    
    
    AHA presses government to rethink EHR certification | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/fsKjTE    
    
    
    Top 6 Financial Game-Changers for Hospitals http://bit.ly/fBwaoG    
    
    
    EMRs a 'double-edged sword' for doc, patient communication . http://bit.ly/9DuQ3F    
    
    
    Job Growth Continues for Healthcare Sector http://bit.ly/gNiMBV    
    
    
    What Is A Cloud Data Center Anyway? - Plug Into The Cloud - InformationWeek http://bit.ly/fLdZEV    
    
    
    Guerra On Healthcare: Frustration With Meaningful Use Widespread -- Meaningful Use http://bit.ly/fUWeXr    
    
    
    FREE SEMINAR 
Meaningful Use Attainment
http://events.linkedin.com/Meaningful-Use-Attainment/pub/296746    
    
    
    Looking for a Cerner PharmNet - Project Manager: http://lnkd.in/agV2xM     
    
    
    looking for a Cerner National Health Inpatient Quality Measures (NHIQM) Project Manager: http://lnkd.in/EusG7b     
    
    
    The Huntzinger Management Group, Inc. (HMG) Featured on Business Day with Terry Bradshaw - Yahoo! Finance http://yhoo.it/r65nLl     
    
    
    Anthelio to bring ICD-10 jobs to Detroit | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/pykulw     
    
    
    Breaking down the barriers to EMR exchange http://bit.ly/cgDRtE    
    
    
    Meditech Consultant needed submit resumes to: http://bit.ly/9dtWAr    
    
    
    EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITES  
Meditech Consultant

                    The Huntzinger... http://bit.ly/dosIpv    
    
    
    Hospitals work to lower 30-day readmission rates http://bit.ly/qQw48o     
    
    
    U.S. healthcare performance score declines | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/mPGss5     
    
    
    3 health IT success stories | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/pHtfn7     
    
    
    Social media guide provides docs with 15 step game plan | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/oo75n4     
    
    
    EHR market to hit $6.5B by 2012 - FierceEMR http://bit.ly/pqPQup     
    
    
    4 priority strategies for hospitals of the future - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/pJvYj6     
    
    
    5 technologies every hospital should be using | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/qVaxy8     
    
    
    Hey recruiters, do you want to search 77 Million resumes online? Do you want to search social media sites? All that at http://ReferYes.com     
    
    
    ACO Final Rules Released http://bit.ly/n2gQ6e     
    
    
    IL doc database launches online http://bit.ly/oDH1wf     
    
    
    Physician Group: Revise Privacy Rule Regarding Research Issues http://bit.ly/np3pio     
    
    
    CHIME Survey Tracks Meaningful Use Progress http://bit.ly/psFhkg     
    
    
    Size matters when it comes to EHR adoption http://bit.ly/uYV7mK     
    
    
    Physician groups initially pleased with final ACO rule 
October 25, 2011 | D http://bit.ly/tzqDcQ     
    
    
    ACO Final Rule: 10 Healthcare Leaders Sound Off http://bit.ly/uwVuF9     
    
    
    MGMA calls for HIPAA 5010 contingency plan to avoid physician practice cash flow disruption Posted http://bit.ly/tn41ZQ     
    
    
    White House calls for health data exchange standards | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/hNOuLB    
    
    
    CIO confidence plunges, says CHIME | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ejV4hC    
    
    
    Hospital Impact - Social media's role evolving in healthcare http://bit.ly/eTz9En    
    
    
    6 Steps to Creating a Connected Health Program http://bit.ly/st7RBe     
    
    
    Healthcare Workforce Planning Techniques Lagging http://bit.ly/tAa4VC     
    
    
    Healthcare CIOs Tell Job Seekers to Keep Skills Sharp http://bit.ly/sg4uxM     
    
    
    AMA Urges House to Pass Doc Fix Extension http://bit.ly/e5i2gK    
    
    
    CPOEs Can Decrease Mortality Rates, Research Shows http://bit.ly/fpV7iO    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/fwcMbH    
    
    
    Healthcare Workforce Planning Techniques Lagging http://bit.ly/rzjUMy     
    
    
    4 Ways to Think About ACO Strategy http://shar.es/XqbwB     
    
    
    Top 5 IT rules for smaller practices http://bit.ly/t5phPq     
    
    
    Checklist: 9 tasks that will get you ready for ICD-10 implem http://bit.ly/rRMBco     
    
    
    26% of CHIME CIOs set to receive Meaningful Use incentives http://bit.ly/sVPJar     
    
    
    Half of health execs use patient satisfaction as physician incentive http://bit.ly/uoNYnp     
    
    
    69% of healthcare execs say budgets are flat or increasing http://bit.ly/tDueJx     
    
    
    Hospital Impact - Do you really have revenue cycle covered? http://bit.ly/tj1dti     
    
    
    Congress Passes 'Doc Fix' Bill; Obama Calls for Permanent Fix http://bit.ly/ezkRwY    
    
    
    Congress Passes 'Doc Fix' Bill; Obama Calls for Permanent Fix http://bit.ly/ezkRwY    
    
    
    Congress Passes 'Doc Fix' Bill; Obama Calls for Permanent Fix http://bit.ly/ezkRwY    
    
    
    Meaningful use takes focus, say three CIOs who've done it | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/tVIz1y     
    
    
    Health record banks eliminate privacy concerns surrounding electronic patient records | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/hVDTIS    
    
    
    Provider data breaches cost billions | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/gR3AbM    
    
    
    EHR helps Marshfield boost care, save Medicare $83M | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/hrBf2N    
    
    
    NIST at work on EHR usability | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/gyaUbK    
    
    
    Healthcare IT Implications of Healthcare Reform | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/f6TreF    
    
    
    Tenet rejects CHS buyout offer, shares skyrocket - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/gYYeSi    
    
    
    Beacon communities: Who will serve as health IT models? | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/cIiPtQ    
    
    
    AHA targets health IT as priority for 2010 | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/duaGLW    
    
    
    Looking for a Meditech Billing Analyst for long term project. Call me if you can help (248) 495-5437    
    
    
    Looking for a Meditech Billing Analyst http://bit.ly/aPikP4    
    
    
    #Britishproble    
    
    
    HAPPY MOTHERS DAY.  A day to celebrate, honor all mothers and express gratitude for the hardships they bear in bringing up a child.    
    
    
    Experienced Healthcare Project Manager (NATIONAL POSITION) http://bit.ly/vlrsQH     
    
    
    Great Opportunity for a Sr. Management Consultant/Interim CIO (NATIONAL POSITION) http://bit.ly/v3wJ1b     
    
    
    A little electronic help for docs helps hospitals, study shows http://bit.ly/s6ivc9     
    
    
    Capstone project requires students to develop an EHR plan that demonstrates meaningful use http://bit.ly/aoRVj4    
    
    
    @Scobleizer A job well done, enjoyed the video's.  What great technology.    
    
    
    Tough teaching tech in healthcare but result is worth it | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/9KII2B    
    
    
    Medication Vending Machines Offer Patient Convenience In Rural Areas http://bit.ly/9Ym5wU    
    
    
    New HHS regulation to keep young adults insured | Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/dznQam    
    
    
    Just changed my twitter background, check it out! Found it at http://www.TwitterBackgrounds.com    
    
    
    Interim Rule Issued on Young Adult Health Insurance Coverage http://shar.es/mhKdD    
    
    
    New Healthcare Bill of Rights to Be Issued Soon http://shar.es/mhKlG    
    
    
    Eye on Quality Will Pay for Hospitals Under New Reform Measures http://shar.es/mhKZL    
    
    
    Five Changes Health Plans Need to Make Now http://shar.es/mhKy0    
    
    
    Five Tips to Guide Your Hospital’s Social Media Policy http://shar.es/mhEtJ    
    
    
    http://www.healthcareitnews.com/news/health-it-expansion-create-tens-thousands-jobs    
    
    
    Exciting Opportunities for Revenue Cycle Project Managers http://bit.ly/uieWra     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving!    
    
    
    ICD-10 Cost, Timing Concerns Explain AMA Vote http://bit.ly/uhm6Zn     
    
    
    Top 12 Uncertainties Hovering Over Healthcare http://bit.ly/unaIGj     
    
    
    Emotional Advertising is Still Most Effective http://shar.es/m4tmI    
    
    
    HealthLeaders Media Breakthroughs - HealthLeaders Media http://shar.es/m4tXX    
    
    
    Finally stopped raining and the Sun is out.    
    
    
    Walgreens backs off on plan to sell genetic test - Health care- msnbc.com http://bit.ly/bOypAu    
    
    
    Economy's health is improving, data show - Stocks & economy- msnbc.com http://bit.ly/bp9hNG    
    
    
    Have a great weekend everyone.    
    
    
    White House Issues First Legal Defense of Healthcare Reform http://shar.es/m4RCQ    
    
    
    Time to Put Patients First http://shar.es/m4RYY    
    
    
    SoCal Hospitals Work On Way to Get Around Physician Employment Ban http://shar.es/m4MsU    
    
    
    EMS Appreciation Week.  Recognize the EMTs at your locol Emergency Medical Services.    
    
    
    Tracking down patient perceptions of EHRs | EHR Watch: http://bit.ly/da0DBw via @addthis    
    
    
    Your Local RHIO/HIE Could Be a Meaningful Partner | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/cSbEEk    
    
    
    Study: Health Data Leaks Still an Issue After New HITECH Rules - http://bit.ly/ctJnuK    
    
    
    Social media for hospitals: Without it, 'you don't exist' | Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/a91OT9    
    
    
    Social media tools may reduce attrition in online health programs | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ew5zmD    
    
    
    10 Strategies for Healthcare M&A Success http://bit.ly/eiDWH4    
    
    
    Telemedicine in ICUs May Trim Critical Care Costs http://bit.ly/i1nNqT    
    
    
    How Hospitals Can Cut Medical Liability Costs http://bit.ly/dR9WnU    
    
    
    Hospital CIO confidence level for meeting meaningful use drops | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/fU4yAf    
    
    
    Survey: Top 5 reasons providers not ready for meaningful use | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/hOm4Z5    
    
    
    Study: Speedy implementation key to reducing EHR costs for docs | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/i0WdMp    
    
    
    The Court sided with Virginia Attorney General Ken Cuccinelli when it http://bit.ly/gOq6Bt    
    
    
    Females pay 30 percent more for healthcare - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/emTz9S    
    
    
    MGMA Tells HHS New EMR Disclosure Requirements ’Onerous’ http://shar.es/mYpO1    
    
    
    Employment Opportunity EPIC Radiant Certified Consultant http://bit.ly/hnVYH4    
    
    
    Health IT consultants in demand | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ciF2gz    
    
    
    10 IT challenges for physician practices in 2012 | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ssgspZ     
    
    
    PepsiCo to pay for workers to get some procedures at Johns Hopkins - http://baltimoresun.com  http://bsun.md/vgR5dB     
    
    
    Doctors™ Top 3 PHR Fears http://bit.ly/tzt5Hk     
    
    
    Will ICD-10 spark coder chaos? | ICD10 Watch: http://bit.ly/a8bzLj via @addthis    
    
    
    Health IT hottest career trend for college graduates | Healthcare IT News: http://bit.ly/aX4YWI via @addthis    
    
    
    Mental and behavioral health providers should be included in meaningful use | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/aKWc5d    
    
    
    Ready or Not, Tech-Savvy e-Patients are Coming http://bit.ly/bg1EPk    
    
    
    Don’t Cut Here! Lower Inpatient Satisfaction Scores an Ominous Sign http://bit.ly/9bkDrh    
    
    
    www.huntzingergroup.com. New postings 2-3 year engagement needs; SQL DBA / Data Miner, Senior PM (CPOE) Senior PM (Meditech BMV)    
    
    
    VA announces 26 winning ideas of its health IT initiative | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/cu4GPP    
    
    
    Big growth projected for HIS market | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/9ftcNZ    
    
    
    Surveys point to health IT jobs on the rise | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/b1MgYN    
    
    
    Looking for a SQL Database Administrator and Data Miner with Healthcare experience.    
    
    
    HHS $84 Million Bringing HIT to "Low-Income & Uninsured" | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/9OxqNo    
    
    
    Global HIS market to grow to $18B by 2016 | Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/bpwUCk    
    
    
    How healthcare organizations can prosper post-healthcare reform | Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/aPYRmD    
    
    
    EHRs: Are they a necessary inconvenience? | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/exa0vl    
    
    
    WIREC signs up 1,000 PCPs | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/gzZEk8    
    
    
    KLAS names top 20 software and service vendors | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/dXnNG1    
    
    
    3 Actions That Could Save Community Hospitals http://bit.ly/gLD0R9    
    
    
    6 Health Systems Team with Dartmouth to Study Quality, Costs http://bit.ly/gzWxmL    
    
    
    HITECH, HIPAA Rules to Launch Simultaneously in 2011 http://bit.ly/eAc4Gl    
    
    
    Oak Hill Hospital (FL) to expand, create jobs http://bit.ly/gunLK9    
    
    
    Celebrate the Current Pace | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/dmCHnx    
    
    
    White House and allies set to build up health law http://bit.ly/cYZMA3    
    
    
    Failure to Extend COBRA Subsidies Could Hurt Many Families, Report Says http://bit.ly/b1hh6O    
    
    
    Twenty Percent of High School Youth Took Prescription Drugs without Doctor’s Rx http://bit.ly/9UTJe7    
    
    
    LOOKING FOR PROJECT MANAGER's Full time position, various openings available! http://www.huntzingergroup.com/career-opportunities    
    
    
    When Implementing a HIS, Big Bang or Phases? | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/brKqpN    
    
    
    Changing the Healthcare System of an Entire Nation | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/cYWxav    
    
    
    Feds Seek Anti-Fraud Technologies to Nab Medicare Cheats http://bit.ly/f77EdW    
    
    
    'Doc Fix' Provides More Questions than Answers http://bit.ly/hpBYdp    
    
    
    OIG: Investigations Recovered $26B in FY2010 http://bit.ly/gLXjlc    
    
    
    Hospitalists Seek Parity With Hospitals http://bit.ly/igpZIr    
    
    
    Catholic Church's role in care at Ariz. hospital hotly debated http://bit.ly/fG5P4R    
    
    
    Study: EMRs' effect on docs' productivity depends on needs, workflow | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/gfP4yD    
    
    
    Find leads for your job openings on search engines and social networks using #referyes http://ReferYes.com     
    
    
    Thomson Reuters IDs 15 Top Health Systems http://bit.ly/xB3pIh     
    
    
    Ford, Microsoft to develop 'Doctor in Your Car' | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/yIk2T8     
    
    
    5 keys to getting your HIE capabilities up and running | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/xUnmWO     
    
    
    AMA releases EHR tutorials | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/yZqZxw     
    
    
    I am not sure about you but #sourcing with #referyes is crazy easy and worth a FREE #recruiter http://ReferYes.com     
    
    
    Premier names 21 top hospitals | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/9uROl6    
    
    
    HITECH Act 'lit a fire' under health systems | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/b3ctao    
    
    
    Just go back from Baltimore.  Why do we have to sit on a plane for 45 mins waiting to park?    
    
    
    Big growth projected for HIS market | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/9ftcNZ    
    
    
    AHIMA to providers: Don't put brakes on ICD-10 - FierceHealthIT http://bit.ly/y0miJg     
    
    
    ’Doc Fix’ Vote Contains Unwelcome News for Hospitals http://bit.ly/9seY71    
    
    
    HHS Releases Final Rule for Temporary EHR Certification Program http://bit.ly/aiIdBy    
    
    
    Lawsuit fears can lead to overtesting in ERs - Health care- msnbc.com http://bit.ly/9KFtwX    
    
    
    Healthcare jobs will grow the fastest of all industries | LinkedIn http://linkd.in/zog0dV     
    
    
    CSC Report Looks Ahead to Stage 2 of EHR Meaningful Use - HDM Latest News Article http://bit.ly/yAQPDB     
    
    
    There is absolutely no denying it now HIPAA 5010 is here- HDM Latest News Article http://bit.ly/xhlyLO     
    
    
    HIMSS calls for speedy but realistic progress on meaningful use | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/9PaWye    
    
    
    Pressure rising on healthcare long before overhaul takes effect http://bit.ly/9WxYfw    
    
    
    As law takes effect, Obama gives insurers a warning http://bit.ly/c6xkt8    
    
    
    Live from HFMA-ANI: Searching for Savings in the Reform Era http://bit.ly/9LoqyY    
    
    
    White House Announces Another $250 Million, This Time for Public Health Infrastructure and Prevention Efforts http://bit.ly/cPaXKp    
    
    
    Patients’ Bill of Rights Announced by White House http://bit.ly/90Hsq2    
    
    
    Are you a good fit for this job? Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/6  #job    
    
    
    The Road to EMR adoption: A Q&A with Heather Haugen and Jeffrey Woodside, Part 1 | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/cS57w7    
    
    
    Obama warns insurance companies not to unnecessarily raise costs http://bit.ly/akapVX    
    
    
    Physicians Turn to Online Communications http://bit.ly/cDJGv5    
    
    
    Study shows promise for electronic pill bottle | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/dBF03e    
    
    
    S&P: Healthcare Costs Growth Slowing http://bit.ly/ginKr9    
    
    
    Public Health Preparedness Jeopardized by Budget Cuts http://bit.ly/fuDgGF    
    
    
    Software re-design is critical for EMR adoption and critical mass | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/edxu1w    
    
    
    5 simple ways to realize ROI from your EHR | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/y88Mzi     
    
    
    ICD-10 deadline do-over? | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/wp543C     
    
    
    Health IT factors into Leapfrogs hospitals rankings http://bit.ly/wFbtHH     
    
    
    Open Health Tools, HIMSS to collaborate on open source standards | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/zXE22k     
    
    
    Health-Insurance Providers Seek Direct-to-Consumer Connections | News - Advertising Age http://bit.ly/zQwXWd     
    
    
    PwC top 6 trends: 'Extreme makeover' for healthcare http://bit.ly/feesz7    
    
    
    Hiring a Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/3  #job    
    
    
    Meaningful Use Tops Healthcare Industry Challenges for 2011 http://bit.ly/f10zPi    
    
    
    Purge What Does the Keane Acquisition Really Mean? | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/bNNsH0    
    
    
    Feds will sink $7M into solar energy system for VA hospital - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/ad02VB    
    
    
    Know anyone for this job? Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/5  #job    
    
    
    ICD-10 inches closer to delay, ICD-11 in the wings | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ABa5Ro     
    
    
    stevenduque#    
    
    
    Does your hospital need a chief mobility officer? - FierceMobileHealthcare http://bit.ly/zwSOk0     
    
    
    Stage 2 Meaningful Use Rule Slated for Feb. 22 - HDM Latest News Article http://bit.ly/AjTc7m     
    
    
    Hiring a Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/3  #job    
    
    
    One-third of medical practices haven't done security risk assessments - FierceHealthIT http://bit.ly/dv6LJ8    
    
    
    Hospital Privacy, Security Officers Make Their Wish Lists http://bit.ly/htVMUf    
    
    
    Obama Signs Red Flags Bill http://bit.ly/gBATWq    
    
    
    Stolen laptop contained medical data on thousands of patients http://bit.ly/g4ji9F    
    
    
    Community Health to push Tenet board nominees to advance hostile takeover http://bit.ly/heV7XV    
    
    
    Blumenthal to set aggressive pace for health data exchange http://bit.ly/hFSrR3    
    
    
    Looking for a Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/  #job    
    
    
    Stage 2 MU released at last | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/AsQiIL     
    
    
    @Affiliatetrib Thanks for the connection.    
    
    
    EHR Meaningful Use Stage 2 Criteria Signals Achievable Maturing of Care Coordination - HDM Latest News Article http://bit.ly/yzeifD     
    
    
    Mozilla Firefox Start Page: http://bit.ly/8DkJR via @addthis    
    
    
    CPOE Systems Fail Leapfrog Test | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/9KZkFj    
    
    
    AP IMPACT: Millions of vaccine doses to be burned - Health - msnbc.com http://bit.ly/9teFeU    
    
    
    Know anyone for this job? Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/5  #job    
    
    
    Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/1  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    #HITsm - Healthcare Social Media Transcript and Analytics http://www.symplur.com/healthcare-hashtags/hitsm/ … via @symplur    
    
    
    Are you a good fit for this job? Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/6  #job    
    
    
    12 integration capabilities EHRs will need to have | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/zbhA5a     
    
    
    @jds_again Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter! Sue Copp http://www.huntzingergroup.com     
    
    
    @jnhuff Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter! Sue Copp http://www.huntzingergroup.com     
    
    
    @NorthernSaving Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter! Sue Copp http://www.huntzingergroup.com     
    
    
    @vanhoick Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter! Sue Copp http://www.huntzingergroup.com     
    
    
    @Mrmarketer_com Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter! Sue Copp http://www.huntzingergroup.com     
    
    
    @kathystover Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter! http://www.huntzingergroup.com  Sue Copp    
    
    
    @NickKellet Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter! http://www.huntzingergroup.com  Sue Copp    
    
    
    @SocialBro Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter! Sue Copp http://www.huntzingergroup.com     
    
    
    Know anyone for this job? Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/5  #job    
    
    
    EHR Incentives Registration Begins January 3 http://bit.ly/eIiwnn    
    
    
    Physicians, Nurses Continue Primary Care Debate http://bit.ly/dW1Veh    
    
    
    Seniors Account for 1 in 3 Hospital Stays http://bit.ly/dVtAq6    
    
    
    CMS Delays Enforcement of Signature Requirement on Lab Orders http://bit.ly/e9XTUs    
    
    
    Drug Firm to Pay Feds $280 Million to Settle Pricing Claims http://bit.ly/fuF4jZ    
    
    
    Saint Joseph Mercy Health System announces merger with IHA http://bit.ly/h0FSQf    
    
    
    Recommended reading for healthcare executives http://bit.ly/eS8Ns2    
    
    
    Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/1  #job    
    
    
    Facebook Marketing: 7 Ways to Use Facebook to Grow Your Business http://bit.ly/Ap3Tdg     
    
    
    Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/1  #job    
    
    
    Know anyone for this job? Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/5  #job    
    
    
    Meaningful Use Criteria Announcement Imminent http://shar.es/mR9Ad    
    
    
    Physician-Patient E-mail Improves Quality, Study Finds http://bit.ly/cRCioE    
    
    
    The "Meaningful Use" Regulation for Electronic Health Records | Health Care Reform Center http://bit.ly/czaCPl    
    
    
    Hiring a Revenue Cycle Project Manager in Wilkes-Barre, PA http://bull.hn/l/F6WU/3  #job    
    
    
    @misth2o Thanks for the following.    
    
    
    I just beat zyngawf_32672925 by 24 points! Think you can beat me? #GamesWithFriends http://wwf-fb.zyngawithfriends.com/mobilestartgame.php?user=18685423 …    
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagr.am/p/Jv0p3lFA8I/     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/Jv0p3lFA8I/     
    
    
    Meaningful use still a challenge despite strides, say hospitals http://bit.ly/IefxFL     
    
    
    Research shows high IT use among Top 100 Hospitals http://bit.ly/JxK6ql     
    
    
    Patients choose hospitals based on social media http://bit.ly/Ioswmh     
    
    
    Taken during a storm. http://pinterest.com/pin/147633694005087528/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Social Networking 
RT @pab5482: loves to see our LinkedIn Grads getting results through the Grad Guide NBC New York http://ow.ly/aRhK    
    
    
    Recruiting Santa Rosa Consulting looking for a system administrator with experience in Microsoft server environments with Meditech    
    
    
    Recruiting a Network Administrator.  Microsoft server operating systems.  Cisco, Healthcare, especially Meditech environment preferred.    
    
    
    Looking for a Siemens Soarian Financials Revenue Cycle project manager consultant.    
    
    
    @mesmer2011 Thank You for adding me to the list of people you follow on Twitter!    
    
    
    ONC Issues Final Rule for HIT Permanent Certification Program http://bit.ly/guHzqP    
    
    
    Top 10 Healthcare Quality Issues for 2011 http://bit.ly/fxVohR    
    
    
    12 Ways to Reduce Hospital Readmissions http://bit.ly/gwDdJN    
    
    
    4 Ways to RAC-Proof Hospital Admissions http://bit.ly/hvU3xO    
    
    
    “Massachusetts gets $16.9M in federal funds to launch statewide HIE” http://bit.ly/PsO5BH     
    
    
    “Clinical decision support tools top hospital IT leaders' wish lists” http://bit.ly/OGeUEd     
    
    
    “Making 'meaningful' strides” http://bit.ly/NRGhPq     
    
    
    “Employment opportunities continued to trend up in the medical industry,” http://bit.ly/OwTol1     
    
    
    Coming soon: Health innovation that matters | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/PsSzs8     
    
    
    For-profit hospital operator HCA reports U.S. probe
http://skygrid.me/QxRe8o     
    
    
        
    
    
    HHS: Affordable Care Act Will Protect Transgender People
http://skygrid.me/MfQXX1     
    
    
    Surveillance may help doctors decide to prescribe
http://skygrid.me/RejLiO     
    
    
    Largest U.S. Hospital Chain Probed for Medically Unnecessary Heart Procedures
http://skygrid.me/OKyoKq     
    
    
    Five students closer to launching their healthcare apps on App Store
http://skygrid.me/OKAnyx     
    
    
    HIMSS and Healthcare IT News Announce Privacy & Security Forum
http://skygrid.me/NlA5ud     
    
    
    Succession planning lacking in healthcare
http://skygrid.me/TcUO7x     
    
    
    Provider-payer ACO cuts readmissions by 26% - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/MjIfXI     
    
    
    “Stage 3 list for meaningful use coming soon” http://bit.ly/Mx2tsm     
    
    
        
    
    
    HHS rules governing electronic fund transfer could save hospitals $9B - FierceHealthIT: http://www.fiercehealthit.com/story/hhs-rules-governing-electronic-fund-transfer-could-save-hospitals-9b/2012-08-08?utm_campaign=twitter-Share-Web#.UCLAcb7MHP0.twitter …    
    
    
    CDC: Kids most vulnerable to new swine flu strain from pigs
http://skygrid.me/RE85aX     
    
    
    Latest unemployment application numbers indicate stable job market
http://skygrid.me/RE8VVc     
    
    
    Grapefruit juice may cut chemotherapy costs
http://skygrid.me/RE9kXH     
    
    
    Hospital blames EHR for doubled ED wait times - FierceEMR http://bit.ly/PabayK     
    
    
    Repeal effort defines GOP House debut - Politics - msnbc.com http://on.msnbc.com/fRuYAQ    
    
    
    RECs to receive additional $12.2M http://bit.ly/hwTyt4    
    
    
    Healthcare repeal would tack $230B onto national debt http://bit.ly/flgH6y    
    
    
    Healthcare Created Quarter of a Million Jobs in 2010 http://bit.ly/geBnKG    
    
    
    11 Hot Healthcare Buzzwords for 2011 http://bit.ly/fYfGh9    
    
    
    4 Leadership Priorities for the New Year http://bit.ly/eQcJV7    
    
    
    Meaningful use includes interoperability http://bit.ly/fWp1ut    
    
    
    For ACO Adoption Success, Leave Cost Out of It http://bit.ly/MXKXDM     
    
    
    Striving for Meaningful Use Stage 2 http://bit.ly/TCRWkL     
    
    
    Data analytics poised for big growth | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/PbbMQE     
    
    
    Coming Next: Doctors Prescribing Apps to Patients http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/20/technology/coming-next-doctors-prescribing-apps-to-patients.html …    
    
    
    Patients worried about medical records going digital http://www.ama-assn.org/amednews/2012/08/20/bisb0820.htm …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Millions of Americans Have Uncontrolled High Blood Pressure: CDC
http://skygrid.me/UrMVMc     
    
    
    Forget Marcus Welby: Today’s docs want a real life http://shar.es/7LFsM  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Not-for-Profit Hospitals Show Stability in a Challenging Market http://bit.ly/Tr2UdR     
    
    
    Practices concerned over ICD-10 switchover, survey says - Healthcare IT News http://www.healthcareitnews.com     
    
    
    Connect with me and view my professional profile on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/J5Xk22  #in    
    
    
    http://www.nomorerack.com/?cr=8280385 
Check out theses great deals.    
    
    
    CDS Reduces Rate of Imaging Test Orders by 25% in Study http://bit.ly/i1l8kk    
    
    
    How to Appeal Denied Claims http://bit.ly/dQzuLO    
    
    
    Insurers, healthcare providers at odds on rules for ACOs http://bit.ly/fOs1Kf    
    
    
    Health information exchanges on the rise http://bit.ly/fJENNU    
    
    
    Detroit pushes healthcare growth with Medical Main Street http://bit.ly/fYnQ26    
    
    
    Interoperability gives UPMC a leg up on meaningful use | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/eJmF8F    
    
    
    Study: Family caregivers want Web-based, mobile tech http://bit.ly/fDlvz4    
    
    
    Better use of technology to capture and share health data is necessary. http://bit.ly/RF44mX     
    
    
    Truman Medical Center achieves Stage 7 | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/QbMhSQ     
    
    
    Omega Healthcare Kicks Out Fat Yield As It Tears Up The Charts - Forbes http://onforb.es/RIXfeE  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Photos: Fast Tech 25 @forbes http://onforb.es/MnV9i5  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Survey analysis: The candidates on health IT | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/PsRnKg     
    
    
    AHA, KKR collaborate to study workplace wellness programs
http://skygrid.me/S3Hq2n     
    
    
    Talking to some old friends I went to school with.    
    
    
    Tenet predicts rosier outlook for 2011 - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/gbL7gu    
    
    
    GE and KeyHIE expand health info exchange collaboration | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/dOIknW    
    
    
    Survey: Docs struggling financially, but new tech makes job easier http://bit.ly/fkQW9p    
    
    
    PwC named Common Security Framework Assessor http://bit.ly/er4sra    
    
    
    Cleveland Clinic creates center for personalized healthcare | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ii5ARV    
    
    
    EHR Spending To Hit $3.8 Billion In 2015 http://bit.ly/fVXjge    
    
    
    VA Racing To Fill 705 IT Positions -- IT Staffing -- InformationWeek http://bit.ly/hXxtLD    
    
    
    Volume of HIT changes expected to shape 2011 - FierceHealthIT http://bit.ly/fON3SO    
    
    
    Healthcare truce likely to be short http://bit.ly/hJvQHU    
    
    
    Ohio AG Mike DeWine seeks to make Ohio 21st state to sue over health care law http://bit.ly/h3tZFu    
    
    
    What really drives EMR adoption | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/eByOV8    
    
    
    Lets Talk Cover Letters | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/fyCGj4    
    
    
    New York awards $109M to boost healthcare IT | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/de32yV    
    
    
    Google Health relaunches, targets wellness audience | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/cHrxWx    
    
    
    Breastcancer.org launches its first-ever mobile app | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/bOSpzd    
    
    
    Report: IT decision makers bullish on jobs for first time this year | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/bGFm1g    
    
    
    CCHIT launches ONC-ATCB certification program | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/b6Rj5L    
    
    
    Obama Administration's Balancing Act: Health Insurance Benefits Vs. Costs http://bit.ly/fbtNih    
    
    
    Hospital vote gets a do-over http://bit.ly/dWMKve    
    
    
    Memorial, St. Vincent's settle tiff on Jacksonville hospital http://bit.ly/g6sUlK    
    
    
    Doctors Communicate Poorly Among Themselves, Study Finds http://bit.ly/fter1O    
    
    
    Latest digital divide solution is tardy, lacks punch http://bit.ly/dJE1Zn    
    
    
    Supreme Court: Residents' earnings should be taxed http://bit.ly/fHV987    
    
    
    Gov. Brown proposes deep healthcare cuts for California http://bit.ly/fbLwnz    
    
    
    More than 3,000 California docs sign up for EHR help http://bit.ly/ekPk29    
    
    
    Road to meaningful use bumpy for some http://bit.ly/hTFY6u    
    
    
    Key PPACA provisions start today, WebMD and Sebelius answer questions | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/aKrsIG    
    
    
    New York awards $109M to boost healthcare IT | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/de32yV    
    
    
    Healthcare Reform Provisions Begin http://bit.ly/9dvDQc    
    
    
    House Republicans Say Meaningful Use Bar Set Low http://www.healthcare-informatics.com/news-item/house-republicans-say-meaningful-use-bar-set-low#.UHBiKBPrOKU.twitter …    
    
    
    Are You Likely to Respond to Exercise?  http://nyti.ms/TtPnnG     
    
    
    Mass layoffs follow purchase of beleaguered Alvarado Hospital http://bit.ly/eN0Ptw    
    
    
    EMRs can improve infection control - FierceEMR http://bit.ly/gIbhQg    
    
    
    Walgreens plans to evolve health, wellness efforts http://bit.ly/ezGK6I    
    
    
    3 big trends for the EHR cloud | Healthcare IT News http://www.healthcareitnews.com/news/3-big-trends-ehr-cloud … via @your_screen_name    
    
    
    Patients want texts and emails, in sickness and in health. http://www.healthcareitnews.com/news/patients-want-texts-and-emails-sickness-and-health … via @your_screen_name    
    
    
    Eighty-one percent of hospitals, 41 percent of docs plan on meeting MU http://bit.ly/gfw3bU    
    
    
    Top 10 trends for 2011 include IT, new care models | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/enifwS    
    
    
    New venture provides critical technology to community health centers http://bit.ly/gLA9fn    
    
    
    UMC Tucson Fires 3 for Privacy Breaches http://bit.ly/    
    
    
    ONC: 4 in 5 Hospitals Will Claim EHR Incentives http://bit.ly/e1EDWR    
    
    
    Preview: HLM Intelligence Report on E-Health Systems http://bit.ly/fSdD1z    
    
    
    Meaningful use spec sheets help to sum up standards http://bit.ly/i9fIhS    
    
    
    To reduce ER overcrowding, think outside the box http://bit.ly/icInux    
    
    
    Big Business: Healthcare's a Gold Mine http://bit.ly/hXbCki    
    
    
    House GOP to resume healthcare repeal effort, but with more civil tone http://bit.ly/ezu4QF    
    
    
    Wall Street traders make more than brain surgeons http://bit.ly/fQxU8G    
    
    
    Doctor shortage forcing some Central New York hospitals to divert patients http://bit.ly/dYLKOP    
    
    
    St. John Providence Health System (MI) to spend $30 million on improvements http://bit.ly/fbayY5    
    
    
    Reading The Last Dance (1) #ebook on Wattpad mobile http://tinyurl.com/2w5e2bu    
    
    
    Opposition to healthcare law eases http://bit.ly/gPJVYv    
    
    
    Columbia St. Mary’s CEO to take position with parent Ascension Health http://bit.ly/eYoMuw    
    
    
    Patient Experience Scores Skew by Region, Providers Say http://bit.ly/hZ33tz    
    
    
    CIOs Sit at the Nexus of Tectonic Shifts | healthsystemcio.com http://bit.ly/eqNLKD    
    
    
    Mapping workflow before EMR selection | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/fX2Fko    
    
    
    Medical Technology Innovation Gaining Ground in China, India http://bit.ly/ekU7rk    
    
    
    HHS: Repeal of Reform Threatens Those with Pre-Existing Conditions http://bit.ly/h4pMvT    
    
    
    MSBCBS Changes Its Name http://bit.ly/eOLuxq    
    
    
    Northeast hospital ponders sale, merger http://bit.ly/fYwv3B    
    
    
    House ACA Repeal Vote Gets Muted Response from Healthcare Lobbyists http://bit.ly/ewGbpw    
    
    
    S&P: US Healthcare Costs Up 6%, But Growth Slowing http://bit.ly/e91Fx2    
    
    
    Healthcare CIOs cite staffing opportunities -- shake, rattle and roll http://exm.nr/bwgZBr    
    
    
        
    
    
    Stop Losing Experienced Nurses http://bit.ly/ccNeXz    
    
    
    EHRs for the bottom line | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/9FCvBy    
    
    
    What’s driving the trend of early-adopting hospital-owned practices | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/bg3dnZ    
    
    
    HIPAA, HITECH Final Rules Expected by Early 2011 http://bit.ly/bB5vrG    
    
    
    http://www.mlive.com/news/grand-rapids/index.ssf/2010/10/u-m_health_system_teaming_up_w.html#modk_smoref_twitt    
    
    
    @Coppie08    
    
    
    Hospitals plan to invest in new information management systems 
Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/brD2jz    
    
    
    Report: Social networking can improve care, lower costs | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/bl5mJA    
    
    
    ONC asks for feedback on PHR privacy, security | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/cOb0mC    
    
    
    Power, budget, availability top concerns for hospital IT infrastructure | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/co9oJP    
    
    
    Reid: Health reform may get 'tweaked' - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/9fepSH    
    
    
    PHR portal could improve chronic disease management | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/a1fq1X    
    
    
    Georgia puts spotlight on health IT jobs | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/96IuVu    
    
    
    Chaka Khan  - I'm Every Woman: http://youtu.be/Q8xuUdI1an0  via @youtube    
    
    
    http://www.yellownow.com/search?query=hair+salon&partner=mm&subid=clicksorpopuvs …    
    
    
    Journal files suit to open Medicare database http://bit.ly/hKOlCl    
    
    
    Minnesota health CEOs look at Medicaid cuts http://bit.ly/hotCKw    
    
    
    Healthcare Lobby Reacts to Obama SOTU http://bit.ly/gSsJWM    
    
    
    AHA: Make Wellness Part of Healthcare Workforce Culture http://bit.ly/eIe6zY    
    
    
    AMA: Patients Lack Education on Physician Credentials http://bit.ly/fJSNcx    
    
    
    Americans oppose yanking healthcare law funds: poll | Reuters http://reut.rs/eJmV02    
    
    
    Orlando’s VA Medical Center taking shape http://bit.ly/dKEz8g    
    
    
    Hospitals put their money on healthcare innovation | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/dSJNyc    
    
    
    Meaningful Use Compliance Could Be Harder Than You Realize http://bit.ly/hRKGkz    
    
    
    GOP-sponsored bill threatens MU funding | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ee3hgZ    
    
    
    Life as a Healthcare CIO: Obtaining Meaningful Use Stimulus Payments http://bit.ly/gsOUkO    
    
    
    Survey: Docs, patients on the same page when it comes to IT priorities http://bit.ly/fH3U6u    
    
    
    $7M awarded to train health IT workers in Ohio | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/eCwD7H    
    
    
    UPMC grant program funds 5 health IT projects | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/gE9Uhc    
    
    
    Pew Survey: Health information third most popular online pursuit | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/ezgF3x    
    
    
    Brooklyn HIE leverages infrastructure to advance value-add services | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/hWYuiP    
    
    
    Graham pushes for state opt-out from healthcare law http://bit.ly/gVPMKu    
    
    
    Mediation can bring justice with no need for a trial http://wapo.st/eAfyN8    
    
    
    Federal Judge in FL Declares Healthcare Law 'Void' http://bit.ly/dFru28    
    
    
    Healthcare Job Postings Surge in January http://bit.ly/gzEnW0    
    
    
    Who's accessing your medical records? | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/hYYIvE    
    
    
    What s Next for Health Reform? http://bit.ly/h9AOWZ    
    
    
    Certifiers Keep Certifying EHRs http://bit.ly/gmuq9n    
    
    
    Senate to vote likely today on health law repeal http://bit.ly/hVAwrC    
    
    
    Disaster-ready and saving money: Medical practice goes to virtualization | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/e9qrwS    
    
    
    MN woman, hospital, fight over husband's medical care http://bit.ly/heeHDX    
    
    
    Nurse Anesthetists’ Scope of Practice Challenged Again in CA http://bit.ly/fM24st    
    
    
    Health Insurer Competition Absent, AMA Says http://bit.ly/i8K6oQ    
    
    
        
    
    
    How Nonprofit Hospitals Must Prepare for IRS Changes http://bit.ly/hBYfUL    
    
    
    Gender Gap Widens in Physicians Starting Salaries http://bit.ly/dVQAXS    
    
    
    Health Law Provision Raises Antitrust Concerns - NYTimes.com http://nyti.ms/dZ8ZGY    
    
    
    GOP seeks to block funding for health law http://bit.ly/eF6h5n    
    
    
    Using EMRs to help eliminate ED interruptions | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/dHwDzE    
    
    
    Warming Injections Lowers Pain http://bit.ly/eX4Bds    
    
    
    Hospitals take online reservations for ER appointments | LinkedIn http://linkd.in/grqAkH    
    
    
    Disease Prevention Gets $750M in Fed Funds http://bit.ly/fxR4rm    
    
    
    Motorcycle Helmets Reduce Spine Injuries http://bit.ly/eX4rwv    
    
    
    VA awards innovation | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/fyMjuF    
    
    
    HCA Announces Management Shakeup, Subsidiary http://bit.ly/fAozCY    
    
    
    HHS Sends EHR Disclosure Rule for Review http://bit.ly/hGZfMk    
    
    
    Are Americans warming up to the use of EHRs? | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/giMDVQ    
    
    
    Will the next ONC leader be a healthcare CIO? | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/h1cAYh    
    
    
    Healthcare Leaders Reveal Uncertainties About Industry Direction http://bit.ly/dTduBX    
    
    
    Federal Budget Pleases Doctors, Not Hospitals http://bit.ly/f4whXf    
    
    
    Does E-Health Stand a Remote Chance? http://bit.ly/f0TTdl    
    
    
    RAC Tip: How to Determine Inpatient Admission Date, Time http://bit.ly/gZR7NS    
    
    
    Security Challenges of EHR Adoption http://bit.ly/fyjIwI    
    
    
    Changing ICU to improve life afterward http://bit.ly/dI6RzC    
    
    
    Obama’s healthcare budget: ER visit but no cure http://bit.ly/dVpwnQ    
    
    
    Hospitals shift smoking bans to smoker ban http://bit.ly/e7JD0f    
    
    
    Five Minute Consult http://bit.ly/fyQfJm    
    
    
    Online healthcare job listings rose sharply in January | Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/fbpcOA    
    
    
    Physicians praise new medical liability bill | Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/hGVRoA    
    
    
    Cloud computing myths vs. risks | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/gkZLOs    
    
    
    Sebelius, Blumenthal: Health IT will power the U.S. economy | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/hjilf6    
    
    
    Health Coaching Plays Role in the ACO http://bit.ly/gOMXKo    
    
    
    Five Job Search Rules You Should Break | Glassdoor.com Blog http://bit.ly/fbb6i2    
    
    
    Medicare’s Three-Day Payment Window, Demystified http://bit.ly/fHHctq    
    
    
    HHS Offers States $200M to Fight Unreasonable Premium Hikes http://bit.ly/enJDRJ    
    
    
    HIMSS hospitals survey: 44 percent ready for Meaningful Use Stage 1 - FierceEMR http://bit.ly/dFeNKd    
    
    
    GE Healthcare moves Centricity to iPad | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/fxpGl7    
    
    
    Hospital Impact - A physician's role in ACOs http://bit.ly/hq9C3u    
    
    
    Utah House OKs hospital immigrant bill http://bit.ly/fXnsgM    
    
    
    MU big business for healthcare consultants http://bit.ly/e3jcAC    
    
    
    Huntzinger Management Group - Healthcare Services http://bit.ly/eRrWgG    
    
    
        
    
    
    5 Ways Green Surgical Teams Save Hospitals Money http://bit.ly/ferEYo    
    
    
    HealthGrades ranks top 50 hospitals for 2011 | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/gh2SNq    
    
    
    Blumenthal: Health IT's transformation is a big social project | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/hrnd4s    
    
    
    Patient Check-In Technologies Cut Cost, Wait Times http://bit.ly/epowsL    
    
    
    Add Healthcare Policy to Medical School Curriculum, Doctors Say http://bit.ly/fXdE65    
    
    
    Sanford Health Inks Deal With Minnesota’s NCHS http://bit.ly/hMxyfs    
    
    
    Alzheimer’s misdiagnosis common http://bit.ly/fiwaKQ    
    
    
    Feds impose first civil fine ever in HIPAA case http://bit.ly/fkMj9W    
    
    
    Ventas to Acquire Nationwide Health Properties in $7.4B Deal http://bit.ly/i0qwhg    
    
    
    Primary Care With a Twist: Docs Go Uninsured http://bit.ly/g4wAwS    
    
    
    Top 12 Most-Read HealthLeaders Stories February 2011 http://bit.ly/dKlYq5    
    
    
    World Economic Forum drives health data initiative http://bit.ly/f2LzGq    
    
    
    Health improving in doctor-patient relationships - Health - Health care - msnbc.com http://on.msnbc.com/h5aWn6    
    
    
    Hospital Groups Urge Obama to Resist Medicaid MOE Cuts http://bit.ly/ifiZro    
    
    
    Debate heats up about hospitals' charity http://bit.ly/hpZ6y8    
    
    
    WV hospitals merge http://bit.ly/fbL87X    
    
    
    CLABSI Reductions Saved $1.8B in Healthcare Costs, Says CDC http://bit.ly/dZ423z    
    
    
    Healthcare Quality Shows Slow Improvement http://bit.ly/ff3CyS    
    
    
    Chicago-area hospital mulls merger http://bit.ly/gw5LaK    
    
    
    Don't Fear the Future of Healthcare - It's Working http://bit.ly/grebjG    
    
    
    Feds: 92% of Nursing Homes Staffed By Criminals http://bit.ly/gTd4OJ    
    
    
    St. Joseph's Community Health Services, Gundersen Lutheran Announce WI Partnership http://bit.ly/eloirc    
    
    
    Senators want access to Medicare claims database http://bit.ly/hqV33r    
    
    
    Wellness Programs Show Hard-dollar Savings http://bit.ly/f6BGRg    
    
    
    Insurance companies' leap into HIE field will change health IT http://bit.ly/h5y9AB    
    
    
    Plastic surgery bouncing back with the economy http://bit.ly/eFaCeO    
    
    
    Studies shows misuse of drugs crowds ERs http://bit.ly/i8WOY8    
    
    
    Review: 141 patients got unnecessary heart stents http://bit.ly/fyl8xo    
    
    
    From 'Cookbook' to Evidence-Based Medicine http://bit.ly/dYurZB    
    
    
    Atlanta's Grady Hospital to shut 2 clinics http://bit.ly/hjWfsz    
    
    
    EMR Market Grew 13.6% in 2010 http://bit.ly/iclEFG    
    
    
    iPad 2 looks even better for docs http://bit.ly/gApXaa    
    
    
    Senators' bipartisan push would publicize MDs' Medicare claims data http://bit.ly/eek6VJ    
    
    
    Cleveland's MetroHealth pressed to run jail medical services http://bit.ly/ect6hW    
    
    
    How Mobile Apps Improve Quality of Care http://bit.ly/eTOkG9    
    
    
    How to Terminate Contracts to Boost Revenue http://bit.ly/g6DMsh    
    
    
    EMR Market Grew 13.6% in 2010 http://bit.ly/fzhaKK    
    
    
    Healthcare Reform: Why We Can't Turn Back http://bit.ly/e6AJNs    
    
    
    Harvard Pilgrim, Tufts Health Plan End Merger Talks http://bit.ly/eTqs27    
    
    
    CCHIT poll shows Stage 2 and 3 qualms http://bit.ly/hn0I4e    
    
    
    Texas doctor begins housecalls for diabetic patients http://bit.ly/icEgK5    
    
    
    OIG Audit Raises Concerns About Medicare Part D Plans http://bit.ly/gVROtG    
    
    
    Hospital stays cost more in Northern California than Southern California http://bit.ly/ftwI0v    
    
    
    TN Legislature rejects health law mandate http://bit.ly/frbyN3    
    
    
    Red Flag Appeals Court Ruling Victory for Physicians, AMA Says http://bit.ly/h5G4gY    
    
    
    HIPAA Security Officer Aces OCR Investigations http://bit.ly/fOIEm7    
    
    
        
    
    
    McKesson To Acquire British Software Vendor System C | HIStalk http://bit.ly/i7raW6    
    
    
    Georgia health plan in $250M hole http://bit.ly/h7TakW    
    
    
        
    
    
    ME’s individual insurers get reprieve http://bit.ly/f6gcKi    
    
    
    Will healthcare law raise state’s Medicaid costs? http://bit.ly/ehAnrh    
    
    
    Following health law, patients request OTC prescriptions http://bit.ly/eP4adN    
    
    
    Physician groups release 13 new guidelines for PCMH accreditation programs | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/fiZ9Mj    
    
    
    Blumenthal: Stage 2 meaningful use on track | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/f98YKz    
    
    
    Docs stress importance of reporting EHR problems | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/bkk5qs    
    
    
    'Terrific head start' to meaningful use | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/9EYq8S    
    
    
    10 Healthcare Reform Market Changes Affecting Physicians http://bit.ly/fV4hXw    
    
    
    OCR Rolls Out HIPAA Training Plan for AGs http://bit.ly/g9reIa    
    
    
    Medical Error Rates Vary Widely, HealthGrades Finds http://bit.ly/fwNthd    
    
    
    AHA Details Hospital Pricing Variations http://bit.ly/hvd8O9    
    
    
    12 million in U.S. are cancer survivors, CDC says - Health - Cancer - msnbc.com http://on.msnbc.com/g2BVNl    
    
    
    LA gets new smoking rules - Health - Health care - More health news - msnbc.com http://on.msnbc.com/i2pXVX    
    
    
    The TIGER Initiative: Hear nurses roar | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/e9WTXO    
    
    
    Emory Healthcare, Saint Joseph’s Hospital Form Partnership http://bit.ly/f785Pf    
    
    
    Feds Offer New Rules for States ACA Waivers http://bit.ly/ftTQOA    
    
    
    CA Investigating Latest Health Net Data Breach http://bit.ly/heBU0p    
    
    
    45% of States Unprepared for Nuclear Disaster, Poll Shows http://bit.ly/hRs3QX    
    
    
    Time to Redefine Normal Blood Pressure, Researchers Say http://bit.ly/g4naqA    
    
    
    MA medical teams sidelined in Japanese disaster aid http://bit.ly/g65hi8    
    
    
    New efforts to simplify end-of-life care http://bit.ly/gIczXA    
    
    
        
    
    
    When politics and HITECH policies collide | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/fVPBVM    
    
    
    55% of Censured Docs Face No Licensing Action by State Medical Boards http://bit.ly/ejHDvD    
    
    
    Security of EHRs add pressure to physicians | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/i1f7I7    
    
    
    U.S. Healthcare Costs Accelerate Slightly http://bit.ly/gSsjaM    
    
    
    CEO Turnover Highest at Nevada Hospitals http://bit.ly/e5iM0g    
    
    
    The need for EHR best practices, lessons learned is validated | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/gPit41    
    
    
    MedPAC Calls for Pay Raise for Doctors, Hospitals http://bit.ly/h9c2hQ    
    
    
    OCR: $5 Million More Needed For HIPAA Enforcement http://bit.ly/ieFtPl    
    
    
    You can't plan enough for EHR implementation | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/9Mh69Z    
    
    
    It’s Good to Be in Healthcare http://bit.ly/dA28VN    
    
    
        
    
    
    EHR online safety system launched http://bit.ly/d5dpOu    
    
    
    Hospital Impact - Putting healthcare reform into action http://bit.ly/fO9ub1    
    
    
    EHRs are part of the patient-centered care model | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/iaViPT    
    
    
    The good, the bad and the ugly EHR implementation | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/hJuaXB    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Cleveland Clinics Marymount Hospital to stop delivering babies http://bit.ly/hR5Prq    
    
    
    HHS to release ACO regs today http://bit.ly/gpTK6E    
    
    
    Medical groups not prepared for HIPAA 5010 compliance | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/hgA987    
    
    
    Republicans' 2012 budget plan alters Medicare, Medicaid | Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/dZ167w    
    
    
    Obama's remarks on fiscal policy - Twitter highlights | Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/ewiFL2    
    
    
    Social media in healthcare surge will drive EHR adoption and demand | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/enaMga    
    
    
    Hospitalist Firms Cogent, HMG to Merge http://bit.ly/gJpzp4    
    
    
    HHS Unveils $1B Program to Reduce Medical Errors http://bit.ly/gaT2uQ    
    
    
        
    
    
    A Time of intense execution | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/ftzn8I    
    
    
    CMS to open meaningful use attestation April 18 | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/f7R7hv    
    
    
    Small hospitals look to big vendors for clinical IT | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/dhPeiA    
    
    
    Hospital system promotes EHR via Twitter, Facebook, YouTube - FierceEMR http://bit.ly/cfWWjI    
    
    
    Understanding rules vital to planning for 'meaningful use' - FierceEMR http://bit.ly/acQW93    
    
    
    Top 100 hospitals named for 2011 | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/egjfxN    
    
    
    What we still must do to achieve widespread adoption of EHRs | EHR Watch http://bit.ly/msjod7    
    
    
    Gap grows in funding retiree healthcare - FierceHealthcare http://bit.ly/lwj1oQ    
    
    
        
    
    
    Patients show positive response to EHRs - FierceEMR http://bit.ly/jeHLrW    
    
    
    More time needed for Stage 2 MU implementation - FierceEMR http://bit.ly/lLXzbV    
    
    
    Proposal for Medicare is unlike federal employee plan http://bit.ly/m4IgW8    
    
    
    DCH survives storm largely unscathed | The Crimson White http://bit.ly/jl1Z0V    
    
    
    Health Plan, Provider Partnerships May Trump ACOs http://bit.ly/kqhl3r    
    
    
    eCW Application Support/Analyst - National Position, -  http://bit.ly/kjKQdn    
    
    
        
    
    
    2012 presidential election promises big HIT players | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/klKkJx    
    
    
    Health IT No. 1 on list of top 10 'hot' careers | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/kwSgOD    
    
    
    First physicians in the nation get MU check | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/jOSgNV    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Health Execs Laud EHRs For Boosting Care -- Electronic Health Records -- InformationWeek http://bit.ly/gYhD8b    
    
    
        
    
    
    Major-league Pitcher Cliff Lee Gives $1 Million to Arkansas Children's Hospital - ArkansasBusiness.com http://bit.ly/fV3Dlc    
    
    
    Top 10 factors for successful EHR implementation | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/fV8NNX    
    
    
    Looking for a several Project Managers with Healthcare experience. Must have Project Managed MEDITECH clinical and...: http://lnkd.in/MX8RGK    
    
    
    Although slower than in previous months, hospitals created 4,100 jobs in May.http://bit.ly/lDl9aV    
    
    
    Recruiting Tips: How to Stay Focused http://bit.ly/kQWRDA  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    @levyrecruits @levyrecruits  At least you got a good laugh on a Friday.  Glad you opened it,    
    
    
    Working on growing Huntzinger Management Group.    
    
    
    Top 5 security threats in healthcare | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/lIlSxp     
    
    
    HHS seeks to simplify electronic transactions for doctors | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/mbUu6R     
    
    
    Top 5 challenges for medical practices | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/jrqhwA     
    
    
    CMS Discloses DRG Coding Vulnerabilities for Inpatient Hospitals http://bit.ly/nDK9Ov     
    
    
    5 Questions to Determine Readmission Rate Effectiveness http://bit.ly/nHpNbx     
    
    
    HHS Issues Final Interim Red Tape Rule http://bit.ly/qTkPJf     
    
    
        
    
    
    Corporate fitness programs survive hard times http://bit.ly/oH33Ix     
    
    
    ONC: We Agree to Stage 2 Meaningful Use Delay http://bit.ly/ogaqzm     
    
    
    Healthcare Finance News http://bit.ly/qSuT2k    
    
    
    How to Recover Health Data After Disaster http://bit.ly/pEiVHL    
    
    
    How Hospitals Address Patient Experience via Mobile Apps http://bit.ly/oVfWT9    
    
    
    AHA Details Hospitals $2.2T Economic Activity http://bit.ly/npVUEX    
    
    
    Three solo doctors offer tips on meaningful use | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/qdJPkW    
    
    
    Joint Commission safety goals should be part of EHR certification | Healthcare IT News http://bit.ly/n17ET4    
    
    
    