My Tweet got quoted >: The Twitterati on the Roxas-Romualdez video, Meralco’s price hike, Justin Bieber in Tacloban http://www.spot.ph/gallery/news_features/2795/-r-ntweets-of-the-week-the-twitterati-on-meralco-rsquo-s-price-hike-justin-bieber-for-tacloban--more-r-n …    
    
    
    It is so quiet in my room except for the sound of this cricket.    
    
    
    I got some great suggestions on twitter on how to stop these "martilyo gang" from stealing at malls. http://fb.me/2K0rquWUH     
    
    
    Don Mariano is one of the many bus companies owned by one Dr. Melissa Lim. She also owns Nova Trasport, Fermina,... http://fb.me/2vVbPsgBX     
    
    
    After so many years, we now have another Miss International 2013,  Bea Rose Santiago @bearose21    
    
    
    But you will always be my favourite of all...RT @aupijuan: .wow! CONGRATULATIONS! > @bearose21    
    
    
    Congrats to your apo! proud grandma. RT @aupijuan: im ecstatic today as my apo won Gold in SEAG -archery team. @bearose21    
    
    
    ah I missed that RT @Simply_Clinton: @aupijuan @bearose21 after Tita Au, there was Precious Lara Quigaman (2005) then now    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @EmpowHER @wisdomsquote @gojackiego    
    
    
    Women's Rights Advocate Paid Her Nanny Three Dollars An Hour http://gawker.com/womens-rights-advocate-paid-her-nanny-three-dollars-an-1483881548 …    
    
    
    Beside the old Bohol Beach Club, Panglao Island, Bohol RT @paulinealcera:  where is Dumaluan?    
    
    
    @paulinealcera Thanks    
    
    
    Pinay Cinderella in Japan urges countrymen to change Japanese perception of Pinoys http://shar.es/OCGOu  via @gmanews    
    
    
    Philippines - Miss International Titleholders 

1964 - Gemma Cruz - California, USA
1970 - Aurora Pijuan - Osaka,... http://fb.me/37B4L7vxP     
    
    
    This Man Blew The Ad Budget For 'The Secret Life Of Walter Mitty' On Disaster Relief http://on.digg.com/IQiazT  via @Digg    
    
    
    Good morning Bohol #visitbohol2014 (@ South Palms Resort Panglao w/ 2 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1dl3T7o     
    
    
    It's a colorful Wednesday morning. Good morning. @ South Palms Resort Panglao http://instagram.com/p/iCnqEmjWjm/     
    
    
    @darthlaurian good morning from sunny Bohol pic.twitter.com/vgMSpcV2St    
    
    
    Looking forward to a tour at Baclayon, Loboc river cruise ,chocolate hills , Albuquerque church ,… http://instagram.com/p/iCzPJbjWgt/     
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @dongpaomagarin    
    
    
    Sunny Bohol . Panglao island had minimal damage #visitbohol2014 @ South Palms Resort Panglao http://instagram.com/p/iC3tLgjWlx/     
    
    
    Why  an SC injunction ? MT @tonylavs: Why the boundary system should be phased out & replaced w a salary system. http://fb.me/11RQz9vZq     
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @DessertComes1st @cuckoo_sing @texjimenez    
    
    
    #juanvote election 2013 watch  is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1338783684 … Stories via @2013Elections    
    
    
    A tarsier at the Philippine Tarsier Sanctuary in Corella  #visitbohol2014 #nofilter @ The Philippine… http://instagram.com/p/iDFCBiDWkC/     
    
    
    Buffet lunch , the Loboc river cruise (@ Loboc River Tourist Complex) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1flt77f     
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Help rebuild Bohol #visitbohol2014 #itsmorefuninthephilippines #lobocrivercruise http://instagram.com/p/iDQt9ODWvT/     
    
    
    Tinikling #visitbohol2014 @ Loboc River Cruise http://instagram.com/p/iDRQlojWvw/     
    
    
    @ReyBelen there is a newly opened viewing deck at the Chocolate Hills Adventure Park #visitbohol2014 . Am here now    
    
    
    @ReyBelen they are back in business    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/mbphNn  Give the gift of light to
those who need them the most. #MaybankProjectHeart pic.twitter.com/sPsTcb4Eq5    
    
    
    Chocolate Hills on ground level #visitbohol2014 @ The Chocolate Hills http://instagram.com/p/iDiLOsjWr5/     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/mbphNn  Be a beacon of hope as you give the gift of light to those who need them the… http://instagram.com/p/iDdpFtDWpN/     
    
    
    Congrats @linocayetano and  Fille http://www.rappler.com/entertainment/showbitz/46165-lino-cayetano-to-wed-ateneo-volleyball-star …    
    
    
    “@juanxi: @philippinebeat pwede mag guest post sa blogwatch about this?” Yes email me. We have consumer watch at Blogwatch.tv    
    
    
    These fossilized shells  found inside one of the Chocolate Hills #visitbohol2014 @ Chocolate Hills,… http://instagram.com/p/iDrnZxjWgz/     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/mbphNn  Be a beacon of hope as you give the gift of light to those who need them most.… http://instagram.com/p/iDdpFtDWpN/     
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @SecondFirsts    
    
    
    The Importance of Blogger Reputation - Pinoy Life At Large | Pinoy Life At Large http://arpeelazaro.com/2013/12/importance-blogger-reputation/ …    
    
    
    Bully Mar finds online defender http://wp.me/p2IXEb-A0  via Spin Busters    
    
    
    This Christmas, you too can help bring light to communities that still have no electricity through Project... http://fb.me/RvcJjOUR     
    
    
    Shame on you Mayor Junjun Binay > 3 Dasma guards who stopped Binay convoy held, freed  http://shar.es/OJzAW     
    
    
    wang wang mentality RT @mavisGal: and he had to drop the line: Don't you know me? tsk tsk tsk tsk...    
    
    
    Just revolting. Even if Dasma secu had lapses in their procedure, why was show of gun power necessary, Mayor Binay? http://m.inquirer.net/newsinfo/?id=548765 …    
    
    
    Binay's peg: what are we in power for ? RT @peacheshonestly: disappointing. Very disappointing.    
    
    
    Too much show of power “@buwayahman:  (devil’s advocate) ...even misconstrued as an assassination attempt. Still, I detest their attitude”    
    
    
    @rochellesychua saying assuming Lapse in security. Still not a reason to flaunt arrogance of power    
    
    
    This is a 2016 preview “@LaTtEX: @rochellesychua  Looks like wang wang culture will be back in full swing when Binays rise to power in 2016    
    
    
    “@bacchus2482:  nahuli ako sa balita, are we talking of the petit black man, with VP seal?  @buwayahman” the son but daughter just looked    
    
    
    @bacchus2482 @buwayahman Sobrang OA the show of arms even if guards at fault    
    
    
    Good morning from balmy  Bohol .  So relaxing at the beach. #visitbohol2014 http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1372980 …    
    
    
    @SenatorBinay @salgado_joey this news item on Mayor Jun Binay does not look good. What can you say? http://newsinfo.inquirer.net/548765/3-dasma-guards-who-stopped-binay-convoy-held-freed …    
    
    
    Enjoying the cool breeze by the  beach #visitbohol2014 http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1372994 …    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @javalavamanila @mbr_grbr    
    
    
    Video of Mayor Binay's  arrogance vs 3 Dasma guards http://newsinfo.inquirer.net/548765/3-dasma-guards-who-stopped-binay-convoy-held-freed …    
    
    
    agree RT @Komiks13: SM should hire the guards RT “@momblogger: Video of Mayor Binay's  arrogance vs 3 Dasma guards http://newsinfo.inquirer.net/548765/3-dasma-guards-who-stopped-binay-convoy-held-freed …    
    
    
    Nakakagalit “@simplyzaida:  Ang YABANG!!! >:(”    
    
    
    Hard to be a cat this Christmas featuring my favorite celebrity cat @iamnalacat & Grumpy cat http://instagram.com/p/iFjPLKjWgx/     
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @mrsunlawyer @wecomeinstyle @aupijuan    
    
    
    “@loko__loko:  @Komiks13 @nonopogi not only 3 guards. They also held the guards on motorcycle on the left.” How many went to the station ?    
    
    
    down with Binay-like pols “@Dazlsilverio: "If Binay becomes Pres, are we all gonna be tiptoeing in fear of this whole clan?" - @Jimparedes”    
    
    
    I am curious to know if Mayor Junjun Binay has one good explanation for this display of power . Was he in fear for his life ?    
    
    
    @loko__loko @Komiks13 @nonopogi @dzbb  the three guards were taken to the Makati City Police.. where they were detained for at least 4 hrs    
    
    
    #juanvote election 2013 watch  is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1338783684 …    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Statement of Binay's camp on Dasmarinas village security guard  incident https://m.facebook.com/notes/anc-247/statement-of-makati-mayor-binays-camp-on-security-guard-incident/10152144357674122 …    
    
    
    @JamAncheta they do not deny arrogant show of armed power    
    
    
    Just arrived in MNL . Waiting for my ride caught in traffic. Always expect to be caught in the worst of traffic these days so leave early    
    
    
    Entitlement issue. “@ReyBelen:  yeah right! Are we naive kids to toy around with their side of the story? #make-believestory”    
    
    
    @boracayinfo it is not like he was In an emergency situation.    
    
    
    Am safe. I wish I took the cab “@WSCRhadem:  hope ure safe noemi, the traffic today is very heavy..... Irritating almost”    
    
    
    Binay 's statement does not explain unnecessary display  of arrogance.    
    
    
    @frederickrdc I heard Binay wanted copy of CCTV tape. But not before security kept a copy.    
    
    
    Just coincidence eh ? The Senate Committee on Energy has found no proof of collusion in power rate hike | http://www.solarnews.ph/news/business/2013/12/19/senate-no-proof-of-collusion-in-power-rate-hike#.UrKCvydc-OE …    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 38 New Followers, 349 Mentions, 407K Mention Reach, 263 Replies, 176 Retweets. via https://sumall.com/twitter     
    
    
    Two hours on the road after  arriving in Manila. Two hours which I could have used to write an article.    
    
    
    Nancy Binay blasts Inquirer for ‘malicious’ report on brother http://shar.es/OlMjB  via @inquirerdotnet    
    
    
    Pls acknowledge that these guards are doing their jobs>Nancy Binay blasts Inquirer for ‘malicious’ report on brother http://shar.es/OlMZm     
    
    
    I screencapped the 5:32 mark where a Binay aide is loading his gun. What was the threat? pic.twitter.com/ijDyHkvCyh    
    
    
    let me check RT @aupijuan: ."...Armed security guards were already surrounding the convoy" ck video    
    
    
    guards follow to the letter. RT @aupijuan:  I believe that the mayor should have been given the courtesy and allowed to pass.    
    
    
    I cannot stand this show of arrogance. Payong pa! @NealvDimarco @aupijuan    
    
    
    A little drizzle will kill him .? Yuck turn off . @PopiSunga @aupijuan    
    
    
    saw that too. were they ready for a gun battle? MT @puretuts: .. ran to the 2nd vehicle then draw chambered a bullet. pic.twitter.com/qHcZcqiTbn    
    
    
    Binay's arrogance is disgusting > GANITO KAMI SA MAKATI? | Netizens hit Binay's Dasma gate clash http://www.interaksyon.com/article/77121/storify--netizens-hit-binays-dasma-gate-clash …    
    
    
    di ba OA . Ready to shoot who/what? who is the enemy? RT @puretuts: @momblogger same fellow now w long firearm .. pic.twitter.com/tISPpqnx47    
    
    
    just yabang power RT @puretuts: same guy with high power firearm slung approach the guard. ..intimidating the guard. pic.twitter.com/qOQGeRASiS    
    
    
    scare tactics yan RT @puretuts: same guy about to hide the long firearm because a PNP personel was approaching pic.twitter.com/EnZI7IkKfy    
    
    
    does not make sense huh RT @aupijuan: Joey Salgado:"sec. suppose to secure their principal." you mean that guy walking around McKinley,    
    
    
    Missy misses me so is staying beside me #catsofinstagram #catstagram #cats#catlovers #kitties… http://instagram.com/p/iGQKChDWkV/     
    
    
    sobra RT @puretuts guy with chalico threatening the two responding guards. after pushing them away from the entrance pic.twitter.com/t4xTAMQqSC    
    
    
    not good. RT @puretuts:  looks like the bodyguard of #binay was pointing a gun at the two responding guards. pic.twitter.com/VhsKtBtVWT    
    
    
    huh? a threat? RT @puretuts: 11:03 PNP drew handcuff pic.twitter.com/RLRNgAgogl    
    
    
    what possible violation? RT @puretuts: 11:49 guards were forced by PNP and bodyguard. It does not look voluntary pic.twitter.com/qb3L9hcjn8    
    
    
    LOL RT @SoWhatsNews: I'm just gonna leave this here... http://twitter.com/SoWhatsNews/status/413602456187461632/photo/1pic.twitter.com/i30MJtspPg     
    
    
    Binay yabang power exposed RT @AskSonnie: no amount of explanation can rationalize a power tripping behaviour #Binay    
    
    
    Singing Christmas carols http://dlvr.it/4XcSTN     
    
    
    Maybe @salgado_joey did not watch this part of the video RT @puretuts:  12:31 PNP hinatak na ang guards. Voluntary? NOT.    
    
    
    In the first two minutes, you see Junjun pointing at the guards RT @missjover:  lumabas ba ng car si BInay? para magpakilala kuno?    
    
    
    I screen capped at 1:09 & 1:14 mark where, Mayor Junjun Binay pointing at security .. pic.twitter.com/lFBSlziCjH    
    
    
    The spokesperson. RT @missjover: who is this @salgado_joey? PR ng mga Binay?    
    
    
    am squinting to see if there was a drizzle RT @Article8Jester: Ang hindi ko maintindihan ay: bakit kailangan ng payong? Sensitive sa hamog?    
    
    
    In other news, "Hammers Stolen Using Store-Bought Jewelries as Weapons in Ace Hardware Heist" http://wp.me/p1RffW-1if  via @SoWhatsNews    
    
    
    Feeling Mary Poppins si Binay aide @bluevill @Article8Jester    
    
    
    Has there been a lifestyle check on the Binay family? Hear so many allegations on their ownership of condos here & there    
    
    
    baka automatic lang for the aide. Protect Mayor from getting darker RT @bluevill: payong. Yup. Di ko maintindihan. @Article8Jester    
    
    
    Someone just needs to file at the Ombudsman. RT @cocoy: I hear so many rumors too. Even from ordinary folk.    
    
    
    Lifestyle check with Binay family pls. RT @PTVph: Aquino: Philippines can succeed vs. corruption because they know what is truly at stake.    
    
    
    ‘Our guards did nothing wrong’— Dasmariñas Village officer http://shar.es/OZfRo  via @inquirerdotnet    
    
    
    they should not be above the law RT @cocoy:  ..so many eons ago, if memory serves me correctly. GMA time. I don't know what happened to it.    
    
    
    Mayor Binay, FYI Under President @noynoyaquino admin, no wang wang mentality. No one is above the law.    
    
    
    Video has over 85,000 views already > 3 Dasma guards who stopped Binay convoy held, freed: http://youtu.be/ojFGo9RN5mY     
    
    
    OH MY! Binay is still trending on twitter. Video is getting viral.  These show how citizens are angry at arrogance. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ojFGo9RN5mY …    
    
    
    The days of epal  and power tripping politicians are numbered. # alamna #epalwatch    
    
    
    So obvious in the video. Power tripping galore > Winnie Monsod: Guards were correct, Binay was wrong http://shar.es/OZ2YD     
    
    
    #yuletide4yolanda If you can spread the word, donate, etc http://twitter.com/PingMedina/status/413620767654674432/photo/1pic.twitter.com/Aca6lG8YCG   via @pingmedina who will spend Christmas in Visayas    
    
    
    not about just about the incident. A public servant should not act that way. @drhenry4 @FerdieTopacio @teddyboylocsin @salgado_joey    
    
    
    duh nothing is instant. change does not happen overnight. Get a grip. @drhenry4 @FerdieTopacio @teddyboylocsin @salgado_joey    
    
    
    Rising from the rubble, post-quake Bohol to offer ‘geoscience tours’ http://shar.es/OZJ3R  via @gmanews #visitbohol2014    
    
    
    House sees Chacha OK in 2014 http://www.thepoc.net/news/breaking-stories/19745-house-sees-chacha-ok-in-2014 …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Voyager launches RaincheckPH – the first rain preparedness app in the Philippines http://www.thepoc.net/features/lintech/news/19746-voyager-launches-raincheckph-the-first-rain-preparedness-app-in-the-philippines …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    The Pinoy Family and Rebuilding the Bigger Family of the Philippine Nation by Fr. Robert Reyes http://www.thepoc.net/component/k2/19750-the-pinoy-family-and-rebuilding-the-bigger-family-of-the-philippine-nation … via @thepocnews    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @mymomfriday    
    
    
    VP Binay on Dasma incident: Mayor Junjun deserved some courtesy http://shar.es/Ox8dC  via @gmanews    
    
    
    Keeping the right mindset and avoiding binge eating over the holidays http://thepoc.net/features/wellness/features/19747-keeping-the-right-mindset-and-avoiding-binge-eating-over-the-holidays …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    feeling King of Makati MT @peacheshonestly: just like everyone else. ..the guards would've declined courteously. "No" is not rude. @gmanews    
    
    
    Christmas kitties #catsofinstagram #catstagram #cats#catlovers #kitties #instacat
#petstagram… http://instagram.com/p/iHy6HFuOrb/     
    
    
    @PingMedina will cook kare-kare & Balabacua served w/ hot rice in the Visayas #yuletide4Yolanda . How to help > pic.twitter.com/GqTzHlH89n    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @Julieanzi @LeorenzJamias    
    
    
    Having a #blogwatch white elephant get-together , bonding time. See you soon.    
    
    
    I love the idea that Ford even thought of our pets. After all, pets are family members too. Look at the pet safety... http://fb.me/RsK2nJlG     
    
    
    Singing or playing Christmas carols is another family tradition that I continue on.  http://aboutmyrecovery.com/singing-christmas-carols …    
    
    
    #Yuletide4Yolanda: Fellow advocate @PingMedina plans to cook kare-kare and Balbacua served with hot rice. A... http://fb.me/2iFq9fu26     
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @mishrendon @EmpowHER @mcmanaloto    
    
    
    Gift-buying for your guy: Finding that one Christmas toy for the big boy http://www.thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19706-gift-buying-for-your-guy-finding-that-one-christmas-toy-for-the-big-boy …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    A white elephant gift exchange is a lighthearted way to have fun with your work colleagues, or at family gatherings    
    
    
    #juanvote election 2013 watch  is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1338783684 … Stories via @pageman    
    
    
    Question is why were they invited to the police station? > Mayor Binay denies ordering arrest of Dasma guards http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/nation/metro-manila/12/19/13/mayor-binay-denies-ordering-arrest-dasma-guards …    
    
    
    Mayor Binay , the rule is to deescalate the incident. You just made it worse by saying there was malice    
    
    
    Blotter that the security did not recognise the Mayor? RT @loko__loko:  baka blotter… w/c is standard i think… para may record.    
    
    
    how terrible RT @bayanmo: Binulabog umano ng isang shooting incident ang departure area ng NAIA-Terminal 3. http://fb.me/1XQNYIayD     
    
    
    JUST IN: Reported shooting incident at NAIA Terminal 3 departure Area - via @iamruelperez | @dziq990    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Good ! > TOP STORY: De Lima forms task force to probe Enrile http://rplr.co/1fqMYlI     
    
    
    @maxell_lander she's not working anymore?    
    
    
    My condolences to the those affected by the death Mayor Talumpa, Salipudin Talumpa and Phil Thomas Lirasan, a one-year-and-a-half-old child.    
    
    
    @rochellesychua see my email please. Hope you can make it.    
    
    
    Missy watching @realgrumpycat in the "Hard to be a cat this Christmas " video  #friskies http://instagram.com/p/iI8ZhhOOqD/     
    
    
    @markcojuangco so cowardly. just horrendous. I hope the killers will be caught soon.    
    
    
    @adrianayalin  was able to catch you earlier  on @tvpatrol.  You are back!    
    
    
    Sometime October, 2 NAIA security execs quit over CCTV deal  . http://shar.es/OkZvJ     
    
    
    The CCTV system should have been bought and installed long ago, but Honrado suspended the bidding http://shar.es/OkZYO     
    
    
    Binay says they brought arms bec they were surrounded. This video shows that the guards never left the guard house http://youtu.be/NZfJF2UNkuk     
    
    
    This news was sometime October 2013 > 2 NAIA security execs quit over CCTV deal   http://shar.es/OkwYY     
    
    
    People expected you to visit NAIA 3 with @MaRoxas > Aquino directs PNP to go after Zambo mayor’s perpetrators - Read: http://bit.ly/1c6ePaT     
    
    
    @bethangsioco Am so appalled because if they can do that to security guards, they can do that to others. So very thumbs down to Binay camp    
    
    
    I abhor bullies! Binay camp claims they brought out their arms because they were surrounded by security guard.... http://fb.me/6ot5BBOWB     
    
    
    FYI @salgado_joey > Statement by Philippine Daily Inquirer Publisher Raul C. Pangalangan http://shar.es/OkA4K  via @inquirerdotnet    
    
    
    so maddening. RT @bethangsioco:  definitely not a non-issue. It showed Binays are willing to break the simplest of rules.    
    
    
    True nature coming out in situations like this RT @ReyBelen: @bethangsioco showing already a glimpse of what "leadership" means to them.    
    
    
    Shut It Down: A Digital-Detox Plan for the Holidays http://ti.me/1fKPOCS  via @techland    
    
    
    How do we keep Christ in Christmas ? #ilove http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1380415 …    
    
    
    A guard did not recognize Governor Davide of Cebu yet he did not make a fuss & just left. http://cebudailynews.ph/news/story/12376/davide-rebuffed-by-guard-leaves …    
    
    
    Heartless, greedy Meralco thrives under privatized, deregulated regime http://www.thepoc.net/features/politi-ko/politiko-features/19749-heartless-greedy-meralco-thrives-under-privatized-deregulated-regime …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    i knew this  Reacting to the spokesperson statement re reason for arms RT @dyonisii: @bethangsioco hala! ngayon niyo lang napansin?    
    
    
    The CCTV video disproves much of the Binays' statement: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KP6lUpkYUjk&feature=youtu.be … via @cocoy    
    
    
    they should inform if that is their plan RT @juanxi: I hear @flyPAL's dubai flights have been leaving luggage for over a month now.    
    
    
    They can compensate the stressed passengers for one or inform them of such delays before they board. @juanxi @flyPAL    
    
    
    report to DTI @DTINCR RT @juanxi: @flyPAL they don't bother. No initiative. Utang na loob pa ng pasahero!    
    
    
    Manila Airport Shooting Leaves Four Dead Including a Provincial Mayor http://ti.me/191jGZV  via @TIMEWorld    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @YoungMomLove @mishaventajado @CD_MFO    
    
    
    trapo mentality . kadiri RT @riryle: and VP Binay said that  junjun just did the right thing?they are sick, and that's scary!!    
    
    
    Filipino Youtube Singers Unite for Typhoon Relief "The Prayer" http://youtu.be/Nrlr0ci4DTs  #yolandaph    
    
    
    yes with @arpeelazaro @rochellesychua RT @BettyRome: ..@ChiliMedley at the 2014 Change planner launch later...    
    
    
    10 things you should NEVER say during presentations http://thenextweb.com/lifehacks/2013/09/12/10-things-you-should-never-say-during-presentations-2/ … via @thenextweb    
    
    
    #2014Budget is NOT “pork-less”; it’s not even “pork-lite”, says Former National Treasurer http://tl.gd/n_1ru5p7s   via  @SocialWatchPH    
    
    
    This is a good idea > Mayor Binay should have been told to go on leave, says Alan Cayetano http://shar.es/OzlcH     
    
    
    The security guards  will receive plaques of appreciation from residents of Dasmariñas Village http://newsinfo.inquirer.net/550173/mayor-binay-should-have-been-told-to-go-on-leave-says-alan-cayetano …    
    
    
    I love this > “This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life 2014!” #changeplanner2014 @ 26th St.… http://instagram.com/p/iKkqLujWkf/     
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @beejing @Raft3r    
    
    
    #changeplanner2014 “This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life" available at Fully Booked ,… http://instagram.com/p/iKpVt6jWp9/     
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @texjimenez @gojackiego @yendreyfus    
    
    
    #juanvote election 2013 watch  is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1338783684 … Stories via @2013Elections    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Happy to see both of you. “@rochellesychua:  @ChiliMedley super duper nice to see you both! ❤️”    
    
    
    Market ! (@ Salcedo Market w/ 14 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1ftMI5i     
    
    
    Still my favorite Saturday market @ Salcedo Market http://instagram.com/p/iLBVzaDWmC/     
    
    
    @JulesMariano @rochellesychua I put my small fashion accessories in it. What do you call it again ?    
    
    
    “@JulesMariano:  @rochellesychua its a hibiscus capiz jewelry box.” Got it.    
    
    
    “@cocoy: Wow, Binay camp still insisting they were disrespected. And armed guards surrounding them. http://www.twitlonger.com/show/n_1ru6n69 ” bwisit !    
    
    
    @cocoy statement of Makati city.  Sheesh. I believe @alanpcayetano was reacting to @VPJojoBinay statement on courtesy extended to mayors    
    
    
    @arpeelazaro started a petition : reprimand of Mayor Junjun Binay for harassing  3 security guards  http://chn.ge/19ixkdu     
    
    
    @cyberdean07 @voltaire @jesterinexile @FrancisAcero I can't understand the need to bring them to the police station. Martial law effect.    
    
    
    Change of semantics  “@cyberdean07: Post-86 version is an "invitation" @voltaire @jesterinexile @FrancisAcero”    
    
    
    I am not forgetting the fact that there are many pols w/ Binay-like mentality out there. Not singling just one politician. #epalwatch    
    
    
    Courtesy exemptions to any government official is under DVA since they are policy makers not the security agency.  http://shar.es/Oij7t     
    
    
    “This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life 2014!" is so much better than Starbucks or any of those... http://fb.me/RpG7fsIC     
    
    
    @rom true but I don't spend at least 2000 pesos to get a planner    
    
    
    @rom I don't drink that much coffee outside of home. I will never reach 21 cups in a 2 months. Maybe in 1 year. Frugal    
    
    
    @rom I use awesome note as a  digital planner and a paper version.    
    
    
    @rochellesychua I find such excuses pathetic . Binay or not, the arrogant actions are disgusting.    
    
    
    lol RT @plsburydoughboy: Props ..for making the 1st Bitstrip that's actually funny http://www.facebook.com/noemidado/posts/10151777418685824:0 …    
    
    
    An overweening sense of entitlement prompted Mayor Binay to behave the way he did
 http://opinion.inquirer.net/67743/feeling-entitled#ixzz2o7KU3wyA …    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @philippinebeat    
    
    
    New blog post -  Looking beyond the ruins, a tour of post-quake Bohol #VisitBohol2014 http://goo.gl/fb/1nrts     
    
    
    Looking beyond the ruins, a tour of post-quake Bohol #VisitBohol2014 http://dlvr.it/4YPLK3     
    
    
    New blog post: " Looking beyond the ruins, a tour of post-quake Bohol "  #VisitBohol2014 http://fb.me/2Bfqx4Cbi     
    
    
    Still a mystery? > Mayor Binay's ‘umbrella at night’ video draws ire on social media http://shar.es/OKZgP     
    
    
    Somebody should have told the VP that courtesy and respect are neither solicited nor demanded. They are earned... http://fb.me/2zaW7Uxcn     
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @jayramablogs @reichmontano    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/mbphNn  Give the gift of light to
those who need them the most. #MaybankProjectHeart pic.twitter.com/sPsTcb4Eq5    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @TotteringMama @pinoymommy @bethangsioco    
    
    
    Christmas kitty , part of the decor #catsofinstagram #catstagram #cats #catlovers http://instagram.com/p/iNIPeNOOn8/     
    
    
    #VisitBohol2014: " Looking beyond the ruins, a tour of post-quake Bohol " You are getting the same experience as... http://fb.me/18WbukYox     
    
    
    #juanvote election 2013 watch  is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1338783684 …    
    
    
    Last minute groceries with others having the same idea.    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Just wondering how an ordinary can spot a fake police officer like the one who shot the mayor in NAIA 3 @pnppio    
    
    
    Photo: Is @SenatorBinay holding a gun here? Too many guns brought out. Wonder why. Source: http://www.filipinobloggersworldwide.com/2013/12/binay-convoy-you-tube-there-lies.html … pic.twitter.com/sXJR4oyNbE    
    
    
    am asking a question.  @carloople @senatorbinay    
    
    
    when I saw the video, looks like a purse @choihilario @SenatorBinay    
    
    
    Photo: President Obama & Queen Elizabeth holding their own umbrella. http://fb.me/2VBrdb4KZ     
    
    
    The worst thing about biases after all is that these can render us blind, deaf, and dumb. http://manilatimes.net/biases/62448/     
    
    
    am more appalled at the show of guns which is obvious in the video. She is silent on it . @cocoy @rochellesychua    
    
    
    I don't deny that. RT @cocoy: Bias http://manilatimes.net/biases/62448/     
    
    
    3 gay students make difference in Zamboanga City standoff http://shar.es/OIstC  via @inquirerdotnet    
    
    
    @TaniaArpa I cringed while reading  it.    
    
    
    @Simply_Clinton I don't think so. I know her. She is opinionated. Sometimes we agree to disagree.    
    
    
    @cocoy @rochellesychua they may just want to be contrary    
    
    
    @Simply_Clinton ah I thought it sounded familiar    
    
    
    I already shared a Chicken Relleno recipe but there are many ways to prepare this all time favorite for Noche... http://fb.me/2IPXBDX6l     
    
    
    As long as you can handle it > President Aquino: It will be boring if we don't have problems... http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/nation/12/22/13/pnoy-it-will-be-boring-if-we-dont-have-problems …  via @ABSCBNNews    
    
    
    On Binays and Dasmariñas Guards: Village Security Implications http://wp.me/p3Jcf0-2  via @aceesmeralda    
    
    
    Palace reminds all public officials: We have a no wang-wang policy http://shar.es/OIEOE  via @gmanews    
    
    
    Not sure how emotionally intelligent you are? Here are 14 signs you have a high EQ.  http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/12/05/are-you-emotionally-intel_n_4371920.html?ncid=edlinkusaolp00000003&ir=Impact …    
    
    
    "The guards volunteered to go with the police. The video bears this out."

Really? I finally found the video of... http://fb.me/2yHOfxwtu     
    
    
    @cocoy I just feel so sorry for them. What if there were others? and just not caught on CCTV    
    
    
    I still do to family RT @manila_bulletin: Fading art: Sending Christmas cards - Read: http://bit.ly/1cIYxl1  pic.twitter.com/4CBBg64EJy    
    
    
    “I believe in justice but I also believe in compassion,” - Erap http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/nation/12/22/13/erap-returns-veterans-visit-arroyo …    
    
    
    Davila weighs in on 'Binaygate,' like it matters http://wp.me/p2IXEb-A8  via Spin Busters    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @EmpowHER    
    
    
    Over a 1 Million hits 6 days after posting >This Man Took Money Meant for Hollywood Blockbuster Ads on #yolandapH http://youtu.be/jU7rhVub0rU     
    
    
    “@godwin_anthony:  what's the latest on #RHLaw” nothing . Still stuck at the Supreme Court @SCPh_PIO    
    
    
    @mongster until now RH Law is stuck in a TRO    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @srhformoso    
    
    
    The issue versus Binay has nothing to do with skin-color.    
    
    
    Street micro entrepreneurs: Bane or boon? http://mail.thepoc.net/features/pera-isipan/features/19761-street-micro-entrepreneurs-bane-or-boon …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    @zenzamora Probably @VPjojobinay fault in a way. In an interview , He mentioned of his goal "the first black president of the Philippines"    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @wecomeinstyle @gojackiego @chuvaness    
    
    
    Where to buy  vietnam dong in Manila?    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics … Stories via @jabjimenez    
    
    
    "@drhenry4:  Mahirap po atang maghanap nyan"  none in BPI foreign exchange main    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AskSonnie Implementing Rules &amp; Regulations of RA 10627, Anti-Bullying Act of 2013 http://www.gov.ph/2013/12/13/implementing-rules-and-regulations-of-republic-act-no-10627/ … pic.twitter.com/OJTCc4dvPs    
    
    
    @drhenry4 not even US dollars.    
    
    
    @JDPasricha @piacayetano @bethangsioco thank you. Cheers    
    
    
    On my recipe blog:  Crepe Covered Embutido http://goo.gl/fb/Hmzh7     
    
    
    If you are feeling adventurous, you can try this well-loved Embutido recipe with  modern twist. I never knew you... http://fb.me/1edhakeLe     
    
    
    time to stop smoking MT @dzIQ990: Headlines: Upon the advise of Sec. Enrique Ona, Pres. Aquino is going on vacation starting Friday, Dec 27    
    
    
    #scrapPork still pork RT @GMANewsOnline: Not a pork barrel, SC says of Judiciary Development Fund  http://gmane.ws/1l8Kuto     
    
    
    Crazy drivers all around. Hard to drive around them. Zen mode    
    
    
    “@cyberdean07:  Achieve stillness in motion.” Listening to music helps    
    
    
    Am almost home sweet home. Last quick stop at neighborhood mall.    
    
    
    “@cyberdean07:  Christmas tunes will help get into the Yuletide spirit. The TRO issued by the SC against Meralco also helps.” How true    
    
    
    Yes I heard . Just weird for him to say that @blueknightPH @HecklerForever    
    
    
    @DennisSiaSy I know what you mean. That is why I am so exasperated.    
    
    
    The perfect planner for me is “This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life 2014!”  http://beautyoverfifty.net/my-favorite-things/the-perfect-planner-for-2014/ …    
    
    
    Humility 101 > Makati mayor urged to take lecture on proper behavior http://shar.es/OODWs  via @inquirerdotnet    
    
    
    “Members of political dynasties act as if they are lords,...as if they are God’s gifts to humanity" http://newsinfo.inquirer.net/551015/makati-mayor-urged-to-take-lecture-on-proper-behaviort …    
    
    
    If you are looking for a 2014 planner, I highly recommend “This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life... http://fb.me/6Dg1UyoYe     
    
    
    @voltaire Gratitude diary is always an excellent idea. We open our hearts and help rewire our brains to work  in more positive ways.    
    
    
    This is just heartbreaking. Losing her only child > Slain kid in NAIA made unusual gesture before dying http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/focus/12/23/13/slain-kid-naia-did-unusual-gesture-dying …    
    
    
    O stressful night! O stressful night! For women, it’s the most stressful time of the year  http://wapo.st/1bV6A0u  via @washingtonpost    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @momblogger @blairbitchbunny    
    
    
    Woman on PrimeTime- The perfect planner for 2014 http://goo.gl/fb/rz9tm     
    
    
    Dasmariñas Village rewards security guards who blocked Binay convoy http://shar.es/OUcD8  via @gmanews    
    
    
    This is the right thing to do > Dasmariñas Village rewards security guards who blocked Binay convoy http://shar.es/OUcUf     
    
    
    But they still want to retain the guards not Antonio. RT @nonstopbabble:  i heard that the security agency's contract has been terminated?    
    
    
    Tonight, we will have a Skype conference celebration from America & Germany. Some of my siblings only know Skype.    
    
    
    Wishing you a Christmas overflowing with Love and Laughter! To the moments of reflection for a moment to stop and... http://fb.me/6rFbqVfKS     
    
    
    Last minute shopping for last minute guests coming over. What joy (@ Shopwise) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1fCtJFG     
    
    
    Lots of Christmas themed candies here @ Shopwise http://instagram.com/p/iSS5bhDWkt/     
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @czarinazarkity    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @MyChaos @ibyang @mishrendon    
    
    
    So easy to drive at EDSA. No traffic. Picking up a friend at the international airport    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    My Vine web profile is coming soon! https://vine.co/momblogger     
    
    
    #ilove the Christmas spirit. http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1396599 …    
    
    
    German delicacies from my daughter in Germany. Thank you Deng for bringing them over http://instagram.com/p/iTK3oADWvF/     
    
    
    Hark the herald the angels sing , as sung by the 1999 Manila children's choir with 2 of my daugh… http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1397089 …    
    
    
    New blog post -  Christmas carols sung by my children along with the choir http://goo.gl/fb/Xg9K0     
    
    
    Christmas carols sung by my children along with the choir http://dlvr.it/4ZCng3     
    
    
    Looks like my fruitcake aged well. http://instagram.com/p/iTXar-DWpa/     
    
    
    “@drhenry4: @momblogger Merry Christmas Ms Noem...” Thanks    
    
    
    @jvejercito @Simply_Clinton @itsbeckxoxo @bethangsioco @PinkOliveDrab @pinoymommy @peacheshonestly @FilipinoScribe @gtongi thanks    
    
    
    2013’s best in beauty and fashion http://www.thepoc.net/features/beauty-and-fashion/features/19770-2013-s-best-in-beauty-and-fashion … via @thepocnews    
    
    
    New on #blogwatch: Pope Francis: Radical for God, Radical for the Poor http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19771-pope-francis-radical-for-god-radical-for-the-poor … by @philippinebeat    
    
    
    3 Christmas Carols (in mp3 format) sung by my 2 girls along with 3 other kids from the 1999 Manila Children Choir. http://aboutmyrecovery.com/christmas-carols-sang-by-children/ …    
    
    
    Pasko na Sinta ko , a Christmas carol sung by my 2 girls & 3 kids from the Manila Children's Cho… http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1398029 …    
    
    
    @PhauraReinz thank you.    
    
    
    May you have the gladness of Christmas
which is hope,The spirit of Christmas
which is peace,The heart of... http://fb.me/24FT32nQP     
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger     
    
    
    Christmas in our hearts. #ilove my family. Have a merry Christmas everyone http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1399271 …    
    
    
    Merry Christmas from our family to yours ! http://instagram.com/p/iUJxukjWit/     
    
    
    My present is the digital canvas print of our family photos taken 3 years ago . Good job Picture City… http://instagram.com/p/iUzMIKDWjN/     
    
    
    Ty for the help here @mrsunlawyer @mrsunlawyer >digital canvas print of our family photos. Good job Picture City http://instagram.com/p/iUzMIKDWjN/     
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @Two_2_Travel    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @pinoymommy @EmpowHER    
    
    
    New blog post -  Home is where the heart is http://goo.gl/fb/iXi8J     
    
    
    Home is where the heart is http://dlvr.it/4ZR4Fv     
    
    
    On my blog: My home is where my family is wherever they may be, even if they are now are scattered all over the world http://aboutmyrecovery.com/home-is-where-the-heart-is/ …    
    
    
    This Christmas, home is where the heart is. #ilove my family. http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1400069 …    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Buying flowers for My Luijoe (@ Market! Market! - @ayalamalls w/ 14 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1cxquRO     
    
    
    Many visiting the cemetery today    
    
    
    Visiting our angel #christmas day @ Loyola Memorial Park http://instagram.com/p/iVr3QcDWnY/     
    
    
    @WSCRhadem @Wenchie318 @metromike0323 @mindanaoan @suigeneris05 @DreyRaikkonen thanks for the greetings    
    
    
    My sister and I on this special day #christmas http://instagram.com/p/iV2fqvDWiX/     
    
    
    Celebrating Christmas Day  with my sister through Skype http://instagram.com/p/iV6j6tDWmT/     
    
    
    On #blogwatch -  Pope Francis: Radical for God, Radical for the Poor http://goo.gl/fb/gbsdo     
    
    
    Pope Francis: Radical for God, Radical for the Poor http://blogwatch.tv/2013/12/pope-francis-radical-for-god-radical-for-the-poor/ … by @philippinebeat    
    
    
    At least he is honest with himself> Failing to meet target in devastated Visayas, Energy chief Petilla to quit post  http://shar.es/OBccJ     
    
    
    Barely anyone at the airport @ Ninoy Aquino International Airport (MNL) Terminal 3 http://instagram.com/p/iWGqmBDWlP/     
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @nonstopbabble    
    
    
    Corrupt politicians & self-serving public servants in the PH, take a good, hard look at what Pope Francis is doing.  http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19771-pope-francis-radical-for-god-radical-for-the-poor …    
    
    
    Radical indeed is Pope Francis. But isn’t it about time we had a Pope who would not hesitate to call the kettle... http://fb.me/34rlKqlda     
    
    
    Cheers! @tonyocruz @marvingermo @philippinebeat @AdeMagnaye @brodfitz @AskSonnie    
    
    
    My day filled with real & virtual family reunions either in Skype or Line  but I loved it best when my daughter called me via Viber.    
    
    
    Pasko at Pelikulang Pinoy: 39th Metro Manila Film Festival http://www.thepoc.net/features/sosyal/news/19772-pasko-at-pelikulang-pinoy-39th-metro-manila-film-festival …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Christmas at the park . (at first I thought it was a tent city) http://www.mb.com.ph/xmas-at-the-park/ …    
    
    
    Favorite Pinoy Christmas destinations during Christmas season http://www.thepoc.net/features/pera-isipan/features/19762-favorite-pinoy-christmas-destinations-during-christmas-season …  by @rachcorner via @thepocnews    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 …    
    
    
    New blog post: Your home is whatever place you long to be.  My home is where my family is at this very moment... http://fb.me/18R1FMVZC     
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @aupijuan @gojackiego @philippinebeat    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 61 New Followers, 394 Mentions, 1.62M Mention Reach, 228 Replies, 158 Retweets. via https://sumall.com/twitter     
    
    
    Haven't been tweeting lately. Anything new in twitter land ?    
    
    
    @BlissfulLiving2 cooking. Family reunions.    
    
    
    Video: A first-hand tour of Tacloban city center one month after #YolandaPh An appeal to restore the hospitals.
http://youtu.be/X8k339g5UNU     
    
    
    Portrait shot I took of my daughter. One of those rare times she allowed me to post a photo of her in… http://instagram.com/p/iYafDODWsS/     
    
    
    Pasko at Pelikulang Pinoy: 39th Metro Manila Film Festival http://www.thepoc.net/features/sosyal/news/19772-pasko-at-pelikulang-pinoy-39th-metro-manila-film-festival …    
    
    
    nitrates? RT @unlawyer: I still don't understand what purpose chicken manure serves in Pinoy firecracker manufacture.    
    
    
    Men are such worry-warts. Let go. Let God.    
    
    
    It is the day after Christmas. Peace on earth will come to stay , when we live Christmas everyda… http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1406328 …    
    
    
    Sipping a cup of hot tsokolate. I sent 1.5 kilos of tablea (bought from Richard Co  @TalesfromtheTum  ) to my... http://fb.me/1fDF8aSGU     
    
    
    Don't drink and drive. Just sleep over if you have to > 4 dead in Christmas Day car crash in Tagaytay http://shar.es/OSTRf     
    
    
    @SUMBUNGANBAYAN is here. What can we do?    
    
    
    good binder ? RT @markcojuangco:  @unlawyer 
Chicken Manure?
No nitrates.
Phosphates, urea, organics.
Oh! As binder?    
    
    
    @markcojuangco that part is fine .    
    
    
    well tis a roller coaster ride. Some highs & lows.  We’ve proven critics wrong ‘discerning’ Filipinos still love Noy – Palace on SWS survey    
    
    
    the Palace lives on high satisfaction ratings. Without it, they are in panic mode RT @felaicabahug:  must be really delusional #ugh    
    
    
    Hanging out with my college classmates & they talked about how arrogant the Binays are. Their question: what next? Does he get away w/ it?    
    
    
    Thank goodness, my classmates are classy than these > Snappy answers to those inappropriate reunion comments http://www.rappler.com/move-ph/ispeak/46651-snappy-answers-reunion-comments …    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger     
    
    
    Then extend RT @inquirerdotnet: 3-day break not enough for Aquino, says health chief http://bit.ly/1eGYg99     
    
    
    he would be less tired if he quit smoking. RT @ka_toto: @inquirerdotnet yes, extend until 2016    
    
    
    Enjoying this cool breeze while it lasts.    
    
    
    Working on the top articles for Blog Watch.    
    
    
    @cocoy @abbiereal can't you get your driver's license in Manila?    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @cafeattinapay    
    
    
    A year full of love onscreen: Sir Chief and Maya’s ever after http://www.thepoc.net/features/sosyal/features/19777-a-year-full-of-love-onscreen-sir-chief-and-maya-s-forever-and-ever-after …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    It's the year of selfies. Love them or hate them..Oxford Dictionary has declared it the Word of the Year for 2013.  http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/poc-youth/19764-selfies-where-do-we-draw-the-line …    
    
    
    A gift from my sister. A new book to read. I am always happier at home. Home is where the heart is. http://instagram.com/p/iaD8KxDWrd/     
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @patriciahizon @mymomfriday @LisaLadrido    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Saving the Lost Art of Conversation
In a fast-paced digital age, an MIT psychologist tries to slow us down. http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2014/01/the-eavesdropper/355727/ …    
    
    
    Am feeling so productive. I hope this carries on till the end of the year.    
    
    
    An MIT psychologist advocates limiting our device usage in “sacred spaces” like the dinner table, the places... http://fb.me/3CLak4NCG     
    
    
    Selfies: Where do we draw the line? . Here are a few things to keep in mind: http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/poc-youth/19764-selfies-where-do-we-draw-the-line … via @thepocnews    
    
    
    I posted 7 photos on Facebook in the album "Virtual Noche buena" http://fb.me/6n1CNiiGj     
    
    
    Is there really a "Napoles" firecracker aside from the Super Yolanda one?    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/XNyjrueO     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/17QrXy1XP     
    
    
    yes for birthdays we do too. RT @BlissfulLiving2: ganyan na meals ng ibang pamilya, even on regular days or other events like anniv & bdays    
    
    
    Congrats @linocayetano RT @alanpcayetano: Congrats Lino & Fille!You Did It!GOD Bless Your Marriage! pic.twitter.com/vD3UQufypV    
    
    
    I am excited to write my plans in here > This Journal Will Actually Change Someone's Life 2014 http://www.rochellesychua.com/2013/12/this-journal-will-actually-change-someones-life-2014.html … via @rochellesychua    
    
    
    The perfect planner for me > This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life 2014 http://beautyoverfifty.net/my-favorite-things/the-perfect-planner-for-2014/ …    
    
    
    ugh hope no one uses it MT @simplyzaida: Aside from the blaring noise they used cow's meat to show ppl on how destructive & dangerous it is    
    
    
    An article I wrote for Blog Watch: Top 13 posts in 2013 http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/features/19783-blog-watch-top-13-posts-in-2013 … #yearender    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @blairbitchbunny @EmpowHER    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @EscapeManila @iamTIANUS    
    
    
    New on #blogwatch: The Big Chinese Bully http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19786-the-big-chinese-bully … by @cocoy    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @PaintersWifePH @MommyRubz @RebelSweetHrt    
    
    
    #juanvote election 2013 watch  is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1338783684 … Stories via @2013Elections    
    
    
    @LisaLadrido wonderful. Happy new year    
    
    
    @talk2GLOBE my daughter now in Vietnam. The bridge data roaming code on your website not working. Please advise ASAP    
    
    
    Read all about. "The Big Chinese Bully" http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19786-the-big-chinese-bully … by @cocoy    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics … Stories via @blogwatchdotph    
    
    
    Kitty  back massage is the best #catsofinstagram #catstagram #cats #catlovers #kitties… http://instagram.com/p/ic7oECuOr5/     
    
    
    #Repost from wenchie318 . Dinner with the Miss international and her court lol http://instagram.com/p/idoBcCDWsN/     
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @gojackiego    
    
    
    LOL RT @BinibiningCamel: Ms Int'l @aupijuan & her court.@tetalimcangco @ceso @_leiyla @supsup010 @rochellesychua pic.twitter.com/LrwZjxKyjS    
    
    
    we look like werewolves ! @supsup010 @rochellesychua @BinibiningCamel @aupijuan @tetalimcangco @ceso @_leiyla    
    
    
    her ladies in waiting RT @supsup010: Pretty Ladies Top 5 Ms International! hahaha @aupijuan @ceso @Wenchie318 pic.twitter.com/c6u2yVrKDq    
    
    
    Umbrellas are so in that @aupijian and  @rochellesychua use it at night http://instagram.com/p/ieRjJhjWsF/     
    
    
    & you still look so svelte RT @aupijuan: @supsup010 @ceso @Wenchie318 i'm eating potato salad & roast chix again...    
    
    
    And we played Dixit journey board games using clues that are political lol http://instagram.com/p/ieTWXCDWuj/     
    
    
    And we played Dixit journey board game http://instagram.com/p/ieTWXCDWuj/     
    
    
    @aupijuan @supsup010 @ceso @Wenchie318 my blouse is also loose to hide belly    
    
    
    ''OMG! I gotta tweet that!'' #bitstrips pic.twitter.com/BoWgLulyMp    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @philipoliveros    
    
    
    DFA: Old passports phased out by 2015  http://m.philstar.com/314190/show/9f51e59b51dbbb12bc91b9c300d3684b/ …    
    
    
    Congrats to my brother @stopepilepsy for receiving US National Award for Innovation in Education. To think he was... http://fb.me/1ba3Y3mM2     
    
    
    Firecracker-related injuries up; dance "Roar" to welcome New Year - DOH http://www.thepoc.net/news/breaking-stories/19789-firecracker-related-injuries-up-dance-roar-to-welcome-new-year-doh …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @bethangsioco @pinoymommy @cuckoo_sing    
    
    
    Blog Watch: Top 13 posts in 2013 via @raggster @cocoy @wenchie318 @venzie @jcmaningat @sexymom & yours truly http://blogwatch.tv/2013/12/blog-watch-top-13-posts-in-2013/ …    
    
    
    On #blogwatch -  Blog Watch: Top 13 posts in 2013 http://goo.gl/fb/QRtgT     
    
    
    The year that was in Blog Watch: Citizen power, TROs , Voters' education and the continued fight against corruption http://fb.me/28qjVIfPy     
    
    
    New on #blogwatch: The ghost of Christmas passed http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19792-the-ghost-of-christmas-passed …  by Dean de la Paz    
    
    
    In case you missed this: Threat to Threat: How to Influence Supreme Court Justices http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19734-threat-to-threat-how-to-influence-supreme-court-justices … by Dine Racoma via @blogwatchdotph    
    
    
    And, for better or worse, people judge you if you can’t tell the difference between their, there, and they’re. http://blogs.hbr.org/2012/07/i-wont-hire-people-who-use-poo/ …    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Best not to use firecrackers but have first aid materials including home remedies like alkaline … http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1419400 …    
    
    
    New on #blogwatch: Just the facts, ma'am (On Mayor Junjun Binay video) http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19793-just-the-facts-ma-am-on-mayor-junjun-binay …  by @raggster    
    
    
    From all these facts, is it now unreasonable to draw factual inferences? (on Binay/Dasmagate incident) http://blogwatch.tv/2013/12/just-the-facts-maam-on-mayor-junjun-binay-and-security-guards-of-dasmarinas-village/ …    
    
    
    @GeloLopez you are so right, I was like "huh" in that Bias and social segregation articles. Not convinced of their arguments    
    
    
    with our without makeup, always beautiful . @aupijuan @philippinebeat @Wenchie318 @ceso @supsup010 @BinibiningCamel    
    
    
    @BurnBookManila because of duh articles like "Bias" and "social segregation"    
    
    
    Noemi's mobile provider is really testing her patience. #bitstrips pic.twitter.com/Tzi4OAXVgZ    
    
    
    On #blogwatch -  Just the facts, ma’am (On Mayor Junjun Binay and security guards of… http://goo.gl/fb/IrgWv     
    
    
    Let us observe precautions to avoid experiencing tragic moments during the new year celebration http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1419735 …    
    
    
    Facts on the Binay/Banyan gate incident: Everything that can be seen in the video can be taken for fact. For... http://fb.me/2I2kWeSNY     
    
    
    Why the customer is NOT always right http://www.thepoc.net/features/pera-isipan/mind-your-own-business/19791-why-the-customer-is-not-always-right …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    On our Health & wellness articles for 2013: Keep calm and stay healthy http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/year-in-pocus/look-back/19794-keep-calm-and-stay-healthy …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Nostalgia -- the best gift and, sometimes, the worst http://www.thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19790-nostalgia-the-best-gift-and-sometimes-the-worst …  by Richard Ramos via @thepocnews    
    
    
    But what is nostalgia, really? And why do we indulge in it, however reluctantly?  http://www.thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19790-nostalgia-the-best-gift-and-sometimes-the-worst …    
    
    
    Nostalgia can keep us paralyzed when we have too much of it.   http://www.thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19790-nostalgia-the-best-gift-and-sometimes-the-worst …    
    
    
    Perhaps one of the true powers of nostalgia is that it can trigger the feeling of hope.  http://www.thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19790-nostalgia-the-best-gift-and-sometimes-the-worst …    
    
    
    New blog post -  Nostalgia — the best gift and, sometimes, the worst http://goo.gl/fb/DrtaH     
    
    
    Nostalgia — the best gift and, sometimes, the worst http://dlvr.it/4bc0b7     
    
    
    Whenever the end of the year rolls by, the combined holidays, and the feeling of having to look back at what... http://fb.me/2U4BJxQg1     
    
    
    As we remember all the good times, we close the door one last time for this year & open a new one, for 2014 http://aboutmyrecovery.com/nostalgia-the-best-gift-and-sometimes-the-worst/ …    
    
    
    Using my planner now  "This journal will change someone's life " details at http://beautyoverfifty.net  http://instagram.com/p/ifvTxbjWos/     
    
    
    I found the perfect planner for ME. I highly recommend “This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life 2014!”   http://beautyoverfifty.net/my-favorite-things/the-perfect-planner-for-2014/ …    
    
    
    100% proceeds of 
"This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life 2014" for #yolandaph #reliefPH http://beautyoverfifty.net/my-favorite-things/the-perfect-planner-for-2014/ …    
    
    
    While playing Dixit board game > "What else would a gathering of citizen advocates think of? " via @philippinebeat pic.twitter.com/nD1ItioAE7    
    
    
    if successful, a dream come true. RT @YahooPH: Choosy taxi drivers may soon face penalties. Details here: http://bit.ly/1ceyCk1     
    
    
    I'm loving this advertising by @Debenhams that actually reflects the world we live in. (via @Upworthy) http://www.upworthy.com/a-catalog-that-believes-reality-can-sell-clothes-better-than-photoshop?g=3&c=ufb2 …    
    
    
    Fully Booked, Power Books & online via Lazada http://www.lazada.com.ph/this-journal-will-actually-change-someones-life-2014-black-95730.html … RT @mark_estavillo: available where?    
    
    
    I am for fair use policy so customer like me who don't download get consistent internet RT @cablay28: FAIR USE POLICY http://pldthome.com/plpfup     
    
    
    In my postpaid mobile LTE, i have a  quota per day RT @cablay28:  how about live streaming of webinar?    
    
    
    @raggster @GeloLopez what is KSS article ?    
    
    
    @JMmelegrito @cablay28 yes still unlimited. Just saying my plan has a quota. Soon @smartcares will implement it.    
    
    
    very disappointing. Usually I agree with her on most issues but the Bias …NO RT @raggster: Kat stuart-santiago, the Biases article. =)    
    
    
    Love this article > 7 Reasons Why You Should Travel Alone At Least Once In Your Life  http://po.st/Y5rNC5     
    
    
    @raggster @adriancuenca BTW I reposted it because FB has an issue with http://thepoc.net  . For FB sharing use> http://blogwatch.tv/2013/12/just-the-facts-maam-on-mayor-junjun-binay-and-security-guards-of-dasmarinas-village/ …    
    
    
    For FB sharing use this > Just the facts, ma’am (On Mayor Junjun Binay and security guards of Dasmarinas Village) http://blogwatch.tv/2013/12/just-the-facts-maam-on-mayor-junjun-binay-and-security-guards-of-dasmarinas-village/ …    
    
    
    Why Fewer Toys Will Benefit Your Kids....“The potential possibilities of any child are the most intriguing and... http://fb.me/RFq31Fss     
    
    
    still many cowards @tweetnirizal    
    
    
    Pinoy secrets: An American learns lessons on life, love, and death-by-videoke http://shar.es/90WAA  via @gmanews    
    
    
    Hundreds of corpses unburied seven weeks after 'Yolanda' http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/nation/regions/12/28/13/hundreds-corpses-unburied-after-yolanda …    
    
    
    STAY SAFE  on New Years Eve by heeding these friendly reminders from the Philippine Red Cross http://fb.me/2cWltKMol     
    
    
    In accordance with PNP- Firearms explosives office & to ensure safety pls take note of authorize… http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1421765 …    
    
    
    New Year Safety Tips from the Philippine Red Cross: When using fireworks & What to do with fireworks burn http://fb.me/2ca8g5763     
    
    
    When will the Philippine government stop pointing fingers and act on the unburied #yolandaPH dead ? http://shar.es/90GOW     
    
    
    “I cannot believe that the purpose of life is to be happy. I think the purpose of life is to be useful, to be... http://fb.me/2XxCs5eJX     
    
    
    di na kailangan basta act on the problem/situation RT @supsup010:  In PH history.. may umamin na bang gobyerno sa kasalanan?    
    
    
    oo nga eh. Pressure needed. RT @supsup010:  true.. but how can they act when in denial? :(    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @manilamommy @nonstopbabble @mymomfriday    
    
    
    Hello busy moms @mymomfriday @manilamommy @nonstopbabble    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @wandergirlana    
    
    
    Bringing out the torotots for tomorrow's New Year 's Eve festivities At home http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1423293 …    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @ibyang @yendreyfus @YoungMomLove    
    
    
    @BlissfulLiving2 yes I will try to get a video recorder that I can place on top of my head    
    
    
    I can't wait to see you all on January strat planning RT @mymomfriday:  thank you Noemi! Happy new year mommas! @manilamommy @nonstopbabble    
    
    
    2013: Top 8 moments that defined the Aquino administration http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/year-in-pocus/feature/19798-mishandled-crises-and-defining-moments-of-the-aquino-administration …  by Lena Rodriguez via @thepocnews    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    On #blogwatch -  2013: Top 8 moments that defined the Aquino administration http://goo.gl/fb/i7a3Y     
    
    
    @voltaire what would the 5 positive ones be? I will let someone look into that    
    
    
    New post on #blogwatch > Kwentong Barbero- More things other than ‘pork’ that stink http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19799-more-things-other-than-pork-that-stink … by Manuel Calleja    
    
    
    What is there left to write about Jose Rizal? A couple of ‘what ifs,’ perhaps. http://thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19797-jose-rizal-what-ifs …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    meron na pala. I will ask someone to write a commentary RT @voltaire: .@momblogger via @mlq3 Ta-dah! http://ow.ly/s7SWl     
    
    
    With @philippinebeat and @xxxriainxxx for quick meet up. And other friends dropped by for quick hello http://instagram.com/p/iiPG8HjWvL/     
    
    
    @Cocoy will write  “@voltaire:  @mlq3 ... for every criticism, look for five positive things to praise. Kung wala-> therapy :)”    
    
    
    Sayang @arpeelazaro was not part “@xxxriainxxx: @rochellesychua @philippinebeat @juned pic.twitter.com/a8gpNUpgnY    
    
    
    @rochellesychua @xxxriainxxx @philippinebeat @Juned last minute Lang talaga. We have a 2pm meeting so everyone met him earlier    
    
    
    @rochellesychua @arpeelazaro @xxxriainxxx @philippinebeat @Juned Oo nga last minute . Sayang . Ryan had to rush for a 2 pm appointment    
    
    
    @voltaire I believe in having positivity. To bring hope    
    
    
    I like these 5 A's RT @voltaire: Yes, at ako 5A's: attention appreciation acknowledgement acceptance allowing :)    
    
    
    true. RT @voltaire: “@FastCoLead: to make people feel good ask about something positive happening in their lives. http://ow.ly/rRUV2 ”    
    
    
    @voltaire I always look at the silver lining.    
    
    
    You were probably raised to believe that no one will like you if you talk about yourself all the time. But a body... http://fb.me/TDPelmx2     
    
    
    Before we  let our young ones adapt tech-savvy lifestyle, we must know the digital dangers first. Here are a few:  http://www.thepoc.net/features/lintech/features/19776-digital-dangers-gadgets-risks-to-children …    
    
    
    Jose Rizal "what ifs" http://www.thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19797-jose-rizal-what-ifs …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    10  tips that can help those who are willing to do something to improve their financial situation http://thepoc.net/features/pera-isipan/wealth-guidelines/19738-10-best-personal-finance-tips-we-should-all-heed …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Kwentong Barbero: More things other than ‘pork’ that stink http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19799-more-things-other-than-pork-that-stink …  by Manuel Calleja via @blogwatchdotph    
    
    
    This beautiful "This Journal Will Actually Change Someone’s Life 2014" allows you to help #yolandaPH and yourself.  http://beautyoverfifty.net/my-favorite-things/the-perfect-planner-for-2014/ …    
    
    
    The ghost of Christmas passed http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19792-the-ghost-of-christmas-passed …  by Dean de la Paz  via @blogwatchdotph    
    
    
    Let us recall the ghosts of Christmas Past and array these against the images of Christmas today.  http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19792-the-ghost-of-christmas-passed …    
    
    
    20 Things To Let Go Of Before The New Year by @ShannonLKaiser http://mbg.is/18GWBrT  via @MindBodyGreen    
    
    
    Let go of all thoughts that don't make you feel empowered and strong.  http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    Firecrackers vs. life and limb http://thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19785-firecrackers-vs-limbs-and-life …  by @rachcorner via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Let go of feeling guilty for doing what you truly want to do. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    2013’s best in beauty and fashion http://thepoc.net/features/beauty-and-fashion/features/19770-2013-s-best-in-beauty-and-fashion …  via @thepocnews Beauty & Fashion Channel    
    
    
    12 round fruits and torotot for #newyearseve http://instagram.com/p/iiuxy6jWqB/     
    
    
    3. Let go of the fear of the unknown; take one small step and watch the path reveal itself. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    In case you missed this > Just the facts, ma'am (On Mayor Junjun Binay) http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19793-just-the-facts-ma-am-on-mayor-junjun-binay … by @raggster    
    
    
    Best wishes @supsup_shamcey & Lloyd Lee > The groom wept, the bride was radiant http://shar.es/9HrVS     
    
    
    Top health stories at @thepocnews: Remember Keep calm and stay healthy http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/year-in-pocus/look-back/19794-keep-calm-and-stay-healthy …    
    
    
    alarming. take care everyone RT @inquirerdotnet: Growing number of ’cracker injuries alarms DOH. Read: http://bit.ly/1eQhs4b  @ninyacalleja    
    
    
    Southern Luzon & Eastern seaboard of Visayas RT @NDRRMC_OpCen: NDRRMC Update on Gale Warning No. 87 issued on 30 DEC
http://tinyurl.com/mbe9eom     
    
    
    #SmartLTE unlimited will be extended beyond December 31, 2013. Please wait for the official announcement via @SmartCares.    
    
    
    What to let go before the New Year #ilove Part 1 http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1426240 …    
    
    
    Pork is no. 2 buzzword #scrapPork > Countdown countdown ‘pag may time: Top 13 buzzwords of 2013 http://shar.es/9H4sX     
    
    
    On my recipe blog:  Buko Fruit Salad http://goo.gl/fb/3LY2V     
    
    
    Our New Year’s Eve  media noche  always has  fruit salad on the dinner table. The most popular fruit salad is the... http://fb.me/2QtYYCtCO     
    
    
    What to let go before the New Year #ilove Part 2 http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1426609 …    
    
    
    I disagree > Communists call for PNoy's ouster from office http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/nation/12/26/13/communists-call-pnoys-ouster-office …    
    
    
    4. Let go of regrets; at one point in your life, that “whatever” was exactly what you wanted.  http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    I wonder what the 20-somethings think of this >28 Important New Year’s Resolutions Every Twentysomething Should Make http://www.buzzfeed.com/regajha/important-new-years-resolutions-every-twentysomething-sho …    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @philippinebeat    
    
    
    @philippinebeat @ansj64 has ousting leaders ever fixed the problem? I want the current leader to fix it. like #scrapPork    
    
    
    5. Let go of worrying; worrying is like praying for what you don’t want. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    6. Let go of blaming anyone for anything.. If you don’t like something, you have two choices, accept it or change it.http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    7. Let go of thinking you are damaged; you matter, and the world needs you just as you are. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    8. Let go of thinking your dreams are not important; always follow your heart. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    Aquino cites gains, foresees more ‘challenges’ in New Year message http://thepoc.net/news/breaking-news/19800-aquino-cites-gains-foresees-more-challenges-in-new-year-message …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Christmas killjoys, Scrooges, and other holiday downers http://thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19796-christmas-killjoys-scrooges-and-other-holiday-downers …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    9. Let go of being the “go-to person” for everyone... stop blowing yourself off and take care of yourself first http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    All I can do is pray. "Praying for our children doesn't mean that nothing will ever go wrong in their lives. But... http://fb.me/6ohZrc9Fj     
    
    
    10. Let go of thinking everyone else is happier, more successful or better off than you.  http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    OMG parents/guardians, what are you doing? RT @ABSCBNNews: Kids still losing fingers to 'Piccolo' firecrackers http://bit.ly/1d3slZu     
    
    
    a good one! RT @EricTTung: It is better to look ahead & prepare than to look back & regret. -Jackie Joyner-Kersee    
    
    
    still with DOH ads, accidents happening RT @godwin_anthony: as a kid i had first hand experience of a neighbor loosing his fingers due to..    
    
    
        
    
    
    I have enough of ousting leaders. I agree w/ @indayevarona. > "YAWN. SORRY GUYS, DISAGREE. Criticize, protest,... http://fb.me/XsjHnGx3     
    
    
    @godwin_anthony ouch. How painful that must be for the kid & you to witness it    
    
    
    11. Let go of thinking there's a right and wrong way to do things or to see the world. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    how sad RT @godwin_anthony:  kaya these kids wont stop unless they get themselves into it 💣    
    
    
    When will this happen in the PH? > Over 500 Chinese lawmakers resign in mass bribery scandal — RT News: http://rt.com/news/china-officials-bribery-scandal-923/#.UsGiKUfNhO8.twitter …    
    
    
    Add the goal  to #scrapPork including the DAP of course > Noy enters last 2 minutes, sets sights on prosperity    http://shar.es/9bW6v     
    
    
    A 2006 video I took of our neighbor's firecrackers' explosion. First time it ever happened in our neighborhood http://youtu.be/w9DnQSjbxFk     
    
    
    Let go of anger toward ex lovers and family...just because it is over doesn’t mean the love was wrong. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    15. Let go of the need to do more and be more; for today, you've done the best you can, and that's enough. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    To more prosperity! Hope! @leugenn @philippinebeat @pinoymommy @tetalimcangco @tikitikitin @pastor_ey @ceso @cocoy @JannMeds @GeloLopez    
    
    
    Goodbye 2013. Let me count  our blessings...2013 was a year of mixed blessings and challenges.   http://shar.es/9od9T     
    
    
    terrible RT @News5AKSYON: 40 year old from Brgy Holy Spirit QC becomes first female stray bullet victim..http://tl.gd/n_1rv9fne     
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @sasa_estepa    
    
    
    Workout time @ Fitness First http://instagram.com/p/ikaxbLjWtG/     
    
    
    @cocoy @ceso now that's a productive day. Will write today too    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @DessertComes1st @Wenchie318 @RebelSweetHrt    
    
    
    #juanvote election 2013 watch  is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1338783684 …    
    
    
    Thanks “@cathybabao:  thank you! happy 2014 to you, butch and the girls!”    
    
    
        
    
    
    Festive here . Buying last minute groceries (@ Eastwood Mall w/ 9 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/JqFNj4     
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Nomi and Zooey are so adorable. They loved the fish #catsofinstagram #catstagram #cats #catlovers… http://instagram.com/p/iksNxMOOoM/     
    
    
    17. Let go of your money woes — make a plan to pay off debt and focus on your abundance. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    Top 10 gadgets of 2013 http://mail.thepoc.net/features/lintech/features/19757-top-10-gadgets-of-2013 …  by @rachcorner via @thepocnews    
    
    
    I will play this video at full volume...A video  I took of our neighbor's deafening firecrackers' explosion in 2006.  http://youtu.be/w9DnQSjbxFk     
    
    
    New on #blogwatch:Super Lolo Enrile, Aquinomics Bomb, Napoles-Luses: Firecrackers & fireworks to mark the end of 2013 http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19811-super-lolo-enrile-aquinomics-bomb-napoles-luses-firecrackers-and-fireworks-to-mark-the-end-of-2013 …    
    
    
    On #blogwatch -  Super Lolo Enrile, Aquinomics Bomb, Napoles-Luses: Firecrackers and… http://goo.gl/fb/gHNrM     
    
    
    or malapit lang. RT @jabjimenez: Directions, pinoy style. "Diretso ka lang. Sa pangalawang kanto, dun ka nalang magtanong." *facepalm*    
    
    
    The Philippines just can’t celebrate the New Year without the blasts and bangs. Enjoy the New Year and start with... http://fb.me/3f1f5utpY     
    
    
    18. Let go of trying to save/change people. The best thing you can do is work on yourself & stop focusing on others. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    #ScrapPork made it to the '10 Hashtags that made 2013' http://www.interaksyon.com/article/77630/scrappork …    
    
    
    19. Let go of trying to fit in and be accepted by everyone. Your uniqueness is what makes you outstanding. http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    @blueknightPH Happy New Year too. Together we will meet our goals.    
    
    
    Super Lolo Enrile, Aquinomics Bomb, Napoles-Luses: Firecrackers and fireworks to mark the end of 2013 http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19811-super-lolo-enrile-aquinomics-bomb-napoles-luses-firecrackers-and-fireworks-to-mark-the-end-of-2013 …  by Dine Racoma    
    
    
    New on #blogwatch: 5 Achievements of the Aquino Administration, and the Philippines in 2013 http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19813-5-achievements-of-the-aquino-administration-and-the-philippines-in-2013 …  by @cocoy    
    
    
    On #blogwatch -  5 Achievements of the Aquino Administration, and the Philippines in 2013 http://goo.gl/fb/EbmcA     
    
    
    Much has been said about the Aquino Administration in 2013, but what really happened in 2013? http://blogwatch.tv/2013/12/5-achievements-of-the-aquino-administration-and-the-philippines-in-2013/ … @voltaire    
    
    
    @rom awesome. I only have one.    
    
    
    20. Let go of self-hate. Who you are matters, and the world needs you as you are. Celebrate you! http://mbg.is/18GWBrT     
    
    
    wonderful. I hope to try it when you get it. RT @artsamaniego: @rom only #10 is what I'm missing, but will have it very soon :)    
    
    
    New blog post -  The power of a praying parent http://goo.gl/fb/EFs90     
    
    
    No one is a perfect parent but we can all be a praying parent. I am aware of my failures in the past and I pray... http://fb.me/6pePxZxer     
    
    
    New on my blog: The power of a praying parent http://aboutmyrecovery.com/the-power-of-a-praying-parent/ …    
    
    
    @peacheshonestly O di ba? I will make sure to amplify the audio of this firecrackers' explosion as 2014 nears    
    
    
    The power of a praying parent http://dlvr.it/4cD2Ss     
    
    
    wow. I wanna try! coffee? lol RT @rom: @artsamaniego you mean this? :) pic.twitter.com/3GyTnQ4dsZ    
    
    
    On my Tech Blog:  Top 10 gadgets of 2013 http://goo.gl/fb/6p0zi     
    
    
    . “Maybe this year, we ought to walk through the rooms of our lives not looking for flaws, but looking… http://instagram.com/p/ilIEMyDWvS/     
    
    
    @jcmaningat thanks! will check on it    
    
    
    @voltaire just so you know it is posted already @noynoyaquino @cocoy    
    
    
    @rochellesychua thanks Roch. Surely 2014 will bring us more prosperity! @philippinebeat    
    
    
    with google glasses on ha? RT @rom: Need to meet @artsamaniego @tonyocruz @cocoy @philippinebeat brainstorm on voters ed. We need this NOW.    
    
    
    President Aquino's reality check via @rapplerdotcom http://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/46931-aquino-presidency-reality-check …    
    
    
    While all my children have flown the coop, all I can do now is pray. Let go and let God. http://aboutmyrecovery.com/the-power-of-a-praying-parent/ …    
    
    
    @Doc4Dead  Now they ask help >  NBI needs help on rotting bodies in Tacloban http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/nation/regions/12/30/13/nbi-needs-help-rotting-bodies-tacloban …    
    
    
    Preparing Buko Fruit Salad http://pinoyfoodblog.com/filipino-food-recipes/noche-buena-dishbuko-fruit-salad/ …  and vegetarian pasta dish for Media Noche.    
    
    
    #ScrapPork , top 10 hashtags for 2013. For 2014, I envision using this hashtag > #scrappedpork http://www.interaksyon.com/article/77630/scrappork …    
    
    
    Together with other citizen advocates, we can do it #scrapPork  RT @JamesMangun:  The fight continues into 2014    
    
    
    @cocoy @SagadaSun < Have you two met up to celebrate? @rom @rochellesychua    
    
    
    Cheers. Miss you old pal. RT @SagadaSun: Happy New Year to old confederates! @cocoy @rom @rochellesychua    
    
    
    I baked rum cake last year. This year tis fruit cake RT @SagadaSun: Made a double-rum cake. Will eat a slice .. @cocoy @rom @rochellesychua    
    
    
    Sana all places RT @solartvnews: Barangay Bangkal in Makati is a no-firecracker zone. #SolarNews    
    
    
    Tsk...How secure is NAIA? As 2013 ends, mentally challenged man breaches Terminal 1 'high-security' fence http://www.interaksyon.com/article/77800/how-secure-is-naia-as-2013-ends-mentally-challenged-man-breaches-terminal-1-high-security-fence …    
    
    
    Cheers to that ! RT @SagadaSun: We'll all be doing BIG things together in the coming New Year I reckon! @cocoy @rom @rochellesychua    
    
    
    2013: Congress and controversies http://thepoc.net/features/politi-ko/politiko-opinions/19810-2013-pork-barrel-and-congress …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Hope springs eternal > 94 percent of Pinoys entering New Year with hope —SWS http://shar.es/9Wii8     
    
    
    No one is a perfect parent but we can all be a praying parent. I am aware of my failures in the past and I pray... http://fb.me/2NrVvk1Nn     
    
    
    While our country faced challenges, take note of the positives: the 5 achievements of the Aquino Administration... http://fb.me/6kTzip60u     
    
    
    Blog Watch Top 13 most popular posts for 2013 http://blogwatch.tv/2013/12/blog-watch-top-13-posts-in-2013/ …    
    
    
    Final reminder : 20 Things To Let Go Of Before The New Year http://mbg.is/18GWBrT  via @MindBodyGreen    
    
    
    Father And Daughter Recreate Old Wedding Photos To Say Goodbye To Late Wife And Mother | Bored Panda http://www.boredpanda.com/father-daughter-recreate-wedding-pictures-ben-nunery-melanie-tracy-pace/ … via @boredpanda    
    
    
    How do you celebrate New Year's Eve. ? #ilove http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1430102 …    
    
    
    5 Ways the Philippines Changed Me FOREVER http://www.idreamedofthis.com/2013/12/25/5-ways-the-philippines-changed-me-forever/ …    
    
    
    Cheers! RT @alfredcaparros: Happy New Year mga madam! @pinoymommy @aupijuan @maltiq    
    
    
    It's official: Pope has not abolished sin, says Vatican http://shar.es/9WQBQ  via @gmanews    
    
    
    @bubblyapp thanks for the RT.    
    
    
    2013 in photos #newyearseve http://instagram.com/p/ildIFZjWgi/     
    
    
    Reading "Korina: Human of the Year" http://wp.me/p2IXEb-Ai  via Spin Busters    
    
    
    Tonight Super Lolo Enrile, Aquinomics Bomb, Napoles-Luses: Firecrackers and fireworks to mark the end of 2013 http://blogwatch.tv/2013/12/super-lolo-enrile-aquinomics-bomb-napoles-luses-firecrackers-and-fireworks-to-mark-the-end-of-2013/ …    
    
    
    Super Lolo Enrile and Lolo Thunder, Aquinomics Bomb, Napoles-Luses, Whistleblower Bomb, Boga Revilla, Jinggoy... http://fb.me/3qz57Eqa8     
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger     
    
    
    @yusufledesma thank you. Happy New year!    
    
    
    Cheers! @iwriteasiwrite @CQ1016 @jesterinexile @xpeanutgalleryx @v_vangogh @philippinebeat @leahnavarro @pinoymommy    
    
    
    Skype chat with my sister in San Francisco while we do a countdown http://instagram.com/p/il2k6xjWio/     
    
    
    Wearing polka dots #newyearseve http://instagram.com/p/il3zfDjWk3/     
    
    
    Happy new year 2014 everyone. Firecrackers explosion getting more frequent and louder at my neig… http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1431117 …    
    
    
    Happy new year 2014 ! http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1431137 …    
    
    
    @frankstupid1 happy new year    
    
    
    Happy New Year. When I wonder what is coming, I tell myself the best is coming, the very best in life and love... http://fb.me/6syj3KQSx     
    
    
    May  2014 see you giving, loving, living and lots of hugging. Wishing you all a happy and healthy life as well as a prosperous New Year.    
    
    
    cheers to a prosperous 2014 @cocoy @teambamaquino @philippinebeat @maria_ressa    
    
    
    Always praying and hoping. Happy New year. RT @arnelc24:  here's to praying for a better Philippines in 2014. Happy new year!    
    
    
    @reemyrobby Happy New Year Robby. More work to be done. @filipinowriter @philippinebeat    
    
    
    @JannMeds Happy New year Bunso. Cheers.    
    
    
    Wearing radiant orchid color (pink-purple) ,  since it is the color of the year 2014  & with polka… http://instagram.com/p/il3zfDjWk3/     
    
    
        
    
    
    I just love the Color of the Year 2014- Radiant Orchid . A captivating harmony of fuchsia, purple and pink... http://fb.me/XBudp2cn     
    
    
    It is now 2014 in the Philippines. We hope your year is filled with  love, laughter, prosperity and health.... http://fb.me/18ZbLSSkb     
    
    
    waking up to the smell of hot tsokolate from tablea . Looking forward to 2014. Good morning.    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @fer_castaway    
    
    
    No harm in trying since it is about healthy choices >The 7 Things I Did To Lose 220 Pounds Without Dieting http://mbg.is/1ca5eiy     
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @rachcorner @annalyn @mishrendon    
    
    
    Most liked posts in Instagram.  Top 2 posts are about .#scrappork  juanachange http://instagram.com/p/inC5ekjWkH/     
    
    
    Supreme Court in a social media age http://shar.es/9gLLE  via @oscarfbtan    
    
    
    New on my blog: Photos: My Top 13 moments in 2013 http://aboutmyrecovery.com/photos-my-top-13-moments-in-2013/ …    
    
    
    Photos: My Top 13 moments in 2013 http://dlvr.it/4cTQZw     
    
    
    Cheers! @maxell_lander @mjal1227 @jeffcanoy @pinoymommy @FDPascual @SirMecMecaniko @Tito_Ces @RonaldORedito @NoypiAquino    
    
    
    Good, old-fashioned values for a great New Year http://www.thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19814-good-old-fashioned-values-for-a-great-new-year … by Jasmine Barrios for @thepocnews    
    
    
    New Year celebrations around the world http://www.thepoc.net/features/what-on-earth/features/19780-new-year-celebrations-around-the-world …  by  @rachcorner via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Hello 2014. Though #blogwatch notes 5 Achievements of the Aquino Administration in 2013, we hope for positive changes http://www.thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19813-5-achievements-of-the-aquino-administration-and-the-philippines-in-2013 …    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    On #blogwatch -  Post-Yolanda: Aquino’s disaster conspiracy with World Bank, ADB http://goo.gl/fb/yqiS7     
    
    
    Post-Yolanda: Aquino’s disaster conspiracy with @WorldBank, @ADB_HQ http://blogwatch.tv/2014/01/post-yolanda-aquinos-disaster-conspiracy-with-world-bank-adb/ … by @jcmaningat    
    
    
    New on #blogwatch: Post-Yolanda: Aquino’s disaster conspiracy with World Bank, ADB http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/blog-watch/commentaries/19816-post-yolanda-aquino-s-disaster-conspiracy-with-world-bank-adb …  by @jcmaningat    
    
    
    #AidMonitorPH When a government cooperates with foreign “development” agencies ( @WorldBank, @ADB_HQ ) in... http://fb.me/10a6cqbgi     
    
    
    Sharing my top 13 moments in 2013 (in photos) includes family, #scrapPork #notocybercrimelaw #juanvote http://fb.me/2C0zFqAj9     
    
    
    And the work continues on @jcmaningat @venzie @tonyocruz @philippinebeat @mobilemaui @pinoymommy @mrsunlawyer @ChiliMedley @ipayness    
    
    
    I just voted "Angry" in "Post-Yolanda: @NoynoyAquino ’s disaster conspiracy with @WorldBank, @ADB_HQ" http://blogwatch.tv/2014/01/post-yolanda-aquinos-disaster-conspiracy-with-world-bank-adb/ …    
    
    
    Pinoy sports in 2013: A year of comebacks http://www.thepoc.net/features/sportacular/features/19815-pinoy-sports-in-2013-a-year-of-comebacks …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    After being lazy and watching the countdown, I will head off to the gym    
    
    
    No harm in trying since it is about making healthy choices >The 7 Things I Did To Lose 220 Pounds Without Dieting http://fb.me/ThnJIZdy     
    
    
    From my kitchen to yours: Happy cooking in 2014. Remember There is no sincerer love than the love of food (quote... http://fb.me/3jowPZ9Qr     
    
    
    and it is happy new year in New York    
    
    
    One of the biggest life-changing event in 2013 is when the last of my kids has  finally flown the coop.  My post > http://aboutmyrecovery.com/the-power-of-a-praying-parent/ …    
    
    
    happy new year! cheers. @the_gogs @gangbadoy @pinoymommy @teddyboylocsin @iamsuperbianca @HecklerForever @carlosceldran @spurs    
    
    
    local personalities that Filipinos searched the most in Google for 2013. http://199jobs.com/blog/the-top-10-most-popular-filipinos-for-2013/ …    
    
    
    My goal this year is to visit my daughter in Europe. So I  need to save up on it so my family and I will be together for Christmas    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Most Important Thing You Can Do In The New Year To Lose Weight, Get Sharper And Live Longer http://huff.to/1dhVjZi  via @HealthyLiving    
    
    
    My New year countdown as it happened in my bubbly audio post  http://bubbly.net/momblogger/posts/1431137 …    
    
    
    Something new for the New Year. Framed Family photos around the house http://instagram.com/p/ilIEMyDWvS/     
    
    
    Family http://instagram.com/p/ino5wNDWs6/     
    
    
    The stronger citizen reporter http://nie.mn/1jlq0Sz  via @NiemanLab    
    
    
    2014 will be the year when we’ll witness the more powerful citizen reporter.http://nie.mn/1jlq0Sz     
    
    
    Reading Predictions for Journalism 2014: @Harvard's @NiemanLab on the Future of Journalism  http://www.niemanlab.org/collection/predictions-2014/ …    
    
    
    I don't think so >The blog is dead, long live the blog http://nie.mn/1jlq58I  via @NiemanLab    
    
    
    Marketing peeps should take note > Think audiences, not just metrics http://nie.mn/19UQsJd  via @NiemanLab    
    
    
    Looking back at the top 13 moments in 2013. Then I will affirm the good things for the New Year 2014. http://aboutmyrecovery.com/photos-my-top-13-moments-in-2013/ …    
    
    
    The holidays heightens my nostalgia.  Looking forward to seeing my eldest daughter arrive in the PH on Jan 3.    
    
    
    Am planning my family vacation now > Mark the dates: Holidays, 4 long weekends in 2014  http://shar.es/9pk7R     
    
    
    Consider Bohol in your travel plans. #VisitBohol2014  Here is a post-quake tour http://aboutmyrecovery.com/looking-beyond-the-ruins-a-tour-of-post-quake-bohol-visitbohol2014/ …    
    
    
    "A great man is always willing to be little." - Ralph Waldo Emerson http://fb.me/U2Zjub4U     
    
    
    Surprisingly my 4 cats were "dedma" over the New year's noise    
    
    
    Post-holiday drink for us merry-makers:) http://fb.me/2eKOgz6Gj     
    
    
    Hope to visit that one day RT @HerDailyDigest: http://wp.me/p1wHI7-1t6   This trip healed me. Nature does wonders to broken souls #Sapa #ttot    
    
    
    In writing your goals > How to plan for a better you in 2014 http://thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19818-how-to-plan-for-a-better-you-in-2014 … via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Nostalgia – it is the gift we give to ourselves, so we may remember all the good times across the years.  http://aboutmyrecovery.com/nostalgia-the-best-gift-and-sometimes-the-worst/ …    
    
    
    Quite interesting to see how my two girls spent their New year. One in the foggy streets in Europe. The other in Vietnam.    
    
    
    @SagadaSun I don't understand why they can't ban it altogether.    
    
    
    @SagadaSun WHo is in charge? @pnppio or @DOHgovph ?    
    
    
    THIS! RT @cocoy: @SagadaSun I agree or duly licensed fireworks company that public/private sector can hire all year round @pnppio @DOHgovph    
    
    
    Don't you just love Radiant Orchid? the color of the year for 2014 ?  http://beautyoverfifty.net/lifestyle-choices/radiant-orchid-is-the-color-of-the-year-for-2014/ …    
    
    
    The four kitties at home #catsofinstagram #catstagram #cats #catlovers #kitties #instacat
#petstagram… http://instagram.com/p/ioGLxsOOt2/     
    
    
    "If you imagine less, less will be what you undoubtedly deserve. Do what you love, and don’t stop until you get... http://fb.me/2Kf63a0Z5     
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @CD_MFO    
    
    
    Woman on PrimeTime- Radiant Orchid is the color of the year for 2014 http://goo.gl/fb/RSxQ1     
    
    
    Good morning!  Here are Top Six Reasons You Should Not Skip Breakfast http://www.doctorshangout.com/m/blogpost?id=2002836%3ABlogPost%3A941092 …    
    
    
    @rodmagaru lol time to eat. coffee first    
    
    
    Seven resolutions -- suggestions, really -- for better social-media use in the new year. http://www.cnn.com/2013/12/31/tech/social-media/social-media-resolutions/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    While Their Kids Sleep, These parents Pull Of This Amazing Stunt... http://www.quickmeme.com/p/3vpa2h  via @quickmeme    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @justinpaolo @chriselemos    
    
    
        
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @Pinay_WAHM @yendreyfus @mymomfriday    
    
    
    #juanvote election 2013 watch  is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1338783684 … Stories via @Namfrel    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics …    
    
    
    Being a mom . Checking  my daughter 's place before her arrival. http://instagram.com/p/ipyjcejWup/     
    
    
    “@PTVph: INFOGRAPHIC: Key features of the 2014 National Budget. pic.twitter.com/NcG7B6oNRD http://fb.me/2ahjkc2lm ”    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 New Followers, 109 Mentions, 2.06M Mention Reach, 85 Replies, 54 Retweets. via https://sumall.com/twitter     
    
    
    Cheers ! #Throwbackthursday 2012 New Year's Eve http://instagram.com/p/ip_FQ7DWss/     
    
    
    Looking forward to this. Really sick of @enjoyglobe spam > Mandatory SIM card registration pushed - Read: http://bit.ly/1cJAWnM     
    
    
    I wonder if @enjoyGlobe employees ever get spammed with useless SMS from banks , real estate ? I keep these SMS for documentation    
    
    
    Tip: if you add a symbol to your password, e.g. $, ∑, it is 1,500 times more difficult to hack it - http://news.yahoo.com/trick-for-safer-passwords-that-are-easy-to-remember-152045926.html?vp=1 …    
    
    
    What kind of registration “@BlissfulLiving2:  @enjoyGLOBE When you buy new prepaid sim cards there is registration na. Within 2 hours Spam    
    
    
    Not much income from our SMS but spammers. , yes “@JosephCataan:  These networks sell our numbers to those banks, real estates. Grrrrr”    
    
    
    Talaga? Then spam next ? “@BlissfulLiving2:  @enjoyGLOBE When you first turn on, may prompt asking for your name. for loss recovery daw”    
    
    
    @philippinebeat no spam SMS on Cars. Yup will blog about all these spammers  @enjoyGLOBE    
    
    
    @philippinebeat maybe @enjoyGLOBE does not know that there is a data privacy law. Will email an IRR to them soon    
    
    
    king of spam sila “@BlissfulLiving2: @momblogger @enjoyGLOBE The first spam arrived within 2 hours...Unbelievable, I got 5 spam in 24 hrs”    
    
    
    Improving? “@BlissfulLiving2:  @enjoyGLOBE .. a month ago. Surprisingly I haven't gotten any new spam for 2 weeks siguro. #newPrepaidSim”    
    
    
    They should be aware of data privacy law “@philippinebeat: . How many banks have given our contact info to call centers? @enjoyGLOBE”    
    
    
    @philippinebeat hmm. Before spam SMS were spam calls. Changed numbers & scolded citibank . This was 10 years ago. None now    
    
    
    What was our rank before ? “@solartvnews: The Philippines ranks 90th in Forbes' list of Best Countries for Business. #SolarNews”    
    
    
    Philippines rank is even lower now RT @beRODJ: r 87th @solartvnews    
    
    
    Just 3 notch lower > Palace not worried by PH drop in Forbes ranking  Read: http://bit.ly/1es1lW1     
    
    
    Showbiz ups and downs in 2013 http://thepoc.net/features/sosyal/features/19809-showbiz-ups-and-downs-in-2013 …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Meralco to customers: Disregard Dec bills via @rapplerdotcom http://www.rappler.com/business/industries/173-power-and-energy/47096-meralco-disregard-december-bills …    
    
    
    What to leave behind in 2013 and what to embrace in 2014 http://thepoc.net/poc-presents/poc-youth/19819-what-to-leave-behind-in-2013-and-what-to-embrace-in-2014 … fia @thepocnews POCYouth    
    
    
    I already paid my @meralco bill 2 days ago. But then Dec bill same as Nov > Disregard Dec bill http://www.rappler.com/business/industries/173-power-and-energy/47096-meralco-disregard-december-bills …    
    
    
    I hope January bill not high RT @WSCRhadem: @rapplerdotcom disregard dec bills and be welcomed by January bills? Hehehe    
    
    
    Which 2 Filipino words made it ? > 38 Wonderful Foreign Words We Could Use in English http://shar.es/9qlNz     
    
    
    On my recipe blog:  White Forest Cake http://goo.gl/fb/xwj2S     
    
    
    Unfortunately, they can cancel visa at any time >  Ex-solon blasts U.S. Embassy for visa cancellation http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/focus/01/02/14/ex-solon-blasts-us-embassy-visa-cancellation …    
    
    
    Measles on the rise. Someone chose not to vaccinate their child.  By choosing vaccination, you will be protecting your child–and mine.    
    
    
    not proven pa RT @JulesMariano: many ppl in the US sre riding this no vaccination trend bec they believe it causes autism.    
    
    
    @JulesMariano New Zealand has a measles outbreak http://tvnz.co.nz/national-news/measles-outbreak-warning-north-island-5789614 …    
    
    
    @JulesMariano @rom how many children are known to be autistic as a result of vaccination? have to compare it when there measles epidemic    
    
    
        
    
    
    Billy and Missy's best moments in 2013. Missy tops it with 3  moments  while Billy gets the top 2 http://instagram.com/p/iqvUMyuOjS/     
    
    
    This Girl Tripped on LSD And Drew Self Portraits Throughout the Night. The Evolution is Astonishing.
Read more at http://www.picstache.com/lists/1902/This-Girl-Tripped-On-LSD-And-Drew-Self-Portraits-Throughout-The-Night-The-Evolution-Is-Astonishing/1#gXLiykP8pj5qdf3S.99 …    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @TheOneCore    
    
    
    Chilly morning that I am wearing a coat.    
    
    
    On my Tech Blog:  Samsung’s Airconditioner: the Smart Inverter can get you to save 70% energy… http://goo.gl/fb/BQJ19     
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @iamNHOJ @immarkyboi    
    
    
    With Bulacan state students for their thesis on online libel.    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @RebelSweetHrt @AnnAMoMshell @ibyang    
    
    
    interesting discussion with the students. Online libel is fair daw to a few respondents. LOL RT @oscarfbtan: I think I know who you're    
    
    
    Inipit roll from Malolos, Bulacan. A pasalubong http://instagram.com/p/isMOjiDWrZ/     
    
    
    My daughter will disagree with you RT @oscarfbtan: Inquirer: Why backpacking is now boring! http://goo.gl/VHT6FR  pic.twitter.com/wkTlBFMNU9    
    
    
    @oscarfbtan Just picked up my daughter from the airport this morning.  SHe had a lot of fun travelling alone  & meeting new friends    
    
    
    @iMacoy Senator Sotto might think it is fair. But of course, he can't think beyond himself.    
    
    
    address please? RT @KamuningBakery: Thanks this tweet. When can we invite you to try our pugon-baked pan de sal & pan de suelo?    
    
    
    @oscarfbtan I can't disclose who thought it was fair.    
    
    
    TGIF! @philippinebeat @leugenn @JannMeds @ceso @cocoy @pastor_ey @pinoymommy @tetalimcangco @tikitikitin @yusufledesma    
    
    
        
    
    
    A total of 1,571 patients with measles  admitted to the San Lazaro Hospital alone, 71 of which have already died. http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/nation/01/02/14/surge-measles-cases-alarms-doh …    
    
    
        
    
    
    #balitang2014sana : Supreme Court declares DAP unconstitutional @interaksyon #scrapPork    
    
    
    #balitang2014sana : Supreme Court declares RA No. 10175 (or Cybercrime Prevention Act of 2012) unconstitutional . @interaksyon    
    
    
    #balitang2014sana : Supreme Court upholds RH Law @interaksyon    
    
    
    #balitang2014sana : Plunder case vs Enrile, Revilla , Jinggoy Estrada now filed at the Sandigan Bayan @interaksyon #scrapPork    
    
    
    #balitang2014sana-  Senators Enrile, Revilla , Jinggoy Estrada  now suspended @interaksyon #scrapPork    
    
    
        
    
    
    New blog post -  My week is filled with high and low moments http://goo.gl/fb/vSa2R     
    
    
    My week is filled with high and low moments http://dlvr.it/4d5jvL     
    
    
    The Commission on Audit claimed that Laguna Gov. ER Ejercito didn't use his PDAF properly: http://bit.ly/1bDbhsz .    
    
    
    @interaksyon yes RT @annaoposa: #balita2014sana Manila Ocean Park and Ocean Adventure have closed down.    
    
    
    DBM junks SARO system, calls 2014 budget ‘release document’ http://www.thepoc.net/news/breaking-news/19825-dbm-junks-saro-system-calls-2014-budget-as-release-document … via @thepocnews    
    
    
        
    
    
    The best of @thepocnews Buhay Pinoy 2013 ..all things Pinoy -- people, culture, lifestyle, social norms, festivities. http://www.thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19821-the-best-of-buhay-pinoy-2013 …    
    
    
    What about you? I visited only 4 > 7 Philippine Islands You Must Visit Before You Die http://www.airasia.com/travel3sixty/digitalexclusives/7-philippine-islands-you-must-visit-before-you-die …    
    
    
    @choihilario I have not been to Samal    
    
    
    @choihilario it is a goal    
    
    
    My #changeplanner2014 says that today is festival of sleep day. I will grab my soft fluffy pillow later & sleep early    
    
    
    Thanks “@smfdejesus: #FollowFriday @mymyupshaw @jutes_ @juanxi @mr_gadget ”    
    
    
    It's my color...the Radiant Orchid is the color of the year for 2014  http://beautyoverfifty.net/lifestyle-choices/radiant-orchid-is-the-color-of-the-year-for-2014/ …    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @DrChrisNorthrup @nonstopbabble @Go4HealthPH    
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @kingdelrosario    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Though @noynoyaquino still has to #scrapPork, he inspired this >2013: The year Filipinos said ‘No’ to corruption  http://newsinfo.inquirer.net/556825/2013-the-year-filipinos-said-no-to-corruption#ixzz2pORpnjRA …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom     
    
    
    Woman on PrimeTime- Discovering my Enneagram type http://goo.gl/fb/8Zd1f     
    
    
    On my blog: Discovering my Enneagram type http://beautyoverfifty.net/out-of-the-box/discovering-my-enneagram-type/ …    
    
    
    The Junjun Binay vs Dasmariñas Village ... Is this true  : Smell of fear?  http://opinion.inquirer.net/68757/smell-of-fear-in-makati#ixzz2pME72hnT …    
    
    
    If citizens ... are afraid of the Binays, do you think these four guards will have the courage? http://opinion.inquirer.net/68757/smell-of-fear-in-makati#ixzz2pOfJOMhF …    
    
    
    Life is like a roller coaster as I experience these high moments and low moments, moments when I feel like I am... http://fb.me/6sMBK8sHc     
    
    
    In a stunning article in Time magazine, it’s revealed that Jenny McCarthy’s son NEVER had autism in the first place. http://graneyandthepig.wordpress.com/2010/02/27/jenny-mccarthy-my-bad-turns-out-my-kid-doesnt-have-autism/ …    
    
    
    "For those of us in the financial services sector, the beginning of the year is about economic& investment outlooks"  http://manilastandardtoday.com/2014/01/03/zeitgeist/ …    
    
    
    @Liddokun well I will do something about this. There must be an investigation either from DILG or from Human Rights Commission    
    
    
    The Blog Watch News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/politics … Stories via @blogwatchdotph    
    
    
    Thanks! @Liddokun @blogwatchdotph    
    
    
    May kabutihan bang nangyari sa mundo nang dahil sa akin? http://thepoc.net/features/buhay-pinoy/features/19823-ano-ang-naging-mabuti-sa-mundo-nang-dahil-sa-akin …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Watching "What I see" on @solartvnews ...I never knew your hubby had a show @RoneVG Season 2 pa. I like it    
    
    
    12 Things to leave behind and say hello to this New Year (Part 1 of 2) http://thepoc.net/features/wellness/commentaries/19830-12-things-to-leave-behind-and-say-hello-to-this-new-year-part-1-of-2 …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Cowardice asks the question - is it safe?
Expedience asks the question - is it politic?
Vanity asks the question... http://fb.me/6ykRnX3N3     
    
    
    Watch Keira Knightley show what kills 2 women a week. By @womensaid (via @Upworthy) #VAW #Abuse http://www.upworthy.com/keira-knightley-called-cut-on-this-scene-watch-as-its-a-scene-millions-of-women-recognize-2?g=2&c=ufb2 …    
    
    
    #DreamDareDo Giveaway #1: DREAM-IT-FORWARD http://inspired.ph/?page_id=29     
    
    
    @enjoyglobe, instead of spamming my timeline, pls look into the 21 spam SMS I received for December 2013 http://techiegadgets.com/telecom/presenting-the-december-2013-spam-sms/ …    
    
    
    Presenting the 21 spam SMS for the month of December 2013. The top SMS spammer is the real estate category with... http://fb.me/6mV2uuPK0     
    
    
    @philippinebeat @enjoyglobe Top Spam SMS is from the real estate category followed closely by banks/loans    
    
    
    OMG so fake-looking > Real-life Barbie and Ken, Valeria Lukyanova and Justin Jedlica meet http://bit.ly/14vBw34     
    
    
    5 Tips to Stay Fit After 50 | @scoopit http://sco.lt/4o2rHV     
    
    
    On my recipe blog:  Hot tsokolate From Tablea http://goo.gl/fb/GMuvY     
    
    
    Here is how I prepared Sikwate or hot tsokolate from Tablea, made from 100% premium cacao beans from Davao... http://fb.me/O34MiCxq     
    
    
    Me Time on New Year’s Eve http://www.thepoc.net/features/pinoy-lgbt/19828-me-time-on-new-year-s-eve …  via @thepocnews    
    
    
    what a role model. RT @juanxi: Family at next table: parents on gadgets. Kids no gadgets. Nobody talking.    
    
    
    @juanxi no I don't use gadgets with family    
    
    
    @juanxi I only use it openly when with fellow bloggers lol    
    
    
    Open Letter to P Noy & Pinoys:  Let us Pray for a Rehabilitation Czar of Competence &.. of Unquestionable Integrity http://mail.thepoc.net/component/k2/19827-a-christmas-open-letter-to-p-noy-and-the-filipino-people-let-us-pray-for-a-rehabilitation-czar-of-competence-and-most-of-all-of-unquestionable-integrity …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Let us Pray for a Rehabilitation Czar of Competence & ...of Unquestionable Integrity http://mail.thepoc.net/component/k2/19827-a-christmas-open-letter-to-p-noy-and-the-filipino-people-let-us-pray-for-a-rehabilitation-czar-of-competence-and-most-of-all-of-unquestionable-integrity … by Fr. Robert Reyes #reliefPH    
    
    
        
    
    
    CHR chair: Court decision on Marcos money a ‘lost round’ for Martial Law victims http://shar.es/9c8Uk  via @gmanews    
    
    
    Protect your children from #measles. Is it time to have them vaccinated? If they are 6  to 11 mo old then they... http://fb.me/SDmpmxrd     
    
    
    How to influence Supreme Court justices http://shar.es/9cDrn  , a post originally from @Blogwatchdotph and reposted by @gmanews    
    
    
    It feels good having my daughter over the past two days.    
    
    
    Do you know your basic personality type? Took this test to determine Enneagram type for a strategy planning session http://beautyoverfifty.net/out-of-the-box/discovering-my-enneagram-type/ …    
    
    
    I know! Hello @Jacs_Do_It    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tsk not good > Facebook Sued for Scanning Private Messages http://ti.me/1ds1VEz  via @TIMEBusiness    
    
    
    A juice recipe to help remove Uric Acid Crystalization in joints...Cucumber juice helps bring down body... http://fb.me/V6cdVO90     
    
    
    FYI Parents RT @I_will_flourish: "Children should get two doses of measles vaccine in order for them to have life long immunity,"~DoH.    
    
    
    Planning your 2014 vacations? Here's the list of official holidays for the year 2014 as declared by Malacanang. http://fb.me/RFEIAvPB     
    
    
        
    
    
    Amazing > 71 Going On 40! Meet Raw Foodist Annette Larkins! http://newsone.com/2423703/annette-larkins-raw-food-diet/ …    
    
    
    Annette Larkins credits her meatless diet of more than 40 years for her radiant youthfulness and her physical... http://fb.me/1aWcc6EoE     
    
    
    Interesting read on the Top media stories of 2013 (Part 3) -- Winners and Losers: http://www.medianewser.com/2014/01/trending-top-media-stories-of-2013-part_3.html#.Usf_3RdnUTV.twitter …    
    
    
    Fair & unsensationalized reporting during the #YolandaPH coverage should go to David Santos @SolartvNews team. http://www.medianewser.com/2014/01/trending-top-media-stories-of-2013-part_3.html#.Usf_3RdnUTV.twitter …    
    
    
    #TRENDING: Top media stories of 2013 (Part 1): http://www.medianewser.com/2013/12/trending-top-media-stories-of-2013-part.html#.UsgCHY0SXIQ.twitter …    
    
    
    Think about this: there are children from around the world  risk their lives, just so they can get an education.  http://www.viralnova.com/school-children-risk/ …    
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger  Stories via @blairbitchbunny @mymomfriday @SecondFirsts    
    
    
    On my Tech Blog:  Presenting the December 2013 spam SMS http://goo.gl/fb/WwTB9     
    
    
    #ItsMoreFunInThePhilippines News is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/1326094470 … Stories via @gemkristel    
    
    
        
    
    
    How much spam sms do you receive? I documented mine. 21 spam sms during Dec 2013, all from one telco http://techiegadgets.com/telecom/presenting-the-december-2013-spam-sms/ …    
    
    
    I have been offered to review those juices but I rather make my own with Matstone (masticating type ). Cheaper pa http://beautyoverfifty.net/lifestyle-choices/matstone-juicer-self-healing-power-with-juicing/ …    
    
    
    @dyonisii Oh I listed these spammers in my post.    
    
    
    Daily Mom Tweets is out! http://paper.li/momblogger/mom  Stories via @cuckoo_sing @LisaLadrido @CD_MFO    
    
    
    Manila and Paris, the World’s Culinary Capitals  in the "15 Best Cities in the World" http://shurver.com/travel/15-best-cities-in-the-world/13/ … #itsmorefuninthePhilippines    
    
    
    Been to 7 so 8 more to go > "15 Best Cities in the World" http://fb.me/1jEHpo6Ca     
    
    
    Discovering my Enneagram type via the Riso-Hudson Enneagram Type Indicator (RHETI) Sampler. http://beautyoverfifty.net/out-of-the-box/discovering-my-enneagram-type/ …    
    
    
    Looking beyond the ruins,  a tour of post-quake Bohol  #VisitBohol2014 http://aboutmyrecovery.com/looking-beyond-the-ruins-a-tour-of-post-quake-bohol-visitbohol2014/ … #itsmorefuninthePhilippines    
    
    
        
    
    
    Think about this: there are children from around the world that daily risk their lives, just so they can get an... http://fb.me/3DprM0JLB     
    
    
        
    
    
    Ang pikon , talo. Use mute button. Sharon Cuneta has had enough, leaves Twitter http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/entertainment/01/04/14/sharon-cuneta-has-had-enough-leaves-twitter …    
    
    
    The 37 Most Awkward English Fails You Can Only Find In Asia http://fb.me/1fDLWVmbM     
    
    
    maybe she has other problems…it's not a twitter thing lang RT @razbayas: Yikes, article reads like she takes herself too seriously.    
    
    
    Five Reasons Why You Should Probably Stop Using Antibacterial Soap (with triclosan) http://blogs.smithsonianmag.com/science/2014/01/five-reasons-why-you-should-probably-stop-using-antibacterial-soap/#.UsjlEJj5oic.twitter … via @SmithsonianMag    
    
    
        
    
    
    yes she could. baka twitter break lang RT @FakeJakeShakes: babalik yan... ilang beses na ba nyang sinabi yan?    
    
    
    Very alarming RT @manila_bulletin: Palace alarmed over rising measles cases - Read: http://bit.ly/1cMBUzF     
    
    
    Live simply. Love generously. Speak truthfully. Pray daily. Leave everything else to God. Via. @Inspire_Us    
    
    
        
    
    
    I am sipping hot tsokolate for merienda. My mom often called it SIKWATE!, the Visayan dialect for this drink. http://pinoyfoodblog.com/pinoy-celebrations/noche-buena/hot-chocolate-drink-from-tablea-tsokolate/ …    
    
    
    Brand new resolutions, fashion and wellness goals http://thepoc.net/component/k2/19833-new-year-s-resolutions-for-2014 …  by Alina Co via @thepocnews    
    
    
    Great idea. This Dad Does Incredible Things To His Kids' Lunches Every Day. I Can't Stop Smiling! http://fb.me/2L7pSoL1V     
    
    
    I will have one for  our 30th wedding anniversary in 2015> Best Wedding Photos of 2013 http://huff.to/1dnuZwX  via @HuffPostWedding    
    
    
    thanks. RT @Pontifex: Dear friends, I wish to thank you for the many kind Christmas greetings.  May the Lord bless you all!    
    
    
    This is such a brillant idea for preparing kids' lunches. http://fb.me/6pFela0JD     
    
    
    Woman on PrimeTime- Cucumber juice to remove uric acid crystallization http://goo.gl/fb/wg72D     
    
    
    I prepared Cucumber juice for my husband & myself. My husband loved it but I felt my throat was on fire. You... http://fb.me/35tuNLl4c     
    
    
    Having a cat massage but appalled to see all my belly fats cascading along with each paw massage  https://vine.co/v/hYgKx1Ll2bh     
    
    
        
    
    
    New blog post -  The price of sight: is Lasik worth the cost? http://goo.gl/fb/z43eW     
    
    
    The price of sight: is Lasik worth the cost? http://dlvr.it/4dn4ty     
    
    
        
    
    
    Wonder what these SC justices will decide on DAP. @SagadaSun @ninongboy @peachybrets    
    
    
    Yes Love is powerful > Love Is... (Holy Shit, I Have Cancer) http://huff.to/1dg0Zmt  via @HuffPostWomen    
    
    
    Indeed RT @marketingwizdom:  When faced with a PR disaster, the first three rules of brand rehabilitation are: repent, repent, repent    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Mom Blogger  Daily is out! http://paper.li/momblogger     
    
    
    @PinoyWatcher Do you live in Taguig area? Maybe best to visit the Taguig City hall  @MMDA @MMDAtweets @alanpcayetano    
    
    
    Even in the face of this tragedy, the families constructed this beautiful memorial to never forget what happened. http://www.viralnova.com/i-noticed-this-tiny-thing-on-google-maps-and-when-i-zoomed-in-well-nothing-could-prepare-me/ …    
    
    
    Have American Parents Got It All Backwards? http://fb.me/2Ww75d1qM     
    
    
    Philippines is one of the Top Countries for 2014 #itsmorefuninthePhilippines http://fb.me/3nhHiTCag     
    
    
    ANYARE? | @senatorbinay says measles should have been eliminated by 2008, so what went wrong? http://www.interaksyon.com/article/77999/anyare--sen--binay-says-measles-should-have-been-eliminated-by-2008-so-what-went-wrong …    
    
    
        
    
    
    The State of Social Media 2013 infographic http://pinterest.com/pin/222928250278864937/ …    
    
    
    