@CBSNews Why don't the guys get it.  In prison, having your pants "sagged" means they're available.  Guess these fashionistas are available.    
    
    
    @marisabirns In prison "sagging" means you're available.  Guess he's more than willing    
    
    
    Don't understand people who continuously breed horses for that perfect one. Where's the rest? Tired of the overflow at the feedlots!    
    
    
    Irresponsibility has resulted in the increase in slaughter.  Have you ever seen what really happens to the horses?    
    
    
    Imagine a horse screaming in fear while being dunked in scalding hot water to remove the pelt.  Now keep breeding without a conscience.    
    
    
    @kirstiealley I look forward to your show.  Best times I have watching TV.  Thank you.  Your energy is so welcomed.  I love the laughs    
    
    
    Yahoo... taxes done ahead of time!    
    
    
    @michellemalkin This is suppose to be a grown man running our country and he's an insecure, immature baby blaming others.  Major dilusion    
    
    
    Our latest rescue, 20ish yr old guy who was scheduled to die, has settled in great.  Has his own band.    
    
    
    Hauling our latest rescue back to the ranch we blew the transfer case and had to be towed. Need donations so bad.  Equipment failing    
    
    
    https://www.facebook.com/groups/107715799275906/ … http://fb.me/GsRnUKkQ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/wIzCjBZw     
    
    
    http://wp.me/p1WnJ9-1i  http://fb.me/YDpXZFgy     
    
    
    Never a dull moment -- http://wp.me/p1WnJ9-1l     
    
    
    Feed a Horse for the Holidays http://conta.cc/u3fDzc  via #constantcontact    
    
    
    Candlelight Vigil for our wild horses.  Join us.  Roseburg, Oregon http://wp.me/P1YtOL-D  /via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    "KEEP THEIR LIGHT SHINING"

Our quest to have candlelight vigils in every state to acknowledge the Dec. 15... http://fb.me/1r9h09ExA     
    
    
        
    
    
    Go fund me! http://www.gofundme.com/woofproject  #gofundme    
    
    
    FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE: Despite overwhelming support to keep horse slaughter out of America three legislators have... http://fb.me/G0uR5Npa     
    
    
    The condition of some of these horses still in the care of the Dept of Ag is atrocious http://fb.me/OBRF9XpR     
    
    
        
    
    
    Don't forget our wonderful animals during this holiday season.  They truly give thanks for your supp... http://www.gofundme.com/chillypepper     
    
    
    PLEASE CROSSPOST: This is what is set to start happening at Cumberland County Animal Control in Fayetteville, NC.... http://fb.me/NEI0i3N0     
    
    
        
    
    
    Go fund me! http://www.gofundme.com/b7e6g  #gofundme    
    
    
    Please help us reach our goal.  Chloe is in an oxygen tent and being treated.  Our vet ... http://www.gofundme.com/Help-Chloe--Vet-Bill-Fund …    
    
    
    Chloe has moved out of the O2 tent and appears to be doing a little better but her vet ... http://www.gofundme.com/Help-Chloe--Vet-Bill-Fund …    
    
    
    Great news -- Chloe is back at her foster home with Kelly and resting comfortably.  res... http://www.gofundme.com/Help-Chloe--Vet-Bill-Fund …    
    
    
    Great news -- Chloe is back at her foster home with Kelly and resting comfortably. She'... http://www.gofundme.com/Help-Chloe--Vet-Bill-Fund …    
    
    
    How awesome everyone is.  We are grateful beyond words for the support and donations.  ... http://www.gofundme.com/Help-Chloe--Vet-Bill-Fund …    
    
    
    2/3rds of the way to our goal.  Will be nice to know that Chloe's care is not financial... http://www.gofundme.com/Help-Chloe--Vet-Bill-Fund …    
    
    
    $675 short of reaching our goal and making sure that Chloe's expenses are covered.  Tha... http://www.gofundme.com/Help-Chloe--Vet-Bill-Fund …    
    
    
    Because of you, she is recovering and feeling better    
    
    
    HELP... I've been asked to help place these horses. The woman that owns them has lost the use of the property and... http://fb.me/1mTJiySQ6     
    
    
    Thank you all for the donations and continued support of the Woof Project.  Without you... http://www.gofundme.com/Help-Chloe--Vet-Bill-Fund …    
    
    
    http://fb.me/PP7nmWU9     
    
    
    Rescue world suffers tragic loss with morning fatality http://fb.me/1H3cboEsp     
    
    
    Won't you please help us get her vet bills covered and return a favor to someone who sacrificed f... http://www.gofundme.com/Ancis-vet-bill     
    
    
    What an absolute blessing!!!  Thank you "anonymous" for the generous donation.  We are just short ... http://www.gofundme.com/Ancis-vet-bill     
    
    
    Looks like we've gotten a final count for Anci's vet bills and have raised our goal to $3500.  Thi... http://www.gofundme.com/Ancis-vet-bill     
    
    
        
    
    
    Action Alert: National Protest Day for Wild Horses http://fb.me/1rgAt9wav     
    
    
    Hi All - Reminder time. We need your help. Please vote.
Visit this link. Click on the first link Click Here to... http://fb.me/1kZaZRtqm     
    
    
    http://fb.me/12UEDY5Ti     
    
    
    Dogs Fall Ill As Owners, Vets and Lawmakers Blame Treats from China http://fb.me/1VAg394GE     
    
    
    Get Wild Horse Slaughter Advocate Off BLM Board! http://fb.me/1As3VUcc0     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1es1gIuNU     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1KSpsYxAz     
    
    
    http://fb.me/V15rvXdS     
    
    
    Horse rescuers expand the scope of their efforts http://fb.me/1c7zC8n3H     
    
    
    Saving America's Horses 15 Things http://fb.me/1uYPmyw7e     
    
    
    ChipIn: Help Keno Beat Cancer http://fb.me/Wu9Rt9o7     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1VAylQilx     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1iMih0YQg     
    
    
    Diamond Naturals Dog Food Variety Recalled http://fb.me/1dcmiKw9O     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1FSQJQfbp     
    
    
    @1stLdyAnnRomney As a career mom & the opportunity to be a stay at home mom - give me a career anytime.  Stay at home is more work.    
    
    
    @1stLdyAnnRomney You are a class act and thank you for speaking for us.  We look forward to you being the First Lady    
    
    
    We did it!! http://fb.me/1pBMSJj0u     
    
    
    I just updated my Weebly website, check it out! http://www.whisperingwindsanimalsanctuary.org/  via @weebly    
    
    
    KENO UPDATE. The vet called me a few minutes ago. The biopsy came back as a hemangiopericytoma tumor. The r... http://www.gofundme.com/j4kyc     
    
    
    Working on our latest horse abuse case.  Waiting on charges to be filed.  http://m.siskiyoudaily.com/svc/wlws.svc/getHtml#article/?sectionId=1459&feedId=1922&articleId=3942453 …    
    
    
    Yearling horse buried alive.  http://m.siskiyoudaily.com/svc/wlws.svc/getHtml#article/?sectionId=1459&feedId=1922&articleId=3942453 …    
    
    
    Keno had to make a trip back to the vet, where they sedated him, cleaned the wound, put in a drain & restit... http://www.gofundme.com/j4kyc     
    
    
    Check it out! I am helping Help Keno Beat Cancer http://www.gofundme.com/j4kyc     
    
    
    K Dog made another visit to the vet today to have his drain removed.  He is not happy with the his new 24/7... http://www.gofundme.com/j4kyc     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1UMk0gVyV     
    
    
    REPOST:

Millions of computers worldwide are set to lose internet access after july 9.   Sounds like a crazy... http://fb.me/IWmv6SWl     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://fb.me/1TeWBX2vI     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1m3xJBaW4     
    
    
    My birthday wish http://fnd.us/c/aJEH8  via @FundRazr    
    
    
    Charlie's Big Adventure http://conta.cc/NGuJwL  http://fb.me/1WW2PNLp7     
    
    
    http://www.whisperingwindsanimalsanctuary.org/available-for-adoption.html … http://fb.me/S6kkpvJM     
    
    
    http://www.whisperingwindsanimalsanctuary.org/mustangs-needing-placement.html … http://fb.me/1TKKpIBiz     
    
    
    Care to share a cup?  Click on the link for details. http://fb.me/19hBqq25A     
    
    
    @ChaseGiving Would love to see Whispering Winds Equine Rescue & Sanctuary entered  #InOnTheGiving http://bit.ly/MrSmEr  #InOnTheGiving    
    
    
    I just updated my website. http://www.whisperingwindsanimalsanctuary.org     
    
    
        
    
    
    Help us Raise the Barn http://fb.me/VgXQ0qgK     
    
    
    "My Mane Friend"  Photo Contest 
Jul 1st - Oct 1st
  
http://bit.ly/12YVa7    
    
    
    Horse photo contest fundraiser underway.  visit http://bit.ly/12YVa7
 for details    
    
    
    Nevada Dept of Ag's wild horse scam  http://bit.ly/12jFCh    
    
    
    2 out of 3 ain't bad - http://eepurl.com/qAqrj     
    
    
    http://eepurl.com/qAqrj     
    
    
    The Nevada AG's office is starting to take notice.  Please view the video and call 775-684-1100    
    
    
    @FindFreebies remove me please    
    
    
    Find out what is going on in Nevada regarding the wild horses.  http://bit.ly/2LEWLc    
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop online through http://iGive.com !... http://fb.me/1YYPoFwoM     
    
    
    Overturn The Legalization of Horse Slaughter for Human Consumption http://www.change.org/petitions/overturn-the-legalization-of-horse-slaughter-for-human-consumption?share_id=GkfRZrwwqs&utm_campaign=action_box&utm_medium=twitter&utm_source=share_petition&utm_source=share_petition&utm_medium=twitter … via @change    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/13ucVf via @addthis  Enter your photos in  My Mane Friend Photo Contest. Winners determined by votes SO DON'T FORGET TO VOTE    
    
    
    TOMORROW, July 14th as this is a very important day for our horses.    
    
    
    The link below will give you all the info you. http://bit.ly/18QF00    
    
    
    Also, be sure when you call please ask for support of H.R.1018, the ROAM Act (Restoring Our American Mustang).    
    
    
    I just updated my website. http://www.whisperingwindsanimalsanctuary.org     
    
    
    Horses needing forever homes - http://eepurl.com/q6RBL     
    
    
    Please help us speak up for the wild horses.  It's easy to do.
http://bit.ly/19Ts5u    
    
    
    @360PhotoContest  Hi.  Would you please promote our Photo Contest too?  Thanks.Whispering Winds Equine Rescue    
    
    
    Speak Up for the Wild Horses -- http://bit.ly/19Ts5u    
    
    
    We lost our son yesterday.  He was a great help here at the ranch and I'm going to miss him desperately.

In lieu... http://fb.me/1xNudKN1Z     
    
    
    Checking out http://bit.ly/8VoHg    
    
    
    Heading to Reno tomorrow.  Be sure to sign the petition for the horses http://bit.ly/19Ts5u    
    
    
    @horsestolove check out http://bit.ly/rV4JD    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/bGdt9    
    
    
    Help save a wild horse herd. Voting only costs $1 per vote & goes directly to help feed, care for, & protect these beautiful horses.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/12YVa7    
    
    
    Vote for your favorite horse photo & help feed wild horses    http://bit.ly/12YVa7    
    
    
    Praising God for another great day.  Our 7 girls are heading to, or should be at, their new homes.  Tomorrow I... http://fb.me/1R8B3U3NH     
    
    
    In support of my sisters http://fb.me/1vFtKknfM     
    
    
    http://fb.me/TvEshLRp     
    
    
        
    
    
    Just want to share -- the other day I was having my quiet time and reading my daily devotional. This struck me... http://fb.me/1wKJzr1Ee     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1OAV90I5o     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1PMCD9k2h     
    
    
    Please put this as your status for at least 1 hour if you or someone you know has an invisible illness ( Crohn's,... http://fb.me/1sq8ypF6M     
    
    
    SPECIAL REQUEST -- I'm looking for a forever home for a 16 yr old TB mare, daughter of Derby winner Sunny's Halo.... http://fb.me/VL5fuckm     
    
    
    All you have to do is like & share http://fb.me/1W7q1Qn9T     
    
    
    Beautiful sunset coming in to Portland.  Looking forward to down time with my family http://fb.me/2IsDXCT2N     
    
    
    Amen http://fb.me/zcrLflTE     
    
    
    Finally...after a couple setbacks we are headed to California.  Come on sunshine!!    
    
    
    Check out this cloud we saw coming through Mt Shasta.  God is amazing http://fb.me/1V3Xkm7UI     
    
    
    praising God for a gracious trip.  Horses delivered and heading back to the yucky rain.  Taking our time and my... http://fb.me/2fiuirpKf     
    
    
    After a week long road trip with my sister hauling her horses, we've had some down time in Portland with our other... http://fb.me/wC8NCMga     
    
    
    Anyone in the Pacific Northwest have room for a retired senior gelding?  Owner needs to find a place as soon as possible.    
    
    
    TAGGING & CAUSES -- Hi all.  I need to ask a favor and request that you NOT tag me or send me "causes" petitions.... http://fb.me/2BLdX97I1     
    
    
    This is my beautiful sister, Becky, and her horses that we took to CA recently.  She is my hero and inspiration,... http://fb.me/1W32X1cap     
    
    
    This is my beautiful sister, Becky, and her horses that we took to CA recently. She is my hero and inspiration,... http://fb.me/KHsJl7Co     
    
    
    Lifelong horse lovers, we have some awesome memories of all of us as kids.  I'm working on an album to honor my... http://fb.me/2hFIBKI07     
    
    
    Been kind of under the weather and in bed today.  But, that doesn't stop my buddy from begging!  I didn't see the... http://fb.me/18xqttRUY     
    
    
        
    
    
    Back in the Portland area and having a National Geographics afternoon at my granddaughters.  Her mom bought a... http://fb.me/zdCWslVi     
    
    
    National Geographics Day at the Gonzales home. This is how we entertained ourselves this afternoon. I don't think... http://fb.me/CcTSVb1T     
    
    
    As most of you know, our son committed suicide just before the past holidays.  The memory of what I saw when I... http://fb.me/1noKCoRIb     
    
    
    As most of you know, our son committed suicide just before the past holidays. The memory of what I saw when I... http://fb.me/1yQzOZU0D     
    
    
    Although I will not get involved in any drama situations, despite whomever it is, I will, from time to time, pass... http://fb.me/2ec7yXNWL     
    
    
    Had a great time paddling on the river this morning with my sister. Soaking wet and sore shoulders but wouldn't... http://fb.me/1WE5dD93K     
    
    
    One more star will shine bright in Heaven tonight.  My sister passed away this morning.  Thank you for all the... http://fb.me/2MyjJ3xR3     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    WOW.  This is how my days have been since my son's death and now my sister's.  I need to pin this picture on my... http://fb.me/2ialE1BAV     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    Remodeling is coming along great.  Almost done with the inside of the house and then will get going outside.... http://fb.me/1qpC0xJIX     
    
    
    I love this and had to repost. http://fb.me/2q55Tza9l     
    
    
    Praise God! http://fb.me/2kSO42yQK     
    
    
    Hi All
It's been a while, and not quite ready to release our new adventure, but it's getting close and we're... http://fb.me/2hC7FqzZY     
    
    
    Dear Forest Trails - Since you choose to monitor our activity and want to continue to try to discredit us... http://fb.me/2zEnztO8v     
    
    
    For those of you who might have wondered where we have gone, or how we are doing - here's a brief update:  After... http://fb.me/14zKrG2Bg     
    
    
    http://fb.me/BXgWuMqA     
    
    
    WOW Reba looks great!  She'll always be one of my top favorites.  CMA is such a good way to slow my day    
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    What an absolutely great day!!  Coming out of the laundry room I glanced out at the horses in the pasture to see... http://fb.me/2mVtnxChZ     
    
    
    What an absolutely great day!! Coming out of the laundry room I glanced out at the horses in the pasture to see 7... http://fb.me/2AxBQesqp     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2yTQXaYgd     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://fb.me/1FvlFuEyK     
    
    
    LA Animal Services
New Hope Blue Alert - Dogs in Need of Extra Medical Help

http://www.LAAnimalServices.com  http://fb.me/1FlE61xcx     
    
    
    Anyone see the shirt Keith Urban is wearing on American Idol tonight??? MUSTANG -- Love it    
    
    
    God's message to you today:  

Be careful not to complain about anything, even the weather, since I am the Author... http://fb.me/AG0tEJRs     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
        
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    Please help Portland Police keep this great unit going.  Seems the protestors don't like having them around... http://fb.me/28OU9tHgu     
    
    
    http://eepurl.com/zi4IX     
    
    
    PLEASE SHARE AND SEE IF WE CAN SAVE THIS GUY: Kimo is located in Salem/Keizer Oregon. I am trying to help a friend... http://fb.me/AkLnmNjS     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    We're getting a check for $10.03 from iGive.  Please help us by joining for free at http://www.iGive.com/TWger0 . #iGiveDoYou    
    
    
    PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE do your due diligence when surrendering any animal to a rescue.... http://fb.me/2jCOQUDaz     
    
    
    NW OREGON -- http://fb.me/1gV11OuHz     
    
    
    Please take action on this simple request and sample letter that covers these talking points.

CCCdA Inc is an IRS... http://fb.me/Mq7Q5gCM     
    
    
    Please sign at the link below & post far & wide:... http://fb.me/1wAf0FYnX     
    
    
    Heading to the coast for a Women's Retreat this weekend.  Looking forward to my quiet time and spiritual... http://fb.me/2Mm4pLedr     
    
    
    @Jodiannarias  From  those of us that r true victims of domestic violence, shame on u 4 trying to cash in. UR the victimizer, not the victim    
    
    
    @Jodiannarias .  I  will  encourage non-profits to turn a deaf ear to you.  You glamorize the  pain  those of us have truly suffered    
    
    
    How heartbreaking.  Please, continue to pray for all of those that have been affected. http://fb.me/TKlFNb0o     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2lQYTL3RT     
    
    
    OK PRAYER WARRIORS -- A door may have opened for us but we need to be sure it is of God.  Please stand with us in... http://fb.me/1Jemx1kpG     
    
    
    Our little Carson that wasn't suppose to make it through the night turned 4 last month.  He now has his own band,... http://fb.me/SjSDHuda     
    
    
    http://fb.me/R5Es1Pg3     
    
    
    speaks volumes of the kind of area we live in.  Oh my http://fb.me/2KxEd7ePa     
    
    
    Thank you for all you did, John.  You inspired so many 2 legged and are the hero of so many 4 legged.  You will be... http://fb.me/z1O6wF4R     
    
    
    To all those that are continuously under spiritual warfare against those that have nothing better to do than... http://fb.me/25IsHpqWy     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    Well, it's time.  Please help by sharing.  We have some cleanup left to do and it's time to close this chapter. http://fb.me/2E2BJj119     
    
    
    Do you recognize this dog? She was found by Mustang Animal Control in Mustang, OK with a severe injury to her... http://fb.me/2DuVUvxTp     
    
    
    It's a never ending battle.  They won't be happy until all the horses are gone.  My heart aches. http://fb.me/2vHXyeSAV     
    
    
    Well, it's official. The property is now on the market. I've loaded almost all the photos (take a look =) ) Will... http://fb.me/xyReT6dF     
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    Amanda -- Praising God for your good news today.  Prayers are far more effective than gossip and slander.  So... http://fb.me/2I5jhM5UO     
    
    
        
    
    
    Turns out that I've had a covered arena this whole time and we've used it for hay, stalls, & storage.  So....hay... http://fb.me/1OWmH20k5     
    
    
    CATHY ATKINSON TROPE " or rescues that are STILL IN BUSINESS (called Whispering Winds) that have had horses for... http://fb.me/2HbiHsUIm     
    
    
    We are so blessed to have friends like you. http://fb.me/6ilMPshUX     
    
    
    OK, all you engineering minds...how is this stairwell constructed??? http://fb.me/1OgjarMQZ     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0a-aV0Rsxmg … http://fb.me/1I903ZBbD     
    
    
    Delays are as much a part of God's plan as answered prayers. He wants you to trust him...  Pastor Rick Warren    
    
    
    Check out "MAY THEY SEE YOU" by Tracy Creech - http://www.reverbnation.com/tracycreech/song/17586038-may-they-see-you …    
    
    
    Help Whispering Winds Animal Sanctuary Hay Drive every time you shop: http://www.iGive.com/QaoRk7Z     
    
    
    http://eepurl.com/ATAJT     
    
    
    This morning, as I started with blurry eyes, I heard a voice (yup, get them in my head all the time!) that said -... http://fb.me/2jDQ3l7Np     
    
    
    Americans Against Horse Slaughter Members Speak Out! - http://shar.es/P57E    
    
    
    Have 4 mares (3 mustangs) needing homes.  If you can help, let me know.  If not, please be sure to forward.  Thank... http://fb.me/XhP6AHHd     
    
    
        
    
    
    Granny says THANK YOU to those that have donated and support our efforts. 

Granny Goose (as we call her) ... http://www.gofundme.com/41aat4     
    
    
    Just a few of our senior citizens enjoying life at Whispering Winds.  

Please help us meet our hay budget... http://www.gofundme.com/41aat4     
    
    
    http://eepurl.com/FF_w5  It'a Blanket Time!    
    
    
    Urgent-Click/Send Comments Needed for CA's Massacre Lakes Wild Horses by Fri, 9/27/13: http://tinyurl.com/lw2zo2l     
    
    
    It's Blanket Time  http://eepurl.com/FF_w5     
    
    
    With the Holidays approaching, many of you may do your shopping online.You can help us every time you shop. It's Free http://www.igive.com/svmz6Gp     
    
    
    Ahhhh.  Facebook has made a mess of our page.  Please spread the word and come to our new page - Whispering Winds Equine Sanctuary.    
    
    
    The same day mustangs are removed, 1000's of cattle are driven onto range.... http://fb.me/6mtmT8t6i     
    
    
    Natomas needs a home.  Read her info here.  If you can help, contact Linda Horn.  Thank you.

REPOSTING  She's... http://fb.me/3gM71Qnpf     
    
    
    How many of you are being scammed by the new "Obamacare?"  You don't get your same doctor or insurance, as... http://fb.me/10HfVk5NV     
    
    
        
    
    
    Rescued Neglected Horse Set to Compete in Equestrian Event

A neglected and near-starved horse that was rescued... http://fb.me/2nDKAitRI     
    
    
    Retired Racehorses Show Off New Skills at Pimlico

Governor Jack, a former racehorse, cantered smoothly and... http://fb.me/6GqJBNzuP     
    
    
    Rescue Horse Rehomed With Paralyzed Driver

Rocky came to the Horse Trust with his mother, Rose, as a skinny 2... http://fb.me/16XunyzyF     
    
    
    CAN YOU HELP JUST A LITTLE???
Here is the PayPal link for Meade Canine Rescue who rescued Mr. Happy.  He is going... http://fb.me/XokqkYXF     
    
    
    Hi all

Please like our new page at Whispering Winds Equine Sanctuary.  FB made a lot of changes on this one that... http://fb.me/MTSIhSx9     
    
    
    Anyone who knows about the endless fight in Nevada against the Dept of Ag and the gathering of the wild ones,... http://fb.me/2piVjdNoX     
    
    
    COMPLETELY UNACCEPTABLE- THIS EQUALS DILIBERT ABUSE AND CRULTY TO ANIMALS 

Make your calls to your... http://fb.me/2WxjkhXhe     
    
    
    COMPLETELY UNACCEPTABLE- THIS EQUALS DILIBERT ABUSE AND CRULTY TO ANIMALS 

Make your calls to your... http://fb.me/2RxyS5GJ0     
    
    
    REPOSTING.  Anyone have room for this precious??? http://fb.me/ZwVlsrKO     
    
    
    Funniest thing I've heard in a long time.  Doggone granddaughter now has me signing this non stop!!! http://fb.me/2rOeZOKdN     
    
    
    URGENT! Old & COLD Doxie needs transport- fresno to Atascadero or close
This dog is a senior and REALLY needs to... http://fb.me/L7aI2KnS     
    
    
    Oh my.  I haven't laughed this hard in forever.  Here's a little pre-Halloween humor http://fb.me/6pBKz0UC4     
    
    
    REPOSTING -- BAY AREA - 2 DONKEYS NEEDING HOME IMMEDIATELY:  --Both donkeys are about 11 HH. about 42 in. to... http://fb.me/21rXS2X1L     
    
    
    How about filling out just a few more Christmas cards this holiday season and let our vets know we appreciate... http://fb.me/VH3rrdHh     
    
    
    Important information http://fb.me/ZjXvFv8u     
    
    
    Important information.  Click on link to read http://fb.me/SwSgfSdT     
    
    
    November 1, 2013,” Bailey'™s Choice Dog Treats LLC of Waleska, Georgia, is recalling certain packages of dog... http://fb.me/10xDkGhV9     
    
    
    @FoxFriendsFirst http://misguidedchildren.com/veterans-affairs/2013/11/obama-to-force-military-families-away-from-tricare-by-tripling-their-fees …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just a reminder.  Help brighten a soldier's holiday and tell them Thank You http://fb.me/6rBb8IosV     
    
    
    Don’t Give it Up!

TODAY’S SCRIPTURE
“A joyful heart is good medicine, but a crushed spirit dries up the bones.”... http://fb.me/ZnNS1GoM     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/3kG2S6Mu3     
    
    
    UPDATE: Virginia Range Wild Horses, Rescued Thanks to AWHPC Supporters, Begin New Life!

Today, we are happy to... http://fb.me/1tiwu7apo     
    
    
    ACTION

Urge Senate Committee to Reject Grazing Act That's Bad for Wild Horses

The public land ranching industry... http://fb.me/1Hm5L9YOs     
    
    
    President Obama Nominates Neil Kornze to Head the BLM

President Obama has nominated Nevada native Neil Kornze as... http://fb.me/2PfL4ZHIo     
    
    
    AMERICAN MUSTANG PREMIERES IN NOVEMBER 2013 http://fb.me/PK0o6ELy     
    
    
    TODAY’S SCRIPTURE
“Now we who have believed enter that rest...”
(Hebrews 4:3, NIV)

God desires for you to live... http://fb.me/3mJgBSsH6     
    
    
    REPOSTING -- EMERGENCY TRANSPORT FOR HORSE NEEDED  Contact betsybueno@aol.com :

Ive have been contacted by a Dog... http://fb.me/6Cer0kXL5     
    
    
    TODAY’S SCRIPTURE
“Can all your worries add a single moment to your life?”
(Matthew 6:27, NLT)

God doesn’t want... http://fb.me/2zYUNqQse     
    
    
    Sign & Share.  Help make a difference and stop horse slaughter in New Mexico http://fb.me/2x3EnBZUm     
    
    
    Well, yesterday marked 1 year since our son, Steve, went to heaven.  It's been a rough up & down year, but God has... http://fb.me/UMJYN7qb     
    
    
    heaven. It's been a rough up & down year, but God has held me up and Jesus has walked by my side the entire way.... http://fb.me/2KZC1ZdSV     
    
    
        
    
    
    HAPPY SATURDAY!

TODAY'S PRAYER -- 

Dear God
Today I am thinking of people who are on the wrong path,... http://fb.me/2Mjl5TOE5     
    
    
        
    
    
    I just updated my website. http://www.whisperingwindsanimalsanctuary.org     
    
    
    Whispering Winds Ranch http://fb.me/1bI05HtMM     
    
    
    PROPERTY FOR SALE: http://fb.me/MDd2GINU     
    
    
    TODAY’S SCRIPTURE 

“The Lord will fight for you, and you shall hold your peace and remain at rest.” 
(Exodus... http://fb.me/1OcaYgKkR     
    
    
    This is my precious, beautiful cousin from Mexico City.  She and her husband are very involved in caring for... http://fb.me/1e4uMabwS     
    
    
    She also does modeling http://fb.me/35sM33BLX     
    
    
    This is my precious, beautiful cousin from Mexico City. She and her husband are very involved in caring for... http://fb.me/1xriLYhF9     
    
    
    Take heart. God is going to show you joy like you've never seen. #TodaysWord @Victoria Osteen @JoelOsteen http://tinyurl.com/ktkna3n     
    
    
    TODAY’S SCRIPTURE
“Be imitators of God, therefore, as dearly loved children and live a life of love, just as... http://fb.me/2UyLpMYV9     
    
    
    I was getting very used to this unusually warm winter weather where it rained at night and sun shone all day.... http://fb.me/31RgFDt2E     
    
    
    When life seems to be dealing you nothing but hard times, try looking for one good thing in the situation and... http://fb.me/30DE2eFp2     
    
    
        
    
    
    If you are considering a pet as a gift, please adopt.  Check out these precious souls at the LA County Shelter.... http://fb.me/2DKn0SH82     
    
    
    Tips to ensure that your horse heals as quickly as possible.

First Aid Kit100By Andrea Caudill of The American... http://fb.me/V3nOtdlZ     
    
    
    Today is International Survivors of Suicide Day. 
Every 40 seconds someone in the World dies by suicide
Every 41... http://fb.me/2xc64RL0D     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/OKcRYzrB     
    
    
    http://www.upworthy.com/the-most-hilarious-parody-video-ive-seen-yet-what-does-the-farmer-say …    
    
    
    Check this out.  Too funny

http://www.upworthy.com/the-most-hilarious-parody-video-ive-seen-yet-what-does-the-farmer-say …    
    
    
    If you're thinking of a new pet this year, please consider adopting. http://fb.me/13qoIhEGZ     
    
    
    Life is 10% of what happens to you, and 90% of how you respond.    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6sWeY1TSW     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/3nIi6X0cH     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6t3QExaR0     
    
    
    Tom & I headed to the local Mission today to deliver a couple boxes of food we got for them.  There should be... http://fb.me/3nWfEs3Xl     
    
    
        
    
    
    The unnamed angels who appear most often in Scripture carry out a variety of tasks—all designed to serve God…... http://fb.me/20JxA0ltQ     
    
    
    I used to be a body builder up to 7 years ago when we moved to Roseburg and I let everything go.  So to change... http://fb.me/1DRXsY48M     
    
    
    After such a long trip, all the way from Louisiana and Marion, TX, are we going to be stuck in Los Angeles? A... http://fb.me/14f91D9jO     
    
    
    Today my wonderful son would have been 42.  I would have called him on the phone and shared the day I went into... http://fb.me/OFyANZTr     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving Everyone.  Hope you all have a great day with friends and family.  Please remember our... http://fb.me/1X1u9qlP9     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/14dWJanon     
    
    
    Happy Hanukka to all our Jewish friends http://fb.me/2xjXrEb8D     
    
    
    Stopped to get a bite to eat after hitting the gym, and I got busted!  Needless to say, her shame on me look... http://fb.me/NYxhCy2I     
    
    
    Please join us this Tuesday.  2 beautiful handmade walking sticks will be given away http://fb.me/1yvptydNA     
    
    
    Oops.  Was gone for a week when this storm moved in & didn't get a change to cut my roses back.  They're all... http://fb.me/13FaaPjYp     
    
    
    Oops. Was gone for a week when this storm moved in & didn't get a change to cut my roses back. They're all stuck... http://fb.me/1K1Ytx9EL     
    
    
    I was up at McChord AFB (Tacoma, WA) this past week.  It was cold cold cold, but no snow.  Some friends of mine... http://fb.me/342hWbXNK     
    
    
    I was up at McChord AFB (Tacoma, WA) working this past week. It was cold cold cold, but no snow. Some friends of... http://fb.me/2v2CkCnG8     
    
    
    If anyone would like to donate and help the horses we have rescued, and get in your year-end tax deduction, feel... http://fb.me/6r3oSpeNj     
    
    
    Whispering Winds Equine Sanctuary is a 501c3 non-profit organization and home for many rescued mustang and... http://fb.me/2GrCLSaEh     
    
    
    Whispering Winds Equine Sanctuary is a 501c3 non-profit organization and home for many rescued mustang and... http://fb.me/15xWcVflx     
    
    
    Please share... http://fb.me/2HTVQXgBk     
    
    
    PLEASE SIGN & SHARE:  This is outrageous. Phil Robertson has a right to his opinion. He made statements about how... http://fb.me/3we1HvBxA     
    
    
    OREGON -- Do you know this horse? If he was dumped, shame on you!  If he got out & lost, contact them to claim him http://fb.me/6CcQrFl5X     
    
    
    Mustangs on the Hill-Sept. 29th on the West Front Lawn of Capitol Hill 2 support the ROAM ACT-Save our Wild Horses http://tinyurl.com/owmq43    
    
    
    As we enter into this week of worshiping the Lord on His birthday, we would like to wish you all a Merry... http://fb.me/2xI6B3rW7     
    
    
    As we enter into this week of worshiping the Lord on His birthday, we would like to wish you all a Merry... http://fb.me/1ZjkQxqQm     
    
    
    Wow!!  6933 likes. What a great year. Would love to hit 7000 before it's over    
    
    
    We hope you all had a great Christmas with family and friends.  As we head into the New Year we are excited the... http://fb.me/16Egcj9Cu     
    
    
    We hope you all had a great Christmas with family and friends. As we head into the New Year we are excited the... http://fb.me/22URF47Aw     
    
    
    HEALTH TIP FOR THIS WEEK:
Many of us enjoy a nice cup of warm tea on a winter day but did you know that some of... http://fb.me/2BTH2NZi2     
    
    
    PLEASE HELP -- PERMISSION TO CROSSPOST.  Argo is a sweet deaf dog that is looking for a couple more people to... http://fb.me/6BTTN40sy     
    
    
    As we approach the end of this year, I wanted to share this with you. Thank you all for your support this past... http://fb.me/SsphKRv3     
    
    
    Check this out.  It is so awesome! http://fb.me/2xiu21IkY     
    
    
    2014 is the Year of the Horse - Happy New Year and prayers for many blessings.

Predictions for 2014 Year of... http://fb.me/1ji4HJLpB     
    
    
    Here's our first selfies of the year. Shoney came in to wish everyone a Happy New Year and couldn't resist the... http://fb.me/2dYrJoqrY     
    
    
    Here's our first selfy of the year. Shoney came in to wish everyone a Happy New Year and couldn't resist the... http://fb.me/3cde9EnIv     
    
    
    FAREWELL 2013.... http://fb.me/18Vnote0J     
    
    
    2014 Here we come.... http://fb.me/O4DyqUqU     
    
    
    TRANSPORT HELP NEEDED!  Austin, TX to Aberdeen, WA
Jan 11/12 and 18/19
 Permission to Crosspost

 CONTACT... http://fb.me/Y9KNwgGS     
    
    
        
    
    
    Walmart Finds Something Disturbing In Its Donkey Meat http://fb.me/1TbqknMYF     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1YBji1LP0     
    
    
    Sponsor A Horse for the Holidays  www.whisperingwindsequinerescue.com    
    
    
    Wild horse round up gathers nationwide protests  http://bit.ly/4ylJ5r    
    
    
    http://www.examiner.com/examiner/x-25094-LA-Equine-Policy-Examiner~y2009m12d29-Wild-horse-roundup-gathers-nationwide-protests    
    
    
    