Stress Relief from Simple Pleasures http://www.bella-vitawellness.com/stress-relief-from-simple-pleasures …    
    
    
    I wish you Enough - saying good bye  http://www.bella-vitawellness.com/i-wish-you-enough …    
    
    
    I wish you Enough http://shar.es/HI85U    
    
    
    Stress Overload: How do you Cope? http://shar.es/HOEfW     
    
    
    Lower Produce Prices Prompt Increased Junk Food Purchases http://shar.es/XWI3X     
    
    
    A Season of Giving…..a Need for Help http://shar.es/XWIjh     
    
    
    Ruby for Women - A Voice for Every Christian Woman http://rubyforwomen.ning.com/  A beautiful and inspiring website - please do visit and "like" it.    
    
    
    Invest in me on Empire Avenue, the Social Stock Market, EmpireAvenue.com, where I am currently trading at 30.36e! http://empireavenue.com/SHARONWEGNER     
    
    
    @GreenMamasPad Thanks for the follow - I'd love to connect on Facebook. See you there.    
    
    
    Study Says Even Being a Bit Overweight Is Risky. How much IS a bit?    
    
    
    Are We Over-snacking Our Kids and turning them into mindless munchkins?    
    
    
    Child Nutrition Bill Passes! : Slow Food USA http://www.slowfoodusa.org/index.php/slow_food/blog_post/child_nutrition_bill_passes/ … via @AddThis    
    
    
    If you haven't seen the documentary - click here to get a glimpse  Fat, Sick & Nearly Dead Extended Trailer http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gv3vEXy_EwU&feature=share …    
    
    
    #arealchange It's time! she's on the call now.    
    
    
    Just got kicked out online #arealchange    
    
    
    Back on the hot line with @sandikrakowsi and PJ #arealchange    
    
    
    If you know it’s going to help build your business, but you start questioning yourself. #arealchange    
    
    
    Attract all of the people who resonate with your gift and to repel everyone else #arealchange    
    
    
    @mamastreasures Hi Nina - excellent call tonight. Glad we connected.    
    
    
    #arealchange Let go of the past and the people who have hurt you. Amen    
    
    
    #arealchange Being a perfectionist is not the sign of a successful business owner. "Fear is nothing more than the absence of belief" PJ    
    
    
    #arealchange - Live in the belief zone    
    
    
    #arealchange  belief helps you find your limitation    
    
    
    #arealchange - do you lack vision? Allow yourself to flow and visualize what you want your life to be like. What does your life look like?    
    
    
    #arealchange - send the light, send them love and leave it!    
    
    
    I'm reading "war of art" by Steven Pressfield. What are you reading?    
    
    
    When stress seems to be getting the best of you, how do you spell relief?    
    
    
    My all time comfort food is rice pudding http://ow.ly/1wpm0o  what's your go to comfort food?    
    
    
    Take a 30 walk today or watch a funny movie and enjoy a good laugh. Fresh sir and laughter are "good medicine".    
    
    
    My husband's favorite quote-"SFOTG". Any idea what that means?    
    
    
    I'd love to hear what you are doing to improve your health and wellness today.    
    
    
    #arealchange - Here we go again. Another dynamic call with Sandi and PJ. woohoo a FREE ipod!    
    
    
    #arealchange - Charlotte just wond a free ipod! You go girl    
    
    
    #arealchange vision and clarity goes back to attraction and repulsion.    
    
    
    #arealchange - if you continue to grow, you have to continue to get clear. re-assess your vision.    
    
    
    #arealchange - Resistance will tell you anything to prevent you from doing your work - Steven Pressfield    
    
    
    #arealchange - stop looking at your competitors and stop answering negative emails. oh yes!    
    
    
    #arealchange - What if?    
    
    
    @CharlotteSiems Good for you!    
    
    
    #arealchange - be honest with yourself about what you are doing with your time. Cut the drama and don't waste time. Time=money.    
    
    
    #arealchange - This IS my job. I am very serious about what I do.    
    
    
    #arealchange - Are you willing to do whatever it takes? Will you do anything to provide for your family?    
    
    
    #arealchange - I will work 30 hours per week and whatever comes will come. I will not jeopardize my health or my family.    
    
    
    Lu    
    
    
    #arealchange - Don't  just pull a set of numbers out of the air and try to start building a life around it.    
    
    
    #arealchange - "no thank you, that doesn't fit into my business plan this year"    
    
    
    #arealchange - I do what I do to share what I know and to make a difference. I have faith that the money will come.    
    
    
    #arealchange - @SandiKrakowski - you are speaking to my friend, Diane who lives with pain everyday, she just found faith.    
    
    
    #arealchange - my computer crashed and I just got back onto the call. Loving this group, Sandi and PJ.    
    
    
    #arealchange - I am a little bit challenged and looking for the clarity to find focus    
    
    
    #arealchange - Love Brendon  Burchard.    
    
    
    #arealchange - Love the War of Art. That little book speaks right to my soul.    
    
    
    #arealchange - my phone died:(    
    
    
    @angelabrooks - for real. the darn phone just died on me.    
    
    
    @angelabrooks I've had a whole lot of that lately, but I'm shaking it off and moving on.    
    
    
    End of summer already and holiday decorations are coming out already.    
    
    
    Sometimes Enough is All You Need http://shar.es/HF6BM     
    
    
    Thanks @DawnWilkerson. No more tweets to Facebook.    
    
    
    For those of you who got blasted my random comments from me the other day - I am so very sorry. I have fixed the e... http://on.fb.me/n1aI8P     
    
    
    Good night friends. It's been a long day and I'm ready for a cup of herbal tea. Until tomorrow...    
    
    
    Are you on Twellow? Check out my listing and register yourself also! http://twellow.com/sharonwegner     
    
    
    Good morning! Any good plans for the weekend?... http://on.fb.me/qVyGNm     
    
    
    A great reminder from RT @chalenejohnson Don't let ur emotions control ur day. U r NOT ur emotions. Stop giving them power.    
    
    
    Does this ring your bell? - RT @DrPeggyMalone - Those who do not have goals are doomed forever to work for those who do.    
    
    
    "Don't let your emotions control your day. You are NOT your emotions. Stop giving them power. Pick yourself up and... http://on.fb.me/n0qUx7     
    
    
    I love this man - RT @waynedyerquotes "Creativity Means Believing you have Greatness" ~Wayne Dyer    
    
    
    Eat your beans and lentils RT @dancinginlife Research shows: that the legume family may help to reduce many chronic diseases.    
    
    
    Also helps to repopulate good gut bacteria RT @HNWellness Eliminate Pathogens and Improve Your Health with Probiotics    
    
    
    I'd love to hear what you do to spoil your pet/s.... http://on.fb.me/pbns1g     
    
    
    This is the look of a content cat. She's glad her daddy is home a... http://on.fb.me/omRMj3  http://on.fb.me/oyT2Lu  http://yfrog.com/h4jt1rzj     
    
    
    Spent the day shopping and now back home making dinner. Nothing exciting - how about you?... http://on.fb.me/qRYkEh     
    
    
    An important message from one of the schools I've attended. What do ... http://bit.ly/q5d1Gr  http://on.fb.me/q8kavD  http://yfrog.com/189fqtj     
    
    
    Life expectancy would grow by leaps and bounds if green vegetables smelled as good as bacon.  ~Doug Larson    
    
    
    Adam and Eve ate the first vitamins, including the package.  ~E.R. Squibb    
    
    
    If you don't like something change it; if you can't change it, change the way you think about it.  ~Mary Engelbreit    
    
    
    Shrimp Fra Diavolo, fresh homegrown green beans and a good pinot noir for dinner    
    
    
    My @Klout score is 33. I improved it by 12 points over the past  30 days! Let's connect on Facebook - I'd love to see you there.    
    
    
    Moving along and taking care of business. How about you, Pam?    
    
    
    Yep. Just wish I had 48 hour days to manage everything.    
    
    
    @JohnMurphyTMA Thanks for the follow. Would love to connect on FB so we can share more.    
    
    
    @Arceliatvt  thanks for the follow. I'd love to be friends on Facebook see you there http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @CExecMom  thanks for the follow. I'd love to be friends on Facebook as well. See you there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @PetiquetteDog I'd love to be friends on Facebook as well. See you there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @travelwritingpr I'd love to be friends on Facebook as well. See you there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @GretchenAvery  Thanks for the follow, Gretchen. I'd love to be friends on Facebook as well. Meet me there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    Love this man. Please watch and share http://youtu.be/YgEZTDtxfiA     
    
    
    Expert Interviews | Stress Relief Program|Stress Management Coach| Lisa Birnesser http://bit.ly/hLqbkO     
    
    
    Check this video out -- Garden Produce_Tomatoes from Bella-VitaWellness http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l_NiAS-2xts&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    @LisaBirnesser Thanks for the retweet Lisa.    
    
    
    @Snack_Girl_  Thanks for the follow. I'd love to connect on Facebook as well. Let's meet @http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q    
    
    
    @SusanPreston  Thanks for retweet Susan. I appreciate you.    
    
    
    @chirosportscoge  Appreciate the follow. I'd love to become friends on Facebook http://www.facebook.com/sharon.wegner     
    
    
    @shanaBrantley  Hi Shana - thanks for the follow. I'd love to meet you here - http://www.facebook.com/sharon.wegner     
    
    
    @GetSusanMktg Hey Susan - thanks for the follow. I'd love to get to know you on Facebook - see you there http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @chirosportscoge  Alicia, I'd love to meet and become friends on Facebook. See you there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @fdgifford Thanks for the follow - I'd love to meet and become friends on Facebook. See you there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @CiaoFlorentina Ciao! - I'd love to meet and become friends on Facebook. See you there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @AnnaNMoore1 Hi Anna, thanks for the follow - I'd love to meet and become friends on Facebook. See you there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @MyLifeSaver1 Thanks for the follow. I'd love to meet up on Facebook. See you on the other side @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @riftvalleylady Jacqueline - thanks for the follow. I'd love to get to know you on Facebook - meet me there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @ArtJonak I appreciate the follow, Art. I'd really like to meet up with you on Facebook. Head over to http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    @whitneycrawford Thanks for the follow Whitney - I would love to meet on Facebook - see you there @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    USDA Recalls 40,000 Lbs. of Ground Beef http://healthland.time.com/2011/09/26/usda-recalls-40000-lbs-of-ground-beef/ … via @TIMEHealthland Time to go TURKEY!    
    
    
    @MossiTech I so appreciate the follow. Let's connect on Facebook - meet me @ http://on.fb.me/r6gB4q     
    
    
    The Real Cost of a Healthy Meal   http://shar.es/bn8FR  this is sooo good!    
    
    
    @chrisek  I love your Twitter background    
    
    
    @MastermindEvent Appreciate the follow and look forward to sharing with you.    
    
    
    How To Get Dinner on the Table in Less Time:  Begin With a Plan - http://goo.gl/aQB6m  via @Shareaholic    
    
    
    @kidsbestlife  Thanks for the RT Denny:) I so appreciate it    
    
    
    @SocialSpud  Thanks for the follow.    
    
    
    @SolvitaBennett I so appreciate the retweet with a link to my website, Solvita! Thank you.    
    
    
    A legend of our time - Timeline: Steve Jobs' career #cnn http://www.cnn.com/2011/TECH/innovation/10/05/steve.jobs.timeline/index.html?&hpt=hp_c2 …    
    
    
    @SusanPreston Susan - thanks for the retweet. I appreciate you!    
    
    
    @BeautyTipsPro Good morning and thanks for the follow. I look forward to your tweets. In health and wellness, Sharon    
    
    
    @everydayfire  Good morning and thanks for the follow. I look forward to your tweets and inspirations. In health and wellness, Sharon    
    
    
    @RakeshSethi1 Looking forward to learning more about Ayurveda from you    
    
    
    Nuts or Acorns? Plus "Nonni's Stroni"- http://goo.gl/QgH2h  via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    @vicdesignstudio Thanks for the follow, Victoria. Looking forward to your tweets. In health and wellness, Sharon    
    
    
    @RabyInstitute Appreciate the follow.    
    
    
    @TheSimonJordan Hey Simon - thanks for the follow. I look forward to your tweets. In health and wellness, Sharon Wegner    
    
    
    @BessBlanco Thanks for the RT Bess. I appreciate you!    
    
    
    Just had an amazing conversation with Ayurvedic guru @RakeshSethi1    
    
    
    Just in case anyone is paying attention - I am in the process of filing a formal complaint to the powers that be at LinkedIn as I have been…    
    
    
    An "old-time" Remedy for Cold and Flu Season  - http://tinyurl.com/3unnw7p  via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    @scottleadership Hey Scott, thanks for the follow. Looking forward to your tweets. In health and wellness, @sharonwegner    
    
    
    Senate Votes for Unlimited Potatoes in Schools http://healthland.time.com/2011/10/19/senate-votes-for-unlimited-potatoes-in-schools/ … via @TIMEHealthland - yet another example of who has the biggest voice    
    
    
    @JulieHamilton_ Thanks for the follow, Julia    
    
    
    By popular demand - Fast, fresh & healthy stir-fry - http://bit.ly/nMZ3ED     
    
    
    @HN18497  Hey there James - thanks for the follow. As a former Realtor who knows all about stress and eating, I'd love to share more info.    
    
    
    @TallahasseeREAL Thanks for the follow. Need strategies for managing stress? From one who knows - http://bit.ly/rnm5Uy     
    
    
    Symptoms, causes and natural treatment of endometriosis http://www.womentowomen.com/sexualityandfertility/endometriosis.aspx … via @AddThis    
    
    
    @barefoot_exec Good Morning Carrie - appreciate the follow. In health and wellness @sharonwegner    
    
    
    @RonaldYau  Ronald, thanks for the follow. Let's connect on Facebook too. In health and wellness, @sharonwegner    
    
    
    It's Mighty Mom to the Rescue! - http://www.bella-vitawellness.com/its-mighty-mom-to-the-rescue … via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    By popular demand - http://www.bella-vitawellness.com/do-these-look- …umpkins-to-you/    
    
    
    @CherylHeppard Thanks for the follow, Cheryl    
    
    
    reading from @time Why Lovin' the McRib Isn't Heart Smart http://healthland.time.com/2011/10/27/why-lovin-the-mcrib-isnt-a-heart-smart-idea/ …    
    
    
    @SamSilverstein Hey Sam, thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    I promise to love, honor and.....  - http://tinyurl.com/63fhgv7  via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    Whatcha gonna do with your Halloween pumpkin? I've got recipes for everything from soup to dessert.    
    
    
    reading from @time Fast Food's Biggest Customer:McDonald's isn't exactly cheap, costing some $28 for a family of four. 
the-middle-class/    
    
    
    reading from @time Fast Food's Biggest Customer: Not the Poor, But the Middle Class http://healthland.time.com/2011/11/07/fast-foods-biggest-customers-not-the-poor-but-the-middle-class/ …    
    
    
    Beef, Bird or........ - http://tinyurl.com/bstdqmv  via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    Beef, Bird or........ http://lnkd.in/3QkJKs     
    
    
    @lamamanecolo thanks for the follow. Can you tell me what you do?    
    
    
    @Momieofquints Thanks for the follow. Am I correct that you are expecting 5 babies!?    
    
    
    @Momieofquints When are they expected to arrive? How exciting for you and your husband! Blessings.    
    
    
    The Beef or the Pork? - http://tinyurl.com/77lhfp4  via @SharonWegner Just in case you missed this one last week. Look for part 2 on Tuesday    
    
    
    One Potato, two potato, three potato, four...more http://bit.ly/ulPctL     
    
    
    One potato, two potato, three potato, four...   - http://tinyurl.com/84yxm8l  via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    reading from @time 1 in 10 Adults Predicted to Have Diabetes by 2030 http://healthland.time.com/2011/11/15/1-in-10-adults-predicted-to-have-diabetes-by-2030/ …    
    
    
    Group predicts 522M could have diabetes by 2030 http://lnkd.in/9n7227     
    
    
    Group predicts 522M could have diabetes by 2030 - Yahoo! News http://news.yahoo.com/group-predicts-522m-could-diabetes-2030-022451328.html … via @YahooNews    
    
    
    While it's UNFORTUNATE that some members of Congress continue to put special interests ahead of the health of America's children?    
    
    
    "They are making sure that two of the biggest problems in the school lunch program, pizza and french fries, are untouched,"    
    
    
    Food companies fight USDA standards. too strict and neglected nutrients that potatoes, other starchy vegetables  "tomato paste" do offer.    
    
    
    Congress is seriously considering language that would effectively categorize pizza as a vegetable in the school lunch program.    
    
    
    School lunches - http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2011/11/15/congress-pushes-back-on-h_1_n_1094764.html …    
    
    
    @Angelicgw451 Thanks for the follow. I'd love to connect on Facebook. See you there at https://www.facebook.com/sharon.wegner     
    
    
    When was the last time you had your blood pressure checked?    
    
    
    As a population, we are eating ourselves to death, creating diseases of lifestyle that are preventable.    
    
    
    Brussels Sprouts, Kale and Spinach - http://www.bella-vitawellness.com/brussels-sprouts-kale-and-spinach/ … via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    What vegetables are you planning for Thanksgiving? http://bit.ly/tmeIMk     
    
    
    I'm GIVING away 12 of  my favorite Thanksgiving recipes - go grab them here http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    I'm GIVING away 12 of my favorite Thanksgiving recipes - go grab them here http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    I'm GIVING away 12 of my favorite Thanksgiving recipes - go grab them here    
    
    
    I just GAVE away 12 of my favorite holiday recipes - Grab them now! http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    Not your Mama's green bean casserole - http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    THE BEST barley and pine nut casserole - http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    Your Thanksgiving  menu all planned out with all of the recipes - http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    2 delicious ways to make kale - one with butternut squash and the other one with apples - http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    Need some low fat, low sodium, healthy Thanksgiving recipes? http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    Make ahead Thanksgiving recipes so you can enjoy your day with friends and family instead of slaving in the kitchen http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    Maple-roasted sweet potatoes and carrots - delish! http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    I'm GIVING away 12 of m y favorite Thanksgiving recipes. Go grab them here    
    
    
    Do you need Thanksgiving recipes that are diabetic friendly? I've got healthier versions for FREE http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    ck out my FREE recipe photos and connect with me on FB http://on.fb.me/vtglXV     
    
    
    I'm GIVING away 12 of my favorite recipes. Go grab them here    
    
    
    Healthier versions of your favorite holiday recipes - http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    Are you tired of the same old Thanksgiving menu? I've created healthy and delicious versions of your favorites! http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    Why not try some of my healthy versions of your holiday recipe favorites? http://bit.ly/ulV8io     
    
    
    I'm just finishing my article and recipe for tomorrow's newsletter. Pumpkin or apple? Let me know here http://on.fb.me/vtglXV     
    
    
    I'm just finishing my article and recipe for tomorrow's newsletter. Pumpkin or apple?  http://on.fb.me/vtglXV     
    
    
    Want the recipes to these holiday favorites? http://on.fb.me/uxGz8P     
    
    
    Cinnamon, Spice and all things.......http://bit.ly/spbKs2    
    
    
    Here's the final recipe to complete your HEALTHIER Thanksgiving menu http://bit.ly/spbKs2     
    
    
    Pumpkin Ricotta Cheesecake - YUM! http://bit.ly/spbKs2     
    
    
    All new - healthy recipes, food photos and articles about health and wellness - http://on.fb.me/rrkYME     
    
    
    reading from @time 3 Heart Risks to Watch for on Thanksgiving Day http://healthland.time.com/2011/11/24/3-heart-risks-to-watch-for-on-thanksgiving-day/ …    
    
    
    3 Heart Risks to Watch for on Thanksgiving Day http://healthland.time.com/2011/11/24/3-heart-risks-to-watch-for-on-thanksgiving-day/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    I hope everyone had a Thanksgiving filled with peace, love and gratitude - http://bit.ly/rxAOel     
    
    
    How do you know if your body is on fire? http://bit.ly/tmeIMk     
    
    
    Explore natural solutions for health weight loss http://www.pharmacablog.com/2011/12/02/enter-to-join-our-30-day-weight-management-challenge/ …    
    
    
    My WHAT'S of fire!  Are you setting yourself up for serious illness? http://bit.ly/uTLFkt     
    
    
    @TheHappypreneur  Thanks for the retweet my friend    
    
    
    Sugar, Sugar and more Sugar - http://tinyurl.com/765yheu  via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    Sugar, Sugar and more Sugar http://lnkd.in/b6vaK8     
    
    
    Some kids' cereals may have way too much sugar, a report finds http://www.latimes.com/health/boostershots/la-heb-sugar-cereal-children-20111207,0,7280271.story …    
    
    
    Recipes for De-Stressing http://bit.ly/v51boz     
    
    
    reading from @time Childhood Obesity: Most U.S. Schools Don't Require P.E. Class or Recess http://healthland.time.com/2011/12/07/childhood-obesity-most-u-s-schools-dont-require-p-e-class-or-recess/ …    
    
    
    @RakeshSethi1 Is this 7 day detox considered a "mini" detox? Or would you suggest a 3 day?    
    
    
    @MetaLiving  have you been hacked?    
    
    
    Diets and New Year's Resolutions - http://tinyurl.com/c2zk4o8  via @SharonWegner    
    
    
    5 Ways To Give This Holiday Season http://huff.to/hq2Czm via @huffingtonpost    
    
    
    Kids should play: study shows physical activity boosts school performance http://ti.me/snXB6B  via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    It's about time! RT @USATODAY Dannon's Activia, DanActive health claims draw $21M fine http://usat.ly/eECgMi    
    
    
    Feds crack down on HCG products - http://USATODAY.com  http://usat.ly/tXLhEC  via @USATODAY What are your thoughts?    
    
    
    Twinkies - Top 10 Iconic Junk Foods http://ti.me/xi38n0  via @TIME    
    
    
    Think purple and prevent Alzheimer`s Disease, Parkinson`s and Multiple Sclerosis http://j.mp/fhRzHl via @AddToAny    
    
    
    I like this video by @tylerflorence http://twitvid.com/UQ6EU    
    
    
    http://twitvid.com/UQ6EU - @tylerflorence Yes indeedy - that is the California Redwoods. It's cold and wet - what are you braising?    
    
    
    Would you take weight-loss advice from a fat doctor? | http://healthland.time.com/2012/01/30/fat-doctors-are-less-likely-to-help-patients-lose-weight/ … via @TIMEHealthland  Ya think?    
    
    
    “I was totally surprised by the findings,” says lead author Sara Bleich, an assistant professor of health policy at Jo…http://lnkd.in/RcgCfX     
    
    
        
    
    
    @TheHappypreneur @lisabirnesser @reading4relief Thanks for the RT Celene. Have a great day!!    
    
    
    Healthcare's Medical Gluttony - Forbes  http://shar.es/fuSGS     
    
    
    @VernaKing I'd love to send you a msg. follow me @sharonwegner and we can connect    
    
    
    Aching Back? Try Massage for Chronic Pain http://ti.me/vktjmN  via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Neotame, New Neurotoxic Sweetener: FDA Says No Label Needed, Not Even in Organics http://bit.ly/gnbvEC   WHAT????    
    
    
    Never give up. There is always hope. Defying My Prognosis http://findarticles.com/p/articles/mi_m0NAH/is_2_29/ai_53929981/    
    
    
    Yoga Room in Terminal 2: Seeking Inner Calm While Traveling http://healthland.time.com/2012/02/06/yoga-room-in-terminal-2-seeking-inner-calm-while-traveling/ … via @TIME    
    
    
    Not So Healthy Seasonal Sipping http://shar.es/Xx6xn     
    
    
    http://news.yahoo.com/s/livescience/20100625/sc_livescience/darksideofmedicalresearchwidespreadbiasandomissions    
    
    
    This is not new. It's just not something that's been made public. Time to get involved in your healthcare.    
    
    
    Why is the FDA wasting time on this?  http://healthland.time.com/2012/02/21/whither-qnexa-a-brief-history-of-diet-pills-and-the-fda/ … via @TIME    
    
    
    Everything in moderation - Even Small Amounts of Holiday Drinking Boost Cancer Risk http://healthland.time.com/2010/12/20/even-small-amounts-of-holiday-drinking-boosts-cancer-risk/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Vitamin D for Your Heart - Dr. Weil's Daily Tip: http://bit.ly/bGz46q via @addthis    
    
    
    Obesity rises in 28 states, remains highest in the South http://shar.es/mOJZk    
    
    
    I graduated from GCNM last April and I am currently attending the Institute for Integrative Nutrition.    
    
    
    Progress? what's  your opinion? The Food Safety Bill Finally Passes, But It's Just the First Step http://healthland.time.com/2010/12/22/the-food-safety-bill-finally-passes-but-its-just-the-first-step/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    FDA: Diabetes drug Avandia raises heart attack risk http://shar.es/mFA0L    
    
    
    Dukan Diet Founder Faces Ethics Hearing http://ti.me/HeZTGU  via @TIMEHealthland " accuses Dukan of prioritizing moneymaking over medicine"    
    
    
    FTC: Nestlé to drop deceptive health claims http://shar.es/mBMoJ    
    
    
    I am launching new nutrition, health & integrative wellness programs. Watch for updates    
    
    
    Why the New Surgical Cure for Diabetes Will Fail! | Dr. Mark Hyman http://drhyman.com/blog/2012/03/28/why-the-new-surgical-cure-for-diabetes-will-fail/ … The cure is not in the surgery.    
    
    
    What does head size have to do with Alzheimer's? http://shar.es/mTXIt    
    
    
    @Rick_Bayless I'm glad somebody has tomatoes that are healthy and growing. Strange year in the garden. Plants are confused.    
    
    
    I love Marion Nestle! via @huffingtonpost: A Visit to my Kitchen: Marion Nestle http://huff.to/aTBbnI    
    
    
    This one is right up my alley! Fiber Rich Recipes to Help You Lose Weight http://bit.ly/am3kZL via @AddToAny    
    
    
    #TerryWahls on the line sharing her story of eating to heal progressive MS    
    
    
    #TerryWahls met her 2 years ago at a Brendon Burchard Experts Academy. I had no idea she had MS at the time.    
    
    
    #TerryWahls - real example of how food is truly medicine.    
    
    
    #terrywahls - get your nutrients from fresh greens, grass fed meats and diets including lots of color    
    
    
    #terrywahls find the gifts in what is happening to you in life. Sometimes life is not fair.    
    
    
    #terrywahls what you eat, how you manage stress, your physical activities all create health.    
    
    
    #terrywahls which diet will you follow? a modified Paleo diet has made a huge difference in her health. From a wheelchair to riding a bike.    
    
    
    #terrywahls - Paleo is better for losing weight, lowering cholesterol and blood pressure    
    
    
    #terrywahls Paleo is not for vegetarians    
    
    
    #terrywahls if you are looking for health, consider going Paleo    
    
    
    #terrywahls - I also have Hashimotos and continue to struggle. Perhaps I need to go Paleo.    
    
    
    #terrywahls become more conscious and aware of what you are eating and how your body responds.    
    
    
    #terrywahls - no gizzards and liver - no thanks. not a muscle or oyster fan either    
    
    
    #terrywahls - not going to eat organ meats.    
    
    
    #terrywahls wonder if liver pate counts?    
    
    
    #terrywahls I have an amazing recipe for liver pate. Just switch out the butter for coconut oil.    
    
    
    #terrywahls I have several friends who have progressive MS. I would love to share this with them.    
    
    
    #terrywahls  Need info on the study she is doing    
    
    
        
    
    
    #terrywahls Many health conditions can be improved with the Wahls modified Paleo diet    
    
    
        
    
    
    Is sugar toxic? - 60 Minutes - CBS News http://www.cbsnews.com/video/watch/?id=7403942n …    
    
    
    The Story of Bottled Water (2010): http://youtu.be/Se12y9hSOM0  via @youtube    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949995654928/ … I am in love with this baby elephant!    
    
    
    #Mother's Day Special - give her a spa gift http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/     
    
    
    Mother’s Day Specials – Essential Oils http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/     
    
    
    Checking out "10 Steps to Get Healthy" on Whole Living Community: http://ning.it/IEmdId     
    
    
    Mother’s Day Specials – Essential Oils http://j.mp/IHNIFS  Treat your favorite mom to a spa day.    
    
    
    Set Realistic Goals! http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/set-realistic-goals/ …    
    
    
    What Exactly IS a Healthy Lifestyle? http://j.mp/Jmir84     
    
    
    Don't like vegetables? check this out! http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949995690740/ …    
    
    
    Stressed and running on overtime? Create a To-Do-List http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/create-a-to-do-list/ …    
    
    
    Create a To-Do-List http://nblo.gs/xmCt0     
    
    
    Brain fog? No energy? Lack of focus? Watch these videos to learn how you can Improve all 3  http://j.mp/K0YgLe     
    
    
    Want Your Kids to Eat Healthier? It Starts with Mom http://healthland.time.com/2010/12/29/want-your-kids-to-eat-healthier-it-starts-with-mom/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Are you raising healthy children? Baby Getting Heavy? The Culprit May Be in the Bottle http://healthland.time.com/2010/12/28/baby-getting-heavy-the-culprit-may-be-in-the-bottle/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    @EleanoreDuyndam pleasure to meet you!    
    
    
    Wow! If you struggle with your weight - please get help! Is the Economy Making You Fat? http://shar.es/XKRxw    
    
    
    RESOLVE, COMMIT or OPTION? HUGE surprise at the end of this posting http://shar.es/XEnCT     
    
    
    Belly fat linked to increased death risk -- no matter what your weight http://shar.es/00q24    
    
    
    Beetroot juice lowers risk of Alzheimer`s disease and dementia http://www.naturalnews.com/030883_beetroot_juice_dementia.html … via @HealthRanger    
    
    
    @HolisticMomsNet My thyroid needs your help Andrea Beaman    
    
    
    @HolisticMomsNet @Andrea Beaman - Hashimotos is messing with my TSH. antibodies are high and endocrinologist is clueless so far    
    
    
    @HolisticMomsNet @Andrea Beaman - am I missing the conversation?    
    
    
    #holisticmoms Iodine - yes or no. I've had doctors tell me both.
 #holisticmoms    
    
    
    I have high TSH antibodies and my white blood cell count is 2.8   #holisticmoms    
    
    
    Would this be a good time to do a cleanse?  #holisticmoms    
    
    
    so, what to do if no meds? I've been on 4 different ones #holisticmoms    
    
    
    Dead cow carcasses 'resurrected' to produce cloned beef http://bit.ly/cDRex5 via @AddToAny    
    
    
    It may be time to visit your local Farmer's Market.

Millions of eggs recalled in salmonella outbreak http://shar.es/03ZN7    
    
    
    Vegan eggplant roll-ups made with MindfulMayo! For more healthy reipes, visit Http://EssentialsforHe http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949996019837/ …    
    
    
    Check the plant number and Julian date on your eggs. How to tell if your eggs have been recalled? http://www.fda.gov/Food/NewsEvents/WhatsNewinFood/ucm223536.htm?sms_ss=twitter … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Looking to lose weight? Drink up http://shar.es/0bSlZ    
    
    
    Why Coconut Oil is Filled With Health Benefits http://www.pharmacablog.com/2012/07/03/coconut-packed-with-healthy-benefits/ …    
    
    
    Health Benefits in Coconut Oil http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/health-benefits-in-coconut-oil/ …    
    
    
    I'll take my Juice Plus any day over those bugs Check this video -- Bear Grylls and how to Bridge the Gap http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ADIaxRpJ7Ac&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    Coming soon to a restaurant near you: calorie counts http://shar.es/0WHVC    
    
    
    Vitamin D and Your Immune System - Dr. Weil's Daily Tip http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/TIP03800/Vitamin-D-and-Your-Immune-System.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Health Benefits of Garlic http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/health-benefits-of-garlic/ …    
    
    
    Health Benefits of Garlic http://nblo.gs/zVLgj     
    
    
    Food expiration dates: What do they really mean? http://green.yahoo.com/blog/care2/54/food-expiration-dates-what-do-they-really-mean.html    
    
    
    Use Vinegar for All Your Health and Beauty Needs http://shar.es/0pqaX     
    
    
    5 Warning Signs of Alzheimer's - Dr, Weil's Daily Tip http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/TIP03807/5-Warning-Signs-of-Alzheimers.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Lack of Sleep Linked With Depression, Weight Gain and Even Death http://shar.es/0rhjl    
    
    
    fruits and vegetables, regular exercise may benefit the brain: The Benefit of Diet and Exercise in Alzheimer's http://shar.es/XOkeR     
    
    
    New Study Suggests Health Coaches Are Key to Weight Loss http://blog.integrativenutrition.com/2012/08/new-study-suggests-health-coaches-are-key-to-weight-loss … via @nutritionschool    
    
    
    One of my favorite lunches is a can of sardines with fresh lemon juice on whole grain crackers. Sard http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949996272721/ …    
    
    
    How to Avoid Becoming Super Sized When You Shop at Costco http://shar.es/vDu6m  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Health Benefits in Coconut Oil http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/health-benefits-in-coconut-oil/ … http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949996375237/ …    
    
    
    Garlic: A Natural Way to Fight Illness http://www.pharmacablog.com/2012/08/17/great-reasons-to-love-garlic/ …    
    
    
    Stress in America: Overweight Children Are Affected More http://healthland.time.com/2010/11/09/stress-in-america-overweight-children-are-affected-more/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
        
    
    
    Are you at a loss when it comes to making quick, healthy meals for your family?    
    
    
    Are you at a loss when it comes to making quick, healthy meals for your family? http://ow.ly/i/Uscw  http://ow.ly/duPCc     
    
    
    Are you at a loss when it comes to making quick, healthy meals for your family? http://ow.ly/duPCc     
    
    
    I've decided to create an e-book that will help you organize a healthy pantry and kitchen with 3 major bonuses http://ow.ly/duPCc     
    
    
    Is slicing, dicing and chopping vegetables a chore?    
    
    
    Let me help you prepare delicious meals your family will love, faster and easier. Join us on Sept 20th....    
    
    
    Dr. William Li Serves TED Cancer Prevention Tips on a Plate - Tonic http://bit.ly/9bInRt    
    
    
    Are you ready to enjoy mouth watering, yet inexpensive meals AND spend more time with your family? Then don't miss out on this......    
    
    
    Disturbing to you? It should be! Second Hand Smoke Exposure Raises Kindergartners' Blood Pressure http://healthland.time.com/2011/01/10/second-hand-smoke-exposure-raises-kindergartners-blood-pressure/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Health Benefits of Garlic  http://nblo.gs/zVLgj     
    
    
    What Exactly IS a Healthy Lifestyle? http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/what-exactly-is-a-healthy-lifestyle/ …    
    
    
    Added Sugar May Raise Cholesterol in Teens http://www.webmd.com/cholesterol-management/news/20110110/added_sugar_may_raise_cholesterol_teens …    
    
    
    http://healthland.time.com/2010/09/23/study-america-is-officially-the-fattest-developed-country-in-the-world/    
    
    
    If you struggle w/ your weight, I will give you a FREE 1 hr consultation. Visit http://www.SharonWegner.com & fill out a health history form    
    
    
    Carrageenan: Yes or No? - Dr. Weil's Weekend Tip http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/TIP04588/Carrageenan-Yes-or-No.html …    
    
    
    Study: Can a Veggie-Rich Diet Make You More Beautiful? http://healthland.time.com/2011/01/12/study-can-a-veggie-rich-diet-make-you-more-beautiful/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Check this video out -- TEDxNextGenerationAsheville 2010 - Birke Baehr - "What's Wrong With Our ... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F7Id9caYw-Y … via @youtube    
    
    
    FDA refuses to require labeling of genetically modified salmon http://bit.ly/cCbG5l via @AddToAny    
    
    
    @momscholar_tx Thanks for the follow. Is there anything I can do to support your weight loss journey?    
    
    
    People keep telling me they WANT CHANGE but don’t take action…. I just don’t get it… if you are SERIOUS, go to www.Bella-VitaWellness.com    
    
    
    How important is it to you to improve your health, reduce stress and increase your happiness? Learn more and go to www.Bella-VitaWellness.co    
    
    
    3 surprising ways fruits and veggies help you lose weight â Amen Clinics http://www.amenclinics.com/blog/3896/3-surprising-ways-fruits-and-veggies-help-you-lose-weight/ …    
    
    
    FDA panel says not enough evidence to verify safety of genetically modified salmon http://bit.ly/9YLrep    
    
    
        
    
    
    To all of my faithful followers - I am bringing down my Bella-Vita Wellness FB page and moving everything onto my... http://fb.me/FjeazQ70    
    
    
    Study: 40% of Kids' Calories Come From Solid Fat and Sugar http://healthland.time.com/2010/10/01/study-40-of-kids-calories-come-from-solid-fat-and-sugar/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Before winter chills get the best of you, boost Immunity Now! http://shar.es/0jQwJ    
    
    
    There is no excuse for child abuse. Side Effect of the Recession: An Increase in Child Abuse http://healthland.time.com/2010/10/04/side-effect-of-the-recession-an-increase-in-child-abuse/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Big Pharma hired ghostwriters to distort truth about hormone replacement therapy drugs http://bit.ly/9Ncd66 via @AddToAny    
    
    
    WHY would you take a chance? Study O.K.'s Light Drinking During Pregnancy. http://healthland.time.com/2010/10/06/study-o-k-s-light-drinking-during-pregnancy-too-good-to-be-true/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Do You Know What You%E2%80%99re Feeding Your Kids? - http://tinyurl.com/3396aku    
    
    
    Is chicken on your menu? Watch The Dr. Oz Show today http://www.doctoroz.com/videos/friday-dr-oz-show    
    
    
    Interesting data point - being 10 lbs. overweight adds about 30 to 60 lbs. of extra force on your knees with each step    
    
    
    @NutritionSchool South Beach will never be the same! We are going to rock their world with health and wellness.    
    
    
    GROW a Better World : The Lunch Box -- Healthy Tools For All Schools http://growmethod.maker.good.is/projects/lunchbox?sort=popular …    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving my U.S. friends. Wishing EVERYONE a day filled with gratitude. #essentialsforhealthyliving    
    
    
    Black Friday Early Bird Sale starts today and ends Monday November 26
http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry/ …    
    
    
    Need to know what to do with those Thanksgiving leftovers? 
http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry/ … includes 3 bonuses!!    
    
    
    Black Friday Special - For the 1st time EVER, I'm going to share with you my best…Tips, Tools, Secre http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949997069542/ …    
    
    
    Black Friday Special Tips, Tools, Secrets & Strategies for creating fast, fresh & healthy meals http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry/ … with 3 added bonuses!!    
    
    
    Black Friday Special Tips, Tools, Secrets & Strategies for creating fast, fresh & healthy meals 
http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry/ … with 3 added bonuses!!    
    
    
    Wish you had a secret strategy that guaranteed you would be able to create fast and healthy meals? http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry/ … 3 added bonuses!!    
    
    
    After a long day, the last thing you want to do is fight crowds at the grocery store, then come home to fix dinner. http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry …    
    
    
    No time, No energy, Everyone’s hungry,You’re exhausted? 
http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry … #BlackFriday    
    
    
    Tips, Tools, Secrets & Strategies for creating fast, fresh & healthy meals 
http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry/ … with 3 added bonuses!!    
    
    
    Wish you had a secret strategy that guaranteed you would be able to create fast and healthy meals? http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry/ … 3 added bonuses!!    
    
    
    No time, No energy, Everyone’s hungry,You’re exhausted? 
http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry … #BlackFriday through CyberMonday    
    
    
    It’s been a long 9 months http://shar.es/0xyOF     
    
    
    Cyber Monday Special - Tips, Tools, Secrets & Strategies for creating fast, fresh & healthy meals 
http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry/ … 3 added bonuses!!    
    
    
    CyberMonday - No time, No energy, Everyone’s hungry,You’re exhausted? 
http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry … #CyberMonday http://bit.ly/UUXuFd     
    
    
    Got a cold, sore throat or the flu? I've got a quick, easy and natural remedy http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/essential-oils/     
    
    
    I want you to Take Me to Tuscany. Enter for a chance to win a 5-star vineyard estate trip from @Travelzoo. #tzootrip http://bit.ly/QnEHmy     
    
    
    Are SUGAR CRAVINGS sabotaging your weight loss success? I’ll teach you how to UNDERSTAND AND REDUCE CRAVINGS. Get access to the FREE webinar    
    
    
    This is NOT a title to be proud of. America Is Officially the Fattest Developed Country in the World http://healthland.time.com/2010/09/23/study-america-is-officially-the-fattest-developed-country-in-the-world/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    How healthy is YOUR family? Are you raising healthy children? Are you ready to radically improve your health and happiness? Let me help you!    
    
    
    Are there any discussions about evening activities - other than dancing?    
    
    
    Total Blueberry Pomegranate cereal from General Mills contains no blueberries and no pomegranates http://www.naturalnews.com/031053_General_Mills_Total_cereal.html … via @HealthRanger    
    
    
    VERY DISTURBING!! Pharmaburger - Food Investigations episode 1 - NaturalNews.tv http://naturalnews.tv/v.asp?v=DE483716CF71BBC79F005FDF473E3511 … via @HealthRanger    
    
    
    Check this video out -- True beauty or photo shop beauty? dove evolution http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iYhCn0jf46U … via @youtube    
    
    
    PLEASE read down to "Not-So-Happy Meals" on this report. Pediatricians vs. Junk Food Giants: http://bit.ly/c3o8df via @addthis    
    
    
    You can prevent this from happening to you: Diabetes Rates Expected to Soar http://healthland.time.com/2010/10/22/diabetes-rates-expected-to-soar/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Artichokes http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/recipes/artichokes/ …    
    
    
    Making healthy food more accessible - Wal-Mart Gives Boost to Push for Healthier Food http://healthland.time.com/2011/01/21/wal-mart-gives-boost-to-push-for-healthier-food/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/YdTJ2A  The unfortunate death of a patient, as well as the article are disturbing and much food for thought. I graduated...    
    
    
    If it's sweet - spit it out! Study: High fructose corn syrup is not the same as sugar - Yahoo! News http://yhoo.it/cXI22H    
    
    
    Mother's diet raises risk of birth defects http://www.naturalnews.com/030215_birth_defects_diet.html … via @HealthRanger    
    
    
    Bonus: Magnesium helps you sleep. Fight and prevent inflammation naturally with magnesium http://www.naturalnews.com/030214_magnesium_inflammation.html … via @HealthRanger    
    
    
    "$7 billion is a bargain when you consider the price of doing nothing." Healthy School Food: Pay Now, Save Later http://shar.es/3aPa0     
    
    
    The power of Garlic - Garlic Broth - Dr. Weil's Healthy Kitchen: http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/RCP00227/Garlic-Broth.html#.URekPihxQTM.twitter …    
    
    
    An apple a day can keep sugar at bay -  https://lifespa.infusionsoft.com/app/hostedEmail/5402880/f4c9ea522cec7909/T …    
    
    
    I'm sorry - I love this! -- FDA Official: "Just Eat A Goddamn Vegetable" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BOyebcrVWb4 … via @youtube    
    
    
    THE premiere expert on internet marketing - bar none! http://www.frank-kern-videos.com/?ref=iwlwoji    
    
    
    From the King of Internet marketing- http://www.frank-kern-videos.com/?ref=iwlwoji    
    
    
    Learn to read food labels - Is White Whole Wheat Flour an Oxymoron? http://www.fooducate.com/blog/2010/12/28/is-white-whole-wheat-flour-an-oxymoron/ … via @fooducate    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    New dietary Guidelines - clear, concise and understandable or vague and politically correct?    
    
    
    Do you read and understand food labels? New Dietary Guidelines Show Politics Still Trumps Science http://healthland.time.com/2011/01/31/new-dietary-guidelines-show-politics-still-trumps-science/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    TAKE ACTION: Stand w/Organic Valley farmers and ask Congress to support healthy and sustainable farming: http://bit.ly/11OqWnA     
    
    
    Why Coconut Oil is Filled With Health Benefits | Pharmaca Project Wellness http://www.pharmaca.com/projectwellness/2012/07/03/coconut-packed-with-healthy-benefits/ …    
    
    
    Self-Love and Self-Confidence. It's and inside job http://j.mp/106XNWK     
    
    
    Is Napping Healthy? - Dr. Weil's Daily Tip http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/TIP04840/Is-Napping-Healthy.html#.UbnkvRZTmH8.twitter …    
    
    
    AMA declares obesity a disease http://www.latimes.com/news/science/la-sci-obesity-disease-20130619,0,4422080.story … - time for health coaches to step in and help. I'm raising my hand!!    
    
    
    Any docs in my area care to have a conversation? I'm available to the South San Francisco Bay Area. http://lnkd.in/Fs6rMm     
    
    
    An excerpt from Mark Bittman's "VB6": http://on.msnbc.com/11rSU8L  via @morning_joe Interesting concept.What if you can't eat wheat, legumes,dairy    
    
    
    Verve Central http://ustre.am/PIpe  Interested - contact me    
    
    
    Join 4 amazing instructors Jul 22-24 for the 3 day workshop Social Media Bootcamp. Enroll Now! http://www.creativelive.com/courses/social-media-bootcamp …    
    
    
    FDA Finally Admits Chicken Meat Contains Cancer-Causing Arsenic  http://intellihub.com/2013/07/21/fda-finally-admits-chicken-meat-contains-cancer-causing-arsenic/ … via @IntelligenceHub    
    
    
    FDA Finally Admits Chicken Meat Contains Cancer-Causing Arsenic http://worldtruth.tv/fda-finally-admits-chicken-meat-contains-cancer-causing-arsenic/ …    
    
    
    Diet or regular - what do you drink? Diet Soda May Lead to Stroke Risk? Really? http://timewellness.wordpress.com/2011/02/11/diet-soda-may-lead-to-stroke-risk-really/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Another California first - Bud in a Bottle: New Marijuana Soda to Launch in Feb. http://healthland.time.com/2011/01/25/bud-in-a-bottle-new-marijuana-soda-to-launch-in-feb/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    DISH Network on #Yelp: We moved to Morgan Hill in April 2013. After searching for Internet options, we had 2 choices… http://www.yelp.com/biz/dish-network-gilroy?pt=review&ref=twitter&v=3#hrid:OZBF3LPQ9-OGbPc618npOA …    
    
    
    From one of my IIN teachers - Do you have healthy guts? Take Our Digestive Health Quiz | John Douillard's LifeSpa: http://lifespa.com/take-our-digestive-health-quiz/#.UgOgkXMn7vo.twitter …    
    
    
    How about another donut? hate vegetables? Reading this may change your mind? http://lifespa.com/what-about-the-liver-for-digestion/#.UgZu-ga3f9s.twitter …    
    
    
    Escoffier Ratatouille Nicoise http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/escoffier-ratatouille-nicoise/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Check out my professional profile and connect with me on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/Hi8afG  #in    
    
    
    Food nutrition health and wellness news http://www.nutrition411.com/component/k2/item/4489-small-intestinal-bacterial-overgrowth-sibo … #NUTRITION411 via @RD411  Never heard of SIBO? Read this to find out.    
    
    
    Paleo Diet - Bugs Gone Wild | John Douillard's LifeSpa: http://lifespa.com/paleo-diet-bugs-gone-wild/#.UhosKMM7vUQ.twitter …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @callmejaneee  Try making a smoothie with coconut water or add a splash of unsweetened cranberry juice and ice.    
    
    
    Low Carb Garlic Lime Chicken http://bit.ly/15i9SIM  via @sharonwegner    
    
    
        
    
    
    Finale - EWL's Bob Brenner Loses 253 lbs** http://p.ost.im/dGGUHF  **Start your transformation now- http://JoinChrisPowellNow.com **    
    
    
        
    
    
    Citrus Seared Salmon - low carb, fast and delicious Essentials For Healthy Living — http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949998882022/ …    
    
    
    Beets, picky eaters and gall bladders Essentials For Healthy Living — http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949998893886/ …    
    
    
    Beets, Picky Eaters and Gall Bladders http://bit.ly/1aj0A0e  via @sharonwegner    
    
    
    Bod•ē 12 week challenge winners from last year http://ustre.am/Krjt 
Start your challenge now http://JoinChrisPowellNow.com     
    
    
    Commit to Be Fit, with Chris Powell http://ustre.am/:2ATHd  http://JoinChrisPowellNow.com     
    
    
    Benefits of the Bod•ē 12-Week Transformation Plan http://p.ost.im/ec2DDr 
Head on over to http://JoinChrisPowellNow.com     
    
    
    Bento Box Soup - Dr. Weil's Healthy Kitchen: http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/RCP02401/Bento-Box-Soup.html#.Ujw1MXDiu8k.twitter …    
    
    
    Superfoods Of The World http://huff.to/1ezLZlv  via @HealthyLiving    
    
    
    50 Of The Healthiest Foods http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949998994302/ …    
    
    
    Former McDonald's Executives to Open a New Healthy-Food Chain http://healthland.time.com/2011/02/16/former-mcdonalds-executives-to-open-a-new-health-food-chain/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    5 Simple Ways for the Whole Family to Shape Up - Dr. Weil's Weekend Tip http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/TIP04948/5-Simple-Ways-for-the-Whole-Family-to-Shape-Up.html#.Ukb421asW28.twitter …    
    
    
    Ever wonder how Chris Powell helps his clients lose weight? Besides exercise - http://VemmaBodeBuzz.bode12.com/     
    
    
    I'm buying breakfast! Cappuccino or Pumpkin spice?  http://bit.ly/1aON3Nw     
    
    
    Cauliflower Steaks, Saucy Shrimp Over Quinoa, Freezer Empanadas, Fiery Kale, Carrot Cake & Stuffed B http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949999046310/ …    
    
    
    Hula Hoop Workouts Burn Calories http://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/news/20110210/hula-hoop-workouts-burn-calories?ecd=wnl_wlw_021911 …    
    
    
    The Perfect Pee | John Douillard's LifeSpa: http://lifespa.com/the-perfect-pee/#.Ul1EvwwPzFM.twitter …    
    
    
    browsing around at http://www.socialmoms.com  -- join me!/    
    
    
    How to Make Chicken Broth http://bit.ly/1fLllXp  via @sharonwegner    
    
    
    Healthy, nutritious and delicious homemade chicken stock http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949999131121/ …    
    
    
    Smoked Salmon Nori Rolls - Dr. Weil's Healthy Kitchen: http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/RCP02402/Smoked-Salmon-Nori-Rolls.html#.UmqKS-y_8Pk.twitter …    
    
    
    This is so wrong! FDA Approves Lap-Band for Millions More Obese Patients http://healthland.time.com/2011/02/19/fda-approves-lap-band-for-millions-more-obese-patients/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Miso, typically made from fermented soybeans, is a powerful flavoring in soups. Its rich, salty flav http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949999290230/ …    
    
    
    Is School Lunch Making Your Kids Fat? http://healthland.time.com/2011/02/07/is-school-lunch-making-your-kids-fat/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    No matter what is going on in life, we can find a reason to thank God. #TodaysWord @JoelOsteen @VictoriaOsteen    
    
    
    The Neuroscience of Why Gratitude Makes Us Healthier http://www.foodrevolution.org/blog/gratitude/     
    
    
    Reflections on this day of Thanksgiving 2013 http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949999357012/ …    
    
    
    Blendtec-holiday-special lowest price including FREE shipping! http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949999357016/ …    
    
    
    http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/how-to-stock-a-healthy-kitchen-pantry-black-friday-special/ … Rock bottom price you can't afford NOT to grab it!    
    
    
    I am grateful, therefore I give  a SERIOUS Black Friday Special https://www.facebook.com/EssentialsforHealthyLiving …    
    
    
    $100 off Blendtec blenders with FREE shipping http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/     
    
    
    Get a head start for a healthy new year - http://bit.ly/17ZoznU     
    
    
    Get a head start on a healthy New year with a healthy pantry and an organized kitchen so you can coo http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949999359776/ …    
    
    
    No time like the present to get a head start on a healthy New year with my Black Friday special - http://bit.ly/17ZoznU     
    
    
    Whole Planet Foundation - Get Involved - Raise a Loan to Change Lives: http://bit.ly/e4Z04n via @addthis    
    
    
    Low Carb Garlic Lime Chicken  http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/recipes/low-carb-garlic-lime-chicken/#.UrQeA6Nsey8.twitter … via @sharonwegner    
    
    
    How To Stock a Healthy Kitchen Pantry - Kindle Edition http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/stock-healthy-kitchen-pantry-kindle-edition/#.UsHZwAm9YMI.twitter … via @sharonwegner    
    
    
    2 days left - Factory Recertified Blendtec Total Blender Classic with WildSide Jar for $279.95 http://bit.ly/1fWDJtC     
    
    
    Ayurvedic Detox  http://essentialsforhealthyliving.com/ayurvedic-detox/#.Usk8s3aTm7k.twitter … via @sharonwegner    
    
    
    !4 day Ayurvedic Detox (aka) Colorado Detox http://pinterest.com/pin/226305949999541101/ …    
    
    
    Another Reason to Skip the Soda: High Blood Pressure http://healthland.time.com/2011/02/28/another-reason-to-skip-the-soda-high-blood-pressure/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Business as we know it has been rewritten. It's about the experience that your customer have    
    
    
    #socialmediathefunway People aren't calling toll free numbers. They find you on Twitter and Facebook    
    
    
    #socialmediathefunway While I'm listening to Sandi, my hubby is making  me dinner    
    
    
    #socialmediathefunway - Presentation this weekend at a non profit and showed them how to make a spinach smoothie. They drank it and like it!    
    
    
    #socialmediathefunway - 10 new followers in 1 hour. I'll take them all the way to better health    
    
    
    #socialmediathefunway - Way to go Charlotte!    
    
    
    #socialmnediathefunway - connection pays - experience makes them stay!    
    
    
    #socialmediathefunway - Sandi, you rock! If you help people to succeed, you WILL prosper.    
    
    
    #socialmediathefunway - 34 new followers - woohoo. Survey on the way - how can I serve you?    
    
    
    #socialmediathefunway - can't get into the website! overloaded....again    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Do you know your numbers? High Cholesterol, Blood Pressure Linked to Early Memory Loss - AOL Health http://aol.it/hKXAsq  via @AOL    
    
    
    Check this out! http://shar.es/3EzWn    
    
    
    In a perfect world - A Health Coach Today Keeps The Doctor Away http://shar.es/38ioh    
    
    
        
    
    
    FDA Recall: Is There Salmonella in Your Skippy? http://healthland.time.com/2011/03/07/fda-recall-is-there-salmonella-in-your-skippy/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Svelte 30 Recall: OTC Diet Pill Contains Undeclared Prescription Drug http://healthland.time.com/2011/02/28/svelte-30-recall-otc-diet-pill-contains-undeclared-prescription-drug/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
        
    
    
    Why Arguing Improves Students' Reasoning Skills http://healthland.time.com/2011/03/17/why-arguing-improves-students-reasoning-skills/ … via @TIMEHealthland My kids could have taught the subject!    
    
    
    The Key to Losing Weight: Don't Rely on Willpower http://healthland.time.com/2011/03/18/the-key-to-losing-weight-dont-rely-on-willpower/ … via @TIMEHealthland - learn to understand your relationship with food    
    
    
    How does  your state rate in the Obesity health poll? http://www.webmd.com/diet/news/20110310/west-virginia-most-obese-state-colorado-least?ecd=wnl_wlw_031911 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Do you suffer from pain, stress, depression Ck this video out -- EFT Documentary Film -Try It On Everything http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vzE0ZvMM3gM&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    Westboro Baptist Church plans to picket Elizabeth Taylor's funeral http://huff.to/e56mY2 via @huffingtonpost    
    
    
        
    
    
    Whoa! 
What do you think about this? WSJ.com - Arizona Proposes Medicaid Fat Fee http://on.wsj.com/hcEenI    
    
    
        
    
    
    Nearly 20% of Lung Cancer Patients Keep Smoking - Yahoo! News http://yhoo.it/fsTV6x    
    
    
    Can Strawberries Prevent Esophageal Cancer ? http://news.yahoo.com/video/health-15749655/strawberries-prevent-esophageal-cancer-24829338    
    
    
    Check out this Meetup with San Jose Naturopathic Medicine Discussion http://meetu.ps/Nh40    
    
    
    Want to Sharpen Your Mind? Drop a Few Pounds http://healthland.time.com/2011/04/14/want-to-sharpen-your-mind-drop-a-few-pounds/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    What's Lurking in Your Meat and Poultry? More than you bargain for. Probably Staph - yummy. http://healthland.time.com/2011/04/15/whats-lurking-in-your-meat-and-poultry-probably-staph/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Up to 100 trillion of them live in our guts! You Know Your Blood Type. What About Your Gut Bug Type? http://healthland.time.com/2011/04/21/you-know-your-blood-type-but-whats-your-gut-bug-type/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
        
    
    
    Reading Boston Bans Sale, Marketing of Sugary Drinks on City Property - http://hvrd.me/eARoJh    
    
    
    Grape Tomatoes in Ready-to-Eat Salads Recalled for Salmonella http://healthland.time.com/2011/05/03/grape-tomatoes-in-ready-to-eat-salads-recalled-for-salmonella/ … via @TIMEHealthland Time to grow your own.    
    
    
    Mike Rowe Senate Testimony : Dirty Jobs : Discovery Channel http://dsc.discovery.com/fansites/dirtyjobs/mike-rowe-senate-testimony.html … - This was a real surprise. A good surprise.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Do your kids bounce around like a flea on a hot brick?  An FDA Panel Will Investigate http://healthland.time.com/2011/03/28/does-food-dye-make-kids-hyper-an-fda-panel-will-investigate/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    1 potato, 2 potato, 3 potato more...or not  I've seen high schools kids order nothing but fries for  lunch. http://tinyurl.com/5tm7atw    
    
    
    Eat more carrots, sweet potatoes, tomatoes & red bell peppers- Veggies, Still Really Good for You http://healthland.time.com/2010/11/22/study-veggies-still-really-good-for-you/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Here's a great recipe for all of those summer vegetables - Ta Da – Tabouli http://www.bella-vitawellness.com/ta-da-tabouli     
    
    
        
    
    
    Holiday Survival Strategies http://shar.es/X0aJl     
    
    
    How do you cut vegetables without a knife or stir without a spoon? This is a must read-  http://tinyurl.com/3vcq67y    
    
    
    How do you cut vegetables without a knife or stir without a spoon? This is a must read http://www.bella-vitawellness.com/blog    
    
    
    Healthy Living: Time to Listen To Our Kids | MomsTeam http://www.momsteam.com/healthy-living-time-to-listen-to-our-kids … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Today, I am " Feeling Good"  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D8GTELtVLvk&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    @kimgarst just connected Hootsuite. Need to connect w/you    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Dr. Andrew Weil on The Worst Diet http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fQDA12ZV2nU … via @youtube    
    
    
    @kimgarst I don't understand it.    
    
    
    @kimgarst I'm so sorry. Lost my dad last year.    
    
    
    http://www.hsph.harvard.edu/nutritionsource/what-should-you-eat/calcium-and-milk/index.html    
    
    
    http://myemail.constantcontact.com/In-the-Kitchen-with-Patty.html?soid=1101415057299&aid=A8sUU913brM … A woman on a mission to teach children about nutrition    
    
    
    I just bought 10 shares in (e)ARR on Empire Avenue http://www.empireavenue.com/ARR     
    
    
    I just unlocked the 'Facebook Friends 1' Achievement on EmpireAvenue.com http://www.empireavenue.com/SHARONWEGNER     
    
    
    I just unlocked the 'Facebook Friends 2' Achievement on EmpireAvenue.com http://www.empireavenue.com/SHARONWEGNER     
    
    
    I just unlocked the 'Facebook Friends 3' Achievement on EmpireAvenue.com http://www.empireavenue.com/SHARONWEGNER     
    
    
    I just unlocked the 'Facebook Friends 4' Achievement on EmpireAvenue.com http://www.empireavenue.com/SHARONWEGNER     
    
    
    I just unlocked the 'Facebook Friends 8' Achievement on EmpireAvenue.com http://www.empireavenue.com/SHARONWEGNER     
    
    
        
    
    
    Who loves Caesar dressing? This one is low in fat - http://www.wholefoodsmarket.com/recipes/2654    
    
    
    Anything is possible as long as you have a burning passion- http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BewknNW2b8Y&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    Do you want more energy, more optimism, more social connections and more happiness?    
    
    
    Americans' home equity near a record low - San Jose Mercury News http://www.mercurynews.com/real-estate/ci_18239100?nclick_check=1 … Not a bright spot in my day, but reality.    
    
    
    What is with the weather in California? Rain again:(    
    
    
        
    
    
    'Dirty' or Not, You Still Need to Eat Your Fruits and Veggies http://healthland.time.com/2011/06/14/dirty-or-not-you-still-need-to-eat-your-fruits-and-veggies/ … via @TIMEHealthland - Wash your fruits and vegetables    
    
    
    A video you should watch- Dr. Mark Hyman at TEDMED 2010 http://drhyman.com/mark-hyman-at-tedmed-2010-5339/ …    
    
    
    ‘An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure’ http://www.bella-vitawellness.com/?p=693     
    
    
    Sometimes it's right in front of us    
    
    
    @donaldwells Sometimes, it's right under your nose.    
    
    
    @donaldwells I do nutritional, health and wellness coaching - now focusing on stress related health issues    
    
    
    @donaldwells It's on the list of "I need to do that next". Not really training videos. I'm re-thinking my business plan    
    
    
    Study: The Link Between Diabetes and Depression Goes Both Ways http://healthland.time.com/2010/11/24/study-the-link-between-diabetes-and-depression-goes-both-ways/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Study: The Best and Worst Foods for Healthy Weight http://healthland.time.com/2011/06/23/study-the-best-and-worst-foods-for-weight-loss/ … via @TIMEHealthland - Absolutely excellent information. Please read!    
    
    
    Thanks. Have a terrace day    
    
    
        
    
    
    @sandikrakowski Sharon in San Jose, Ca - can't wait!    
    
    
        
    
    
    #vatraining Tune in to Sandi Krakowski on the line now!    
    
    
    #vatraining - Amity a pit bull? no way    
    
    
    #vatraining Love you Sandi Krakowski and Amity! Boy do I hear what you are saying.    
    
    
    #vatraining - bring on a personal assistant and an Amity clone!    
    
    
    #vatraining - get masterful! And learn to let go of control AKA "get help"    
    
    
        
    
    
    One of the top PREVENTABLE Diseases - Diabetes Cases Double to 347 Million http://on.wsj.com/kSyaCt     
    
    
    #VATRAINING in 30 minutes with Sandi Krakowski    
    
    
    #vatraining - ok, ready for more. bring it on.    
    
    
    #vatraining - clam up or blow up - I love that!    
    
    
    #vatraining - r u have been resisting? - listen to @sandikrakowski She's had me in tears, touched my heart, opened my eyes & cracked me up.    
    
    
    14.6 hours -    
    
    
    #vatraining 14.6    
    
    
    #vatraining - oh thank God - it's not me:)    
    
    
    @only1golda @sandikrakowski should have checked wording b 4 sending. But the message is the same    
    
    
    #vatraining - what can you do to get the answer yourself? Think. Be empowered.    
    
    
        
    
    
    #vtraining - how often do you have to clear your cache?    
    
    
    @ChefChiarello how to use a knife and don't touch the stove - it's HOT!    
    
    
    #vatraining. It's not about your ego. Get over it and serve your clients and customers.    
    
    
    #vatraining - how funny - I check out everyone on FB, Twitter and LinkedIn before I accept a friend request. Absolutely!    
    
    
    New Use for Duct Tape: Fighting Infection http://healthland.time.com/2011/07/01/new-use-for-duct-tape-fighting-infection/ … via @TIMEHealthland - you will not believe this one!    
    
    
    America Sees Its Obesity Rates and Raises Them http://healthland.time.com/2011/07/08/america-sees-its-obesity-rates-and-raises-them/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
        
    
    
    Baby boom! 16-lb. newborn may set Texas record “I was just amazed when he came out, how big he was. I’m just proud of him” WHAT????    
    
    
    #Timemanagement - Sharon Wegner from San Jose California on the line for Time Management with Sandi Krakowski - whoo hoo    
    
    
    #timemanagement - Struggling from stress related health issues? http://www.Bella-VitaWellness.com     
    
    
    #timemanagement - Inner Circle is a must if you are going to move forward in your business    
    
    
    #Timemanagement - need to learn how to create a healthy meal plan based on your personal needs & likes? Visit http://www.Bella-VitaWellness.com     
    
    
    What do you do to serve yourself every day?    
    
    
    To Ward off Dementia, Try Staying Healthy From Head to Toe http://healthland.time.com/2011/07/14/to-ward-off-dementia-try-staying-healthy-from-head-to-toe/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    I just bought 50 shares in @droz on Empire Avenue at http://empireavenue.com/ipo/twitter/droz … http://www.empireavenue.com/ipo/twitter/droz …    
    
    
    I just bought 50 shares in @oprahwinfreynet on Empire Avenue at http://empireavenue.com/ipo/twitter/oprahwinfreynet … http://www.empireavenue.com/ipo/twitter/oprahwinfreynet …    
    
    
    "Unfortunately, the budget signed by Gov. Brown compelled us(Amazon)to terminate the Associates Program for California-based participants."    
    
    
    Another big surprise - foul play. US Senator caught admitting that lame duck session is 'rigged' http://www.naturalnews.com/030585_lame_duck_session_Senate.html …    
    
    
    Time to get my passport updated. Top ten lies about Senate Bill 510 http://www.naturalnews.com/030587_Senate_Bill_510_Food_Safety.html …    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Study: How Chronic Stress Can Lead to Depression http://healthland.time.com/2011/08/03/study-how-chronic-stress-can-lead-to-depression/ … via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    