Come see our website! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/index.aspx  #IHCCSTEM    
    
    
    Our newly renovated library is almost done! Stop by to see it.  http://twitpic.com/dhqsqs     
    
    
    The clock tower on a great fall day!  http://twitpic.com/dhqsv4     
    
    
    Thanks to @CityVisionsMN for our new profile photos!    
    
    
    Thank you to our 1st followers! @RMarkYoungblood @superCompSci @CenturyCollege @matthewmj    
    
    
    RT@NCWITAIC Know a young woman with aspirations in computing? Get application info in both Spanish & English: http://bit.ly/18ScVbu     
    
    
    For teen girls, for adult mentors and volunteers! http://ow.ly/pVNOA  #STEM @technovationMN    
    
    
    Why study IT at @InverHillsCC? Help others by quickly solving their critical technology needs! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    What's The Next Big Thing For Engineering Students? A Lab That Fits In A Backpack  http://onforb.es/16BXyzt  via @Forbes    
    
    
    Why study Engineering at @InverHillsCC? Make a difference by inventing solutions to everyday problems! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    The Need for Belonging in Math and Science, what can hold women back.  via @sciam http://ow.ly/q1R0n     
    
    
    How Emerging Technology Will Save Women's Lives During Childbirth  http://onforb.es/18frF0N  via @forbes    
    
    
    Cyber security more important than ever http://ow.ly/q3GNn     
    
    
    Be a Computer Programmer at @InverHillsCC and write the code that powers the modern world! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/ ...    
    
    
    Cool Astro Pic of the Day! http://apod.nasa.gov/apod/astropix.html … @apod    
    
    
    Help society by developing innovative materials used in healthcare & pharmaceutical fields @InverHillsCC http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    My 10 Best Pieces Of Career Advice For Millennials  http://onforb.es/18oUmfI  via @forbes    
    
    
    A pic of our Community Garden before the snow flies http://twitpic.com/dij0hd  Thx @CityVisionsMN    
    
    
    Good News For Millennials: A Big Company Might Actually Hire You - with STEM skills  via @YahooFinance http://ow.ly/q7wQT     
    
    
    @InverHillsCC STEM students or curious about STEM - follow us @IHCCSTEM    
    
    
    Network Technology & Security @InverHillsCC Design, setup, and maintain the systmes that run the Internet! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Thanks to our new followers! @ingridmara @AdamVWahlberg @rebeccaschatz @mnmark24    
    
    
    @IHCCSTEM Check out our updated web page! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    @InverHillsCC Like us on Facebook! https://www.facebook.com/IHCCSTEM     
    
    
    Manipulate the powerful genetic building blocks of life in cutting edge lab experiences. Study Biology @InverHillsCC http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    This is what inspires girls in STEM #hpstem http://huff.to/1c85IFm  via @HuffPostTech    
    
    
    Help others by quickly solving their critical technology needs, study Math @InverHillsCC http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Thx to our new followers! @JHoseney @noramayc @Samsamum    
    
    
    The $40 Indian tablet that could help bridge America’s digital divide http://wapo.st/1agc99x     
    
    
    Build, upgrade and repair computers and other hardware! Study IT @InverHillsCC http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans and the ecosphere. Biology @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Build and program high-tech robots to follow your every instruction! Study Engineering @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Work in a professional help desk and network administration environment - learn IT support @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    @amyklobuchar Thanks for following!    
    
    
    Express your creativity and unlock the solutions to complex problems through computers @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Rocket21 Nurturing kids' dreams http://shar.es/IurWe  @rocket21    
    
    
    Young Children Turning to Mobile Devices, Report Finds via @educationweek http://ow.ly/qgIO7     
    
    
    Explore green technology by building working motors powered by the sun @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Minneapolis Mayor Rybak to run Generation Next via @mprnews http://ow.ly/qkiJz     
    
    
    Transform everyday raw materials into amazing compounds, in Chemistry @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    @InverHillsCC Follow @IHCCSTEM on Facebook! https://www.facebook.com/IHCCSTEM     
    
    
    Learn how to protect networks and servers from frequent attacks with advanced cybersecurity tactics @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Strive for what you want http://wp.me/p28HMs-li  via @anitasquilt #girlsintech #STEM    
    
    
    Learn to program in advanced languages such as C++, JAVA, HTML, JavaScript, Python, and PHP @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Schools Aren't Teaching Kids To Code; Here's Who Is Filling The Gap by @selenalarson http://readwr.it/b0DI     
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans and the ecosphere. Biology @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Dare to try! http://wp.me/p28HMs-9J  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    Thx 2 our new followers! @TruesourceIT @MJNS1225 @Scientista_Talk @smilegenic @GynzyUS    
    
    
    Brilliant use of technology and marketing! Tweet a Coffee: Send an eGift via Twitter: http://youtu.be/AxPZj9x_Dsk  via @YouTube    
    
    
    http://anitasquilt.org/2012/09/25/in-systerhood-lending-a-global-hand/ …    
    
    
    It's the Little Things http://wp.me/p28HMs-6U  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    Build, upgrade, and repair computers and other hardware @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  #Mathematics    
    
    
    Why Are There Still So Few Women in Science? http://nyti.ms/18ROWK9     
    
    
    The Power of Community http://wp.me/p28HMs-aK  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    3 tips to keep girls interested in STEM #hpstem http://huff.to/19McVKZ  via @HuffPostTech    
    
    
    Systerhood and Feminism http://wp.me/p28HMs-8a  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    @systers_org Great stories need to be shared!    
    
    
    Explore green technology by building working motors powered by wind turbines. http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  #STEM    
    
    
    Write the code that powers the modern world - from websites to business applications http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  @InverHillsCC #STEM    
    
    
    The Journey with Mentors and Friends http://wp.me/p28HMs-6Q  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    Work with powerful networks, servers, firewalls, and more! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  #STEM @InverHillsCC    
    
    
    3600 of my closest online friends http://wp.me/p28HMs-el  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    Has employment of women and minorities in S&E jobs increased? http://www.nsf.gov/nsb/sei/edTool/data/workforce-07.html … via @NSF_NSB    
    
    
    Survey finds STEM grads still in high demand, short supply  via @KCBizjournal http://ow.ly/qzBel     
    
    
    Nudging Girls Toward Computer Science http://nyti.ms/18VXwrr  #STEM #girlsintech    
    
    
    25 Years of Systers http://wp.me/p28HMs-er  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    I see two people clasping hands.
#RorschachDoodle http://g.co/doodle/twguwx     
    
    
    Top 25 Free Online Resources In Computer Science via @efyindia http://ow.ly/qDFIV     
    
    
    Bridging the gender gap in Computer Science! http://ow.ly/qDJik  @sfbayrane    
    
    
    #STEM skills seeping into blue-collar jobs: http://bit.ly/1frJFuH   via @heraldextra    
    
    
    I just liked "The Invisible Bicycle Helmet | Fredrik Gertten" on Vimeo: http://vimeo.com/43038579     
    
    
    Profiles: How Latinas are Finding Their Way into Software Dev http://ow.ly/qFGDF  #girlsintech #STEM    
    
    
    Write the code that powers the world - websites, phone apps, and business applications http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  #STEM .@InverHillsCC    
    
    
    I created group Inver Hills CC STEM Division - Students and Alumni on Linkedin.: http://lnkd.in/bSuTTi3     
    
    
    Students & Alumni - Join the conversation at IHCC STEM LinkedIn group page! http://ow.ly/qKIgC     
    
    
    .@InverHillsCC Students & Alumni - Join the conversation at IHCC STEM LinkedIn group page! http://ow.ly/qKIgC     
    
    
    @InverHillsCC Students & Alumni - Join the conversation at IHCC STEM LinkedIn group page! http://ow.ly/qKIgC     
    
    
    Discover ways to hep society by developing innovative materials used in pharmaceutical, agriculture, and engineering fields...    
    
    
    Protect networks and servers from attacks with advanced cybersecurity tactics http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/   .@InverHillsCC #STEM    
    
    
    The 10 fastest growing job titles are all in Tech http://ow.ly/qRYDD  #STEM    
    
    
    97% of participants go on to enroll in college! http://vimeo.com/75840627  @GenesysWorksTC    
    
    
    Supporting Underrepresented Groups http://wp.me/p28HMs-hP  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    STEAM vs. STEM? Where does art & design fit in? http://ow.ly/qUbvW     
    
    
    We Don’t Need Beards to Achieve in Computing! http://wp.me/p28HMs-jw  via @anitasquilt    
    
    
    Happy Monday! What is something you're looking forward to this week? #Monday #STEM    
    
    
    Did you know that "71% of new jobs are going to be computer related in every field"? http://ow.ly/qUWJ5  #STEM #computer #technology...    
    
    
    "Like" our Facebook page! https://www.facebook.com/IHCCSTEM     
    
    
    Did you know math such as, Algebra, Arithmetic, & Geometry can be dated back to 3000 BC in Ancient Egypt?! #funfact #math #STEM #education    
    
    
    Did you know...the color television system was developed by John Logie Baird in 1928. #funfact #Tuesday #technology    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on Facebook! http://ow.ly/qUW2v  #college #Facebook #education    
    
    
    Never Settle http://wp.me/p28HMs-ni  via @anitasquilt    
    
    
    3D printer practice.. http://ow.ly/r0Bvv  #Technology #STEM    
    
    
    Jolly green comet blazes a trail towards sun... http://ow.ly/r0BgH  #science #STEM #IHCC    
    
    
    STEM research current and future opportunities. http://ow.ly/qZBkN  #STEM #science #research #education    
    
    
    Did you know...the first cell phone call was made back in 1973? #funfact #technology #STEM #mobile    
    
    
    Help NCWIT teach 1000 girls to code in 2014! http://ow.ly/r100P  @NCWIT #STEM #girlsintech    
    
    
    Follow us on Facebook! http://ow.ly/qZB89  #Facebook #socialmedia #IHCC #STEM #college #education    
    
    
    Youtube + Xbox One... http://ow.ly/r1PFC  #Technology #Youtube #Xbox #innovation #STEM    
    
    
    Great post! @MenloVentures @SaiAvala @Uber @WarbyParker @TechCrunch    
    
    
    @KerryMacuska Yes! Educational leaders should start getting more aggressive with #Technology. It's a growing field! Great post!    
    
    
    Follow us on Pinterest and check out our awesome STEM boards! http://ow.ly/r1N96  #Pinterest #Socialmedia #STEM #education    
    
    
    Great post via @brianabbey: Only 1 in 10 engineers are women. We should fix that. #dontunderestimategirls #STEM @goldieblox (via...    
    
    
    Couldn't have agreed more! @educationweek: Consider Location, Not Just the Institution, in Picking a College http://bit.ly/1axLKoa ...    
    
    
    It pays to be in Tech! Top Cities Creating Tech Jobs! http://ow.ly/r1QdD  #Technology #job #opportunities #STEM #education    
    
    
    Love this post! This definitely creates awareness about the shortage of Technology skills! @LPFI: Technology skills gap threatens US...    
    
    
    Don't forget to follow us on Facebook! http://ow.ly/r3ql5  #Facebook #STEM #socialmedia    
    
    
    Thank you for following us! Looking forward to your tweets and potentially working with you in the future! @ITLearnMore @Zaniaclearning    
    
    
    Where does the Twin Cities rank in Tech jobs? http://buff.ly/18b9Ruv  #Technology #STEM #Minnesota #Minneapolis #StPaul    
    
    
    5 reasons VCs should favor code-savvy founders... http://ow.ly/r1Pzp  #Technology #STEM #education #innovation    
    
    
    Love success stories! How Latinas are Finding Their Way into Software Development! http://buff.ly/1aJiV7n  #diversity #STEM #girlsintech    
    
    
    Bridging the Gender Gap! - Microsoft Research! http://buff.ly/18bawMn  #girlsintech #STEM #education #Technology    
    
    
    Nudging Girls Toward Computer Science! http://buff.ly/1aJjtKh  #girlsintech #technology #education #STEM    
    
    
    Students & Alumni of IHCC-STEM programs join our new LinkedIn group! http://linkd.in/1bWEdj5  @InverHillsCC    
    
    
    #STEM grads are high in demand! http://buff.ly/1aJjEW2  #science #technology #engineering #math #education    
    
    
    These are always inspiring...Life as a female engineer! http://buff.ly/1aJjQ7R  #engineering #STEM #inspiration #women    
    
    
    It pays to be in #STEM! Check out the salaries, data, and trends! http://buff.ly/1aJk7Yh  #career #technology #science #engineering #math    
    
    
    Do you have questions about #STEM? We can help! http://buff.ly/18g0SYQ  #education #college #science #technology #engineering #math    
    
    
    Retweet if you agree! Very inspiring!    
    
    
    Be awesome! It's MONDAY! #Monday http://buff.ly/18g0WHX  pic.twitter.com/NK1eAJ3PC5    
    
    
    Why Science Majors Change Their Minds and how to fix that: http://nyti.ms/uXYYSz     
    
    
    Looking for something to do in Mpls on Thanksgiving? http://ow.ly/ra7EB     
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on Facebook! http://ow.ly/r7tWm  #Facebook #socialmedia #STEM #education    
    
    
    Thank you to our new and awesome followers @hseroboticsteam and @getfleck!    
    
    
    Adding real, hands-on projects to the first year class mix can help! http://buff.ly/18jGoym  #STEM #Science #education    
    
    
    The Long-term Benefits of #STEM http://ow.ly/r7uFs  #education #future #science #tech #engineering #math    
    
    
    Here are some amazing things to do in #Minneapolis on #Thanksgiving! http://buff.ly/1aThByH  #Minnesota #holiday #thankful    
    
    
    Love this! Great share @benjicraig: Encouraging Girls to Hack and Make http://bit.ly/1i2bnmu  #STEM #education    
    
    
    Manipulate the powerful genetic building blocks of life in cutting edge laboratory experiences! #Biology #science #STEM #education    
    
    
    Great share via @projecteve1: 10 Tips to Stop Procrastinating - Project Eve http://buff.ly/1jE43ZS  #productivity #education #procrastinating    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrFm  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #STEM boards on #Pinterest! http://ow.ly/r7uJL  #socialmedia #education    
    
    
    Congrats! @smithsonian: Women in Science Wed: Mildred Clare Scoville recognized for her work in medical ed & public health...    
    
    
    We couldn't have agreed more! @HuffingtonPost: Why more women should get engineering degrees http://huff.to/1cuc2qQ  #hpSTEM #Engineering    
    
    
    Yay Minnesota!! @CarlsonMBA: #Minnesota has the highest number of Fortune 500 companies per capita in the US. http://ow.ly/reJI2  #MBA    
    
    
    Write codes that powers the modern world from video games, interactive websites, apps, & business applications. #Computer #Tech #STEM    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsNF  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    Inver Hills wishing you all a very Happy Thanksgiving! #holiday #thankful #turkey #celebration #Thanksgiving    
    
    
    What are some things that you are thankful for? #Thanksgiving #turkey #holiday    
    
    
    Transform everyday raw materials into amazing compounds. #Chemistry #Science #STEM #education    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrKG  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Great quote! @deg511: “We cannot change the cards we are dealt, just how we play the hand.” 
― Randy Pausch @goodreads    
    
    
    Haha! Great picture! @Videomathteach: Finals are coming!
Nooooooooooooo…... pic.twitter.com/exmUfPt2f7    
    
    
    @benjicraig Keep up the great posts!    
    
    
    Are Minnesotans ready for the snow? #Minnesota #Snow #winter    
    
    
    Interesting share @SNStudents: Mice on steroids: Long after they’ve stopped receiving steroids, mice continue to build muscle...    
    
    
    Thanks @TouchApp_uk for following!! Looking forward to your tweets!    
    
    
    10 Apps to get Kids Excited about Science! http://buff.ly/18XXDU4  #Science #STEM #App #games #education    
    
    
    It's an honor to have you as a Follower @cjmoeller! We're looking forward to your tweets!    
    
    
    Yay Engineering!! @threejoy Thanks for following us! We're super excited!    
    
    
    What are you giving on #GivingTuesday? #Tuesday    
    
    
    Thanks for sharing! @tptMN: RT @_HealthPartners: Commentary on why girls might be more prone to #concussions than boys!...    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrM1  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans and the ecosphere. #Biology #Science #STEM #education    
    
    
    I little humor for Tuesday! http://buff.ly/18XXLDc  #humor #Tech #STEM #Tuesday pic.twitter.com/Wup9LJlHA8    
    
    
    @joshanisfeld Thanks for following!    
    
    
    @HerConcussion Thank you for following us!    
    
    
    @fightpcs Hope you're having a wonderful Tuesday! Thanks for following!    
    
    
    @HerConcussion Looking forward to it!    
    
    
    @tptMN Thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrNk  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    You are absolutely Amazing. Don't let anyone else tell you otherwise. http://buff.ly/18jDC6P  #Amazing #motivation pic.twitter.com/BawlOyFxeT    
    
    
    UPS Also Said To Be Testing Drone Delivery, Constant Robot Background Hum Increasingly Inevitable http://buff.ly/18jEecw  #Tech #robot    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsSt  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    Hoping everyone got to their destinations safely this morning in the snow. #Minnesota #snow #winter    
    
    
    This should be interesting! @Niketa: Fascinating: "Google has quietly acquired 7 technology companies in an effort to create a new...    
    
    
    Work with powerful networks, servers, firewalls, & more at IHCC! http://buff.ly/18lZ5Mb  #STEM #education #technology pic.twitter.com/mYHVwx7nAa    
    
    
    Very true. People often think of the internet or computers. @deg511: There is sense that we don't even notice the simplest technologies...    
    
    
    Free download of SCRATCH - Imagine, Program, Share! http://buff.ly/1eXsiC9  #app #game #technology #STEM    
    
    
    New Pathways To Stem-focused Careers « Programs A - Z « Twin Cities Public Television http://www.tpt.org/?a=programs&id=23284 … via @TPT    
    
    
    It is unfortunate that the world has lost a great leader, Rest in Peace Nelson Mandela. #RIP    
    
    
    Stay warm Minnesotans! #Minnesota #cold    
    
    
    Wow! Great share via @HuffPostScience: This is where perseverance lives in the brain http://huff.to/1cqBPRZ     
    
    
    Stay warm Minnesotans! #Minnesota #cold #winter    
    
    
    Teaching kids how to code! http://buff.ly/18uU7wJ  #technology #computer #STEM #education pic.twitter.com/G3xAkKyHE6    
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans & the ecosphere. Study #biology at IHCC http://buff.ly/18uUg3j  pic.twitter.com/4Z2Ysxx5ur    
    
    
    Work with powerful networks, servers, firewalls, & more. Network Technology & Security at IHC… http://buff.ly/19afdV3  pic.twitter.com/JjgFUfKNun    
    
    
    Awesome Christmas tree decorating!... http://buff.ly/18uUojl  #Christmas #tree #holiday #nerd #science pic.twitter.com/YRoFJBcedf    
    
    
    Did you know that #women filled 60% of #tech jobs this year? That's AMAZING! http://buff.ly/IYGrU8  #STEM    
    
    
    Check out the latest #Google Doodle! http://buff.ly/19d2uAX     
    
    
    Go get em'! @HamlineU: Undergrads: It's one of the biggest recruiting events of the year. #MNprivcolleges Job & Internship Fair...    
    
    
    Learn what most schools don't teach! http://buff.ly/IYGLSR  #coding #education #technology #STEM    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrPK  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Lovin' all the support! @marieA2013: @takebackthetech @JoyCookPR @UN_Women Also long gone are those days when women were discouraged from...    
    
    
    Stay warm!! @tptMN: Warm thx 2 @vivluvjrny4ever, @IHCCSTEM, @AugsburgCollege, @JessicaAyub 4 RTs abt Sat.'s #NelsonMandelaMemorial in MN!...    
    
    
    That would be the best scientific study ever! @edyong209: You gotta love a scientific study where collecting results literally involves...    
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans & the ecosphere. Study #Biology at IHCC! http://buff.ly/1jNTy9b  pic.twitter.com/jSFzhO36AM    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsTy  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    Prepare for this winter! Here are some natural immune boost! #Biology #Science #health http://buff.ly/1jNU0Er  pic.twitter.com/q7D9fBMxBA    
    
    
    #Minnesota do you agree? Stay warm everyone! http://buff.ly/1f7eSms  #cold #winter pic.twitter.com/hrE7DrKquC    
    
    
    Great share via @Jo_Miller: Improving representation of women and minorities in STEM will enrich scientific research & development in US...    
    
    
    Build, upgrade, and repair computers and other hardware! #Technology #STEM #tech #education    
    
    
    Discover the living world around you while working with recognized biologists in small teams. #Science #Biology #STEM #education    
    
    
    How is your Tuesday morning? #Tuesday    
    
    
    Congrats! @stkatemlis: Congrats to our winter graduates! pic.twitter.com/2WlcVc25wV    
    
    
    Interesting approach! @arikaraji: How to raise awareness of sustainability issues? Use humour !!!  http://nyti.ms/1bCOrUM  &...    
    
    
    Very well said! @KSzajner: Connected education requires connected teachers! Are you connected? #ties13    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrQR  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    New #Tech innovation! Would you buy one? http://buff.ly/1fBv9kw  pic.twitter.com/q1mUh6aH1o    
    
    
    Don't know which #STEM program is for you? Take the quiz! Check out our programs! http://buff.ly/19vweJo  #education #college    
    
    
    This is AWESOME! @STEM_Works: 2013 STEM News in Review Scavenger Hunt is up! C'mon, reminisce with us! http://ow.ly/rReTv     
    
    
    Great share via @LPFI: Students delve into programming in #HourOfCode http://bit.ly/19ssj05     
    
    
    Help others by quickly solving their critical #technology needs! #STEM    
    
    
    Keep calm students! It's finals week! http://buff.ly/1c1aEx8  #college #education pic.twitter.com/ETbGUsSQDJ    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsUd  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    Build, upgrade, and repair computers and other hardware! #Technology #STEM #tech #education http://buff.ly/1c1aKVz  pic.twitter.com/soIsEg4NPv    
    
    
    Don't know what STEM program to enroll in? Take a short assessment to see which program you should be in! http://buff.ly/1fn70xr     
    
    
    Google Glass Lets You Wink to Snap a Photo http://buff.ly/1c1cpKK  #googleglass #technology #innovation    
    
    
    Smartphone App Uses Selfies to Check Your Cholesterol Level http://buff.ly/1c1cHBl  #technology #smartphone #app #selfies #innovation #health    
    
    
    Good guidance! Thanks for the share! @YouTernMark: 5 Key Google+ Tools that you may not be using yet by @mqtodd http://goo.gl/tHBKOG ...    
    
    
    This is awesome!! @Divdabble: @BlackGirlsCode @mashable I couldn't favorite this enough!!! I'm in my 30s but these girls inspire me to...    
    
    
    Great quote! I love it! @threejoy: “Education: learning to find your purpose. Upon finding your purpose: what did I learn?” 
― Bauvard...    
    
    
    The Universal Translator Is Real and Its Name Is Sigmo http://buff.ly/1fnbTqc  #Technology #innovation    
    
    
    Discover ways to help society by developing innovative materials used in the healthcare, pharmaceutical, agriculture, textile, &...    
    
    
    Does anyone use Viber? http://buff.ly/18ZIgdD  #technology #app #STEM #innovation    
    
    
    Did you know...Yahoo was involved in making the Siri app? http://buff.ly/18ZInpj  #technology #innovation    
    
    
    Still have some people left on your Christmas list? Mac Pro goes on sale! http://buff.ly/1hokKcq  #Apple #mac #technology    
    
    
    Amazing plate showing fossilized remains of Uintarcinus socials crinoids! Found at http://buff.ly/JIgJDK  #science pic.twitter.com/TyfFULTmha    
    
    
    Wow. Great share! @thomsonreuters: CHART: The number of hacking attacks on U.S. businesses since 2005: http://bit.ly/1cFLVel     
    
    
    Quick Infographic 101 breakdown for you via @GynzyUS: Infographics are everywhere, but do you – and your students – know how to read...    
    
    
    Work in a professional help desk and network administration environment! #career #technology #STEM    
    
    
    @MPRnews Privacy is extremely important to me. Thank you for sharing the great article!    
    
    
    Have you gotten your #HourOfCode in today? #Coding #tech #computer    
    
    
    awesome! @msftcitizenship: #FollowFriday to youth #STEM super stars @FridayInstitute @washingtonstem @EDUCTO @DIYGirls    
    
    
    Still have people on your Christmas list? Here's some awesome gift ideas via @techsavvymama: #STEM holiday gift! littleBits Kits Teach...    
    
    
    Excited to have some new followers! Thank you for following us @msftcitizenship @YouTernMark @STEMclubs @TheNextSiValley!    
    
    
    Great question! It's going to be a long journey, but we can do this! @janelmwrites: Q4: How can we change those existing...    
    
    
    Calling all 2yr & 4 yr #cyber college students interested in getting hands-on experience, Apply here:  http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    Can I get some love from my #STEM peeps? Follow us on Facebook! https://www.facebook.com/IHCCSTEM  #SocialMedia #womenintech #Science    
    
    
    Exciting stuff. I really admire the work being done for this. @DavidWSeattle: Worth a very careful look: Well informed & ambitious new...    
    
    
    Eye cells can now be inkjet-printed..could lead to cures for certain blindness. http://buff.ly/19B3Wx6  #science pic.twitter.com/mWUgr9z6d0    
    
    
    Amazing images of asteroid Vesta!! http://buff.ly/19B3TBA  #science #discovery #STEM    
    
    
    DHS Announces Expansion of Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative | Homeland Security http://buff.ly/1fs9uun  #Student #volunteers #DHS    
    
    
    My Daughter's Career in Tech: a Futurespective of a Life Yet to be Lived http://www.projecteve.com/marily-nika-tedx-script-my-daughters-career-in-tech-a-futurespective-of-a-life-yet-to-be-lived/ …    
    
    
    DHS announces 2014 Secretary’s Honors Program (SHP) #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative for college students http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Thanks for sharing! @ForbesTech: 14 bad tech habits to break in 2014 http://onforb.es/1jA3o0H     
    
    
    My Daughter's Career in Tech: a Futurespective of a Life Yet to be Lived - Project Eve http://buff.ly/1d3kHll  #Tech #womenintec #STEM    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative has 100+ student volunteer assignments open @dhs_ice, @tsa @USCG, etc. http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Everyone LOVES #food! Follow our #Pinterest Eat Science Board! #socialmedia #science http://ow.ly/rFy0h     
    
    
    Acting Sect. Rand Beers "DHS is excited SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative...increasing engagement w/ students” http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Calling all 2yr & 4 yr #cyber college students interested in getting hands-on experience, Apply here:  http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP  #student...    
    
    
    Stay warm out there #Minnesotans! #cold #winter #holiday    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative is developing next gen. #cyber leaders & talent. Apps close 1/3/14 http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    DHS’s SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative is meant to attract the best & brightest #cyber talent http://goo.gl/0ABzRV  #Student...    
    
    
    #Cyber Students, do you desire to protect & secure our Nation while building a rewarding career? Apply http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP  #students...    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrRq  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    IHCCSTEM wishes everyone a Merry #Christmas! #holiday    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative volunteer positions begin spring 2014 & cont. thru summer 2014 Apply:  http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    Wow!! That is exciting! @HuffPostScience: Astronomers say they may have spotted first alien planet http://huff.to/1d3o0sP     
    
    
    Space Walk #2 HAPPENING NOW!! Check it out! http://buff.ly/1g1raOs  #Science #Space pic.twitter.com/twoM0yPxq5    
    
    
    [PHOTO] Sunlight makes cool effect on chair leg http://buff.ly/19MbXPR  #science pic.twitter.com/QG4N2U4QQy    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsUH  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative is offering volunteer #cyber assignments @ 60+ DHS nationwide locations http://go.usa.gov/ZYj5 ...    
    
    
    Did you get a iPad for Christmas? Here are 11 Best Apps to download! http://buff.ly/19Mc127  #tech #Christmas #present #App    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative is developing next gen. #cyber leaders & talent. Apps close 1/3/14 http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Sounds like good news to us! Awesome! @TechCrunch: Code․org: 2 Weeks And 600M+ Lines Of Code Later, 20M Students Have Learned An "Hour Of...    
    
    
    This is something EVERYONE should read and know. Thanks for the great share via @lifehacker: Worried about card skimming at the gas pump?...    
    
    
    Great list! @edworkspartners: Top Scientific Discoveries of 2013 http://edwks.org/0_t  via @wiredscience #Science #STEM    
    
    
    [PHOTO] Beautiful Glacial Cave in the Canadian Rockies. http://buff.ly/19jMVXX  #discovery #landscape #glaciers pic.twitter.com/NDR5drqZMx    
    
    
    #Cyber students in SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative will work w/ DHS #cyber professionals to gain invaluable hands-on experience    
    
    
    Have you ever wondered how many bacteria live in your body? http://buff.ly/19jN9y8  #facts #science #health #biology    
    
    
    Are you a big gamer? 6 exciting gaming trends to watch for in 2014. http://buff.ly/1hGDHHm  #tech #game #innovation #2014    
    
    
    Want to feel like a "superhero"? Smart Glasses will give you that "power." http://buff.ly/1hGDLqB  #tech #SmartGlasses #superhero #innovation    
    
    
    Do you take multivitamins? This study shows that they may be a waste of money. http://buff.ly/1hGEQig  #multivitamins #health #science    
    
    
    Looking for some experience? DHS is now taking applications for their 2014 Secretary's Honor Program (SHP) Cyber Student Volunteer...    
    
    
    SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative allows #college students to gain experience in exciting #cyber fields like cyber threat analysis.    
    
    
    Make an impact; Apply to 2014 Secretary’s Honors Program #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative for college students http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    #Cyber Students, do you desire to protect & secure our Nation while building a rewarding career? Apply http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    What Makes Girls Fall In Love With Computers And Code? http://techcrunch.com/2013/12/29/what-makes-girls-fall-in-love-with-computers-and-code/?ncid=twittersocialshare … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    What makes girls fall in love with computers and code? http://buff.ly/JENdi8  #coding #computers #tech #womenintech    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative has 100+ student volunteer assignments open @dhs_ice, @tsa @USCG, etc. http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Don't know what #STEM program you want to enroll in? We can help! Take this survey to find out! http://buff.ly/18TAdkJ  #college #education    
    
    
    Google's Chromebooks have hit their stride - http://buff.ly/JENB04  #Google #tech #Chromebook    
    
    
    Make an impact; Apply to 2014 Secretary’s Honors Program #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative for college students http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrSl  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Happy New Year's Eve!    
    
    
    Come see our website! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/index.aspx  #IHCCSTEM    
    
    
    Our newly renovated library is almost done! Stop by to see it.  http://twitpic.com/dhqsqs     
    
    
    The clock tower on a great fall day!  http://twitpic.com/dhqsv4     
    
    
    Thanks to @CityVisionsMN for our new profile photos!    
    
    
    Thank you to our 1st followers! @RMarkYoungblood @superCompSci @CenturyCollege @matthewmj    
    
    
    RT@NCWITAIC Know a young woman with aspirations in computing? Get application info in both Spanish & English: http://bit.ly/18ScVbu     
    
    
    For teen girls, for adult mentors and volunteers! http://ow.ly/pVNOA  #STEM @technovationMN    
    
    
    Why study IT at @InverHillsCC? Help others by quickly solving their critical technology needs! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    What's The Next Big Thing For Engineering Students? A Lab That Fits In A Backpack  http://onforb.es/16BXyzt  via @Forbes    
    
    
    Why study Engineering at @InverHillsCC? Make a difference by inventing solutions to everyday problems! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    The Need for Belonging in Math and Science, what can hold women back.  via @sciam http://ow.ly/q1R0n     
    
    
    How Emerging Technology Will Save Women's Lives During Childbirth  http://onforb.es/18frF0N  via @forbes    
    
    
    Cyber security more important than ever http://ow.ly/q3GNn     
    
    
    Be a Computer Programmer at @InverHillsCC and write the code that powers the modern world! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/ ...    
    
    
    Cool Astro Pic of the Day! http://apod.nasa.gov/apod/astropix.html … @apod    
    
    
    Help society by developing innovative materials used in healthcare & pharmaceutical fields @InverHillsCC http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    My 10 Best Pieces Of Career Advice For Millennials  http://onforb.es/18oUmfI  via @forbes    
    
    
    A pic of our Community Garden before the snow flies http://twitpic.com/dij0hd  Thx @CityVisionsMN    
    
    
    Good News For Millennials: A Big Company Might Actually Hire You - with STEM skills  via @YahooFinance http://ow.ly/q7wQT     
    
    
    @InverHillsCC STEM students or curious about STEM - follow us @IHCCSTEM    
    
    
    Network Technology & Security @InverHillsCC Design, setup, and maintain the systmes that run the Internet! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Thanks to our new followers! @ingridmara @AdamVWahlberg @rebeccaschatz @mnmark24    
    
    
    @IHCCSTEM Check out our updated web page! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    @InverHillsCC Like us on Facebook! https://www.facebook.com/IHCCSTEM     
    
    
    Manipulate the powerful genetic building blocks of life in cutting edge lab experiences. Study Biology @InverHillsCC http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    This is what inspires girls in STEM #hpstem http://huff.to/1c85IFm  via @HuffPostTech    
    
    
    Help others by quickly solving their critical technology needs, study Math @InverHillsCC http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Thx to our new followers! @JHoseney @noramayc @Samsamum    
    
    
    The $40 Indian tablet that could help bridge America’s digital divide http://wapo.st/1agc99x     
    
    
    Build, upgrade and repair computers and other hardware! Study IT @InverHillsCC http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans and the ecosphere. Biology @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Build and program high-tech robots to follow your every instruction! Study Engineering @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Work in a professional help desk and network administration environment - learn IT support @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    @amyklobuchar Thanks for following!    
    
    
    Express your creativity and unlock the solutions to complex problems through computers @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Rocket21 Nurturing kids' dreams http://shar.es/IurWe  @rocket21    
    
    
    Young Children Turning to Mobile Devices, Report Finds via @educationweek http://ow.ly/qgIO7     
    
    
    Explore green technology by building working motors powered by the sun @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Minneapolis Mayor Rybak to run Generation Next via @mprnews http://ow.ly/qkiJz     
    
    
    Transform everyday raw materials into amazing compounds, in Chemistry @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    @InverHillsCC Follow @IHCCSTEM on Facebook! https://www.facebook.com/IHCCSTEM     
    
    
    Learn how to protect networks and servers from frequent attacks with advanced cybersecurity tactics @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Strive for what you want http://wp.me/p28HMs-li  via @anitasquilt #girlsintech #STEM    
    
    
    Learn to program in advanced languages such as C++, JAVA, HTML, JavaScript, Python, and PHP @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Schools Aren't Teaching Kids To Code; Here's Who Is Filling The Gap by @selenalarson http://readwr.it/b0DI     
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans and the ecosphere. Biology @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/     
    
    
    Dare to try! http://wp.me/p28HMs-9J  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    Thx 2 our new followers! @TruesourceIT @MJNS1225 @Scientista_Talk @smilegenic @GynzyUS    
    
    
    Brilliant use of technology and marketing! Tweet a Coffee: Send an eGift via Twitter: http://youtu.be/AxPZj9x_Dsk  via @YouTube    
    
    
    http://anitasquilt.org/2012/09/25/in-systerhood-lending-a-global-hand/ …    
    
    
    It's the Little Things http://wp.me/p28HMs-6U  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    Build, upgrade, and repair computers and other hardware @IHCCSTEM http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  #Mathematics    
    
    
    Why Are There Still So Few Women in Science? http://nyti.ms/18ROWK9     
    
    
    The Power of Community http://wp.me/p28HMs-aK  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    3 tips to keep girls interested in STEM #hpstem http://huff.to/19McVKZ  via @HuffPostTech    
    
    
    Systerhood and Feminism http://wp.me/p28HMs-8a  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    @systers_org Great stories need to be shared!    
    
    
    Explore green technology by building working motors powered by wind turbines. http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  #STEM    
    
    
    Write the code that powers the modern world - from websites to business applications http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  @InverHillsCC #STEM    
    
    
    The Journey with Mentors and Friends http://wp.me/p28HMs-6Q  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    Work with powerful networks, servers, firewalls, and more! http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  #STEM @InverHillsCC    
    
    
    3600 of my closest online friends http://wp.me/p28HMs-el  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    Has employment of women and minorities in S&E jobs increased? http://www.nsf.gov/nsb/sei/edTool/data/workforce-07.html … via @NSF_NSB    
    
    
    Survey finds STEM grads still in high demand, short supply  via @KCBizjournal http://ow.ly/qzBel     
    
    
    Nudging Girls Toward Computer Science http://nyti.ms/18VXwrr  #STEM #girlsintech    
    
    
    25 Years of Systers http://wp.me/p28HMs-er  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    I see two people clasping hands.
#RorschachDoodle http://g.co/doodle/twguwx     
    
    
    Top 25 Free Online Resources In Computer Science via @efyindia http://ow.ly/qDFIV     
    
    
    Bridging the gender gap in Computer Science! http://ow.ly/qDJik  @sfbayrane    
    
    
    #STEM skills seeping into blue-collar jobs: http://bit.ly/1frJFuH   via @heraldextra    
    
    
    I just liked "The Invisible Bicycle Helmet | Fredrik Gertten" on Vimeo: http://vimeo.com/43038579     
    
    
    Profiles: How Latinas are Finding Their Way into Software Dev http://ow.ly/qFGDF  #girlsintech #STEM    
    
    
    Write the code that powers the world - websites, phone apps, and business applications http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/  #STEM .@InverHillsCC    
    
    
    I created group Inver Hills CC STEM Division - Students and Alumni on Linkedin.: http://lnkd.in/bSuTTi3     
    
    
    Students & Alumni - Join the conversation at IHCC STEM LinkedIn group page! http://ow.ly/qKIgC     
    
    
    .@InverHillsCC Students & Alumni - Join the conversation at IHCC STEM LinkedIn group page! http://ow.ly/qKIgC     
    
    
    @InverHillsCC Students & Alumni - Join the conversation at IHCC STEM LinkedIn group page! http://ow.ly/qKIgC     
    
    
    Discover ways to hep society by developing innovative materials used in pharmaceutical, agriculture, and engineering fields...    
    
    
    Protect networks and servers from attacks with advanced cybersecurity tactics http://www.inverhills.edu/stem/   .@InverHillsCC #STEM    
    
    
    The 10 fastest growing job titles are all in Tech http://ow.ly/qRYDD  #STEM    
    
    
    97% of participants go on to enroll in college! http://vimeo.com/75840627  @GenesysWorksTC    
    
    
    Supporting Underrepresented Groups http://wp.me/p28HMs-hP  via @anitasquilt #STEM    
    
    
    STEAM vs. STEM? Where does art & design fit in? http://ow.ly/qUbvW     
    
    
    We Don’t Need Beards to Achieve in Computing! http://wp.me/p28HMs-jw  via @anitasquilt    
    
    
    Happy Monday! What is something you're looking forward to this week? #Monday #STEM    
    
    
    Did you know that "71% of new jobs are going to be computer related in every field"? http://ow.ly/qUWJ5  #STEM #computer #technology...    
    
    
    "Like" our Facebook page! https://www.facebook.com/IHCCSTEM     
    
    
    Did you know math such as, Algebra, Arithmetic, & Geometry can be dated back to 3000 BC in Ancient Egypt?! #funfact #math #STEM #education    
    
    
    Did you know...the color television system was developed by John Logie Baird in 1928. #funfact #Tuesday #technology    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on Facebook! http://ow.ly/qUW2v  #college #Facebook #education    
    
    
    Never Settle http://wp.me/p28HMs-ni  via @anitasquilt    
    
    
    3D printer practice.. http://ow.ly/r0Bvv  #Technology #STEM    
    
    
    Jolly green comet blazes a trail towards sun... http://ow.ly/r0BgH  #science #STEM #IHCC    
    
    
    STEM research current and future opportunities. http://ow.ly/qZBkN  #STEM #science #research #education    
    
    
    Did you know...the first cell phone call was made back in 1973? #funfact #technology #STEM #mobile    
    
    
    Help NCWIT teach 1000 girls to code in 2014! http://ow.ly/r100P  @NCWIT #STEM #girlsintech    
    
    
    Follow us on Facebook! http://ow.ly/qZB89  #Facebook #socialmedia #IHCC #STEM #college #education    
    
    
    Youtube + Xbox One... http://ow.ly/r1PFC  #Technology #Youtube #Xbox #innovation #STEM    
    
    
    Great post! @MenloVentures @SaiAvala @Uber @WarbyParker @TechCrunch    
    
    
    @KerryMacuska Yes! Educational leaders should start getting more aggressive with #Technology. It's a growing field! Great post!    
    
    
    Follow us on Pinterest and check out our awesome STEM boards! http://ow.ly/r1N96  #Pinterest #Socialmedia #STEM #education    
    
    
    Great post via @brianabbey: Only 1 in 10 engineers are women. We should fix that. #dontunderestimategirls #STEM @goldieblox (via...    
    
    
    Couldn't have agreed more! @educationweek: Consider Location, Not Just the Institution, in Picking a College http://bit.ly/1axLKoa ...    
    
    
    It pays to be in Tech! Top Cities Creating Tech Jobs! http://ow.ly/r1QdD  #Technology #job #opportunities #STEM #education    
    
    
    Love this post! This definitely creates awareness about the shortage of Technology skills! @LPFI: Technology skills gap threatens US...    
    
    
    Don't forget to follow us on Facebook! http://ow.ly/r3ql5  #Facebook #STEM #socialmedia    
    
    
    Thank you for following us! Looking forward to your tweets and potentially working with you in the future! @ITLearnMore @Zaniaclearning    
    
    
    Where does the Twin Cities rank in Tech jobs? http://buff.ly/18b9Ruv  #Technology #STEM #Minnesota #Minneapolis #StPaul    
    
    
    5 reasons VCs should favor code-savvy founders... http://ow.ly/r1Pzp  #Technology #STEM #education #innovation    
    
    
    Love success stories! How Latinas are Finding Their Way into Software Development! http://buff.ly/1aJiV7n  #diversity #STEM #girlsintech    
    
    
    Bridging the Gender Gap! - Microsoft Research! http://buff.ly/18bawMn  #girlsintech #STEM #education #Technology    
    
    
    Nudging Girls Toward Computer Science! http://buff.ly/1aJjtKh  #girlsintech #technology #education #STEM    
    
    
    Students & Alumni of IHCC-STEM programs join our new LinkedIn group! http://linkd.in/1bWEdj5  @InverHillsCC    
    
    
    #STEM grads are high in demand! http://buff.ly/1aJjEW2  #science #technology #engineering #math #education    
    
    
    These are always inspiring...Life as a female engineer! http://buff.ly/1aJjQ7R  #engineering #STEM #inspiration #women    
    
    
    It pays to be in #STEM! Check out the salaries, data, and trends! http://buff.ly/1aJk7Yh  #career #technology #science #engineering #math    
    
    
    Do you have questions about #STEM? We can help! http://buff.ly/18g0SYQ  #education #college #science #technology #engineering #math    
    
    
    Retweet if you agree! Very inspiring!    
    
    
    Be awesome! It's MONDAY! #Monday http://buff.ly/18g0WHX  pic.twitter.com/NK1eAJ3PC5    
    
    
    Why Science Majors Change Their Minds and how to fix that: http://nyti.ms/uXYYSz     
    
    
    Looking for something to do in Mpls on Thanksgiving? http://ow.ly/ra7EB     
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on Facebook! http://ow.ly/r7tWm  #Facebook #socialmedia #STEM #education    
    
    
    Thank you to our new and awesome followers @hseroboticsteam and @getfleck!    
    
    
    Adding real, hands-on projects to the first year class mix can help! http://buff.ly/18jGoym  #STEM #Science #education    
    
    
    The Long-term Benefits of #STEM http://ow.ly/r7uFs  #education #future #science #tech #engineering #math    
    
    
    Here are some amazing things to do in #Minneapolis on #Thanksgiving! http://buff.ly/1aThByH  #Minnesota #holiday #thankful    
    
    
    Love this! Great share @benjicraig: Encouraging Girls to Hack and Make http://bit.ly/1i2bnmu  #STEM #education    
    
    
    Manipulate the powerful genetic building blocks of life in cutting edge laboratory experiences! #Biology #science #STEM #education    
    
    
    Great share via @projecteve1: 10 Tips to Stop Procrastinating - Project Eve http://buff.ly/1jE43ZS  #productivity #education #procrastinating    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrFm  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #STEM boards on #Pinterest! http://ow.ly/r7uJL  #socialmedia #education    
    
    
    Congrats! @smithsonian: Women in Science Wed: Mildred Clare Scoville recognized for her work in medical ed & public health...    
    
    
    We couldn't have agreed more! @HuffingtonPost: Why more women should get engineering degrees http://huff.to/1cuc2qQ  #hpSTEM #Engineering    
    
    
    Yay Minnesota!! @CarlsonMBA: #Minnesota has the highest number of Fortune 500 companies per capita in the US. http://ow.ly/reJI2  #MBA    
    
    
    Write codes that powers the modern world from video games, interactive websites, apps, & business applications. #Computer #Tech #STEM    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsNF  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    Inver Hills wishing you all a very Happy Thanksgiving! #holiday #thankful #turkey #celebration #Thanksgiving    
    
    
    What are some things that you are thankful for? #Thanksgiving #turkey #holiday    
    
    
    Transform everyday raw materials into amazing compounds. #Chemistry #Science #STEM #education    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrKG  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Great quote! @deg511: “We cannot change the cards we are dealt, just how we play the hand.” 
― Randy Pausch @goodreads    
    
    
    Haha! Great picture! @Videomathteach: Finals are coming!
Nooooooooooooo…... pic.twitter.com/exmUfPt2f7    
    
    
    @benjicraig Keep up the great posts!    
    
    
    Are Minnesotans ready for the snow? #Minnesota #Snow #winter    
    
    
    Interesting share @SNStudents: Mice on steroids: Long after they’ve stopped receiving steroids, mice continue to build muscle...    
    
    
    Thanks @TouchApp_uk for following!! Looking forward to your tweets!    
    
    
    10 Apps to get Kids Excited about Science! http://buff.ly/18XXDU4  #Science #STEM #App #games #education    
    
    
    It's an honor to have you as a Follower @cjmoeller! We're looking forward to your tweets!    
    
    
    Yay Engineering!! @threejoy Thanks for following us! We're super excited!    
    
    
    What are you giving on #GivingTuesday? #Tuesday    
    
    
    Thanks for sharing! @tptMN: RT @_HealthPartners: Commentary on why girls might be more prone to #concussions than boys!...    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrM1  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans and the ecosphere. #Biology #Science #STEM #education    
    
    
    I little humor for Tuesday! http://buff.ly/18XXLDc  #humor #Tech #STEM #Tuesday pic.twitter.com/Wup9LJlHA8    
    
    
    @joshanisfeld Thanks for following!    
    
    
    @HerConcussion Thank you for following us!    
    
    
    @fightpcs Hope you're having a wonderful Tuesday! Thanks for following!    
    
    
    @HerConcussion Looking forward to it!    
    
    
    @tptMN Thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrNk  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    You are absolutely Amazing. Don't let anyone else tell you otherwise. http://buff.ly/18jDC6P  #Amazing #motivation pic.twitter.com/BawlOyFxeT    
    
    
    UPS Also Said To Be Testing Drone Delivery, Constant Robot Background Hum Increasingly Inevitable http://buff.ly/18jEecw  #Tech #robot    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsSt  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    Hoping everyone got to their destinations safely this morning in the snow. #Minnesota #snow #winter    
    
    
    This should be interesting! @Niketa: Fascinating: "Google has quietly acquired 7 technology companies in an effort to create a new...    
    
    
    Work with powerful networks, servers, firewalls, & more at IHCC! http://buff.ly/18lZ5Mb  #STEM #education #technology pic.twitter.com/mYHVwx7nAa    
    
    
    Very true. People often think of the internet or computers. @deg511: There is sense that we don't even notice the simplest technologies...    
    
    
    Free download of SCRATCH - Imagine, Program, Share! http://buff.ly/1eXsiC9  #app #game #technology #STEM    
    
    
    New Pathways To Stem-focused Careers « Programs A - Z « Twin Cities Public Television http://www.tpt.org/?a=programs&id=23284 … via @TPT    
    
    
    It is unfortunate that the world has lost a great leader, Rest in Peace Nelson Mandela. #RIP    
    
    
    Stay warm Minnesotans! #Minnesota #cold    
    
    
    Wow! Great share via @HuffPostScience: This is where perseverance lives in the brain http://huff.to/1cqBPRZ     
    
    
    Stay warm Minnesotans! #Minnesota #cold #winter    
    
    
    Teaching kids how to code! http://buff.ly/18uU7wJ  #technology #computer #STEM #education pic.twitter.com/G3xAkKyHE6    
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans & the ecosphere. Study #biology at IHCC http://buff.ly/18uUg3j  pic.twitter.com/4Z2Ysxx5ur    
    
    
    Work with powerful networks, servers, firewalls, & more. Network Technology & Security at IHC… http://buff.ly/19afdV3  pic.twitter.com/JjgFUfKNun    
    
    
    Awesome Christmas tree decorating!... http://buff.ly/18uUojl  #Christmas #tree #holiday #nerd #science pic.twitter.com/YRoFJBcedf    
    
    
    Did you know that #women filled 60% of #tech jobs this year? That's AMAZING! http://buff.ly/IYGrU8  #STEM    
    
    
    Check out the latest #Google Doodle! http://buff.ly/19d2uAX     
    
    
    Go get em'! @HamlineU: Undergrads: It's one of the biggest recruiting events of the year. #MNprivcolleges Job & Internship Fair...    
    
    
    Learn what most schools don't teach! http://buff.ly/IYGLSR  #coding #education #technology #STEM    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrPK  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Lovin' all the support! @marieA2013: @takebackthetech @JoyCookPR @UN_Women Also long gone are those days when women were discouraged from...    
    
    
    Stay warm!! @tptMN: Warm thx 2 @vivluvjrny4ever, @IHCCSTEM, @AugsburgCollege, @JessicaAyub 4 RTs abt Sat.'s #NelsonMandelaMemorial in MN!...    
    
    
    That would be the best scientific study ever! @edyong209: You gotta love a scientific study where collecting results literally involves...    
    
    
    Explore the dynamic interrelationships between humans & the ecosphere. Study #Biology at IHCC! http://buff.ly/1jNTy9b  pic.twitter.com/jSFzhO36AM    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsTy  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    Prepare for this winter! Here are some natural immune boost! #Biology #Science #health http://buff.ly/1jNU0Er  pic.twitter.com/q7D9fBMxBA    
    
    
    #Minnesota do you agree? Stay warm everyone! http://buff.ly/1f7eSms  #cold #winter pic.twitter.com/hrE7DrKquC    
    
    
    Great share via @Jo_Miller: Improving representation of women and minorities in STEM will enrich scientific research & development in US...    
    
    
    Build, upgrade, and repair computers and other hardware! #Technology #STEM #tech #education    
    
    
    Discover the living world around you while working with recognized biologists in small teams. #Science #Biology #STEM #education    
    
    
    How is your Tuesday morning? #Tuesday    
    
    
    Congrats! @stkatemlis: Congrats to our winter graduates! pic.twitter.com/2WlcVc25wV    
    
    
    Interesting approach! @arikaraji: How to raise awareness of sustainability issues? Use humour !!!  http://nyti.ms/1bCOrUM  &...    
    
    
    Very well said! @KSzajner: Connected education requires connected teachers! Are you connected? #ties13    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrQR  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    New #Tech innovation! Would you buy one? http://buff.ly/1fBv9kw  pic.twitter.com/q1mUh6aH1o    
    
    
    Don't know which #STEM program is for you? Take the quiz! Check out our programs! http://buff.ly/19vweJo  #education #college    
    
    
    This is AWESOME! @STEM_Works: 2013 STEM News in Review Scavenger Hunt is up! C'mon, reminisce with us! http://ow.ly/rReTv     
    
    
    Great share via @LPFI: Students delve into programming in #HourOfCode http://bit.ly/19ssj05     
    
    
    Help others by quickly solving their critical #technology needs! #STEM    
    
    
    Keep calm students! It's finals week! http://buff.ly/1c1aEx8  #college #education pic.twitter.com/ETbGUsSQDJ    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsUd  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    Build, upgrade, and repair computers and other hardware! #Technology #STEM #tech #education http://buff.ly/1c1aKVz  pic.twitter.com/soIsEg4NPv    
    
    
    Don't know what STEM program to enroll in? Take a short assessment to see which program you should be in! http://buff.ly/1fn70xr     
    
    
    Google Glass Lets You Wink to Snap a Photo http://buff.ly/1c1cpKK  #googleglass #technology #innovation    
    
    
    Smartphone App Uses Selfies to Check Your Cholesterol Level http://buff.ly/1c1cHBl  #technology #smartphone #app #selfies #innovation #health    
    
    
    Good guidance! Thanks for the share! @YouTernMark: 5 Key Google+ Tools that you may not be using yet by @mqtodd http://goo.gl/tHBKOG ...    
    
    
    This is awesome!! @Divdabble: @BlackGirlsCode @mashable I couldn't favorite this enough!!! I'm in my 30s but these girls inspire me to...    
    
    
    Great quote! I love it! @threejoy: “Education: learning to find your purpose. Upon finding your purpose: what did I learn?” 
― Bauvard...    
    
    
    The Universal Translator Is Real and Its Name Is Sigmo http://buff.ly/1fnbTqc  #Technology #innovation    
    
    
    Discover ways to help society by developing innovative materials used in the healthcare, pharmaceutical, agriculture, textile, &...    
    
    
    Does anyone use Viber? http://buff.ly/18ZIgdD  #technology #app #STEM #innovation    
    
    
    Did you know...Yahoo was involved in making the Siri app? http://buff.ly/18ZInpj  #technology #innovation    
    
    
    Still have some people left on your Christmas list? Mac Pro goes on sale! http://buff.ly/1hokKcq  #Apple #mac #technology    
    
    
    Amazing plate showing fossilized remains of Uintarcinus socials crinoids! Found at http://buff.ly/JIgJDK  #science pic.twitter.com/TyfFULTmha    
    
    
    Wow. Great share! @thomsonreuters: CHART: The number of hacking attacks on U.S. businesses since 2005: http://bit.ly/1cFLVel     
    
    
    Quick Infographic 101 breakdown for you via @GynzyUS: Infographics are everywhere, but do you – and your students – know how to read...    
    
    
    Work in a professional help desk and network administration environment! #career #technology #STEM    
    
    
    @MPRnews Privacy is extremely important to me. Thank you for sharing the great article!    
    
    
    Have you gotten your #HourOfCode in today? #Coding #tech #computer    
    
    
    awesome! @msftcitizenship: #FollowFriday to youth #STEM super stars @FridayInstitute @washingtonstem @EDUCTO @DIYGirls    
    
    
    Still have people on your Christmas list? Here's some awesome gift ideas via @techsavvymama: #STEM holiday gift! littleBits Kits Teach...    
    
    
    Excited to have some new followers! Thank you for following us @msftcitizenship @YouTernMark @STEMclubs @TheNextSiValley!    
    
    
    Great question! It's going to be a long journey, but we can do this! @janelmwrites: Q4: How can we change those existing...    
    
    
    Calling all 2yr & 4 yr #cyber college students interested in getting hands-on experience, Apply here:  http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    Can I get some love from my #STEM peeps? Follow us on Facebook! https://www.facebook.com/IHCCSTEM  #SocialMedia #womenintech #Science    
    
    
    Exciting stuff. I really admire the work being done for this. @DavidWSeattle: Worth a very careful look: Well informed & ambitious new...    
    
    
    Eye cells can now be inkjet-printed..could lead to cures for certain blindness. http://buff.ly/19B3Wx6  #science pic.twitter.com/mWUgr9z6d0    
    
    
    Amazing images of asteroid Vesta!! http://buff.ly/19B3TBA  #science #discovery #STEM    
    
    
    DHS Announces Expansion of Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative | Homeland Security http://buff.ly/1fs9uun  #Student #volunteers #DHS    
    
    
    My Daughter's Career in Tech: a Futurespective of a Life Yet to be Lived http://www.projecteve.com/marily-nika-tedx-script-my-daughters-career-in-tech-a-futurespective-of-a-life-yet-to-be-lived/ …    
    
    
    DHS announces 2014 Secretary’s Honors Program (SHP) #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative for college students http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Thanks for sharing! @ForbesTech: 14 bad tech habits to break in 2014 http://onforb.es/1jA3o0H     
    
    
    My Daughter's Career in Tech: a Futurespective of a Life Yet to be Lived - Project Eve http://buff.ly/1d3kHll  #Tech #womenintec #STEM    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative has 100+ student volunteer assignments open @dhs_ice, @tsa @USCG, etc. http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Everyone LOVES #food! Follow our #Pinterest Eat Science Board! #socialmedia #science http://ow.ly/rFy0h     
    
    
    Acting Sect. Rand Beers "DHS is excited SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative...increasing engagement w/ students” http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Calling all 2yr & 4 yr #cyber college students interested in getting hands-on experience, Apply here:  http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP  #student...    
    
    
    Stay warm out there #Minnesotans! #cold #winter #holiday    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative is developing next gen. #cyber leaders & talent. Apps close 1/3/14 http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    DHS’s SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative is meant to attract the best & brightest #cyber talent http://goo.gl/0ABzRV  #Student...    
    
    
    #Cyber Students, do you desire to protect & secure our Nation while building a rewarding career? Apply http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP  #students...    
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrRq  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    IHCCSTEM wishes everyone a Merry #Christmas! #holiday    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative volunteer positions begin spring 2014 & cont. thru summer 2014 Apply:  http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    Wow!! That is exciting! @HuffPostScience: Astronomers say they may have spotted first alien planet http://huff.to/1d3o0sP     
    
    
    Space Walk #2 HAPPENING NOW!! Check it out! http://buff.ly/1g1raOs  #Science #Space pic.twitter.com/twoM0yPxq5    
    
    
    [PHOTO] Sunlight makes cool effect on chair leg http://buff.ly/19MbXPR  #science pic.twitter.com/QG4N2U4QQy    
    
    
    Check out our awesome #Pinterest boards! http://ow.ly/rbsUH  #socialmedia #creative #ideas #STEM    
    
    
    SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative is offering volunteer #cyber assignments @ 60+ DHS nationwide locations http://go.usa.gov/ZYj5 ...    
    
    
    Did you get a iPad for Christmas? Here are 11 Best Apps to download! http://buff.ly/19Mc127  #tech #Christmas #present #App    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative is developing next gen. #cyber leaders & talent. Apps close 1/3/14 http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Sounds like good news to us! Awesome! @TechCrunch: Code․org: 2 Weeks And 600M+ Lines Of Code Later, 20M Students Have Learned An "Hour Of...    
    
    
    This is something EVERYONE should read and know. Thanks for the great share via @lifehacker: Worried about card skimming at the gas pump?...    
    
    
    Great list! @edworkspartners: Top Scientific Discoveries of 2013 http://edwks.org/0_t  via @wiredscience #Science #STEM    
    
    
    [PHOTO] Beautiful Glacial Cave in the Canadian Rockies. http://buff.ly/19jMVXX  #discovery #landscape #glaciers pic.twitter.com/NDR5drqZMx    
    
    
    #Cyber students in SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative will work w/ DHS #cyber professionals to gain invaluable hands-on experience    
    
    
    Have you ever wondered how many bacteria live in your body? http://buff.ly/19jN9y8  #facts #science #health #biology    
    
    
    Are you a big gamer? 6 exciting gaming trends to watch for in 2014. http://buff.ly/1hGDHHm  #tech #game #innovation #2014    
    
    
    Want to feel like a "superhero"? Smart Glasses will give you that "power." http://buff.ly/1hGDLqB  #tech #SmartGlasses #superhero #innovation    
    
    
    Do you take multivitamins? This study shows that they may be a waste of money. http://buff.ly/1hGEQig  #multivitamins #health #science    
    
    
    Looking for some experience? DHS is now taking applications for their 2014 Secretary's Honor Program (SHP) Cyber Student Volunteer...    
    
    
    SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative allows #college students to gain experience in exciting #cyber fields like cyber threat analysis.    
    
    
    Make an impact; Apply to 2014 Secretary’s Honors Program #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative for college students http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    #Cyber Students, do you desire to protect & secure our Nation while building a rewarding career? Apply http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    What Makes Girls Fall In Love With Computers And Code? http://techcrunch.com/2013/12/29/what-makes-girls-fall-in-love-with-computers-and-code/?ncid=twittersocialshare … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    What makes girls fall in love with computers and code? http://buff.ly/JENdi8  #coding #computers #tech #womenintech    
    
    
    The SHP #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative has 100+ student volunteer assignments open @dhs_ice, @tsa @USCG, etc. http://goo.gl/0ABzRV     
    
    
    Don't know what #STEM program you want to enroll in? We can help! Take this survey to find out! http://buff.ly/18TAdkJ  #college #education    
    
    
    Google's Chromebooks have hit their stride - http://buff.ly/JENB04  #Google #tech #Chromebook    
    
    
    Make an impact; Apply to 2014 Secretary’s Honors Program #Cyber Student Volunteer Initiative for college students http://go.usa.gov/ZYDP     
    
    
    If you haven't done so already, Like us on #Facebook! http://ow.ly/rbrSl  #socialmedia #STEM #college #education #students    
    
    
    Happy New Year's Eve!    
    
    
    