Such a sweet painting! Happy to sell a giclee of it! http://fb.me/1uPPiRMne     
    
    
    Unnamed Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tCXe9     
    
    
    Red Desert Horse by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tFrfs     
    
    
    Arabians in the Desert Progression Horse Painting By A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tHP2z     
    
    
    Arabians in the Desert Progression Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tK8uG     
    
    
    Arabian Gold, Horse Painting of Four Black Arabian Horses by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tO2g6     
    
    
    Arabian Gold in Progress Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tQb9n     
    
    
    Arabian Gold Horse Painting, by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tRN9g     
    
    
    Appaloosa Sketch from my Book, A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tU4g0     
    
    
    Bear and Fish Sketch by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/tXn2P     
    
    
    Roses Heart to Heart by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/u0kL8     
    
    
    Looking to the Light I am Free, Horse Sketch by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/u2Kui     
    
    
    Midnight Sun Dance24 x 30 Oil on Canvas    ©Laurie Pace    Graphics One Design 1998-2012  Contact me for your own co... http://nblo.gs/u6JI0     
    
    
    Fresh from the studio today!  Visit the painting and close ups at... http://fb.me/BgXNt2af     
    
    
    Another Collection starter at $199. http://fb.me/1IfuKfPVS     
    
    
    The Progression of a Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/u8Dqk     
    
    
    Tales of Texas in progress... 8 x 10 oil on Panel hopefully finished tomorrow. Painted three or four hours today.... http://fb.me/I0WZMtbD     
    
    
    Old Tales of Texas, Cowboy Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/u9Tjo     
    
    
    Pony Up 1 by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Horse Paintings and Equine Art for Sale http://nblo.gs/ufmu5     
    
    
    Flower Pop, Flower Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uinJQ     
    
    
    HORSE PAINTING GIVE AWAY BY A TEXAS ARTIST LAURIE PACE http://nblo.gs/umpR8     
    
    
    Blue Horse  Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/urE5C     
    
    
    The Journey of Three Arabians, Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/utycf     
    
    
    Cypress Watering Hole Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uEWEn     
    
    
    Three at the Watering Hole, Signature Painted Pony, Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uI9kM     
    
    
    This is the beginning stages for a commission painting I am doing for a client in the UK.  We went through four... http://fb.me/1M53Lu3Ku     
    
    
    Progression of Arabian Horse Painting Equine Art by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uKahv     
    
    
    Progression on Three Arabian Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uNhVH     
    
    
    Arabian Horse Painting in Progress by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uOtiW     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057922758496/ … http://issuu.com/CFAI.co/docs/visual_language_april_2012_cfai.co/1 …    This is our Second Edition of Visual Language.. ENJOY!    
    
    
    Spirt With Us is finished. I completed the collector single edition hard back book today that will mail out with... http://fb.me/W1lvAK4c     
    
    
    Spirit With Us, Three Arabian Horses Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uSpma     
    
    
    Moose Art on Paper by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uV23k     
    
    
    Early Sunflowers, Oil Painting of Yellow Sunflowers by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uXqEy     
    
    
    Currently reading http://issuu.com/CFAI.co/docs/visual_language_vol_2_april_2012_cfai/1 … NEW Magazine is out. Liz Hill is on the cover.    
    
    
    Winter Appaloosa Lights by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/uZvra     
    
    
    Determined, Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/v2kMe     
    
    
    Tomorrow morning, MONDAY, will be a small horse painting giveaway posted on my blog.  Visit the blog for the link... http://fb.me/18xYeGO4K     
    
    
    BLUE HORSE Painting Giveaway, by a Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/v45yy     
    
    
    Trotter, Horse drawing on Paper, by a Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/v6x1x     
    
    
    Moonlight Crossing Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/v9bBF     
    
    
    Beginnings of a new abstract painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vcuzn     
    
    
    Progression of Abstract Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/veQsj     
    
    
    The Abstract Painting Continues by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vgUsi     
    
    
    Mason's Abstract Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vj9BA     
    
    
    Daiden's Canvas Abstract Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vllAm     
    
    
    Elijah's Panel Abstract Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vnweE     
    
    
    Girl on Sand Painting Figurative Art by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vq6zV     
    
    
    Horse Painting in Progress by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vtzjq     
    
    
    Progress on Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vwyfn     
    
    
    Leap of Faith, abstract Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vAG2T     
    
    
    Three at the Watering Hole, Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vCJeB     
    
    
    Dog and Cat Portrait in colors by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vFHPU     
    
    
    Cat and Dog Painting Portrait Progression by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vIegx     
    
    
    Progression Dog and Cat Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vL6iO     
    
    
    Cat and Dog Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vOpL2     
    
    
    Where were you when they crucified my Lord? Painting of my Heart, A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vShpe     
    
    
    Dog and Cat portrait almost done! By A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vUS06     
    
    
    Cat and Dog portrait by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/vXGqt     
    
    
    Coco and Lucky Portrait complete by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/w0guU     
    
    
    Snowball Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/w2M5J     
    
    
    Shhh...the new issue was released FIVE days early. Nancy Medina is our cover artist; catch the art review of Utah... http://fb.me/1v7tLyyO9     
    
    
    Todays Horse Contest Give Away requires you to submit an email to me. Sheriff Paul Fletcher will draw the winning... http://fb.me/1s9w9a4KV     
    
    
    Snowball by Lady L, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/w6hzB     
    
    
    Beginnings for Lady L, Her first REAL Painting.  Proud Oma, Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/w8HnL     
    
    
    Flower Painting on Blue by Lady L, Mini Me of Oma, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wa8H8     
    
    
    This painting was almost complete when I decided to scrape the canvas last week... stay tuned and next post will... http://fb.me/1wmVExIy0     
    
    
    This is OLD RED appearing from a scraped canvas... which is really pretty cool with the undertones coming... http://fb.me/1hfdCsLmj     
    
    
    Three Horses on the Bridge, Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wbOEA     
    
    
    Working on a longhorn today for my Dallas Art Gallery. http://fb.me/19JC7uWDX     
    
    
    Old Red Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wfnIo     
    
    
    Mid Morning Get Away Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/whV6k     
    
    
    Longhorn in Progress, Longhorn Bevo Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wkqCW     
    
    
    INTO THE LIGHT will be at Mirada Fine Art in about a month. 28 x 42 inches of thick palette knife oil. I can send... http://fb.me/GtOL1Jti     
    
    
    This is my Horse Book for 2012. http://fb.me/1SwccE2Lp     
    
    
    Into the Light Contemporary Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wqg4I     
    
    
    Reworked and finished. 18 x 27 x 2 inches, sides are painted, ready to hang.  Morning Get Away. When they hang in... http://fb.me/1ePzzojkp     
    
    
    NOt sure where I am going with this yet...it is in progress to Andrew Swift's music, son of artist Sallie-Anne Swift http://fb.me/1jxv7H4G6     
    
    
    Adding more color and texture.... 30 x 40 x 2 inches. Solid Oil no Impasto.  Spirit Paint Fury http://fb.me/Y7krb3ez     
    
    
    White Daisy Painting by Lady L from Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wrOSa     
    
    
    Morning Get Away Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wwDXS     
    
    
    On my Easel Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wzDmC     
    
    
    Horse Painting in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wCiEM     
    
    
    Fury Horse Painting Completed! By Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wELQv     
    
    
    Crowning the Hill, A Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wHEVk     
    
    
    Landscape sketch Painting on Canvas by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wJKTj     
    
    
    Longhorn Sketches by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wLykB     
    
    
    Longhorn Sketches for Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wOcTD     
    
    
    Longhorn Sketches for Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wRCuo     
    
    
    Blue Hills First Base Coat by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wUqM6     
    
    
    Blue Hills Palette Knife Landscape Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wWRDk     
    
    
    Blue Hills progresses, Landscape Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/wZfwX     
    
    
    Blue Hills A Palette Knife Landscape by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/x1G9x     
    
    
    Longhorn Painting on canvas by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/x3oOV     
    
    
    Blue Hills Palette Knife Landscape By Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/x5Ls0     
    
    
    Longhorn Painting in progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/x8Onu     
    
    
    Big Tree Longhorns One by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xbGx5     
    
    
    Big Tree Longhorn Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xe74A     
    
    
    The Boys, Portrait by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xgiBC     
    
    
    Just sold RED SHOED PONIES at Mirada Fine Art. Thank you Steve. http://fb.me/1P6SRgB6S     
    
    
    Back to the Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xiXwZ     
    
    
    Enclosed, Nude Abstract Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xkRiR     
    
    
    Red Shoed Pony Painting Sold at Mirada Fine Art, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xna4S     
    
    
    Empowered by the Father, Words of my Heart by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://j.mp/IWa2qd     
    
    
    "Wine Cups and Indian Blankets" - An original 8x6 inch landscape oil painting by George De Chiara http://j.mp/LFk1pT     
    
    
    Fragments of Thought - Original Abstract by Filomena de Andrade Texas Contemporary Artist http://j.mp/LFkuZ6     
    
    
    Indian Blanket by Sheri Jones http://j.mp/LFl0X7     
    
    
    Enclosed Abstract Nude by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://j.mp/LFl616     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923089225/ … Visual Language Magazine from CFAI.co    International Contemporary Fine Art    
    
    
    Longhorn two Painting on the canvas, A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xqgoy     
    
    
    Artists of Texas: http://bit.ly/JAwerW     
    
    
    Longhorn 2 Painting continues, by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xtEY0     
    
    
    Thick layering of Paint Longhorn Painting Two by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xw9Bb     
    
    
    We are at 3000 readers! http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visual_language_vol_1_no_4?mode=window=%23222222 … http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923103492/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    http://robincheers  http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visual_language_vol_1_no_4?mode=window=%23222222 … http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923103492/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    http://artistsofarizona.blogspot.com  http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visual_language_vol_1_no_4?mode=window=%23222222 … http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923103492/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    My new Pony book is out for 2012. The Spirit of the Paint. http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923103492/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    http://ArtistsofAlabama.blogspot.com  http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visual_language_vol_1_no_4?mode=window=%23222222 … http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923103492/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    SALLIE-ANNE SWIFT http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visual_language_vol_1_no_4?mode=window=%23222222 … http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923103492/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visual_language_vol_1_no_4?mode=window=%23222222 … http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923103492/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Jeanne Illenye http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visual_language_vol_1_no_4?mode=window=%23222222 … http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923103492/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    In the Garden Painting Children, by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xydQN     
    
    
    Reunion Impressionistic Painting in the Garden by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xA9Ao     
    
    
    Wolves of Snake River Painting in Progress By Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xEX8N     
    
    
    Of the Evening   24 x 30 inches nude  just finished in the studio...or close to finished. http://fb.me/1JGKYuKAa     
    
    
    Wolf Painting continued by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xHtEe     
    
    
    Values and Contrast Snake River Wolf Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xKRcI     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923132017/ … $500 cash prise best of show. OPEN to all artists.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923132155/ … Texas Contemporary Fine Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    Wolves of Snake River in progress, Wolf Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xNywM     
    
    
    Wolves of Snake River, Wildlife Wolf Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xPEUx     
    
    
    Begonia Flower Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xRbnT     
    
    
    His Morning Glories: Burst into Bloom Morning Glories http://hismorningglories.blogspot.com/2012/05/burst-into-bloom-morning-glories.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923149963/ … $149 First Painting of Summer Horses 100 days of color painting horses  Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    Of the Evening Nude Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xU2wb     
    
    
    White Wind Horse Painting by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/xWwBE     
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting One, One Hundred Horse Paintings the Colors of Summer 2012 , by A Texas Artist ... http://nblo.gs/xYhLh     
    
    
    Summer Horse 2 Painting, One Hundred Horse Paintings for One Hundred Days of Summer for $100, by A Te... http://nblo.gs/y0UNF     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923173677/ … 100 days of 100 horses for $100 each from Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting 3, One Hundred Horse Paintings for One Hundred Days of Summer for $100  by Texa... http://nblo.gs/y36We     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923178666/ … CFAI Figurative Summer show open to ALL artists. 500 dollars best of Show first prize.    
    
    
    Summer Horse 4 , 100 Horses of Summer for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/y5bKL     
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting 5, 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/y6Cme     
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting 6, 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each by a Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/y89c7     
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting 7 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/y9YWr     
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting 8 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yc4OK     
    
    
    August 11th, Dutch Art Gallery in Dallas I will be teaching a one day workshop with the Palette knife.  Come join... http://fb.me/1IGnSAqU3     
    
    
    Summer Horse Two for $100  I have already sold One, Six and Seven. http://fb.me/1NBsj6Gj1     
    
    
    Summer Horse Three for $100. http://fb.me/17QNraZko     
    
    
    Summer Horse Four for $100 http://fb.me/uqQAvQz8     
    
    
    Summer Horse 9, 100 horse paintings in 100 Days from Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yedfB     
    
    
    Summer Horse 11 , 100 Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ygwsO     
    
    
    Summer Horse 12, 100 Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yiQTy     
    
    
    Summer Horse 10, 100 horses of summer by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ykm9s     
    
    
    Summer Horse 13, 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each, by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ym16c     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923234197/ … Colors on George Ayers Palette CFAI.co    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923234209/ … Interview with cfai.co artist Joe Mancuso    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923234215/ … Mujer-de-Mercado by Susan Santiango  Time to submit work to the CFAI.co juried show. There is a $500 for best of show.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923234221/ … Art Challenge – May 2012 – “Sunshine” — Contemporary Fine Art International  BEST OF SHOW! Carol Peterson    
    
    
    Summer Horse 14, 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yoeUQ     
    
    
    This sold today to a new owner in Colorado. Thank you! http://fb.me/1XT4McyyF     
    
    
    This sold today to a new collector in California. Thank you! http://fb.me/1I13QhkfL     
    
    
    Just sold on Cfai.co. Thank you!!! http://fb.me/zjE43Qmp     
    
    
    Summer Horse 15 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yqCqh     
    
    
    Just finished this yesterday entitled RELATIONSHIPS and it is 22 x 28 and available.  Sounds like a relationship... http://fb.me/1J3XkZTXk     
    
    
    Summer Horse 16 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each, by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ysRVY     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923253665/ … 24 x 36 Sunlight Play newly painted and posted for sale on CFAI.co by Texas Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    Summer Horse 17  Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace  100 horses for 100 days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/yvfgv     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923255398/ … 100 Horse Paintings in !00 Day for $100 each. A Texas Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923255615/ … JUST RELEASED! http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visual_language_vol_1_no_5?mode=window=%23222222 …    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923257480/ … Summer Horse No 17 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    Laurie Pace sold a 16.00" x 16.00" print on http://FineArtAmerica.com ! http://fineartamerica.com/saleannouncement.html?id=3d306d66825309b5cde202f526244931 … via @fineartamerica    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923258174/ … Summer Horse 3 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace $100    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923260336/ … Summer Horse no 20 from Texas Artist Laurie Pace $100    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923260338/ … Summer Horse Nine by Texas Artist Laurie Pace $100    
    
    
    Summer Horse 18,100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yxTuI     
    
    
    Summer Horse 19, 100 Horses for 100 Days for $100 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yAbQm     
    
    
    Summer Horse Twenty, 100 Horses for 100 Days for $100 each by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yCLej     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923274027/ … 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days of Summer for $100 from Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923274032/ … $450 from Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    Summer Horse 21 100 horse paintings for 100 Days for $100 each by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yFqk1     
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting 27 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yH5rX     
    
    
    Summer Horse 22 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 Each by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yIgP9     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923288628/ … Another wonderful original from three yr old Lady L.  Check out the video of this painting from sketch to canvas.    
    
    
    Summer Horse 23 , 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 each, by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yKXzX     
    
    
    Summer Horse 9 of 100 Horses for 100 days of Summer for $100 http://fb.me/1aXlkj4i5     
    
    
    Summer Horse 22 http://fb.me/1ZDK1g7y8     
    
    
    Summer Horse 24 by Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/yNu2c     
    
    
    Summer Horse 25 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/yQ1Nv     
    
    
    Summer Horse 26 by Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horse paintings for 100 days of summer for $1... http://nblo.gs/yRHS4     
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting no 27 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yTwIK     
    
    
    Summer Horse Painting no 28 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yW8UX     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923326887/ … Summer Horse 31   100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100  by Laurie Pace    
    
    
    Summer Horse 31 By Texas Artist Laurie Pace... 9 x 12 http://fb.me/25fkAB5Hj     
    
    
    Summer Horse 27 by Laurie Pace http://fb.me/1ZHqGEM8W     
    
    
    Summer Horse 29    
    
    
    Summer Horse 26 http://fb.me/1SglnnV43     
    
    
    Summer Horse 3 http://fb.me/1QjRmUjWr     
    
    
    I have sold all but three of the 31 horse paintings done this month.  Please stop by and see if there is one left... http://fb.me/1XBM3agfF     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923329046/ … $100 on CFai.co by Kimberly Conrad. Stunning Collectible Art    
    
    
    Summer Horse 29 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/yYZ02     
    
    
    Listed it on CFAI.co tonight and it sold within a minute. Thank you! http://fb.me/17a4rOE7Q     
    
    
    Summer Horse 33 just sold as well..only up for maybe 30 seconds... but going to a wonderful home. Thank you.... http://fb.me/1LFGezZ6x     
    
    
    Summer Horse 30, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/z1FFs     
    
    
    @DrTCB2010  Good to see you on Twitter Dr B    
    
    
    Summer Horse 31 from Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/z4jSo     
    
    
    Available! Summer horse 36.  Just posted. http://fb.me/1TvWF3MMG     
    
    
    Just posted Summer Horse 37 and it sold immediately. Thank you! http://fb.me/1PJbn6zAo     
    
    
        
    
    
    Summer Horse 32 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/z6FlJ     
    
    
    Summer Horse 33 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 http://nblo.gs/z8sbx     
    
    
    His Morning Glories: Abundance in His Morning Glories http://hismorningglories.blogspot.com/2012/06/abundance-in-his-morning-glories.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Summer Horse 34, by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zasnM     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923365162/ … Todays $100 painting from Laurie Pace on CFAI.co  SUMMER HEAT  100 horse paintings in 100 summer days for $100 each    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923365267/ … Summer Horse 39  100 days of 100 Horse Paintings for $100 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    Summer Horse 39... the last for tonight. http://fb.me/1CLm7iRVz     
    
    
    Summer Horse 35 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zd7ah     
    
    
    Summer Horse 36 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zfM8F     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923380822/ … Summer Horse 40, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. Texas Artist Laurie Pace    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923380906/ … Summer Horse 41 from Texas Artist Laurie Pace. 100 horses in 100 days for $100 each.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923381503/ … 22 x 28 inches of incredible color from Texas Artist Laurie Pace. $2250 RELATIONSHIPS.. gotta see it to understand it!    
    
    
    Summer Horse 37 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zhRkH     
    
    
    Summer Horse 38, by Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for  ... http://nblo.gs/zl45j     
    
    
    Support CFAI in obtaining grant money for our artists... http://lnkd.in/Q3VvwP     
    
    
    PLEASE go vote for CFAI  Sacramento location for us to be considered for a grant for our artists. http://fb.me/2dvOVwfJn     
    
    
    Mission: Small Business℠: http://bit.ly/OJyySW     
    
    
    https://www.missionsmallbusiness.com/      Please go vote for CFAI to help promote Artists around the world! http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923394863/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Summer Horse 39, by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse paintings in 100 days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/znzWv     
    
    
    ©Laurie Pace   Graphics One Design 1998-2012Contact Laurie for Commission work or to purchase a paint... http://nblo.gs/zoPKI     
    
    
    Summer Horse 40 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horse paintings for 100 days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zpFhl     
    
    
    Summer Horse 41 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horse paintings for 100 days of summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zs0sT     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923408953/ …  This is summer horse 41 from 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 and is available.    
    
    
    NOW AVAILABLE.. Summer Horse 41. $100 http://fb.me/21csk0lFE     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923410172/ … july 2012 Southwest Art Ad featuring some incredible artists.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923410325/ … Read about Texas Artist George DeChiara at CFAI.co    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923410335/ … Missouri Artist Lorrie Boydston is a featured artist on CFAI.co Colors on my Palette.    
    
    
    Summer Horse 42 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/zuOfI     
    
    
    Summer Horse 43 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zxhg4     
    
    
    Summer Horse 44 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zzz38     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923426946/ … 100 horse paintings or 100 days  of Summer for $100 each    
    
    
    Summer Horse 45 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zC5G2     
    
    
    Summer Horse 46 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 Each. http://nblo.gs/zE0lS     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923440876/ … Energy 100 horse paintings for 100 days for $100.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923441914/ … Big John    
    
    
    Summer Horse 47 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings in 100 days of summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/zFtpf     
    
    
    Summer Horse 48 from Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horses for 100 summer days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zH8md     
    
    
    Summer Horse 49 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horses for 100 days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/zIXHb     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923460985/ … NuMedica: Total Vegan Protein Shake Vanilla ... Terry and I use it every day!    
    
    
    Summer Horse 50 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/zKVGb     
    
    
    Summer Horse 51 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/zNbKm     
    
    
    Summer Horse 52 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/zPwdy     
    
    
    Summer Horse 53, By Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horse paintings in 100 days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zRMjd     
    
    
    Summer Horse 54, By Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/zTtMp     
    
    
    Summer Horse 55 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/zVtc8     
    
    
    Summer Horse 56 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/zY0UL     
    
    
    Summer Horse 52... still available. http://fb.me/19czn2Oxk     
    
    
    Summer Horse 55 Still available. All others are sold! Watch my blog tomorrow at 7 am central time for the next in... http://fb.me/VJ92zVjR     
    
    
    Summer Horse 57 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings in 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/A0Cy1     
    
    
    Summer Horse 58 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/A3wnr     
    
    
    Laurie Pace sold a 11.88" x 12.00" print on http://FineArtAmerica.com ! http://fineartamerica.com/saleannouncement.html?id=d6a418bf70848dae4988e25bc02f40e7 … via @fineartamerica    
    
    
    Summer Horse 59 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/A5Mn3     
    
    
    Summer Horse 60 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/A7Lf1     
    
    
    Summer Horse 61 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 http://nblo.gs/A9KAo     
    
    
    Summer Horse 62 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/Ac58L     
    
    
    Summer Horse 63 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AeFMb     
    
    
    Summer Horse 64 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horse paintings in 100 days of summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/Ah68p     
    
    
    Drew Brees Football Sweeps http://wildfireapp.com/     
    
    
    This is the only unsold of the series so far... it needs a home.... http://fb.me/1erhbFLKF     
    
    
    Working on this one right now... may or may not be done yet. http://fb.me/19rC1tEyG     
    
    
    Summer Horse 65 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horse paintings in 100 days of summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/AiZsO     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923575836/ … 100 Horses in 100 days for $100 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace Horse #65    
    
    
    Summer Horse 66 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horse paintings in 100 days of summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/AkUGc     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923582227/ … Still available at $100    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923582235/ … New one for today $100  for 100 horses in 100 Days by L Pace    
    
    
    Summer Horse 67 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horses for 100 days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/AntX5     
    
    
    Summer Horse 68 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horses for 100 days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AoJjF     
    
    
    Summer Horse 69 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horses for 100 days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/AqcSv     
    
    
    Summer Horse 70 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horses for 100 days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/As0mQ     
    
    
    Summer Horse 71 By Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horses in 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AtPwT     
    
    
    Summer Horse 72 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horses for 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/Azw2G     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923618469/ … See all issues of Visual Language on http://issuu.com     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923618534/ … See some of our incredible VL issues here.    
    
    
    Summer Horse 73 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/ABLpC     
    
    
    Today's horse of the day... is still available. http://fb.me/161j8jt9t     
    
    
    Yesterdays is still available. Look at the close ups on this one! http://fb.me/1GUwlK9Zh     
    
    
    Summer Horse 74 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horses in 100 days of summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/ADHse     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923629660/ … Just sold number 74 this morning! 100 Horses for 100 days... only one of the series is unsold so far!    
    
    
    Summer Horse 75 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days for $100 each http://nblo.gs/AFbC0     
    
    
    Summer Horse 76 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AGHgq     
    
    
    Summer Horse 77 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AINBY     
    
    
    This one just posted today and is available. http://fb.me/1gFgWyQL2     
    
    
    Number 68 is still available. I have sold 75 out of 77 horses to date. http://fb.me/1uyV6XmDP     
    
    
    Summer Horse 78 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AKUMI     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923658620/ … Visual Language Vol 1 No 7 CFAI.co Sept 2012    JUST RELEASED!    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/163114817724679123/ … Visual Language Vol 1 No 7 CFAI.co Sept 2012    
    
    
    http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visuallanguagesept12?mode=window=%23222222 …   Roxanne Steed from CFAI.co http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923658860/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visuallanguagesept12?mode=window=%23222222 …  Hall Groat II Art Review of Judy Crowe http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923658885/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    http://issuu.com/cfai.co/docs/visuallanguagesept12?mode=window=%23222222 …   Texas Artist Barbara Jones on CFAI.co http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923658913/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    We have chosen Forks over Knives http://j.mp/RBQJeM     
    
    
    Summer Horse 79 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AN52D     
    
    
    Summer Horse 80 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/APjbx     
    
    
    No 79 is available.  Beautiful thick layering on this. click through for the closeups. http://fb.me/2dZ3jUMkb     
    
    
    Today's horse is number 80... and it is also available.  100 Horses in 100 Days for $100 each. The book covering... http://fb.me/Dk3sF8fN     
    
    
    Summer Horse 81 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/ARkKP     
    
    
    Summer Horse 82 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AT3uI     
    
    
    Summer Horse 83 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AUPgJ     
    
    
    Summer Horse 84 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/AX9rY     
    
    
    Summer Horse 85 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/AZCSu     
    
    
    Summer Horse 86 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/B1Wme     
    
    
    Two Day Equine Palette Knife Workshop in Dallas Oct 12-13th http://fb.me/1Rxq9DDgF     
    
    
    Sold today at Mirada Fine Art in Denver. http://fb.me/1HfhORunL     
    
    
    Sold at Dutch Art in Dallas last week. http://fb.me/BAvaUqGj     
    
    
    Summer Horse 87 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/B4x2Z     
    
    
    Summer Horse 88 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/B6LB9     
    
    
    Summer Horse 89 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/B8AS8     
    
    
    This one is available. Today's Mixed Media http://fb.me/1Ww2u7mxP     
    
    
    Summer Horse 90 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/BarBN     
    
    
    Summer Horse 91 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/BcMcv     
    
    
    Summer Horse 92 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/BfgCo     
    
    
    Summer Horse 93 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/BhCh0     
    
    
    This one is still available. http://fb.me/2mnXoJ3rr     
    
    
    This one sold this morning! Heading for Tennessee. http://fb.me/1kD8jK2FV     
    
    
    Summer Horse 94 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horse Paintings for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/Bk2B0     
    
    
    Summer Horse 95 By A Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/BmmF6     
    
    
    Summer Horse 96 by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 horses painting in 100 days of summer for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/Boexj     
    
    
    Summer Horse 97 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/Bqkzm     
    
    
    All the horses are almost gone for the summer. One remains unsold and there are three left to come out, 98,99 and... http://fb.me/L0S4szMg     
    
    
    Summer Horse 98 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, 100 Horses for 100 Days for $100 each. http://nblo.gs/BsR4B     
    
    
    Summer Horse 99 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace 100 Horses for 100 Days of Summer for $100 each http://nblo.gs/BvuVA     
    
    
    SUMMER HORSE 100...CELEBRATING Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ByjLb     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923795709/ … Visual Language Vol 1 No 7 CFAI.co Sept 2012 with near 20,000 readers!    
    
    
    Paints of Autumn #1  Horse Painting Winds of Autumn by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BB17k     
    
    
    Full Bloom Hydrangea by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BDO23     
    
    
    Paints of Autumn #2  True Color Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BFG5J     
    
    
    Crossing the Plains by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Horse Painting at Mirada Fine Art http://nblo.gs/BHulw     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923822362/ … Visual Language Vol 1 No 7 CFAI.co Sept 2012  HEading to 25,000 readers!    
    
    
    Relationships, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BJm5m     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923831148/ … Paints of Autumn Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace $295  16 x 16    
    
    
    Paints of Autumn Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BL0ys     
    
    
    Paints of Autumn Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BN24g     
    
    
    Paints of Autumn Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BSrqq     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923856626/ … $100 by Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace The Paints of Autumn    
    
    
    Paints of Autumn Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BVbWM     
    
    
    Determined Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BX6M5     
    
    
    Paints of Autumn #7 Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/BZtXS     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923878777/ … $100 Laurie Pace Paints of Autumn    
    
    
    Autumn Floral Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Paints of Autumn http://nblo.gs/C3kwK     
    
    
    Trying out Hoot Suite. Has anyone used it or is using it?    
    
    
    Well I just sent out messages typing it once and it reached Linked In, Google Plus, Facebook and Twitter, pretty darn cool, HootSuite    
    
    
    When I type this one message on HOOTSUITE it goes out everywhere.    
    
    
    Paints of Autumn, Kitchen Counter Collections 2 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/C5ZhP     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923894046/ … CFAI.co Visual Language This was our first issue back in February of 2012. It has had over 134,000 readers.    
    
    
    Just finished a two day paint of this 24 x 36 oil on canvas... Horse of Fire is the title. It is available. http://fb.me/1U3m84EFx     
    
    
    Paints of Autumn Kitchen Counter Series 3, Flower painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/C8nE1     
    
    
    Kitchen Counter Collections 4, Hydrangea Flowers by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CatJK     
    
    
    The Paints of Autumn No 8 Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CduUF     
    
    
    Paints of Autumn 11 Appaloosa by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CfrPv     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923933110/ … From my easel last week... drying.. HORSE OF FIRE.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057923933120/ … Laurie Pace  THE BETA available at Mirada Fine Art in Denver.    
    
    
    Flower Gathering by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Nancy Medina Workshop Painting http://nblo.gs/Ckv9q     
    
    
    Hill Climber Mixed Media on Canvas by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CnLcv     
    
    
    Running in Spirit Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CqR8c     
    
    
    Two at Play becomes Crossing the Plains by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CtDQS     
    
    
    Sunrise Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace Workshop Giveaway in August http://nblo.gs/Cvy0D     
    
    
    Horse of Fire Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CyckS     
    
    
    The Beta, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CBir5     
    
    
    Crowning the Hill Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CEnQ6     
    
    
    Process Painting Landscape by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CH7iP     
    
    
    Progress of Tuscan Scene by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CKr4L     
    
    
    Fields of Red Poppies Tuscan Landscape by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CNfpm     
    
    
    Progress Painting Texas Longhorn by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CPl54     
    
    
    Progress on the Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CRFiU     
    
    
    Progress on the Bevo Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CUNz6     
    
    
    Progress of Bevo Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/CXSup     
    
    
    Longhorn Painting in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/D0Lb0     
    
    
    Progress on Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/D4h9T     
    
    
    Progress Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/D8N9b     
    
    
    Sweet Filly palette knife horse painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace at Mirada Fine Art Denver http://nblo.gs/DetIu     
    
    
    Horns Completed Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DhdQ2     
    
    
    Sailboat in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Justus Pace http://nblo.gs/DmmH3     
    
    
    Continuation of Sailboat painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DpJzn     
    
    
    Summer Sail to Sunset Sailboat Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DtjNT     
    
    
    Last Horse of Summer Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DwC7A     
    
    
    Sunflower Explosion Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DzZFR     
    
    
    Racing the Storm, Sailboat Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DCCWR     
    
    
    Cowboy Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DFg7Z     
    
    
    Watering Hole - Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DIjJ0     
    
    
    Between Two Points, Figurative Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DKDwB     
    
    
    I have started an 8 x 5 foot painting of horses crossing the Rio Grande. It is a commissioned painting for a law... http://fb.me/28zWZG5hR     
    
    
    Progress Sketch Journey of the Rio Grande by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DP680     
    
    
    Not a Step Closer was painted in Feb of 2008. It was purchased as a gift for the woman that owns it. She needs to... http://fb.me/1CW5FVLso     
    
    
    The next step on Rio Grande was the edging in of the first layer of paint. http://fb.me/1myYG0G72     
    
    
    Journey of Horse Painting Rio Grande 8 x 5 ft by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DSZ2D     
    
    
    Journey 3 Horse Painting Rio Grande by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DVne6     
    
    
    Journey of a horse painting Rio Grande by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/DXCBm     
    
    
    Journey of Horse Painting Rio Grande by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/E0Obl     
    
    
    Final Paint Layering, Strength in color Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/E2feD     
    
    
    Journey of a horse painting Rio Grande by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/E3ZRT     
    
    
    Progress Horse Painting San Jacinto River by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/E6iTD     
    
    
    San Jacinto River Crossing, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/E9zhI     
    
    
    San Jacinto River Journey Continues, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EcAJk     
    
    
    San Jacinto River Crossing Horse Painting Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EePwk     
    
    
    San Jacinto River Crossing  A journey in a horse painting with Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EgUUq     
    
    
    San Jacinto River Horse Painting Journey with Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EjP1X     
    
    
    San Jacinto Horse Painting Journey by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ElLKe     
    
    
    San Jacinto River Crossing almost done! Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Eoke7     
    
    
    The Beta Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EqE6O     
    
    
    The Get Away, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Euq1R     
    
    
    The Cowboy, Cowboy Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EwQa7     
    
    
    Time for some special holiday print prices for those special gifts. http://fb.me/1goBpx8Z0     
    
    
    Laurie Pace sold a 24.00" x 20.00" print on http://FineArtAmerica.com ! http://fineartamerica.com/saleannouncement.html?id=57a5bb7e44914398415ab2e06d935d01 … via @fineartamerica    
    
    
    Cowboy in Progress, Cowboy Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EyRQw     
    
    
    Cowboy Painting Continues by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EAU2p     
    
    
    Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EDyUy     
    
    
    Yellow Blooms at Rare Gallery Jackson Hole Wyoming by A Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EFTJN     
    
    
    Gathering figurative painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EIjht     
    
    
    Just finished this one tonight.  30 x 40 inches and brilliant colors in Acrylic this time. See some close ups... http://fb.me/2aiob6x25     
    
    
    First Free Painting Give Away Drawing for Fall, By Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ELUv8     
    
    
    Flowers of Fall, Flower painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EOxfD     
    
    
    Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EQE7I     
    
    
    Actively working on Tree Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ESl7L     
    
    
    Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EVsTS     
    
    
    Second Give Away Painting Drawing by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/EXYtw     
    
    
    Beginnings of STARLIGHT, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/F0t52     
    
    
    Starlight Run Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/F33ly     
    
    
    Starlight Wolf Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/F6bgi     
    
    
    Winter Storm Moving In Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/F80IQ     
    
    
    White Stallion Galloping Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/F9BrP     
    
    
    Headstrong Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FbPEX     
    
    
    Pony Express Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ff0zt     
    
    
    Pony Express Two... Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Fhs1n     
    
    
    Autumn Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FjUKH     
    
    
    Autumn Horse, Palette Knife Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FkdL8     
    
    
    Walk in the Garden, Figurative Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FnfhC     
    
    
    Watering Hole SOLD Horse Painting at Mirada Fine Art, Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FpRaf     
    
    
    Looking Back for Him... Horse Painting sold at Mirada Fine Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FrpTF     
    
    
    Appaloosa in the Wind, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FtdkK     
    
    
    Longhorn Painting, New Pastures by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FwGbv     
    
    
    Sunflower Painting Give Away, By Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FzGYe     
    
    
    Abstract Horse Painting The Get Away by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FCcT7     
    
    
    Challenge Abstract Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FEB23     
    
    
    Abstract Horse Paintings, Indian Paint Pony by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FIcAd     
    
    
    Spirit of Fire Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FJROa     
    
    
    Hydrangea Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FLPuA     
    
    
    Hard Days Work, Roping Painting, Horse, Cow, Cowboy by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FOQcm     
    
    
    A Moment Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FSa7r     
    
    
    Geraniums in Pots by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Flower Painting http://nblo.gs/FUCcd     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924493333/ … Visual Language Contemporary Fine Art presents French Still Life Artists Nicholas Elliott    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924493335/ … Visual Language Contemporary Fine Art features an interview with Colorado Artist John Harrell.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924493338/ … Visual Language Contemporary Fine Art Judy Crowe Winner of the Fall Juried Show at CFAI.co    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924493343/ …  Nancy Eckels in our January Abstract Issue of Visual Language Contemporary Fine Art    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924493348/ … Laurie Pace Art Review by NY Art Critic Hall Groat III Visual Language Contemporary Fine Art    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924493356/ … Elizabeth Chapman Abstracts in Visual Language Contemporary Fine Art    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924496905/ … Over 95,000 impressions already and only out for a week!  Enjoy our newest  Visual Language Contemporary Fine Art    
    
    
    Bowl of Roses, Flower Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FWYly     
    
    
    Dahlia in Bloom, Flower Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/FZQbn     
    
    
    Words of my heart, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/G10Qt     
    
    
    Nine on the Horizon, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/G1IKG     
    
    
    Face of Grace, Child figurative Portrait by Texas Artist Laurie Pace and South Carolina Painter Conni... http://nblo.gs/G3CH7     
    
    
    Limited time and only a few prints available. http://fb.me/1Kz8Soraj     
    
    
    One more 20 x 24 of a favorite from the summer. Only 10 available at this pricing. http://fb.me/1qDDouiuF     
    
    
    My last third piece on sale this week with 10 prints available. http://fb.me/1gAZooWbv     
    
    
    Figurative Painting Girl in Garden by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/G63ah     
    
    
    First Edition Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/G9WYC     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924533924/ … It is free to subscribe to our monthly Visual Language Magazine. Home    
    
    
    Leaving it Behind, Equine Art, Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GeJu6     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924537063/ … Subscribe FREE to once a month digital copies of Visual Language emailed directly to you.    
    
    
    Girl and Goat, Figurative Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ggh78     
    
    
    Late Roses Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Gj5Q8     
    
    
    Words of My Heart, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Gl09s     
    
    
    Keep the Flame burning, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Gmkqf     
    
    
    Abstract Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Go0uF     
    
    
    Magnolias in Bloom, Flower Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GqxyK     
    
    
    Orange Sneakers by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Gsp3K     
    
    
    Passion of Seven Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GurTm     
    
    
    Mountain Pony Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Gx6Yg     
    
    
    Blessings watercolor by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GyrJr     
    
    
    Roses Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GAntx     
    
    
    Secrets Figurative Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GCp8U     
    
    
    The Journey Landscape and Path painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GFtBw     
    
    
    The Baptism, Watercolor painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GJJXT     
    
    
    Wedding Day Pop Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GLhGg     
    
    
    White Flowers by Texas Artist Laurie Pace Flower Painting http://nblo.gs/GOav2     
    
    
    Horse Painting, Free to Run by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GQuID     
    
    
    Horse Painting, the Horse Whisperer, by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GT2bc     
    
    
    White Poppies, Flower Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GVCqB     
    
    
    I started over on my list for newsletters to clean it out this year. Please sign up if you want to receive it... http://fb.me/2nHhrXGxU     
    
    
    Three day Promotional.... http://fb.me/1s22IvZgI     
    
    
    Rose Painting, Flower Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/GYQsk     
    
    
    http://ellepace.com/workshops.html   
Sign up for my newsletter and free giveaways.... http://fb.me/1U8k2hvQK     
    
    
    Pop Art Niki, Commissioned painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/H0Q3K     
    
    
    Contemporary Abstract Landscape, The Other Side of the World, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/H2kVD     
    
    
    Quiet Night With You, Pop Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/H51no     
    
    
    Sunday Morning Color Rose Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/H7wWH     
    
    
    Taylor Ponies, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/H9M2q     
    
    
    Magnolia Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Hc635     
    
    
    Racing Time Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HfPI8     
    
    
    First Horse Painting 2013 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Hig4R     
    
    
    Progress on Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HjMwh     
    
    
    Horse Painting Continues by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HlBEk     
    
    
    Horse Painting in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Hp4aH     
    
    
    Journey Three Early Dawn Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Hrrqp     
    
    
    Started another one... http://fb.me/wNtm0mMa     
    
    
    First the acrylic layering of Naples yellow... and then begin sketching in charcoal http://fb.me/2ccHHHvMK     
    
    
    Bathed in Gold Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HtS8M     
    
    
    Last Push Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HwAJo     
    
    
    River Bank Horse Painting By Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HzENe     
    
    
    Night Snow Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HBgkY     
    
    
    Which Direction Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HD9Jz     
    
    
    It's All Mine, Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HGqnB     
    
    
    Free Calendar Drawing from Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HJ7Oj     
    
    
    Summer Pony in Winter, Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HLpxo     
    
    
    Hesitation Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HNLdz     
    
    
    Midnight Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HR5Wh     
    
    
    Running Through Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HSDPh     
    
    
    Spirited Journey Progression Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HUv3o     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874030/ … Linda McCoy Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874044/ … Barbara Mason   Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874048/ … Holly Hunter Berry Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874067/ … Annie OBrien Gonzales Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874072/ … Jan Clay Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874074/ … Amy Whitehouse Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874077/ … Barbara Churchley   Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874080/ … Pamela Blaies Texas Artist    Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874087/ … Richard Newill   Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874092/ … Richard Newill Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874097/ … Gabriele Bitter Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874100/ … Carol Engles Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874106/ … Kay Crain Missouri Artist  Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874113/ … Carol Nelson Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874117/ … Filomena Booth Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874128/ … Rob Compton Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874136/ … Gibson Pottery and Glass Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874157/ … Suzy Pal Powell Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874178/ … Amy Hillenbrand Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874182/ … Russell McCall Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874196/ … Diane Whitehead Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874200/ … Anne Hines Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874207/ … Mary Jo Zorad Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874210/ … Conni Togel Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874223/ … Marchita Priest Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874227/ … Hall Groat II Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874231/ … Lisa McKinney Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/54958057924874240/ … Dutch Art Gallery Visual Language Magazine Contemporary Fine Art March 2013    
    
    
    Progress of Spirited Journey Horse Painting Gift of Love by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/HWMOP     
    
    
    Spirited Journey Horse Paintings Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/I0giU     
    
    
    A Gift of Love Journey of the Spirit

http://vimeo.com/58417900     
    
    
    Horse Paintings progress, The Spirited Journey by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/I2Un5     
    
    
    Closing in on the finish... Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/I4BOR     
    
    
    White Wind Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/I8dLX     
    
    
    Standing Ground Horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/I8dLW     
    
    
    Big Wolf Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/I9MyB     
    
    
    Nine Strong Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IbC6k     
    
    
    Signature Painted Pony Pull Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IexSZ     
    
    
    Three Horses of Color by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ihd04     
    
    
    Full Bloom Hydrangea Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ijc8n     
    
    
    Confusion, The Good People Series Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IlYXk     
    
    
    Progress Horse Painting Crossing the County Line by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IpdVR     
    
    
    Progress Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IpSbC     
    
    
    Beginnings ...really New ones! Abstract Figurative Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Iu2GQ     
    
    
    Final Image  Crossing the County Line Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Iu2GP     
    
    
    Stepping further with Figurative Abstract by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IxyZ9     
    
    
    Working Wet on Wet finding Figures by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IzvPO     
    
    
    My work can now be seen at The White Dog Gallery in Carbondale, Colorado. http://fb.me/1XdS83Tt3     
    
    
    Now available at The White Dog Gallery http://fb.me/2vegk4EPa     
    
    
    Standing Ground now at The White Dog Gallery  40 x 40 inches http://fb.me/wZWG21wh     
    
    
    From Sketch to Mid way in Figurative abstract Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IBJfr     
    
    
    Close ups of the Figurative Abstract by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ICxIP     
    
    
    Figurative Abstract Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IFBEd     
    
    
    The Good People Figurative Abstract Paintings by Texas Artist Laurei Pace http://nblo.gs/IHcaC     
    
    
    Progress Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IJaLX     
    
    
    Texas Longhorn Painting in progress with Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IMg24     
    
    
    Longhorn Bevo Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IPFwz     
    
    
    Found Love Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IQdGH     
    
    
    Cypress Water Hole Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IRsxO     
    
    
    Descent from Snowy Mountain by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IUjLW     
    
    
    Horse of Fire Abstract  Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IW1mY     
    
    
    Hints of Picasso Flower Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/IXKDd     
    
    
    Sunflower Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/J0jj3     
    
    
    Alpha Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/J3re6     
    
    
    Beta Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/J5byB     
    
    
    Red Moon Winter Solstice Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/J6l2z     
    
    
    Herd over the Hudson Horse Paintings by Texas Equine Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/J840i     
    
    
    Exhausted Female Figurative Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Jbion     
    
    
    Falling into Winter, Abstract Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Jdk81     
    
    
    First Race of Spring Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JffYx     
    
    
    Answering the Call, Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JilCE     
    
    
    Deep in Red Rage Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JkNy3     
    
    
    Koi Digital Art Photography by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JlVMQ     
    
    
    Four Black Horses Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JneR0     
    
    
    Full Circle Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Js5q0     
    
    
    In Awe Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JsB5q     
    
    
    Mountain Herd Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Jug3k     
    
    
    Pony Daze Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JvLwU     
    
    
    Playing for Papa by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JznC1     
    
    
    Race to the Lake Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JBiuN     
    
    
    Horse Two Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JBD2L     
    
    
    Horse One Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JDAsb     
    
    
    Purple Cone Flower Photography by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JH4Qi     
    
    
    Laurie Pace Palette Knife Workshops...Sign up NOW! http://nblo.gs/JPygL     
    
    
    New Beginnings? From Golden Pond Studio, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JQ49w     
    
    
    Second Beginnings?  Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Golden Pond Studio http://nblo.gs/JRpiM     
    
    
    Third Times a Charm?  Horse Paintings from Golden Pond Studio, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JV21c     
    
    
    Losing Direction... a Herd of Five Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace Golden Pond Studio http://nblo.gs/JWYhN     
    
    
    Hesitation 9 x 12 oil on canvas Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/JYvFt     
    
    
    Indian Paint Pony 30 x 30 inches Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/K0voT     
    
    
    Loosing Direction Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/K2Z5v     
    
    
    Losing Direction  30 x 40 Oil on Canvas  AVAILABLE http://fb.me/CYHhPVPH     
    
    
    Horse Sketches for horse painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Golden Pond Studio http://nblo.gs/K4jgT     
    
    
    First Day Progress on Early Morning Race Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Golden Pond Studio http://nblo.gs/K5IoJ     
    
    
    Continued Painting on Early Morning Race Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Golden Pond Studio http://nblo.gs/K7AOm     
    
    
    Continued Painting on Early Morning Race Horse Paintings from Texas Palette Knife Artist Laurie Pace,... http://nblo.gs/Kbggb     
    
    
    Continued Painting on Early Morning Race Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Golden Pond Studio http://nblo.gs/KcXck     
    
    
    Another Horse was Found in Racing the Morning! Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KeSjB     
    
    
    Sunset Journey Sail Boat Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KgQNK     
    
    
    Sail Boat Painting continued by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KiG25     
    
    
    Progress on the Sail Boat Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Kkhbp     
    
    
    Final Sail! Sail Boat Painting completed by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KlTRD     
    
    
    Summer Winds Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KpxKm     
    
    
    The Palette Knife People living tight?  Really? Abstract Figurative on the easel of Texas Artist Laur... http://nblo.gs/Krstd     
    
    
    Palette Knife People adding layers to their lives... By Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KsV4z     
    
    
    Gathering... The Good People are Gathering. Figurative Palette Knife Painting by Texas Artist Laurie ... http://nblo.gs/Ku0Xv     
    
    
    Day Break Commissioned Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KwUcd     
    
    
    Progress on Day Break Commissioned Oil Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KyL4d     
    
    
    Day Break Commissioned Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KAjhB     
    
    
    Day Break Commissioned Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KCdDs     
    
    
    Day Break Commissioned Oil Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KFtAV     
    
    
    Day Break Commissioned Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KGXRZ     
    
    
    Day Break Horse Paintings commission work by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KI2sp     
    
    
    Day Break Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KKIRr     
    
    
    Golden Boy.. in progress....need to know if there is interest in 100 horses in 100 days this summer.... http://fb.me/2Snr2Ueds     
    
    
    MIrada Fine Art bound.  Midsummer Night Gathering... 28 x 42 inches Oil... Oil...Oil layered in about 20 plus... http://fb.me/2tDZ3sWUB     
    
    
    This painting just arrived in Kentucky at South Hill Gallery in Lexington KY.  Go by and see it in person. http://fb.me/EiuGEcfc     
    
    
    Star Light Run is also at South Hill Gallery in Lexington KY.  30 x 40 in gorgeous colors. http://fb.me/2jTKslVjj     
    
    
    Final Night Descent from Snowy Mountain is the third piece now at South Hill Gallery in Lexington, KY.  18 x 27... http://fb.me/Kgv5hGbP     
    
    
    Her Favorite Pink Flowers by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KMFaN     
    
    
    Texas Contemporary Fine Artist Laurie Justus Pace: http://lauriepace.artspan.com/#.UX_ymwNNYh8.twitter …    
    
    
    Golden Boy Horse Paintings in progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KO4Rq     
    
    
    Golden Boy Progresses... Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KPuCf     
    
    
    Golden Boy Breaks through...Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KSUeZ     
    
    
    Summer Horse 82 2012 Pony Series Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KUnl5     
    
    
    Have no clue on the direction. Have done this once, added oils, washed it and brought it back to this state. It... http://fb.me/2MOsfli7r     
    
    
    Summer Solstice Celebration 2013, Good People Series by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KVqaY     
    
    
    Summer Solstice Celebration 2013, Good People Series by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KWysW     
    
    
    Un-Named Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/KZN5A     
    
    
    Not Black or White Horse Paintings in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/L1wC6     
    
    
    Found Love Horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/L32Yb     
    
    
    Hesitation Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/L4UCw     
    
    
    Almost finished... 22 tubes of paint later. http://fb.me/1YfMwibaj     
    
    
    Paint Pony Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/L7OOH     
    
    
    Appaloosa in the Wind, Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/L91vi     
    
    
    Running in Color in Progress but almost done.  Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Lahtd     
    
    
    This was the next step for Green Fields. http://fb.me/30kzwmP4Q     
    
    
    Colors of Wind in Progress Horse painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LdvyG     
    
    
    Green Fields late this morning.  It is 32 x 48 inches and lots of  layers of paint. It is available. http://fb.me/204XPBaag     
    
    
    Weathering the Storm in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Abstract Horse Paintings http://nblo.gs/LfD0F     
    
    
    Final Stretch Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Abstract Horse Paintings http://nblo.gs/Lh74P     
    
    
    The Pear, fruit painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LiK6N     
    
    
    Left Overs Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LmItf     
    
    
    Downhill appears in Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Lngla     
    
    
    IN progress in the studio.... http://fb.me/uposKQwo     
    
    
    I posted 7 photos on Facebook in the album "Downhill" http://fb.me/2Emx4ebK8     
    
    
    Downhill Horse Painting Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LowYG     
    
    
    Downhill Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Lq1VQ     
    
    
    Two in the Sun, Abstract Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LuQ0A     
    
    
    A slide show of a painting for a fund raiser here in Dallas in August... check out the show and then visit the... http://fb.me/2aMsmIvVs     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Painting begins by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Lww7W     
    
    
    The Challenge, a contemporary horse painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Lybgn     
    
    
    Contemporary Figurative Painting, SUMMER SOLSTICE, third painting in THE GOOD PEOPLE SERIES by Texas ... http://nblo.gs/LAz4P     
    
    
    Completed GOLDEN BOY Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LBOmI     
    
    
    Rock Hard 30 x 30 mixed Media, going to Mirada Fine Art in Denver. http://fb.me/2sKAYZ8pH     
    
    
    Rock Hard, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LDgfM     
    
    
    Worked last night for about three hours, frustrated and went to bed... got up and have worked another five... http://fb.me/28XQ1w7fN     
    
    
    Weathering the Storm contemporary horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LGliL     
    
    
    Beginnings of Green Fields Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LIk2C     
    
    
    Day Two Green Fields Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LJGh6     
    
    
    Green Fields Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LL1Zy     
    
    
    Down Hill Final Painting Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LNPwO     
    
    
    Blue Mist Horse Painting in Progress Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LPehC     
    
    
    Blue Mist Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LQPOD     
    
    
    Paintful Painful Journey on Canvas with Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LSmIJ     
    
    
    Visual Language Magazine Vol 2 No 7 July 2013 Contemporary Fine Art http://issuu.com/visuallanguage/docs/visuallanguagemagazinevol2no7july20/1 … via @Issuu    
    
    
    Visual Language Magazine July Issue now out on http://ISSUU.com  http://lnkd.in/xRJPAx  http://lnkd.in/t3dcAV     
    
    
    Final Stretch is now available at South Hill Gallery in Lexington KY  http://southhillgallery.com/?17  http://fb.me/AwIw5qlL     
    
    
    Also new at South Hill Gallery http://southhillgallery.com/?17   This is WEATHERING THE STORM. http://fb.me/1XDbPqCWk     
    
    
    Color Fast Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LVRWq     
    
    
    Color Fast Final Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/LXBex     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace and July Issue of Visual Language Magazine 2013 http://nblo.gs/LYTZZ     
    
    
    Crossing the Meadow Contemporary Knife Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace almost complete! http://nblo.gs/M0jbu     
    
    
    Crossing the Meadow Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/M2JpG     
    
    
    Beginnings Sketch to Canvas Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/M4Evw     
    
    
    Laurie Pace Studio Visit June 2013 #constantcontact http://conta.cc/11taFk8     
    
    
    Laurie Pace Studio Visit June 2013 http://conta.cc/11taFk8  http://fb.me/1vbxKvOL2     
    
    
    Nude Sketch on Canvas by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/M9I5d     
    
    
    Nude Painting UnNamed by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MbB6o     
    
    
    Three in the Sun Contemporary Horse Paintings  by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/McMGM     
    
    
    The Stare Wolf Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MdMK2     
    
    
    Blues Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MgxKR     
    
    
    Crossing the County Line Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MiqqR     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Loosing Direction at Mirada Fine Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MjXD9     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Appaloosa in the Wind at Mirada Fine Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Mlvwc     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Indian Paint Pony at Dutch Art Gallery by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MpkQ8     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Commissioned Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MqTl2     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Relationships by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ms0ZL     
    
    
    VL Artist of the Day http://fb.me/LxogPhDT     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Red Shoed Pony by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MtQIA     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Leap of Faith by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Mx28w     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Into the Light by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MyZY3     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings White Wind by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MACZE     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Journey by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MEd3n     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Mid Morning Get Away by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MFOhw     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Old Red by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MGNa4     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings #1 New Direction by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MHYLX     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings # 2  by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MLlOj     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings #3 Determined by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MNfY8     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings #7 Firecracker by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MOOLM     
    
    
    Beginning of New contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MQd8I     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Wish Upon a Star Rewinding by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MTxvP     
    
    
    Contemporary Horse Paintings Shiny Red Shoes by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MUMxE     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings #4 Surprise by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MVZs7     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings #5 Summer Storm by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/MYbAI     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings #6 Contemplation by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/N11WS     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings #8 Patches by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/N2HQD     
    
    
    Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings #9 Red Eagle by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/N4iZ4     
    
    
    Blaze of Glory, Morning Sun Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/N7oaB     
    
    
    Three Grazing Summer Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Venetian Plaster Mixed Media http://nblo.gs/N8Ivd     
    
    
    Beneath the Branches, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/N9SxO     
    
    
    Three Grazing is moving on... Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Nbxcg     
    
    
    Treasures by the Sea by Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Nf3kq     
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/un-2GY  #in    
    
    
    PROCESS PAINTING by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NgXx2     
    
    
    Captured Blooms by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NiB28     
    
    
    Progress on Colors of the Night Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Nk20B     
    
    
    Colors of Night Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NmY8n     
    
    
    Progress of Summer Nude 1 2013, Palette Knife Nude Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NojQL     
    
    
    Summer Nude 1 2013, Palette Knife Nude Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NpSIc     
    
    
    Standing Ground, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace at The White Dog Gallery, C... http://nblo.gs/Ns1IB     
    
    
    Crossing the County Line, Contemporary Horse Palette Knife Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Nv3la     
    
    
    And Then There were Eight, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NwLgA     
    
    
    Crowning the Hill featured at Mirada Fine Art ~ Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ny5dR     
    
    
    Sun Bathing Buffalo by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Contemporary Wildlife Palette Knife Painting http://nblo.gs/NAFuS     
    
    
    Winter White Wolf Contemporary Wildlife Palette Knife Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NBWmM     
    
    
    When You Wish Upon a Star... your dreams comes true.
32 x 48 inches of stunning color. http://fb.me/2ZFnBl92n     
    
    
    No 12 in the Summer Herd Series 2013  Buy it here:... http://fb.me/Sk5n1Hfu     
    
    
    Appaloosa in the Wind, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NDkgv     
    
    
    Three at the Watering Hole, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NEMAj     
    
    
    Summer Herd 10 Sunset Rising Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NIjjR     
    
    
    JUST WET on the easel... had to share as it made me smile.  No 17 in the group, so I jumped ahead! Could not help... http://fb.me/6ieERxnHj     
    
    
    Racing the Night Summer Herd 11 Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NK6de     
    
    
    12 The Pair, Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NLoyn     
    
    
    13 Sun Stretch Summer Herd 2013, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NMplZ     
    
    
    14 In a Hurry Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NPgQi     
    
    
    15 JUMP Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NQVvc     
    
    
    16 Bow to the Rain Summer Herd 2013 Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NSkrq     
    
    
    Been in the studio... finished one this morning. Promise to post pictures in the next 24 hours.    
    
    
    Started at my workshop and finished here at home today.... http://fb.me/2tQYPgGMB     
    
    
    This is my donated silent auction piece for the Children's Charity this weekend in Dallas.  As a teacher for over... http://fb.me/JY21PdQq     
    
    
    The Painted Ponies began in 2006 as can be tracked all over the internet. 
http://ellepace.com/the-painted-pony.html … http://fb.me/1Rd6GRf43     
    
    
    I have been blogging for 2550 days in a row... missing only one or two over the past ALMOST seven years...... http://fb.me/HQQ7AKC6     
    
    
    Strength of Day Painted at my workshop last weekend in Dallas. http://fb.me/11eBCb5Md     
    
    
    Two at the Raising... also painted at the workshop last weekend.... http://fb.me/LNL4LpgK     
    
    
    Appaloosa in the Wind available through one of my representing galleries in Colorado http://fb.me/1VvDcbAJG     
    
    
    Standing Ground... http://fb.me/6p73v16Fd     
    
    
    Starlight...... http://fb.me/2JRCyW079     
    
    
    Taking the knife doing people like I do horses... The Good People Series began with this one. SOLD Commission... http://fb.me/2IAYd6LGY     
    
    
    Also using the palette knife pull, my wolves that sell in Jackson Hole and in Dallas. This one just sold last... http://fb.me/IhaxnGeD     
    
    
    Crossing the Plains sold at my Colorado Gallery last month as well. Another signature Painted Pony Pull http://fb.me/2M4fWucj0     
    
    
    My Discovery Workshop last weekend. Challenging Artists to go beyond the representational as they approach the... http://fb.me/1vTbeLRol     
    
    
    This was done many years ago and was actually published on a Christmas Card for a law firm in the East. My Winter... http://fb.me/2JHo26K4u     
    
    
    Through the Fall Foliage painted in Oct 2010... http://fb.me/2yzob7yj7     
    
    
    Rites of Spring 7/19/2010... http://fb.me/2gKhbZB7y     
    
    
    Three of Color  6-8-2011... http://fb.me/1M6HXinmW     
    
    
    5/1/2011 Posted on my blog and DP site... Colorado River Ponies... http://fb.me/1UmTpqApM     
    
    
    8/21/2011  Horizon Horses... http://fb.me/1HY6eLEKo     
    
    
    Seven in the Herd  6/30/2010... http://fb.me/1MODAkd5g     
    
    
    Repeat post form last year... I did three 5 x 8 paintings for a law firm in Houston Texas... this is the process... http://fb.me/2hy1PqDLu     
    
    
    My very first painted pony book of my work came out in 2007 on http://Lulu.com  and is still available. http://fb.me/2FB6yHRRR     
    
    
    This is the 2008 book filled with my horses from 2007. http://fb.me/2QCGqSV9T     
    
    
    This is my lulu shop with ALL of my books available.  These books contain the best selected pieces of my work... http://fb.me/6igOUzAUl     
    
    
    Back to the studio tomorrow to paint... heading to dinner with family.    
    
    
    Before I forget.. watch this month for a give away of a mid sized painting on my blog. http://fb.me/1iKZqJ61o     
    
    
    17 Summer Herd 2013 Three Ponies in the Meadow Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NUAws     
    
    
    Three Horses in the Meadow
http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/  http://fb.me/1lRPmLl9V     
    
    
    18 Strength of Day Abstract Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NXPJi     
    
    
    Stop by for the latest available paintings. http://fb.me/2gjcSrbCq     
    
    
    ARTIST OF THE DAY VL and AOT.. PAMELA BLAIES.... http://fb.me/YlyZwmjL     
    
    
    One of the things I have done for years is use my art working with Children, this includes mainstream as well as... http://fb.me/HbXczJiz     
    
    
    A quick note that this page will be unpublished while we are with family the next few weeks.  Blessings to you... http://fb.me/2iNoyxaEX     
    
    
    19 Two at the Raising Contemporary Abstract Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/NZah5     
    
    
    Herd on the Occoquan Overlook Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/O06Wx     
    
    
    Indian Paint Pony Abstract Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/O2MMM     
    
    
    Orange Sneakers, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/O4x6G     
    
    
    Dipping, Figurative Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/O5Xt6     
    
    
    Curb Side Discussion by Texas Artist Laurie Justus Pace http://nblo.gs/O7lAF     
    
    
        
    
    
    Raw Equine Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OaEJ6     
    
    
    Two of a Kind, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ocb4k     
    
    
    Found Love Drawing for a give away painting from Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OddO0     
    
    
    Something on the easel... his name is Tucker... and his rider is Bella. http://fb.me/Hx3M5J2J     
    
    
    Register 4 GIVE AWAY painting 24 x 30 http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/2013/08/found-love-drawing-for-give-away.html …    
    
    
    White Stallion Rules, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Oel8O     
    
    
    more progress on the background of Tucker. http://fb.me/2qD9boqeu     
    
    
    NOt done yet... will sit like this until I put the final icing on... http://fb.me/1OleeHdzY     
    
    
    Appy Two contemporary horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ohufh     
    
    
    Water's Edge Completed by Contemporary Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ohufg     
    
    
    A  Moment Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ojcgo     
    
    
    I have a winner.... Found Love will be flying to South Carolina to it's new home.  Thank you to all who participated. http://fb.me/2D23H3PAm     
    
    
    Tucker Begins Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OkAZ6     
    
    
    Tucker explodes...Horse Paintings at their beginnings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Oms3u     
    
    
    Tucker forms up... Horse Paintings by contemporary fine artists Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OpoFY     
    
    
    Bella's Song Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Oqx1x     
    
    
    Water's Edge in Progress by Texas Contemporary Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OrIII     
    
    
    Water's Edge Complete by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OujvV     
    
    
    Blue Moon Wolf beginnings by Contemporary Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OwBY0     
    
    
    Blue Moon Wolf Contemporary Wolf Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Oy8kz     
    
    
    Beginnings of a new Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OzyH8     
    
    
    New one started... http://fb.me/22X9th7R2     
    
    
    Horse Paintings White Stallion Running by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OCIjU     
    
    
    White Runner  Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ODVnj     
    
    
    Check it out on the blog, and see more details and purchasing here:... http://fb.me/2FNdXzVEE     
    
    
    Painting on the move... Ready to purchase. http://fb.me/2JPEas7xS     
    
    
    Mid Summer Night Gathering
Oil on Canvas
32" x 48" http://fb.me/37B8TBVZZ     
    
    
    Beginnings of Making Headway Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OEYOk     
    
    
    Making Headway Contemporary Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OGpDU     
    
    
    For  a short few days... get a print of The Advantage... perfect shopping for the holidays... early! http://fb.me/6sWc1wTkX     
    
    
    For just a few days... early Christmas Shopping! http://fb.me/6iUW7tZfQ     
    
    
    Beginnings of a Pulled Painted Ponies... Contemporary Horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OJVKs     
    
    
    Night Runners, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OLmFQ     
    
    
    Seven Strong Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OMzF2     
    
    
    Check out the New Website.  Give my Facebook Page a like too please! http://fb.me/Jrn8LnzE     
    
    
    Watering Hole Contemporary Horse Abstract Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OOvha     
    
    
    Shiny Red Shoes Contemporary Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OR207     
    
    
    Canadian Three Pack by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Wolf Paintings http://nblo.gs/OSocq     
    
    
    Horizon Horses Fall Play, Contemporary Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OU2Gv     
    
    
    Horning In, Bevo Texas Longhorn Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OWRgM     
    
    
    Horsing Around Contemporary Abstract Horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/OZdsO     
    
    
    Do not miss this figurative painted pull at Mirada Fine Art. http://fb.me/1QApUOtIV     
    
    
    Moonrise Through the Mountains, Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/P0OwR     
    
    
    Fall is in the air... temps are in the low nineties. Stop by and LIKE my FACEBOOK Fan Page and visit my new... http://fb.me/21gkTKAnA     
    
    
    Sunrise Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/P2gqw     
    
    
    Sunrise Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/2013/09/sunrise-contemporary-horse-painting-by.html#.UjZJhLEn4eo.twitter …    
    
    
    A Herd of Color Contemporary Abstract Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/P5Y8I     
    
    
    A Pair... Abstract Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/P6H9h     
    
    
    A Walk in the Garden, Figurative Children Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/P8tB3     
    
    
    Direction Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Pao8m     
    
    
    Epsilon Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PdNKG     
    
    
    Orange Horse Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Pg0l6     
    
    
        
    
    
    Headstrong Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PiZYl     
    
    
    Silver's Gang was painted in the fall of 2011 and it sold within Days of completion.  One of my favorites for... http://fb.me/6rI71sK2m     
    
    
    Just came to the sudden realization that I do not have strong enough files up on FAA for most images...so over the... http://fb.me/TV9DPnX5     
    
    
        
    
    
    Contour Drawings with Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Element of Art: Line http://nblo.gs/PkTSl     
    
    
    Appy Fun Revisited from 2007 Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PnMpN     
    
    
    Watching #cspanchat and loving Sen Cruz from Texas doing a filibuster    
    
    
    Rope Dance, Cowboy Horse Cow Painting, Western Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PpLgV     
    
    
    Hesitation in progress, sketch on Canvas, Contemporary Fine Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Psj1h     
    
    
    Taking Flight Contemporary Horse Painting in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Pv8RF     
    
    
    He Brought Me Roses, Contemporary Rose Palette Knife Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PwSE2     
    
    
    Spirit Arabian Gold, Contemporary Horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Pydee     
    
    
    Lesson Two for Art... Seven Elements of Art... SHAPES by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PAgx2     
    
    
    White Knight Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PD52c     
    
    
    Pre Canvas Sketch Sailboats at Sunset, Contemporary Sailboat Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PEQHw     
    
    
    Contemporary Sunset Sailboat Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PGrrk     
    
    
    Contemporary Sunset Sailboat Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PIIWx     
    
    
    Contemporary Palette Knife Sailboat Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PLysb     
    
    
        
    
    
    FORM is the third Element of Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/POkc3     
    
    
    Over the Weekend... New Beginnings, Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PRf1w     
    
    
    Do not miss it! http://fb.me/1X2h8IbgC     
    
    
    Horse Painting in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PTkzl     
    
    
    Seven in the Sun, Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie pace http://nblo.gs/PUZLF     
    
    
        
    
    
    Blooms, Flower Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/PZKTU     
    
    
    Magnolia Flower Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Q0UuJ     
    
    
    Line Shape Form and SPACE, the fourth element of Art by Texas Art Teacher Laurie Pace. http://nblo.gs/Q298d     
    
    
    Mixed Media Collage Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Justus Pace http://nblo.gs/Q4FyK     
    
    
    Four Black Horses Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Q7zvt     
    
    
    Bathed in Gold, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Q98nM     
    
    
    Abstract Contemporary Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QaHvq     
    
    
        
    
    
    Heart Contemporary Fine Art, Heart Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie pace http://nblo.gs/Qf3bS     
    
    
    Line Shape Form Space Value    Value the New Element of Art for this week by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QgBSN     
    
    
    Texas Contemporary Fine Artist Laurie Pace http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/#.UmVjtZ9Fh8I.twitter …    
    
    
    I keep tweaking this. Getting better at the added HTML things. Enjoy. http://fb.me/6uWJRg4KS     
    
    
    Lone Wolf Progressive Wolf Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QipPQ     
    
    
        
    
    
    Lone Wolf Saga Painting continues... by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QnXzX     
    
    
    Lone Wolf Contemporary Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QpTXi     
    
    
    Starting the first painting for the two three feet by four feet oil paintings for the Toby Keith Kids Korral in... http://fb.me/37uSrnQ3F     
    
    
    First layers went on this past week on the first painting.  You can donate to the foundation here.  This is one... http://fb.me/2TE1uGf6h     
    
    
    Unfinished Beauty, Flower Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QrZdy     
    
    
        
    
    
    Two from the Herd, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Qu8pX     
    
    
    Line Shape Form Space Value Color    COLOR the New Element of Art for this week by Texas Artist Lauri... http://nblo.gs/QvBen     
    
    
    The Journey Painting One for Toby Keith's Kids Korral in Oklahoma. Horse Paintings by Texas Artist La... http://nblo.gs/Qxzip     
    
    
    Texas Contemporary Fine Artist Laurie Pace  paints for the Toby Keith's Kids Korral OK http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/#.UnBFMhTwsBk.twitter …    
    
    
    Day Two Horse Paintings for the Kids Korral, Toby Keith Foundation Oklahoma, Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QzwKZ     
    
    
    I titled it THE QUEST... almost finished at this point... but I need to start on number two... they are driving... http://fb.me/2uYH3WFL5     
    
    
        
    
    
    ON A QUEST Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QDrpI     
    
    
    More to read today and more to see on the process. http://fb.me/3tJAYC5ir     
    
    
    On a Quest almost finished Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QFbDH     
    
    
    The Quest Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QGAoz     
    
    
    Textures, the Last Element of Art by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QI2se     
    
    
    Having a Birthday http://nblo.gs/QKgJD     
    
    
    Texas Contemporary Fine Artist Laurie Pace Having a Birthday! http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/#.UnkMdMWp90w.twitter …    
    
    
    Second Large contemporary horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QMIsZ     
    
    
    Update for the Holidays. You might want to watch to keep up as I add more art for the holidays. http://fb.me/1XWeYHw3O     
    
    
    Traveler 30 x 30 oil on canvas... AVAILABLE. http://fb.me/3mNHtZlXD     
    
    
    Progress on Second Contemporary Horse Painting for Toby Keith Foundation Kids Korral by Texas Artist ... http://nblo.gs/QQ7CN     
    
    
    Fearless Together, Contemporary Horse Painting Toby Keith Foundation Oklahoma by Texas Artist Laurie ... http://nblo.gs/QTjmg     
    
    
    Original Palette Knife Wolf Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QTDdz     
    
    
    Intent  Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Justus Pace  Available. http://fb.me/31tZkRVau     
    
    
    INTENT Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Justus Pace  Available. Contact me. http://fb.me/1WxzuCEPB     
    
    
    Dawn Rises  Wolf Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Justus Pace  24 x 36 Oil on Canvas. Available. http://fb.me/1TBnqathI     
    
    
    Storm Chasers   Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Justus Pace   16 x 20 inches. Available. http://fb.me/Xp0cJW1e     
    
    
    Left Overs, Contemporary Horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QW7tM     
    
    
    Storm Chasers Abstract Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/QZ2NS     
    
    
    Art Lesson on line and color by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/R1vay     
    
    
    Contemporary Wolf Painting in Progress by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/R3Q3q     
    
    
    Find my work featured on page 18ish.... http://fb.me/14Fpjnylg     
    
    
    Actually this works faster...how neat. Got to remember this trick. http://fb.me/2zKEYAvXZ     
    
    
    VL -Visual Language Magazine and Art Tells the Story Contemporary Fine Art http://visuallanguagemagazine.com/#.UoQtH_PbsTE.twitter …    
    
    
    Past and present issues of Visual Language Magazine, VL http://visuallanguagemagazine.com/issues.html#.UoQt92iCrXA.twitter …    
    
    
    Dawn Rising Contemporary Wolf Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/2013/11/dawn-rising-contemporary-wolf-painting.html#.UoQwflOy8mI.twitter …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Artists of Texas Home - Daily Painters of Texas http://www.artistsoftexas.org/#.UoQyWDQrwgE.twitter …    
    
    
    White Runner Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/R7PwA     
    
    
    Head Strong, Colorful Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Ra1rY     
    
    
    Red Poppies on Blue  Large Contemporary Flower Painting of Poppies by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Rb5yq     
    
    
    The Traveler, An Abstract Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace. http://nblo.gs/RcfDE     
    
    
    Monday Art Lesson with Laurie Pace, and register for free Horse Painting by Wednesday, Nov 20th, 2013. http://nblo.gs/RdyUh     
    
    
    Descent Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace Holiday Gifts Under $150 http://nblo.gs/Rf1YU     
    
    
    Happy Birthday Kelly Pace http://nblo.gs/RgDhq     
    
    
    In Progress Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RicLx     
    
    
    Golden Rod and Mirada Fine Art Gallery, Denver with Contemporary Equine Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RjUvA     
    
    
    Rare Cat Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RlruQ     
    
    
    Reflections of His Glory... Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RnnMj     
    
    
    Monday Lesson on Vacation!  BUT enjoy my 12 Days of Christmas Giveaways starting today. Laurie Pace T... http://nblo.gs/Rqzmr     
    
    
    The 12 Days of Christmas Art Giveaway. Visit my blog to register for all 12 days starting today.  This is the... http://fb.me/2IAS3c3BU     
    
    
    Enjoy my 12 Days of Christmas ART Giveaways starting today. Laurie Pace Texas Artist http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/2013/11/monday-lesson-on-vacation-but-enjoy-my.html#.UpNs_x7okHM.twitter …    
    
    
    12 Days of Christmas Giveaway Painting 2 by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RsItI     
    
    
    Day Three, 12 Days of Christmas Giveaway by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RuueD     
    
    
    Day Three... stop by and see the art for the day... 12 Days of Giveaways... http://fb.me/2uSKshXLW     
    
    
    Day Four Twelve Days of Christmas Art Giveaways by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Rwc7p     
    
    
    Day Five Twelve Days of Christmas Art Giveaways by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RzdjJ     
    
    
    Day Six Twelve Days of Christmas Art Giveaways by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RAtUs     
    
    
    Day Seven Twelve Days of Christmas Art Giveaways by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RBlAV     
    
    
        
    
    
    Day Eight Twelve Days of Christmas Art Giveaways by Texas Artist Laurie Pace
 http://shar.es/DlwMX  via @sharethis    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Day Tenth Twelve Days of Christmas Art Giveaways by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RHpM6     
    
    
    Day Eleven of the Twelve Days of Christmas Art Giveaways by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RJ1fs     
    
    
    Enjoy and Thank you Andrew Swift, son of Sallie-Anne Swift. http://fb.me/1ZJoQW0K4     
    
    
    Day Twelve of the Twelve Days of Christmas Art Giveaways by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RL4YF     
    
    
    Here is the video... Enjoy. http://fb.me/1HKAI3ogk     
    
    
    Painting in Progress Ponies on the Ridge Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RNNK5     
    
    
    Progress of Ponies on the Ridge Horse paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/ROPcQ     
    
    
        
    
    
    This is the less expensive soft back book on Magcloud. http://fb.me/2KTKUvQoA     
    
    
    Limited time... I have three paintings available for Holiday gifts at a good price. http://fb.me/36vPy8yeX     
    
    
    Only for five days... a huge 24 x 36 inches print for $168. http://fb.me/2vx2PYnom     
    
    
    This is number three and it is my most popular horse for prints. http://fb.me/3f9qTC2JZ     
    
    
    True Blue Hydrangeas and Sunflowers by Floral Artist Nancy Medina
 http://shar.es/DPiVE  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Beginnings of a commissioned Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RPSxt     
    
    
    Day 2 Commissioned Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RSDGz     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    One more day.... http://fb.me/6upezZ9wg     
    
    
    Completion of Reverence to the Sun, a Contemporary Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/RXL8P     
    
    
    Heart to Heart Beginnings, Mixed Media Heart Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/S0M6b     
    
    
    Progress on Hearts by Texas Artist Laurie Pace, Heart Paintings http://nblo.gs/S1U6H     
    
    
    Progress on Heart Mixed Media Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/S2Tve     
    
    
    Day 1 Orange Horse Painting, Abstract Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/S4aES     
    
    
    Day 2 Extended Gift Giveaway.  Summer Blooms by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/S7soc     
    
    
    Day 3 Red Filly, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/S983m     
    
    
    Day 4 Sunflower Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/SazmE     
    
    
        
    
    
    Day 5 Abstract Horse Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/SclSA     
    
    
    Last day for free giveaway of this fab painting. http://lauriepace.blogspot.com/#.UrYlmi3wPVo.twitter …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Abstract Heart Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/SfGaf     
    
    
    Video of Painting with Laurie Pace  Joys of Christmas Eve. http://nblo.gs/SgTqE     
    
    
    Unto Us a Child is Born... http://nblo.gs/SjgNa     
    
    
    Whatever You Do... Day One New Painting by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Skq6o     
    
    
    New painting on the easel... drop by to watch the progress. Back in the studio after 10 days of bronchitis ... http://fb.me/RnznWOdl     
    
    
    Day Two Whatever you Do... Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace. http://nblo.gs/SlDeR     
    
    
    Watch "How Great Thou Art, Five Hearts by Laurie Pace, Music by Carrie Underwood, "How Great Thou Art""  Vimeo http://vimeo.com/81770018  #Vimeo    
    
    
    Day Three Progression Painting, Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/SmNJD     
    
    
        
    
    
    Day Five Progression Painting of  Horse Jumping with Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/SqixQ     
    
    
    Day Six in Progress Painting of Jumping Horse by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/SrsXX     
    
    
    New Years Progress on Contemporary Horse Paintings by Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Sslg4     
    
    
        
    
    
    Refining the layers on Contemporary Horse Paintings with Texas Artist Laurie Pace http://nblo.gs/Swuba     
    
    
        
    
    
    