@GIZEH75 @TerrySullivan Thank you Emmanuelle!    
    
    
    @alifesobeautifl @GIZEH75 Ouch!! That is not fun!! Stay warm:)    
    
    
    @TeckieGirl Yes!! It did think we would get some lol.. A little disappointed!    
    
    
    @mikegodleman @alifesobeautifl @GIZEH75 Hi Mike! Great to see you!    
    
    
    @mikegodleman @alifesobeautifl @GIZEH75 Life is great!! Still getting settled in and just put up our Christmas decorations:) So much to do!    
    
    
    @mikegodleman Yes, we had some fun convos!! How have you been Mike?    
    
    
    Iran president takes to #Twitter after nuclear deal http://usat.ly/1chjUeu  via @USATODAY    
    
    
    @DrGaryBotox ouch:) But last much longer right? Are you happy w/ the results? #Voluma    
    
    
    Social stocks battered; #Twitter below $40 http://ow.ly/raQ0M  via @usatoday #socialmedia    
    
    
    @RaviCAtDell @USATODAY Thanks Ravi! Happy Monday!    
    
    
    @1creolegurl @USATODAY Thank you Chanette!    
    
    
    31 Twitter Tips: How To Use Twitter Tools And #Twitter http://ow.ly/raQhs  via @forbes    
    
    
    31 Twitter Tips: How To Use Twitter Tools And #Twitter http://ow.ly/raQlX  via @forbes    
    
    
    Please check out an amazing #author & my great friend @amowriting and purchase a copy of her new book here http://bit.ly/1emCunu     
    
    
    @indadseyes @ChelseaKrost You too Andrew!! Looking forward to Thanksgiving:)    
    
    
    @flaxroots Thanks!! What's your 1st name:)??    
    
    
    @TerrySullivan It is way too cold Terry lol. Has been dreary for too long. Don't remember this last year:)    
    
    
    @SusanCross1 Good morning Susan!!! Happy Tuesday!    
    
    
    @GretchenVanD Hi Gretchen! Hope you are a bit warmer your way:) How are you? Ready for Thanksgiving?    
    
    
    @tedesco_paul Thanks Paul!! Love @amowriting    
    
    
    Tuesday's #Twitter Tip- Don't follow just competitors in your niche- How does this bring you business? #thinkaboutit    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Haha!! Thanks a lot Emmanuelle:)    
    
    
    @MariaVarella3 Hi Maria!! Happy Tuesday!! I see this all the time. I look at tweeps followers and they just focus on their competitors:)    
    
    
    @justpearlzJP It drives me CRAZY LaNette!! Great to interact w/ tweeps in your niche but we have to broaden our scope don't you think?    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Is that your street? Do you live in the heart of Paris Emmanuelle?    
    
    
    @justpearlzJP  I love Social Media tweeps but they probably aren't going to hire me:)    
    
    
    @justpearlzJP How are you today? Staying warm?? It is so cold here in #Dallas!    
    
    
    @justpearlzJP Ah!! You are in Dallas lol. I don't want to go outside lol.    
    
    
    @MariaVarella3 Happy Tuesday to you Maria!! xo Are you ready for Thanksgiving?    
    
    
    @btreasurer Hi Bill! Thanks so much for the follow! Have a fantastic day!    
    
    
    @chicocowater Thanks for the follow!! Love Coconut products!    
    
    
    @JohnEMichel Thanks for connecting John! Have a wonderful day:)    
    
    
    @justpearlzJP Thanks:) What part of Dallas are you in? I'm in Trophy Club.    
    
    
    @MIXTECADURHAM Thanks for the follow!! Love Tacos & Tequila:)    
    
    
    @MIXTECADURHAM Where is your website??    
    
    
    @MIXTECADURHAM I see it now on your profile:)    
    
    
    @chicocowater I buy a lot of coconut products. Wish they were a little less expensive but I still buy them:) Love coconut water!    
    
    
    @JohnEMichel You too John!!!    
    
    
    @justpearlzJP Oh okay! I seem to live far from everyone:)    
    
    
    @FrankieFaded Thanks for the follow Frank. Have a fantastic day:)    
    
    
    @FinanceWithFunk Thanks for the follow Trisha!    
    
    
    @MariaVarella3 Sounds like a fun day!! I used to host dinners for friends.. Now it is just the 2 of us:)  Have a fun and festive day:)    
    
    
    @MariaVarella3 We are making a traditional turkey dinner for 2:) Then going to a movie I think:)    
    
    
    Check out these amazing Tweeps  @ChelseaKrost @robynstevensPR @AndeLyons @RockTheVote @gogirlfinance    
    
    
    @chicocowater @AmazonUK ah!!! You must come to the #US:)    
    
    
    @Drew_Farnsworth Thanks for the follow Drew! Congrats on your win!    
    
    
    Protected Tweets- 5 Reasons You Don’t Want To Protect Your #Tweets http://bit.ly/HRVb7E  via @turnitsocial #Twitter    
    
    
    @bendragonborn Thanks for the follow Dianne!    
    
    
    @DrGaryBotox Awesome!!    
    
    
    @MelissaOnline @Turnitsocial Thanks Melissa!    
    
    
    Congrats to @DrGaryBotox for being selected to provide Allergan's  #Voluma  in #Chattanooga #fillers #beauty    
    
    
    @HLN_Moore @Turnitsocial Thanks Helene!!    
    
    
    @KikiLeeStylStar @Turnitsocial Thank you Kike!    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Have a wonderful Thanksgiving Trey w/ your family!    
    
    
    @eKoffee How have you been? Great to see you!    
    
    
    @eKoffee Sounds like fun!!!! #blackcoffeefriday    
    
    
    @JDixon215 Thanks for the follow Jennifer! Great to connect!!    
    
    
    Do not take life too seriously. You will never get out of it alive. Elbert Hubbard    
    
    
    @KikiLeeStylStar @Turnitsocial You too!! Are you hosting Kike? Love your name:)    
    
    
    @AndeLyons @ChelseaKrost @robynstevensPR @RockTheVote @gogirlfinance Woohoo! It's rocking now w/ you in our #Twittersphere Ande!!!!    
    
    
    @dtfpress Happy Tuesday Deborah!    
    
    
    @KikiLeeStylStar @Turnitsocial Yes for just the 2 of us haha!!! Love that lol. Turkey is very easy to prepare!!    
    
    
    @indadseyes @ChelseaKrost Thanks Andrew!! Happy Thanksgiving!    
    
    
    @UKFestivals2013 Thank you so much!! Same to you!    
    
    
    @deJabs Thanks Christian! Happy Wednesday to you!    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 Yes, everything bought and ready to go:)  Enjoy!!:)    
    
    
    @KikiLeeStylStar Happy Wednesday Kike!!!    
    
    
    @AndeLyons How is my Twabulous friend Ande today??    
    
    
    @CuttingEdge_US So appreciate your follow. Happy Holidays:)    
    
    
    @GretchenVanD Hi Gretchen:) Finally sunshine our way!! Happy Thanksgiving:)    
    
    
    @GretchenVanD So glad you have some sunshine too! Tired of gloomy lol. Thanks Gretchen!!!!    
    
    
    @RichWeatherly43 HI Rich!! Has been awhile!! Hope you have a wonderful Thanksgiving:)    
    
    
    @dianebogut @Tall_Papa @GretchenVanD @debraoakland @PhotoPad_vg @fionaannv @kimgarst @ConnieImage mashed potatoes and gravy!!    
    
    
    @SpecLoglines Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @robert_manners Same to you Robert!!!    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman Happy Thanksgiving Tom!    
    
    
    Thanksgiving #Hugs to @AndeLyons @aprileparella @dianebogut @TerrySullivan @AuntRuby @ConnieImage @Affilipede @MelanieEndert    
    
    
    @robynstevensPR  Happy Thanksgiving to my favorite #Pr Tweep:)    
    
    
    Wishing Everyone a fabulous and festive #Thanksgiving:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Have a great day Emmanuelle! I can smell the turkey cooking. #yummy    
    
    
    @itsALEXAonline Happy Thanksgiving Alexis!!    
    
    
    @brandelixircomm Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Thank you:)    
    
    
    @LoriMoreno  Happy Friday Lori!! How was your Thanksgiving?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @indadseyes @ChelseaKrost You too Andrew!! Thank you:)    
    
    
    @einfal Thanks Raphael!! Hope you have a great day:)    
    
    
    @robertore62 @ChelseaKrost Thanks for the rt Roberto!!    
    
    
    @bewonderfulnow Hi Tom! Have a fantastic weekend:)    
    
    
    @JohnnySpiva Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    #Facebook Is Trailing Social Messaging #Apps Globally http://onforb.es/1jGjoZY  via @forbes    
    
    
    @drparkave Have a fabulous day Paul!! #HappyFriday!    
    
    
    @GretchenVanD How was your Thanksgiving Gretchen?    
    
    
    @drmarthalee My pleasure!! Hope you have a fantastic weekend!    
    
    
    @dianebogut It was wonderful Diane! Just the 2 of us but perfect:) How was yours?    
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1 @ChelseaKrost Afraid to ask:)    
    
    
    @GretchenVanD @dianebogut I love green beans during the holidays. Do you make green bean casserole? #myfave    
    
    
    @AndeLyons Good morning beautiful Ande!!!    
    
    
    @AuntRuby Morning hug beautiful lady:)    
    
    
    Why shop there on Thanksgiving? So ridiculous!! #WalmartFights sparks a trend on #Twitter http://yhoo.it/1hp71oc  via @yahoo    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Hi Emmanuelle! Craziness!! Why tweeps go shopping at Walmart on Thanksgiving is insane!! I refuse to shop on Thanksgiving:)    
    
    
    @DarrylJDaug Thanks Darryl for the follow!    
    
    
    @Econsultancy @Snappening Love Pinterest and recommend my clients get more involved in it!!    
    
    
    @dianebogut Have a fabulous day:)    
    
    
    @GretchenVanD @dianebogut Haha! Yes, getting ready to go workout myself Gretchen!!!    
    
    
    Seems like a quiet day in my Twittersphere:)    
    
    
    @nlcondit Doing great Nicole! Are you making or wrapping?    
    
    
    5  Tips for Terrific Power Tweeting http://bit.ly/1b4rZ7I  via @jeffbullas #Twitter #hashtags    
    
    
    Effective Content Marketing Approaches 4 Increased Business Revenue http://bit.ly/19aR0tW  via @jplussocial #Contentmarketing #socialmedia    
    
    
    @ContentSimply thanks for the rt!    
    
    
    @pamfong7 @jeffbullas Thanks Pam!! Have great weekend:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Ty Emmanuelle:)    
    
    
    TV & Radio Talk Show Host: The Chelsea Krost Show, #Millennial Spokesperson/ #Brand Consultant. http://bit.ly/131Xn41  #Follow @ChelseaKrost    
    
    
    @Snappening Here it is and I need to change it back to my name:) http://www.pinterest.com/turnitsocial/     
    
    
    @Snappening Thanks for asking!!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 @ChelseaKrost Chelsea IS the best! Love her energy, passion and integrity!!    
    
    
    @MariaVarella3 Hi Maria!! Are you enjoying the long holiday weekend?    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 @ChelseaKrost What are your plans today??    
    
    
    @CatherineHeroux @ChelseaKrost Thanks Catherine! Have a wonderful afternoon!!    
    
    
    @robertore62 @ChelseaKrost @davidblaine Hi Roberto!!    
    
    
    @RichWeatherly43 @klout Thanks Rich!!!    
    
    
    @chevd80 Was really good Cheval. Just the 2 of us but that is fine:) What about you?    
    
    
    @wrapitgiftbag Much success with it Adam!!    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 A huge #HAPPYMONDAY Audra:) How are you??    
    
    
    @AuntRuby Oh yeah Ruby!! Let's do it:) xo    
    
    
    @CatherineHeroux @ChelseaKrost Was a nice day today Catherine!! Thank you:)    
    
    
    @robertore62 Love Italy and want to return some day:)    
    
    
    The Ultimate List of #Pinterest Tips http://bit.ly/18WfoDf  via @AmyLynnAndrews #socialmedia #marketing    
    
    
    @AdibaNelson Just made it on Adiba! Busy day!! How was yours?    
    
    
    @valeriegeiss Was fantastic chatting with you Valerie!! Have a wonderful evening:)    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman Hi Tom! Happy Tuesday! Thanks for the Tuesday greeting:)    
    
    
    @chevd80 THanks for the tweet Cheval!!    
    
    
    Check out one of my #favorite singers @AudraLynn21    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman Love #Pinterest!!!    
    
    
    @tomkalowski Thank you for the follow Tomasz!    
    
    
    @TORIngAmerica Thank you Tori!! Have a fantastic night!    
    
    
    @NormaDoiron Hi Norma! Thank you so much for the list add:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 See you tomorrow Emmanuelle!    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman You will learn to love it:)    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman I hate to say it but was so bogged down here that I didn't go outside but to open the door. I think it was hot today:)    
    
    
    @AdibaNelson Still eating it:) Finished the mashed potatoes and green bean casserole this afternoon:)    
    
    
    9 Great Tips to Help You Get Started With #Google+ http://bit.ly/1eMWdfG  via @fredfelton  on @Turnitsocial #socialmedia    
    
    
    @TORIngAmerica I didn't write it but thanks:)    
    
    
    @TORIngAmerica Love your avatar Tori!!    
    
    
    @andelyons Hope you had a super day Ande!!! #Hugs from Dallas!    
    
    
    @MediaBrosMKT Thanks for your rt. Where are you located?    
    
    
    #SmartMarketing-  @Target spreads brand love through #Vine http://bit.ly/1dQ1erp  #socialmedia    
    
    
    @AndeLyons Love you Andelish! You always spread such positivity and great vibes!!!Have a great day:)    
    
    
    @valeriegeiss Same here Valerie!! Can't wait for @ChelseaKrost new weekly chat #MillennialTalk on Dec 10 w/ @Adam_K_Levin on #cybersecurity    
    
    
    @MediaBrosMKT Thank you for the rt!! Have a great day:)    
    
    
    @LauraBWilliams2 Thank you so much Laura for the rt!! Happy Wednesday!    
    
    
    @AdibaNelson Haha! I love cranberry sauce!! Do you leave it chunky?? Love it that way with the whole berries:)    
    
    
    "How Gen-Y Employees Can Handle Negative Stereotypes in  Workplace" Chelsea Krost Show at 9 pmET w/ @BWeissPresents http://bit.ly/ImlliL     
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @Smith_CourtneyM @AdibaNelson @ChelseaKrost @JenniferHain @EmilyTheOtt Haha!! Thanks Elizabeth!!    
    
    
    @Smith_CourtneyM Hi Courtney! Have a great evening:)    
    
    
    @ChelseaKrost Show starts in 15 mins!!! Incredible show tonight w/ #Pinstagram founder @pekpongpaet http://bit.ly/ImlliL  #Instagram #radio    
    
    
    @dianebogut Check your dm:)    
    
    
    @DacronFans Thanks so much!! Have a great night!    
    
    
    Check out my friend @dianebogut 's Indigo project http://www.indiegogo.com/projects/date-like-a-recruiter … #author    
    
    
    @KellyAnnGorman @ChelseaKrost @DailyDimmick @bobbi_bobbi @lethemknow So cold right now Kelly in #Dallas!! #IceStorm    
    
    
    Gotta love #Dallas- Yesterday 80's and today 30's and ice!!    
    
    
    How are some of my favorite TweetStars @DrACAnderson @AndeLyons @TerrySullivan @AdibaNelson @robynstevensPR @dianebogut    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Hi Tumi!!! Wonderful to see you in my Twittersphere!!! How are you?    
    
    
    @chicmodern #Brrr lol. SO cold. Went to store today to load up on comfort food:)    
    
    
    @dianebogut So are you Diane!!! Have a fantastic night. Going to go downstairs and relax a bit:)    
    
    
    @KellyAnnGorman @ChelseaKrost @DailyDimmick @bobbi_bobbi @lethemknow Thanks Kelly! Are you getting the cold weather your way?    
    
    
    @AndeLyons @DrACAnderson @TerrySullivan @AdibaNelson @robynstevensPR @dianebogut Twabulous Ande:)    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Very good but cold lol. We are having a winter storm:)    
    
    
    @dianebogut I am a tropical weather gal:)    
    
    
    @chicmodern Ah what part of Dallas? I went to Tom Thumb and their produce was bare lol.    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Yes, have the heat on lol.    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Never:)    
    
    
    @chicmodern I don't know that area:) I'm in Trophy Club. Not stepping outside tomorrow lol.    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Have a great night Tumi!!! Love seeing you here today:)    
    
    
    @beccamooreLRD Doing super Rebecca!! How have you been?    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Double dose #Mwah    
    
    
    @SharisBerries Thank you Shari! Same back to you:)    
    
    
    @chicmodern Ah far far away:)    
    
    
    @chicmodern Stay warm Tonia:)    
    
    
    @DrACAnderson Wonderful April but just a little cold lol. Freezing here in Dallas!!    
    
    
    @patrickmahan Thanks for the follow Patrick!    
    
    
    @Smith_CourtneyM Thanks Courtney!!!    
    
    
    @MelanieEndert Enjoying the temps Melanie:)??    
    
    
    @DrACAnderson Thanks April!! Feeling great just cold haha!! Have a fantastic evening:)    
    
    
    5 Tips for #Twitter Engagement http://bit.ly/1eU2jLi  via @Turnitosocial #socialmedia    
    
    
    @DrACAnderson Thanks! You too:)    
    
    
    @barbarabarna @letlifehappen @AndeLyons @BZSocialMedia @whirlydudes @GreenSkyDeb @KirkJaco I am iced in lol. So will be tweeting a lot:)    
    
    
    @AdibaNelson @DrACAnderson Whew!! See you found it!!    
    
    
    @snowdenmcfall Thanks so much and wishing you an amazing weekend!    
    
    
    @JeffreyMook1 HI Jeff! Thanks so much for the follow!    
    
    
    Your thoughts everyone? Should #Facebook, Yahoo, and #Twitter really judge what's news? http://bit.ly/1gcyYj0  via @pcworld #socialmedia    
    
    
    @KikiLeeStylStar Thanks Kike!!! You are so sweet! Thanks and hope you have a wonderful weekend!    
    
    
    @JonFerchen Hi Jon!!! Have a fantastic weekend:)    
    
    
    @leilanihaywood @pcworld Thanks for your input Leilani and I do agree! I must admit that I learn a lot of my news right here on Twitter:)    
    
    
    @Truvianni @pcworld Very true!! How are you Gianni!! I am a #Twitter addict and get much of my news right here:)    
    
    
    @AndeLyons @letlifehappen @barbarabarna @BZSocialMedia @whirlydudes @GreenSkyDeb @KirkJaco Same back at you Ande:)    
    
    
    Anyone know if #Dallas airport has incoming flights today and taxis?? Cannot get taxi services to answer:)    
    
    
    @dfwairport Are there incoming flights currently? Expecting someone from Washington via @AlaskaAir    
    
    
    @dfwairport ty so much!! Also, is it possible to get taxis going from airport??    
    
    
    @dfwairport Have called approx 6 taxis and no answer.    
    
    
    @dianebogut @TerrySullivan Haha, not until middle of next week Diane:) But the sleet is over:)    
    
    
    @dfwairport Do I have to call or will someone be able just to grab it?    
    
    
    @dianebogut @TerrySullivan no lol. I am snug in my house here on #Twitter:)    
    
    
    Friday #Hugs to @craftygirl62 @SusanCross1 @dianebogut @TerrySullivan @robynstevensPR    
    
    
    @leilanihaywood I have a real addiction for #Twitter and find most of mine here since this is where I spend most of my time:)    
    
    
    @Truvianni @pcworld That's awesome Gianni!! How did you happen to decide on a man from Tex as your character?    
    
    
    @jennyolivia Hi Jenny!! I'm in Trophy Club. Have you ventured out today?    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 Hi Audra!! How is my favorite #singer today??So love your music!!    
    
    
    @aprileparella A big Happy Friday Aprile. Haven't chatted with you for quite some time. How are you? We are freezing here in #Dallas:)    
    
    
    @robynstevensPR @AndeLyons @DrACAnderson @TerrySullivan @AdibaNelson @dianebogut Thanks!!!    
    
    
    Amazing!! Another reason to love #Twitter- No Internet?Twitter Will Be Available Offline In Emerging Markets http://bit.ly/IwPXxV     
    
    
    What do you think? Should #Facebook, Yahoo, and #Twitter really judge what's news? http://bit.ly/1gcyYj0   via @pcworld #socialmedia    
    
    
    @ebongeka @pcworld Morning Ebong. I agree!! Thanks for your response. Big plans for the weekend? I am iced in here in Dallas.    
    
    
    @ideabloke It is beyond bracingly cold Randy in Dallas lol. We are iced in.    
    
    
    @TerrySullivan Have a fantastic Saturday Terry!    
    
    
    @KirkJaco Happy Saturday Kirk!    
    
    
    @BoomStrategies Thanks for the follow Tomyka!! Have a fantastic weekend:)    
    
    
    @chasenvision Thanks Walt for the follow!    
    
    
    What Burning #Facebook Questions Does YOUR Business Have?  http://bit.ly/197EkI0  via @MSocialBusiness #socialmedia    
    
    
    Chelsea Krost, #Millenial Lifestyle Expert, TV & Radio Host, Author http://bit.ly/16viCw6  via @galtime #brands #millennials    
    
    
    @mlolmstead @MSocialBusiness Thanks Meredith! Hope you have a fantastic weekend:)    
    
    
    Big #Shoutout to @DrRobMelillo @robynstevensPR You are awesome:)    
    
    
    @ebongeka  I hope you get snow and not ice:) So many road and biz closures. We are truly iced in:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Hi Emmanuelle:) How was your day?    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 I imagine that Christmas time in Paris is beautiful!!    
    
    
    #Shoutout to my fab #Dallas tweeps @angelinasimms @MelanieEndert @TerrySullivan @TaraItalian Stay warm:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Wonderful!! Thank you:)    
    
    
    Twitter Tips: How To Use Twitter Tools And #Twitter http://ow.ly/ry6F2  via @forbes #socialmedia    
    
    
    How to #hashtag your way to social media success http://ow.ly/ry715  via @cmo_o #socialmedia    
    
    
    23 Steps To Build Your Personal Brand http://ow.ly/ry7cc  via @jeffbullas #SocialMedia #branding    
    
    
    5  Fantastic Tips To Rise To The Top On #Pinterest http://ow.ly/ry7kO  via @Turnitsocial #Socialmedia    
    
    
    The Three Tribes of Social Shopping http://ow.ly/ry6XA  via @Harvardbiz #SocialMedia #marketing #brands    
    
    
    @digecomm Thanks James!!    
    
    
    @KellyMSteinbach You too Kelly!!    
    
    
    @chevd80 That's great Cheval! I've spent today being #stircrazy lol. Can't get out of my house with the ice:)    
    
    
    @Qureishi Thanks for the rt!!    
    
    
    @YouBrandInc So appreciate your rt!    
    
    
    @VinnyVerrico Thanks Vinny for the rt. Have a great night!    
    
    
    @OmerShubert Thank you Omer for sharing! Have an awesome night!    
    
    
    @chevd80 Hope you had an enjoyable day Cheval:)    
    
    
    23 Steps To Build Your Personal Brand http://ow.ly/ry7e2  via @jeffbullas #SocialMedia #branding    
    
    
    @GlenGilmore @jeffbullas Hi Glen! Hope you are enjoying the weekend and thanks for sharing:)    
    
    
    @TaraItalian  Would love to Tara if I can dig myself out from this ice :)    
    
    
    @VinnyVerrico Thank you Vinny! I need to tweet more. Hard to find the time to work on my own #SM:)    
    
    
    @taylor__park Thanks so much Taylor for your follow. Have a great night!    
    
    
    What Burning #Facebook Questions Does YOUR Business Have?  http://bit.ly/197EkI0  via @MSocialBusiness #socialmedia    
    
    
    @ilovelaceyg Thanks for the rt Lacey!!    
    
    
    @happyvancouver Thank you for the rt !! Have a great day:)    
    
    
    @brianloebig So appreciate your rt Brian!    
    
    
    @yourgirlprez Thank you for the rt!!    
    
    
    @ValerieDeveza Thanks Valerie! Really appreciate your rt!    
    
    
    @BodyMindSoil We are now connected Shawn:)    
    
    
    @danivdes Thanks for the follow Danielle! Have a fantastic day!    
    
    
    @danivdes Thanks!! Will do:)    
    
    
    5 Tips on How to Use #Slideshare for your Brand http://bit.ly/1bpZMaN  via @fredfelton on @turnitsocial #socialmedia    
    
    
    #Millennials- Make sure to join @ChelseaKrost 's brand new #TwitterChat on Dec 10 at 8 pm ET!!! Use the hashtag #MillennialTalk    
    
    
    Chelsea Krost, #Millenial Lifestyle Expert, TV & Radio Host, Author http://bit.ly/16viCw6  via @galtime #brands #millennials    
    
    
    @DrACAnderson Happy Sunday April!! Still iced in here lol. Looks like I will be til Wednesday:) Have lots of food though:)    
    
    
    7 Tips to Build Your Best Personal Brand on #LinkedIn http://bit.ly/1cj1jgs  via  @kleimkuehler on @TurnitSocial #socialmedia #branding    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 So sorry!! Flu?? Still iced in but doing great!    
    
    
    @VinnyVerrico Social Media definitely can help for sure!    
    
    
    @DrACAnderson I knew it was coming and literally stocked up right before the storm. I wasn't expecting it lol. The day before it was 80.    
    
    
    Big #ShoutOut @DrRobMelillo for doing such amazing things for kids w/ #autism    
    
    
    One of my favorite #PR Tweeps @robynstevensPR #Philly    
    
    
    5 To Do #Apps Worth Having http://bit.ly/1hGlQ5V  via @FredFelton on @TurnitSocial #Socialmedia    
    
    
    @marcoRecorder @fredfelton @Turnitsocial Thanks so much!! Have a great week:)    
    
    
    @VinnyVerrico Congrats!!! Wish you much success:)    
    
    
    @PayrollGuyChris Thanks for the follow Chris!    
    
    
    @TipsByKaren Thanks for the follow Karen! Have a fantastic week:)    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 Hope you are feeling better this afternoon Audra!    
    
    
    @LaurenMGalley Hi Lauren! Hope you have a great week:)    
    
    
    @bambiibella Thank you Emily!! So appreciate and hope you are staying warm:)    
    
    
    Time to take a long Twitter break:)    
    
    
    How to #hashtag your way to social media success http://ow.ly/ry71Q  via @cmo_o #socialmedia    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 So happy!!! A lot of tweeps are sick right now:) #fluseason    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 Wow!! 10 inches!! We have tons of ice so we are iced in lol.    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @LaurenMGalley Yes Elizabeth lol. I am ready to get out of here lol. #stircrazy    
    
    
    @chevd80 @LaurenMGalley You too Cheval!!    
    
    
    @indadseyes Thanks Andrew!! You are awesome!    
    
    
    @LaurenMGalley Best of luck!! You will do great!    
    
    
    7 Tips to Build Your Best Personal Brand on #LinkedIn http://bit.ly/1cj1jgs  via  @kleimkuehler on @TurnitSocial #socialmedia #branding    
    
    
    23 Steps To Build Your Personal Brand http://ow.ly/ry7f7  via @jeffbullas #SocialMedia #branding    
    
    
    5  Fantastic Tips To Rise To The Top On #Pinterest http://ow.ly/ry7m0  via @Turnitsocial #Socialmedia    
    
    
    Twitter Tips: How To Use Twitter Tools And #Twitter http://ow.ly/ry6Fy  via @forbes    
    
    
    7 Tips to Build Your Best Personal Brand on #LinkedIn http://bit.ly/1cj1jgs  via  @kleimkuehler on @TurnitSocial #socialmedia #branding    
    
    
    @MrsPRProtocol Glad you enjoyed Barbara! Have a great week!!    
    
    
    @umairquraishi Thank you for sharing Umair!! Hope you have a super incredible week:)    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman So appreciate all your tweets Tom!! Have a wonderful day:)    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @LaurenMGalley It is crazy here. Finally today we should have some thawing. The sun is OUT!!!    
    
    
    @indadseyes We had a decent ice fall lol.    
    
    
    Please follow an extraordinary tweep & friend @DrRobMelillo #autism #add #adhd #kids    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 Sorry, ours is starting to melt a bit and then going to freeze again. The sun was out for a bit today:)    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 I am afraid of the flu shot lol.    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @LaurenMGalley That is cold Elizabeth!! It is just above freezing here in Dallas but temps will not stay there:)    
    
    
    @deJabs Thank you Christian!!Happy Monday!    
    
    
    @christinenese Hi Christine:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AndeLyons @happywivesclub @JonathonAslay @GreenSkyDeb You look GORGEOUS in red:)    
    
    
    @CantonCathy @DrRobMelillo Haha!!    
    
    
    Monday #ShoutOut to some extraordinary Tweeps @DrRobMelillo @robynstevensPR @Andelyons @ChelseaKrost @TaraMarkus @AuntRuby    
    
    
    @humbleranger Hi Matt! Hope you have an incredible week!!    
    
    
    @freetobescott Thank you for the rt Scott!    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @LaurenMGalley Sorry!! We had our horrible weather and looking forward to the thaw!!!    
    
    
    @deJabs Woohoo! You are back in France!! Congrats:)    
    
    
    @garthturner Thanks for the follow Garth!    
    
    
    @AuntRuby Sorry Ruby!! Hoping today is better:)    
    
    
    @ZahidaKhan Great to see you today Zahida!! Happy Tuesday:)    
    
    
    @TerrySullivan No Terry:) I am afraid to venture out with the ice still on the road:)    
    
    
    @JonathonAslay Good morning Jonathon!! Hope you have a fantastic week:)    
    
    
    @JonathonAslay I think so!!! Also depends on someone's definition of #monogamy    
    
    
    @AuntRuby Doing super fab!! Picked up a new client and excited to start working with him:)    
    
    
    @AuntRuby I really love working with personal brands. Find it much more rewarding:)    
    
    
    @AuntRuby @ChelseaKrost YES!! AND new Twitter Chat tonight at 8 pm ET about #CyberSecurity & #CyberScams for the holidays!! #MillennialTalk    
    
    
    @deJabs I think when you move away for an extended time, it is never the same when you return:) Hopefully better!! Do you live in Paris?    
    
    
    Join a great new Twitter Chat tonight at 8 EST w/ host  @ChelseaKrost http://bit.ly/19tag6c  #MillennialTalk    
    
    
    @deJabs Sounds perfect!! What town?    
    
    
    #Shoutout to an amazing Tweep @DrRobMelillo #Autism #ADHD #Aspergers    
    
    
    @superdivakerry @RebelMouse Great  Kerry and thank you so much!    
    
    
    @chevd80 Very productive Cheval. Working with a new client:) That always makes me happy:) How are you?    
    
    
    @chevd80 Tweet me the link for your show!!!    
    
    
    @SocialStratagem Thank you for the follow Greg!    
    
    
    Join @ChelseaKrost now for #MillennialTalk #LIVE Twitter Chat    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 Are you joining us tonight Audra for #Millennialtalk ?    
    
    
    @BrandIdeas  Hi Timm! Welcome to #MillennialTalk .    
    
    
    @NewsToLiveBy Hi Danny!! How are you!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @_hannahbeasley  Hi Hannah! Welcome to #MillennialTalk :)    
    
    
    @melis_wilson How are you Melissa!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @LaurenMGalley @chelseakrost It certainly is!! Ready to learn how to keep your credit safe ??? #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @cmnathanson Hi Melissa!! Welcome to #MillennialTalk    
    
    
    @goKicker So excited to hear from @Adam_K_Levin tonight about #Cybersecurity! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @HelenAgresti @ChelseaKrost @Adam_K_Levin Hi Helen!! Wecome to Chelsea's Twitter Chat!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @adam_k_levin is co-founder and Chairman of http://Credit.com  & Identity Theft 911 & Expert in cyber finance security! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @ENPancotti Hi Elizabeth!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @ENPancotti Yes!!! #MillennialTalk    
    
    
    @HelenAgresti Hi Helen!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @Adam_K_Levin Hi Adam, Did you see the question:) #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @dannyhrubin Hi Danny! Welcome!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @TheGoldner @goKicker Great point Greg!!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @milwomanspeaks @ChelseaKrost How do you keep them straight in your head? #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @twestnedge @Adam_K_Levin @ChelseaKrost That is a tough one when you do have a lot of clients and passwords.  #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @RJRobledo7 Thanks for the info lol #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @LaurenMGalley Are Apps that help you store your passwords safe? #millennialtalk  Great question @Adam_K_Levin    
    
    
    @chevd80 Hi Cheval!!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @greggweiss @cmnathanson @volunTEENnation haha!! I only write online checks!! #MillennialTalk    
    
    
    Q2 @Adam_k_Levin What r some things that people r doing with their smartphone - that isn’t all that smart? #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @MichelFalcon No problem Michel!! We are still here:) #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @The_RachelRoss #Cybersecurity Here's the link for details:) http://bit.ly/19tag6c  #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @bronco4540 @rizal_mthghyv @Chelseakrost Hi Mark!!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub Hi Eliazabeth!!!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    Loving this chat w/ @Adam_K_Levin and @Chelseakrost #Millennials #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @kobikwelu I totally agree!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @Adam_K_Levin @ChelseaKrost I agree and sometimes the links seem so authenticate!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @The_RachelRoss @kobikwelu Good idea!! I don't make purchases via cell but I do banking on cell. #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @CynthiaY29 @rizal_mthghyv @Chelseakrost Hope you are enjoying Cynthia!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Yes Trey!! We are talking to @Adam_K_Levin about #CyberSecurity #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @Adam_K_Levin Interesting Adam!! I didn't realize that! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @meaganfraser4 @ChelseaKrost Haha!! #MillennialTalk    
    
    
    @BrandIdeas @ChelseaKrost @Adam_K_Levin I use paypal all the time:) #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @BrokeMillennial @ChelseaKrost Hi Erin!!! Glad you made it:) #millennialtalk    
    
    
    RT I feel this is often overlooked  Make sure site has valid security certif, address says https & url right! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    Loved the chat tonight @Adam_K_Levin & @ChelseaKrost #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @cmnathanson Haha! me too:) #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @thePRprincesss Next chat Dec 17:) #millennialtalk    
    
    
    Bye everyone!!!! #millennialtalk    
    
    
    @careerkick Yes!! I believe next week's #MillennialTalk will be about #GoalSetting:) Did you enjoy the chat?    
    
    
    @BrandIdeas Thanks Timm for joining in tonight for #MillennialTalk!    
    
    
    @chevd80 You too Cheval! Thank you for joining us tonight for #MillennialTalk!    
    
    
    @ENPancotti Sure Elizabeth!!! What part of Dallas do you live in?    
    
    
    What Burning #Facebook Questions Does YOUR Business Have?  http://bit.ly/197EkI0  via @MSocialBusiness #socialmedia    
    
    
    @AdibaNelson  Muy buenos dias a ti:)    
    
    
    @ENPancotti I don't know the area:) I live in Trophy Club.    
    
    
    @See_More_Money My pleasure Ruth!! Have a fantastic day!!    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @AdibaNelson Yes;)    
    
    
    @AdibaNelson I used to speak much better but no longer use Spanish as much as I did. Also was great w/ French:)    
    
    
    @AuntRuby Great to see you today Ruby!! Love you:) xo    
    
    
    @ZakStamborIR Thanks so much Zak for the follow!    
    
    
    @MOMMethod My pleasure! Have  a great day:)    
    
    
    @JimmyWinMedia Hi Jimmy!! Sent you dm.    
    
    
    @rebecca_mill HI Rebecca!! You can listen to @emilyeraleigh 's interview on #podcast after the show here http://bit.ly/1iMQa0m     
    
    
    The Three Tribes of Social Shopping http://ow.ly/ry6YO  via @Harvardbiz #SocialMedia #marketing #brands    
    
    
    @berkeslaw Thank you David!! So are YOU!! #friend    
    
    
    @RidingWithVW @bryankramer @AliceMartin8 @SusanCosmos @JuntaeDeLane Thanks Valerie!!    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman Thanks for the wonderful compliment Tom!! Hope you have an incredible Friday!    
    
    
    @thepeav @HarvardBiz Thanks Jim!! Hope you had a fabulous Thursday!    
    
    
    @chevd80 @ebongeka Great Cheval! Will try to listen tomorrow. Just now getting on computer! Was a really crazy day:)    
    
    
    @dianebogut Haha! I have the house decorated but that is it lol. The ice storm delayed my Christmas shopping:)    
    
    
    @CherylMagill It is GORGEOUS!! How cozy!!! Tweet me more pics of inside when you can!! Absolutely LOVE it!!!    
    
    
    @MatthiasHuesgen Thanks for connecting!    
    
    
    @ebongeka HI Ebong! Can't wait to listen to your interview. Spent all day with Triple A and my car lol. No time to tweet:)    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman Very sweet, thanks!!!    
    
    
    @dianebogut Haha! Yes, and then since yesterday my car has not been working.FINALLY, I got it resolved!! #batterydied lol    
    
    
    @ebongeka Yes, finally! 3 trips from AAA & finally they came around to my thinking to replace my battery which was under warranty with them    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Haha! Not too bad just long:) Thanks Trey!!!    
    
    
    @thepeav @HarvardBiz Not too bad Jim!! Just glad tomorrow is Friday:) Have a great day tomorrow.    
    
    
    @CherylMagill @SWAGGMAG I bet it is cold and windy today Cheryl:)    
    
    
    @dianebogut ouch!! I still have lots of ice in my yard but the streets are fairly clear now. Very cold tonight! #Dallas    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Thanks Trey!! So love #virtualhugs!! One back to you:)    
    
    
    @CherylMagill @SWAGGMAG Same here lol    
    
    
    @SWAGGMAG @CherylMagill Chicago. Love her home!!!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 @ChelseaKrost @AdibaNelson @itsALEXAonline Good morning!! Just waking up:)    
    
    
    @RBAnglers Thanks Eric! Have a fantastic weekend!    
    
    
    @SharonNicholas @snowdenmcfall @debraoakland @GreenSkyDeb @LoriMoreno @JessAmethyst @debbie4pazhi HI Sharon!! Happy Saturday everyone:)    
    
    
    @snowdenmcfall Thanks so much Snowden! Happy Saturday!!!    
    
    
    @AndeLyons How is the Supreme Goddess Ande Lyons??    
    
    
    @inspire_me_to @ChelseaKrost @thepoorchef1 Thank you So much! Love what you are doing to give #Kids a quality read:) #books #children    
    
    
    @meaganfraser4 Thank you Meagan! So appreciate:)    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub Have a great day Elizabeth!! When are you heading to #LA? For biz or pleasure?    
    
    
    @AuntRuby @fionaannv @AndeLyons @TonioMarrero @MeeoMiia @leo_kristine  It is ugly here in Dallas but I hope sunshine on the way!!    
    
    
    @HelpWeveGotKids Have a wonderful weekend Tracie!    
    
    
    If you haven't optimized your #LinkedIn page, you must read this http://bit.ly/INZEro  via @TerrySullivan #socialmedia #jobsearch    
    
    
    @TerrySullivan Great post Terry on #LinkedIn http://bit.ly/INZEro     
    
    
    @MagnetBootGuy Congrats!!    
    
    
    @itsALEXAonline Sorry I missed it!! I wasn't online last night:( How was the concert??    
    
    
    @wtoussaint @kleimkuehler Thanks so much Wilson!    
    
    
    @rebecca_mill Did you hear the interview Rebecca??    
    
    
    @SuzanneHarden Thanks Suzanne!! So appreciate:) xo    
    
    
    @willisteam @sanzplans So jealous Linda!! Can you pls share that #sunshine with me in #Dallas?    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 How are you Ms Paris??    
    
    
    @KarenPilarski Thanks for the Rt Karen!! @TerrySullivan worked magic on my #LinkedIn page:)    
    
    
    @wtoussaint @kleimkuehler Thanks!! I need to really start writing more and posting more content:) So busy lol. Have a great weekend:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Love shopping!! What are you buying?? I am working a bit and going to try and do some shopping too:)    
    
    
    @lockieandrews Hi Lockie!! @TerrySullivan is amazing w/ @LinkedIn    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Ah for #Christmas!!!  Have fun!! Take some photos!    
    
    
    @KarenPilarski You are so sweet Karen!! Are you working today or going to relax?    
    
    
    @mikebertelsen Hi Mike and thank you!    
    
    
    @NovumDivesMike Good luck with your new #startup!!    
    
    
    @KarenPilarski Yes a lot to do and fit a party in lol but you have to make time for fun!! Good luck w/ the move:) I did that in September:)    
    
    
    @Trinh_Anthony Well reach out to @TerrySullivan!! Mine is optimized now in searches as well;)    
    
    
    23 Steps To Build Your Personal Brand http://ow.ly/ry7g6  via @jeffbullas #SocialMedia #branding    
    
    
    @chevd80 You are doing great work Cheval!! #Bullying is such an important topic!!! #radio    
    
    
    @chevd80 Thanks Cheval! I believe in Chelsea and what she is doing so it is an incredible opportunity for me:)    
    
    
    @HelpWeveGotKids Sorry Tracie!    
    
    
    @EmmeNation @AdibaNelson @TheaAndrews @elizabethtraub @EmilyTheOtt A big hello Emme! It's been while!!!!    
    
    
    @englishsisters Great to see you ladies!    
    
    
    @chevd80 Responded Cheval. Was making breakfast:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    2 incredible new artists @EmilyTheOtt @AudraLynn21 You must follow them!! Love their #music #Entertainment    
    
    
    Please follow this awesome Tweep @DrRobMelillo #Autism #ADD #ADHD #Neuroscience    
    
    
    @aprileparella A big hello Aprile! So great to see your beautiful face!! Are you enjoying the holidays?    
    
    
    @_Pixelbrand Doing fantastic actually Chris and yes enjoying!! It is passing by too quickly this year lol. What about you?    
    
    
    @AudraLynn21 @EmilyTheOtt Doing fantastic!!! Have a great week ladies!    
    
    
    @StrongLoveBlog1 Thanks so much!    
    
    
    Please connect w/ 2 of my incredible friends @aprileparella & @DrRobMelillo    
    
    
    @Mark_Weissman Going great Mark! Picked up an incredible client and doing lots of shopping lol. How are you doing?    
    
    
    @AndeLyons @TonioMarrero @AuntRuby @fionaannv @MeeoMiia @leo_kristine Arey you snowed in Ande??    
    
    
    @TonioMarrero @AuntRuby @fionaannv @AndeLyons @MeeoMiia @leo_kristine Sorry about that!! We had it a few weeks ago but ours was ice!!    
    
    
    @_Pixelbrand So jealous!! I spend a week in Chile 20 years ago. LOVE it:) What takes you there Chris?    
    
    
    @debraoakland Hi Debra!! Enjoy your week:) You deserve a break!!    
    
    
    @AndeLyons Would be so great if we could arrange an offline meet w/ a few of our friends next year Ande!!    
    
    
    @DrSheriMeyers Hi Sheri! Hope you have a fantastic week:)    
    
    
    @TonioMarrero @fionaannv @AndeLyons @AuntRuby @leo_kristine @MeeoMiia I thought you LOVED the cold Tonio lol.    
    
    
    @fionaannv We are supposed to be up to 70's by Thurs here in Dallas and then temps dropping a bit lol.    
    
    
    @SpitToonsSaloon Thanks so much!!    
    
    
    @AuntRuby Good morning beautiful. Happy Tuesday:)    
    
    
    @TonioMarrero  Haha! Gotcha Tonio. You should have seen Dallas a few weeks ago. I STILL have ice in my yard!    
    
    
    @_Pixelbrand I cannot remember all the places... Santiago was where I stayed but visited surrounding areas. Fantastic country!!    
    
    
    @AuntRuby @fionaannv @AndeLyons @leo_kristine @MeeoMiia @TonioMarrero Great Ruby!! How many inches lol?    
    
    
    Best-Selling Author @DrRobMelillo Launches New TV Show to Help Families With Special Needs  http://bit.ly/1gEno0c  #tvshow    
    
    
    @AndeLyons @letthemknow @RT @JesseWojdylo I do I do!!!    
    
    
    @AndeLyons @letthemknow @RT @JesseWojdylo I want to learn it deeper!!! Really starting to utilize it:)    
    
    
    @fionaannv So true!!! Love your photo Fiona!    
    
    
    @Mark_Weissman I think so too. This was a great year for me and keeps getting better:)    
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1 OMG!! Very excited for you!! Let me know please how it goes:) Please be safe!    
    
    
    @DrSheriMeyers Thank you Sheri!! Wishing the same for you:)    
    
    
    Please check out my friend @chevd80 's interview w/@AlHammer http://bit.ly/18Uwjpl  #radio    
    
    
    @chevd80 @AlHammer Yes! Just went to lunch and had delicious bbq!! Gorgeous sunny day in Dallas:)    
    
    
    @MillennialMagz Thanks so much for the follow!    
    
    
    Great Twitter Chat tonight for #Millennials at 8 pm ET w/ @ChelseaKrost called #MillennialTalk http://bit.ly/JnYofM     
    
    
    @chevd80 @AlHammer Hard 8 in Roanoke    
    
    
    @chevd80 @AlHammer You select your meat and they pile it on a tray:)    
    
    
    Join the Convo tonight at 8 pm ET on a new incredible Twitter Chat - #MillennialTalk #Millennials #Goals http://bit.ly/JnYofM     
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1 Have a wonderful visit Megumi!! Will be thinking about you tomorrow:) !!    
    
    
    @TammySigond Thanks Tammy!! #MillennialTalk    
    
    
    The #Hottest New Twitter Chat -#MillennialTalk Starts in 10 minutes!! Join @HeidiOran @TheGoldner & Host @Chelseakrost #Goals #Career    
    
    
    Need some #GoalSetting tweaks for 2014? Join #MillennialTalk Twitter Chat  Now w/ @Chelseakrost http://bit.ly/JnYofM     
    
    
    Get ready #NOW for a fantastic hour w/ a new Twitter chat #Millennialtalk via @chelseakrost http://bit.ly/JnYofM     
    
    
    Join #MillennialTalk Twitter Chat Now in Progress!! Details here http://bit.ly/JnYofM     
    
    
    @EmmeNation @AdibaNelson @TheaAndrews @elizabethtraub @EmilyTheOtt Thank you:) #MerryChristmas:)    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @AdibaNelson @ChelseaKrost @SSGriffin @CraftBeerBetty @dianebogut @itsALEXAonline @Smith_CourtneyM Have fun Elizabeth!    
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1 How did today go Megumi?    
    
    
    @GretchenVanD Have a wonderful day Gretchen!!!    
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1 That is amazing!! I cannot wait to hear more!! So happy for you. Did you get pics?    
    
    
    7 Tips to Build Your Best Personal Brand on #LinkedIn http://bit.ly/1cj1jgs  via  @kleimkuehler on @TurnitSocial #socialmedia #branding    
    
    
    @lonestarsally @dikeough @GrandmaOnDeck Thanks Sally! Have a great weekend!    
    
    
    @LoriMoreno @dianebogut @thebikinichef @GretchenVanD @Tall_Papa @fionaannv @DailyDimmick @debraoakland @YogaArmy Merry Christmas everyone!    
    
    
    @indadseyes @ChelseaKrost Thank you Andrew!! Have a wonderful weekend and Happy Holidays!    
    
    
    @dianebogut Ready for Christmas Diane?    
    
    
    @sanzplans Thanks Anita!! Happy Friday:)    
    
    
    @thepeav How has your week been so far Jim?    
    
    
    Happy Friday Everyone! Please follow my incredible friends @DrRobMelillo @robynstevensPR #TopTweeps    
    
    
    Twitter Tips: How To Use Twitter Tools And #Twitter http://ow.ly/ry6GX  via @forbes    
    
    
    @RBAnglers Hi Eric! Have a great weekend!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Happy Friday Emmanuelle!! Hope you enjoy the weekend:)    
    
    
    @DrACAnderson Great to see you April! Hope your weekend is Twabulous!    
    
    
    @TerrySullivan @TheBugBarians Thank you Terry! Hoping to spend more personal time here next year!! #NewYearsResolution    
    
    
    @TheBugBarians @TerrySullivan Merry Christmas to both of you!    
    
    
    Twitter Poll- Do you feel that your personal Twitter timeline is a sea of group tweets?    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Happy Saturday Emmanuelle:)    
    
    
    @BrandIdeas Hi Tim! Hope you are having an incredible day!    
    
    
    @HarperYi Hi Harper.I seem 2 get nothing but mostly "group tweets" lately. My name included with others and hard to get to individual tweets    
    
    
    @HarperYi I try to answer them individually so the entire group doesn't get bombarded with the replies lol.    
    
    
    @HarperYi Are you enjoying your holiday break?    
    
    
    @MRGSOMEDMAR Thanks for connecting Mike!    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Hi Trey!!! Do you feel that way too lol?    
    
    
    @HarperYi Hahah! I guess I better "trim" the tree:)    
    
    
    @TotalSocials Feeling it too lol?    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO It is getting a bit annoying:) I know peeps r busy and try to consolidate, but time to be more conscious of how we tweet :)    
    
    
    @HarperYi Sounds great to me!! Let her indulge:)    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Busy!!! I took on a new client:) So that is a great thing! What about you??    
    
    
    @HarperYi Yes, I find it difficult to work on my personal Social Media as so busy with my clients. Going to work on that for 2014:)    
    
    
    @HarperYi I'm looking for a great copywriter to do a small project for me. Do you know of one?    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Fantastic Trey!! Congrats:) So proud of you! You are an amazing person:)    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Going to talk to Chelsea about having you on #HotTopics early next year!    
    
    
    @HarperYi Yesss!! When can we talk? Want to get it done for the new year!!    
    
    
    @HarperYi I am the worst at self promo:)    
    
    
    @HarperYi Hard to do that during the holidays:) Do you workout? Movement is the key!! That is what I found!    
    
    
    @HarperYi Now that I sit at computer all day, I have to workout:)    
    
    
    @HarperYi I think I'm too humble lol. Not good in Social Media:) lol    
    
    
    @HarperYi When would you like to chat about it?    
    
    
    @HarperYi Monday works great!! Dm me your phone# and the time we can chat:) I am free most of day!    
    
    
    @HarperYi I use portion control too. When I eat out, normally I take half my food home. In Texas, it is very easy to overeat:)    
    
    
    Please connect with an amazing Tweep @DrRobMelillo #autism #add #adhd #LD    
    
    
    @HarperYi Thanks Harper! Are we talking EST??    
    
    
    @HarperYi Ah!! You know soda really packs the pounds!!! I am going to stop it again too. I do use agave in my coffee and tea:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 It is raining in Dallas!! And COLD lol. Have a wonderful Saturday:)    
    
    
    @HarperYi Yes, as I am Central:) I get very confused at times because I keep my computer set on EST time zone:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 I need to shop but I am not very inclined to go out in rain and cold. I want to hibernate:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @HarperYi Hope you have a great weekend Harper!! Looking forward to Monday!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 We don't have a lots of rain here normally. The past few months have been pretty gloomy!! I lived in Fl 4 years & love #sunshine:)    
    
    
    #Twitter Turns Ugly Over PR Person's Idiotic Tweet http://on.mash.to/JSrSCX  via @mashable    
    
    
    @SophieSelfie @mashable I would say so Sophie!! Not sure why people don't think before they tweet such stupid content!!    
    
    
    @SophieSelfie @mashable Haha! Very true J.J.:)    
    
    
    @SophieSelfie Ymw:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @_Pixelbrand YES!! Loving this time of year!! You are having warm weather aren't you?    
    
    
    @workingwithdave @mashable Haha!! Yes, they are an odd lot:)    
    
    
    @successipes Thank you Lori:)    
    
    
    @TeckieGirl Cold lol. Going to @BonefishGrill Southlake tonight:) How are you?    
    
    
    @TerrySullivan Thanks Terry! Merry Christmas to you and Cydney!!    
    
    
    @BrandIdeas Thanks Tim! Hope you have a Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @TeckieGirl @BonefishGrill Looks like a nicer day today! We have #sunshine in #Dallas!! What a great dinner last night at Bonefish Grill!    
    
    
    @ilovelaceyg Hi Lacey!! How are you?    
    
    
    @BrunoGebarski @LisaBarone @sewatch haha! Thanks!! Sorry!    
    
    
    @BrunoGebarski 8 Tips for Building Your Internal #ContentMarketing Strategy via @LisaBarone http://bit.ly/1ceHomJ     
    
    
    Hope everyone is having a wonderful Sunday!    
    
    
    Connect with an amazing Tweep @DrRobMelillo - Creating awareness and sharing research on #autism #add #adhd    
    
    
    @Outcastotter Thank you:) Having a great day so far!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Going shopping in a bit:)    
    
    
    @JCPhotography01 Hope you are enjoying your Sunday Joann!    
    
    
    The #GreatDebate on Content Ownership, #Copywriting Tips http://bit.ly/1fRWOhk  via @BardOfBoston on @hububhub #content    
    
    
    What #Millennials Can Learn From Masters Of Sex Part 2: http://youtu.be/7-ZISNVesbc  via @ChelseaKrost    
    
    
    @Outcastotter You too!!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Thanks!! I know how you like shopping too:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Thanks:)    
    
    
    The Top 5 Reasons Your #Website Visitors Bounce http://bit.ly/1hwFoam  via @B2Community #business #seo    
    
    
    10 Reasons Visual #Content Will Dominate 2014 via http://bit.ly/197zTwo  @B2Community #contentmarketing #socialmedia    
    
    
    8 Tips for Building Your Internal #ContentMarketing Strategy http://bit.ly/1ceHomJ  via @LisaBarone on @sewatch #socialmedia    
    
    
    What Burning #Facebook Questions Does YOUR Business Have?  http://bit.ly/197EkI0  via @MSocialBusiness #socialmedia    
    
    
    @StrongLoveBlog1 Thanks Carl! Hope you have an incredible week!    
    
    
    The #GreatDebate on Content Ownership, #Copywriting Tips http://bit.ly/1fRWOhk  via @BardOfBoston on @hububhub #content    
    
    
    The Top 5 Reasons Your #Website Visitors Bounce http://bit.ly/1hwFoam  via @B2Community #business #seo    
    
    
    @OMNVTVGenMe @GlenGilmore @HeidiOran @MillennialMktg @muslimillennial Thanks so much!!    
    
    
    @ThomasYongo Hi Thomas!! How are you?    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Wishing you a very Merry Christmas Emmmanuelle:)    
    
    
    @MEHEP4U Thanks for the rt!    
    
    
    @KarenPilarski Thank you Karen!! Are you enjoying the holidays:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Thanks!!!! You are so sweet:)    
    
    
    Special #Shoutout to @DrRobMelillo an amazing Tweep dedicated to helping #children #autism #add    
    
    
    @ThomasYongo Working out tweeting lol.    
    
    
    @RyanTotka Hi Ryan!! Do you know @ChelseaKrost ?? Thought I would introduce you two:)    
    
    
    @ThomasYongo Too funny!! I love to Tweet but not when I am #workingout!!!!    
    
    
    10 Reasons Visual #Content Will Dominate 2014 via http://bit.ly/197zTwo  @B2Community #contentmarketing #socialmedia    
    
    
    @ThomasYongo Haha! Okay do 100 crunches and 25 tweets:)    
    
    
    @MeaganKristen1 @B2Community Everyone is #Visual and thankful platforms are helping us to share it!!    
    
    
    @scottrohrig Hi Scott! Happy Holidays:)    
    
    
    How Brands Use #Infographics To Create More Powerful Messaging http://bit.ly/1kwFdOI  via @B2Community #socialmedia #contentmarketing    
    
    
    @ThomasYongo WOWEE!! That's alot of crunches and PAIN!!    
    
    
    @SimplyDesignsK Thank you for your rt Kristy!    
    
    
    @StacyMichelleB Thanks Stacy! Same to you!! Are you planning on a big Christmas celebration?    
    
    
    @meaganfraser4 Thanks Meagan!    
    
    
    @DrSheriMeyers @Affilipede @debraoakland @Dawn_Abraham @susan_e_winter @MiaLyngeA Thank you Sheri!! Wishing you and yours the same:)    
    
    
    @colecolemeyer Hi Cole!! I try:) Hope you have a fantastic Christmas:)    
    
    
    @Lindsay39 Thanks for the rt!    
    
    
    @Affilipede Happy Holidays Wayne!! You are such a generous Tweep!! Thanks so much for all you do:)    
    
    
    @JonesClass Thanks Kevin!!    
    
    
    How Brands Use #Infographics To Create More Powerful Messaging http://bit.ly/1kwFdOI  via @B2Community #socialmedia #contentmarketing    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman ty Tom!!    
    
    
    @colecolemeyer Don't worry Cole! Had finger surgery today so typing w/ 1 hand lol.    
    
    
    The Top 5 Reasons Your #Website Visitors Bounce http://bit.ly/1hwFoam  via @B2Community #business #seo    
    
    
    @MyVAService @B2Community Thanks Jody!! So important to know:)    
    
    
    @SarahZiba Thanks for the rt Sarah!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AndrewBehrensNJ  Thanks Andrew!! How was yours?    
    
    
    @itsALEXAonline @AndrewBehrensNJ @ChelseaKrost Is that your Mom ALexa? Hard to see:)    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman Yes, it is Tom! Thank you so much and hope your 2014 is the best year ever!!    
    
    
    @zobefit Had a really nice Christmas!! Looking forward to New Years too!! Glad you enjoyed:)    
    
    
    @AndrewBehrensNJ Mine was perfect! Quiet and small:)    
    
    
    @MinisinkDebbie Thanks for the rt Debra!! Have a very #HappyNewYears!    
    
    
    @TheFeliciaShow Thanks for the follow Felicia!!    
    
    
    @TheFeliciaShow Tried to check your site but it's password protected:)    
    
    
    @Affilipede Hi Wayne! How was your Christmas?    
    
    
    Big #Shoutout to @DrRobMelillo an amazing #doctor dedicated to those w/ #autism #adhd    
    
    
    10 Reasons Visual #Content Will Dominate 2014 via http://bit.ly/197zTwo  @B2Community #contentmarketing #socialmedia    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MyFutureMedia @LinkHumans @Rob_Bayne Thank you and Happy New Year!    
    
    
    @lohpohonn @B2Community @Elpose_CN Thanks Paul!! So appreciated!    
    
    
    @Affilipede I did Wayne! So glad yours was incredible!    
    
    
    @itsALEXAonline @AndrewBehrensNJ @ChelseaKrost LOVE lulu clothes!!!! So sweet:) She looks so young!    
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman Good morning Tom!! Are you enjoying a long weekend or do you have to work today?    
    
    
    @SyrenBlue Good morning Mendy!!    
    
    
    How To Use Google Analytics To Create Killer Content http://amex.co/1ikUiU1  via @mashable #bloggers #contentmarketing    
    
    
    10 Hottest Stories About Social Media in 2013 http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/230491   via @EntMagazine @lauraentis #SocialMedia    
    
    
    @SyrenBlue Thanks and same to you Mendy!    
    
    
    @aprileparella Hi Aprile! Hope you had a wonderful Christmas!    
    
    
    @BigHitWebinars Thank you !! My pleasure:)    
    
    
    @ARSocialTree @AndeLyons @letlifehappen @barbarabarna @whirlydudes @GreenSkyDeb @KirkJaco Thank you so much Andrea!!    
    
    
    @copykatrecipes @STARFORCEHH Thanks Stephanie!    
    
    
    #Amazon sold 426 items per second in run-up to Christmas http://bit.ly/1eJVOPb  via @verge #holidays #onlineshopping    
    
    
    @KLGruver Hi Kathy!! How was your Christmas?? I thought we were following each other!!    
    
    
    How to Find Influencers Who Already Want to Share and Link to Your Content http://bit.ly/1cXbWG1  via @KISSmetrics #bloggers #content    
    
    
    @GoodieBagMarket @KISSmetrics Thanks for the rt    
    
    
    @KLGruver How have you been Kathy?    
    
    
    @ChrisReimer @verge isn't that crazy??    
    
    
    8 Tips for Building Your Internal #ContentMarketing Strategy http://bit.ly/1ceHomJ  via @LisaBarone via @sewatch #socialmedia    
    
    
    The #GreatDebate on Content Ownership, #Copywriting Tips http://bit.ly/1fRWOhk  via @BardOfBoston on @hububhub #content    
    
    
    How To Use Google Analytics To Create Killer Content http://amex.co/1ikUiU1  via @AmericanExpress #bloggers #contentmarketing    
    
    
    10 Hottest Stories About Social Media in 2013 http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/230491   via @EntMagazine @lauraentis #SocialMedia    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Sustaintologist Thanks for the follow Lizette!    
    
    
    @ConnieImage Good morning Connie! Still enjoying the holidays?    
    
    
    @KLGruver Oh yes!! Things are going in the right direction!!! Have a wonderful weekend Kathy!    
    
    
    @GlenGilmore @lauraentis Thanks Glen!! #HappySaturday    
    
    
    @AurelioToral THanks for the rt!    
    
    
    @LynnPowered Hi Lynn! Thanks for your rt and Happy Saturday:)    
    
    
    #Amazon sold 426 items per second in run-up to Christmas http://bit.ly/1eJVOPb   via @verge #holidays #onlineshopping    
    
    
    @ConnieImage Super duper!! Working a bit today lol. My job never stops but will be talking a break later today!! Enjoy:)    
    
    
    @ConnieImage Thanks Connie! I really am:)    
    
    
    @Affilipede Thank you Wayne!! Wishing you a wonderful New Years!    
    
    
    @AndeLyons Hi Ande!! Are you still enjoying the holidays? Was Santa good to you??    
    
    
    How to Find Influencers Who Already Want to Share and Link to Your Content http://bit.ly/1cXbWG1  via @KISSmetrics #bloggers #content    
    
    
    Why Social Networks Are Crazy for Private Messaging http://on.mash.to/1dKQfe7  via @mashable #socialmedia    
    
    
    35 Mind Numbing #YouTube Facts, Figures and Statistics – #Infographic http://bit.ly/JzGupD  via @JeffBullas    
    
    
    The Year in #Twitter: Top Milestones of 2013 http://on.mash.to/1cxe4YP  via @mashable    
    
    
    @StuartDaniels21 Thanks Stuart!    
    
    
    @MagnetBootGuy Sent you a dm!    
    
    
    @DrMiaRose Thank you Mia!! Happy New Year:)    
    
    
    @Affilipede You are always so incredibly sweet Wayne!! #Muah    
    
    
    @whirlydudes Haha!! Nicest thing I have heard all day:) #HappyNewYear    
    
    
    @HarperYi It was great chatting with you Harper!!    
    
    
    @BrianRBaird Thanks Brian!! I have had some "Dede" time moments:) Love what I do!! How about you?    
    
    
    @LisaCroccoPR You are so sweet Lisa:) Thank you!!! Looking forward to your tweets!    
    
    
    @Broadcast_Hann My pleasure Hannah! Hope you are having a fantastic holiday!    
    
    
    @Broadcast_Hann Has been really wonderful Hannah thanks!    
    
    
    Follow @ChelseaKrost for the Latest Trends for #Millennials    
    
    
    @AbbyTakesMnhttn Thank you Abby!!    
    
    
    @BrianRBaird That's how I live my life:) Makes life more interesting:)    
    
    
    @LisaCroccoPR Same for you Lisa!! Tomorrow going to stay mostly #unplugged!!    
    
    
    @AmieTheGr8 Same you too Amie: #HappyNewYear    
    
    
    @bewonderfulnow Thanks for the rt Tom!! Are you planning a big New Years celebration?    
    
    
    @TygrScott Happy New Years Scott!    
    
    
    @HarperYi Good morning Harper! You are up early this morning lol.    
    
    
    Another Reason To Love #Twitter- Twitter feed warns Australian swimmers when sharks are nearby http://bit.ly/Ke2RBx  via @RT_com    
    
    
    @HarperYi Sounds great!! I have been up for hours too:)    
    
    
    Follow Millennial #ThoughtLeader @ChelseaKrost #millennials #speaker #host    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 @ChelseaKrost Hi Emmanuelle!! Happy Sunday:)    
    
    
    How To Use Google Analytics To Create Killer Content http://amex.co/1ikUiU1  via @AmericanExpress #bloggers #contentmarketing    
    
    
    Starting To Slowly Fall In Love With #Google+ http://on.mash.to/19Ua8R5   via @mashable    
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1  Good morning!! What mischief are you up to today Megumi?? :)    
    
    
    #Amazon sold 426 items per second in run-up to Christmas http://bit.ly/1eJVOPb   via @verge #holidays #onlineshopping    
    
    
    @MorganNetwork I find myself now getting so much of my news from #Twitter!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Thank you Emmanuelle!! Plans today?    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 At home lol. Afraid to go out because I keep spending money:)    
    
    
    @DrACAnderson Sounds yummy!! I love stews!!!    
    
    
    Why Social Networks Are Crazy for Private Messaging http://on.mash.to/1dKQfe7  via @mashable #socialmedia    
    
    
    35 Mind Numbing #YouTube Facts, Figures and Statistics – #Infographic http://bit.ly/JzGupD  via @JeffBullas    
    
    
    @LinkedInWriter Have a fantastic week Carol!    
    
    
    @chevd80 It was wonderful Cheval. Thanks for sharing. I was bullied incessantly in grade school. Left a lifetime impression.    
    
    
    @MorganNetwork Thank you Tom!!    
    
    
    @InspireTravel13 Thanks for the follow Kristin!    
    
    
    @LinkedInWriter You too Carol! Looking forward to it:) #HappyNewYear    
    
    
    @Liz_Aiello Thanks for connecting Liz! #HappyNewYear    
    
    
    Sunday #Shoutout to 2 Tweeps to Follow @ChelseaKrost @DrRobMelillo 2 Amazing Tweeps doing great things!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @loriruff @chevd80 So true Lori!! How are you??? Did you have a nice Christmas?    
    
    
    @JennaJadee So am I:) Will be fun!!! #HappyNewYear    
    
    
    @JennaJadee Thank you!!!:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    10 Hottest Stories About Social Media in 2013 http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/230491   via @EntMagazine @lauraentis #SocialMedia    
    
    
    How to Find Influencers Who Already Want to Share and Link to Your Content http://bit.ly/1cXbWG1  via @KISSmetrics #bloggers #content    
    
    
    35 Mind Numbing #YouTube Facts, Figures and Statistics – #Infographic http://bit.ly/JzGupD  via @JeffBullas    
    
    
    @iTweetTheirName Thank you!!!    
    
    
    The Year in #Twitter: Top Milestones of 2013 http://on.mash.to/1cxe4YP  via @mashable    
    
    
    @iTweetTheirName Thank you!!:) Have a great day!    
    
    
    The 3 Biggest Challenges People Face with #Twitter http://bit.ly/14LiaGx     
    
    
    @clhergenroether Thanks for the follow Cara!! #HappyNewYear    
    
    
    @DawnBurgun Thank you for the follow Dawn! Have a great day!    
    
    
    Marketers Learn to Play by #Facebook's Changing Rules http://ow.ly/s9CpV  via @mashable #socialmedia    
    
    
    #MondayTwitterTIp- Don't attack a brand or person here unless you have your facts!! Attempting 2 discredit someone without them is not cool!    
    
    
    Please rt my previous tweet:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @twinesocial Going to write a post about this for tomorrow:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 @jamucsb Nice to meet you and now following!! Helloooo Emmanuelle!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @JennaJadee Thanks Jenna:)    
    
    
    @swiftieloveit @ChelseaKrost She is the best isn't she Ashley?    
    
    
    @tamijardine Thanks Tami!! Sending you HUGELY positive #Twitterkarma!!    
    
    
    @JennaJadee Thank you!!    
    
    
    @AllanaPinkerton Thank you Allana for your rt!    
    
    
    The 3 Biggest Challenges People Face with #Twitter http://bit.ly/14LiaGx     
    
    
    @Affilipede @DrMiaRose @DrSheriMeyers @MiaLyngeA @debraoakland @Dawn_Abraham @susan_e_winter Happy New Years Wayne!    
    
    
    @AndeLyons You deserve it Ande! No, nearly impossible isn't it? Enjoy and #HappyNewYear    
    
    
    @loriruff  So sorry Lori!! Hugs!!:)    
    
    
    #follow @DrRobMelillo Professor, Neurologist. Author: Disconnected Kids Reconnected Kids & book on causes & how to prevent #Autism, #adhd    
    
    
    @ActorWebs @StevenVincent @randygravitt @Paul_O_Williams @FilmLadd @5thcinema My pleasure!! Have a wonderful night:)    
    
    
    Why Social Networks Are Crazy for Private Messaging http://on.mash.to/1dKQfe7  via @mashable #socialmedia    
    
    
    10 Hottest Stories About Social Media in 2013 http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/230491   via @EntMagazine @lauraentis #SocialMedia    
    
    
    @AndeLyons @AugstMcLaughlin @DanVForbes Woohoo!! Happy New Year Andelish!    
    
    
    Marketers Learn to Play by #Facebook's Changing Rules http://ow.ly/s9Ctq  via @mashable #socialmedia    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 A big Hello Emmanuelle!!    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 Thank you so much Emmanuelle:)    
    
    
    The Year in #Twitter: Top Milestones of 2013 http://on.mash.to/1cxe4YP  via @mashable    
    
    
    10 Reasons Visual #Content Will Dominate 2014 via http://bit.ly/197zTwo  @B2Community #contentmarketing #socialmedia    
    
    
    How to Find Influencers Who Already Want to Share and Link to Your Content http://bit.ly/1cXbWG1  via @KISSmetrics #bloggers #content    
    
    
    The 3 Biggest Challenges People Face with #Twitter http://bit.ly/14LiaGx     
    
    
    @LaurenMGalley Happy New Year Lauren!    
    
    
    @chevd80 Happy New Year Cheval!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @OlivierSoret Hi Oliver! Thanks for your rt!    
    
    
    Looking for Social Media Guest Bloggers for @Turnitsocial Tweet me if interested!! #Twitter #infographics #Facebook LinkedIn    
    
    
    @Cocoonfxmedia Every few months, I have to take them in to clear the viruses. I have an expensive anti virus and still not working!    
    
    
    @parkdodge It is crazy how often I have to take my computers in for maintenance!    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Do you feel it works faster?? I love my #ipad:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 I have 1 computer that is totally dead and one on the way! Just had both fixed a few months ago lol.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO As you know, we are constantly exposing ourselves to viruses and I am over the top ready to resolve this!! T    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @IlyaIussa You really made my day Ilya!! Thank you so much for your kind words!! You started my 2014 off with a smile:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 I know!! I got some gorgeous boots for Christmas which I ruined already:(    
    
    
    @perketing Fantastic Margaret! I see we live close:) I'm in Trophy Club.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO I'm a big fan of yours Trey!! You are an incredible person:)    
    
    
    @perketing I'm near 170 and 114. We could meet at Heritage Trace Pkwy! Just name the day:)    
    
    
    @GIZEH75 I scuffed them last night on a step ladder. Hoping shoe polish will help.    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Would be great!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1 Happy New Year Megumi!    
    
    
    @perketing I think I am free Friday. I work from home too:)    
    
    
    @TreyWheelerCEO Thank you Trey!! It would be an honor:) I am passionate about what I do and that is what makes the difference:)    
    
    
    What's the best thing that happened to you in 2013?    
    
    
    @perketing Very cool!! What about tomorrow then? We could meet for coffee or lunch.    
    
    
    Follow @DrRobMelillo  Author of "Disconnected Kids" #autism #ADHD    
    
    
    @patricklee6669 I so know that!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @perketing What time is good for you? There are so many places...  Olive Garden, Houlihans, BJ's, .....    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Thanks Tumi!! Did you have a good New Years Eve?    
    
    
    @JesseMoore_ Sorry about your loss Jesse!    
    
    
    @perketing Sent you a dm:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @RLHSWAP Thank you Robert!    
    
    
    The 3 Biggest Challenges People Face with #Twitter http://bit.ly/14LiaGx     
    
    
    @OlivierSoret Thanks Oliver!!!    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Not too wild but fun!! Too much champagne:)    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @chevd80 @MaherMaso Awesome!!!    
    
    
    @chevd80 @MaherMaso I'm in Trophy Club!!    
    
    
    @everypostme @Turnitsocial Sent you a dm!! Thanks!    
    
    
    @RyanSauers Thank you Ryan and same for you:)    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Haha!!!    
    
    
    @chevd80 @MaherMaso A city:) That's where I live! I see your guest is in Frisco?    
    
    
    @chevd80 Hi Cheval! Got your email and will be in touch tomorrow. Really tired tonight and cannot think lol.    
    
    
    @Tumi101 Glad you had a great evening:)    
    
    
    @aprileparella @TerrySullivan @ChelseaKrost @ModGirlMktg Congratulations Aprile!! Happy New Year!    
    
    
    @TerrySullivan Happy New Year to you and Cydney!!    
    
    
    @HarperYi Hi Harper! Haven't forgotten about you! Was crazy busy today!! Will be in touch tomorrow:)    
    
    
    @elizabethtraub @EmilyTheOtt @MightyMommy @gertymars @fondalo You staying warm everyone?    
    
    
    @HealthyLoserGal @roxanamjones @thegoalcontrol @InspowerBooks @EngagedMarriage @crystalandrus @DrWayneWDyer @CrystalVision Thanks so much:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @dianebogut @Turnitsocial Whenever there is time:)    
    
    
    Happy Friday to @EmilyTheOtt @dianebogut @ChelseaKrost @DrRobMelillo @chevd80 @elizabethtraub    
    
    
    Top #Podcasters Share Success Tips http://bit.ly/1dsUrRG  via @smexaminer #socialmedia #radio    
    
    
    @patdabiere Hi Pat!! Thanks:) #HappyNewYear    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1 @Tumi101 hahah! Texans don't like me:)    
    
    
    @MegumiHoshino1 @Tumi101 I am so not Texan. My politics and attitude definitely are different:)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Engschoolhouse That's awesome! Great to meet you:)    
    
    
    @fondalo @elizabethtraub @gertymars @MightyMommy @BundlePost Robert, I just have to take some time to look at it. Have been swamped!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Tom__Coleman @MelonieDodaro @MyVAService @SocialBoLLC @MartinSherv @JesseWojdylo @TygrScott @MySOdotCom Thanks Tom!    
    
    
    I rarely get a personal tweet anymore!! Anyone else feeling this way?    
    
    
    