Aphorism I http://nblo.gs/md4tI     
    
    
    Aphorism II http://nblo.gs/mgNri     
    
    
    HERMES: A new Twitter Corpus http://nblo.gs/mGuiB     
    
    
    Re-fusing form in genre study by Amy J. Devitt (2009) http://nblo.gs/nao5j     
    
    
    Re-fusing form in genre study by Amy J. Devitt (2009) II http://nblo.gs/nliZM     
    
    
    Flogs, i.e. the subversion of the blog genre http://nblo.gs/nNbTQ     
    
    
    hjälp! what kind of notation is the fowllowing? PHP5? PHP6?
	public function start()
	{ $this->startTime = $this->getTimestamp();}    
    
    
    Can't remeber we used arrows (->) in our php :-/    
    
    
    Recasting the blog as a collection of blog posts http://nblo.gs/ofYgi     
    
    
    Genre and Web Design http://nblo.gs/oCwMt     
    
    
    Web 2.0 Storytelling: Emergence of a New Genre http://nblo.gs/oFQ6m     
    
    
    eContent Discovery, textAnalytics, webGenre Identification, topicDetection and emotionMining for Web Development, Mobile Apps and Social Ne…    
    
    
    Your Site Genre http://nblo.gs/oRsVs     
    
    
    Följ oss på Facebook och i bloggarna!: Stockholms officiella besöksguide: http://www.visitstockholm.com/sv/Nyheter/Facebook/#.TqkfYZ_hW58.twitter … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Book Review: Genres on the Web (Mehler et al. 2010) http://nblo.gs/p7o5t     
    
    
    Mining emotions with lexical affect sensing http://nblo.gs/pei7z     
    
    
    Collaborative Blogging http://nblo.gs/phSnR     
    
    
    Gestalt Processes in User-Web Interaction: A Two-Side View http://nblo.gs/pDChL     
    
    
    Follow the comment thread with us!
Mining genres with lexical affect sensing? - http://www.forum.santini.se/2011/10/mining-emotions-with-lexical-affect-sensing/ …    
    
    
    User-Web Interaction: Gestalt in Information Retrieval http://nblo.gs/q07CN     
    
    
    Invitation to Facebook page http://nblo.gs/q8ifa     
    
    
    Towards Language–Independent Web Genre Detection (2009) http://nblo.gs/qbLZD     
    
    
    Web Genre and the Emergent Properties of Web Sites http://nblo.gs/qrHMz     
    
    
    Reading Suggestions? Knowledge Discovery & Social Networks http://nblo.gs/qxY7j     
    
    
    Provocation or Food for thought? Web sites as AI Mind Persons http://nblo.gs/qJ8o3     
    
    
    Question: How do you inject emotions into chatbots, Andres? http://nblo.gs/r2TLn     
    
    
    Social Media & Web Development http://nblo.gs/r41Qx     
    
    
    Book Review. Genres in the Internet (2009) http://nblo.gs/rnCNk     
    
    
    Forthcoming: Automatic Identification of Genre in Web Pages (2012) http://nblo.gs/rHDYL     
    
    
    Book Review: Syntax-Based Collocation Extraction (2011) http://nblo.gs/rI5ae     
    
    
    Book Outline: Automatic Identification of Genre in Web Pages (2011) http://nblo.gs/sJ6CM     
    
    
    Reading Suggestions: Genre & Sentiment-Emotion http://nblo.gs/t1EJS     
    
    
    Genre, Social Actions and Social Intelligence http://nblo.gs/tii6F     
    
    
    Beyond Topic: Genre and Search http://nblo.gs/tzRqe     
    
    
    I created group The WebGenre R&D Group on Linkedin.: http://lnkd.in/9qCCZ5     
    
    
    The WebGenre R&D Group has been created on LinkedIn-- http://lnkd.in/YFnxUx     
    
    
    The WebGenreBlog:  Adjectives and adverbs as indicators of affective language for automatic genre detection: http://lnkd.in/XYGtsc     
    
    
    The WebGenreBlog:  Adjectives and adverbs as indicators of affective language for automatic genre detection http://lnkd.in/YcR6hc     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/V2VrrR  Hi,    prepositions... interesting! Would you share your references? I am curious...    Best wishers, Marina    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/3swCzR  Hi Menno,  your website (Thinknowlogy, Fundamentally designed Artificial Intelligence) is exciting.    As far as...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/943_6p  Not sure about the meaning of "simulated intelligence" or "real intelligence". They might be new categories......    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/N4zi95  Jan, it seems to me that the web has unveiled the universe of strong emotions, public likes and dislikes. Language...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/N-K7Sm  That's an idea :-)    
    
    
    http://www.linkedin.com/groups/WebGenre-R-D-Group-4301498 …    
    
    
    Marina is playing with Buffer. Don't you know what Buffer is? A new aggregating application :-)    
    
    
    Structured, managed and "genres" http://bit.ly/wWMrqm     
    
    
    Overview: Automatic web Genre Identification: http://lnkd.in/CvzWE6     
    
    
    Overview: Automatic web Genre Identification http://lnkd.in/-fg_Bm     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/aeenYA  However, I do not know, David, the kind of data and problems you are dealing with. I do not know if you have...    
    
    
    Free Twitter Lexicon Download: http://lnkd.in/8mysDK     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/JF7xgM  Hi Myungchul, check your Download folder.  I could download everything, although I got the "access failed" message....    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/x5qWUP  Hi,     if you go to the Text Mining Group on LinkedIn, you will find a list of suggested data mining tools,...    
    
    
    Is there any Blog Dataset publicly available to download? http://lnkd.in/8fx-UT     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/YAVc3k  Great! Thanks Ali.    
    
    
    Reblogging: Big Data: http://lnkd.in/d8Ak7i     
    
    
    Genre and Noise: http://lnkd.in/gY6VDX     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/9eKDsV  Hi Antoinette,     all the links work from my computer. I repaste them here, so you can try again:    Link to the...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/RJq3CC  Hi Yuehong,    in a fully supervised single-label machine learning approach, you have a corpus of documents where...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/5Qn75V  Hi Yuehong,    if your problem is about ambiguity (i.e. a word can have several senses), try to see whether the...    
    
    
    Genre and Noise: Experiments: http://lnkd.in/xMsPBa     
    
    
    Games, use cases and instinct as a matter of genre: http://lnkd.in/tCC2T2     
    
    
    Games, use cases and instinct as a matter of genre http://lnkd.in/cGQpWf     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/-BwGNz  Hi Nilay,    I have the following suggestions:    Automatic Summarization Focusing on Document Genre and Text...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/5kD5tz  Hi,    I would also suggest the following:    -- Multi-document summarization by sentence extraction (paper)  --...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/uwer5x  As far as I know, there is a summarization module in NLTK (python)    Have also a look at these multi-document...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/_E2PVZ  Thanks a lot!    
    
    
    Dissemination: Free Web Corpora: http://lnkd.in/dGuG3U     
    
    
    Dissemination: Free Web Corpora http://lnkd.in/6YhM8g     
    
    
    From Big Unstructured Data to Contextualized Information: http://lnkd.in/dJHsTz     
    
    
    From Big Unstructured Data to Contextualized Information http://lnkd.in/8ucizZ     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ck9TcX  Hi Mshall,    Simone Teufel introduced a new a rhetorical-level analysis of scientific research articles called...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/mRTBXr  Hi Alexandro,    It is indeed a classification problem. In all the text analytic solutions that I have used/tried...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Qfph5m  Hi Ron,    I see it more as an automatic text classification problem. Genre, sublanguage, domain are TEXTUAL...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/VD5rPi  Hi Peter,    my view of big data is a large large large corpus of  single documents/texts. For ex, billions of web...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/SpuXvi  Thanx, Daniel.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/YTPjEh  Hi Mitiku,    try and have look. Or see research with learner corpora here:...    
    
    
    Big Data, BAD Predictions, and How to Improve It? - Lithosphere Community http://lnkd.in/6dXSXb     
    
    
    Google Maps goes retro for early April Fools' Day - Ingame on http://msnbc.com  http://lnkd.in/9Fffr6     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/hbd6ga  Thanks for the suggestion, Nitesh.  Marina    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/P-2MX2  Hi Ron,  what an interesting answer! Yes, Ron, your answer helps me understand better how the concepts of genre...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/XM8Beq  Hi Tom, thanks for your useful list. My experience with some of these products is that they need substantial...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/SKHa43  Hi Tom,    as for examples of genre classification done by humans, Mark Rosso worked a lot with this topic. Here...    
    
    
    Discussion Summary: From Big Unstructured Data to Contextualized Information: http://lnkd.in/u3UsRK     
    
    
    Discussion Summary: From Big Unstructured Data to Contextualized Information http://lnkd.in/zKdE8P     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/gz4m_C  Alexander: the machine learning algorithm makes a difference. I tried a naive bayes classifier and an SVM (within...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/AySgSV  Hi David,    can you give examples of "confabulation"? Do you mean "conversation", "dialogue", or something more...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TGx-th  Thanks, David. I understand better now. It sounds fascinating...  Cheers, Marina    
    
    
    Dissemination: Acknowledgement Search Engine and Next Generation Search Engines http://lnkd.in/s3N8cf     
    
    
    How to construct a taxonomy of user's interests automatically?: http://lnkd.in/BuAKSd     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/VpzkqS  Hi Leonid,    I know what you mean. I am also following the online Stanford NLP course and I was quite surprised to...    
    
    
    How to construct a taxonomy of user's interests automatically? http://lnkd.in/EdqykG     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/sJC72r  Hi Alexander,    as far as I know with support vectors, overfitting is unlikely to occur. I had small datasets and...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/BA6R4q  Hi Nigel,    thanks for letting me know. I have now removed the floating bar.    Cheers Marina    
    
    
    Summer School in Information Retrieval: RuSSIR 2012: http://lnkd.in/CxTNSZ     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/VhhMSW  Dear Alexander and Leonid,    It might be that genre classification is more unpredictable than classification with...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TZtk7R  Great!   I will send to you both the datasets in the next days.  Leonid, pls send me your regular email address,...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/xSKKHT  Thanks Francois! That would be great. Must check whether the data can be shared, first....    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/dxv4jz  Aha! Interesting... Thanks Sujit.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/NTHbhq  Hi Alexander.    yes I understand...    Since I used weka, I also used the data mining book associated with it...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/FZG6Dp  Thanks a lot for all the suggestions, Ina!  Cheers, Marina    
    
    
    New Social Software: LucidMeetings: http://lnkd.in/9paXUQ     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/6MG6Ny  Prateek: thanks. I will have a look at it.  Alexander: yes, it is likes, blogs, social network actions...    
    
    
    Electronic Meeting as a Genre of Organizational Communication: http://lnkd.in/JAsjhe     
    
    
    Electronic Meeting as a Genre of Organizational Communication http://lnkd.in/8A8pgy     
    
    
    Reading Suggestions: Social Network Analysis and Mining for Business Applications: http://lnkd.in/S6S4nx     
    
    
    Reading Suggestions: Social Network Analysis and Mining for Business Applications http://lnkd.in/m57dep     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/UcQp4s  Richard and James  Your questions, suggestions, experience are very inspiring and useful for my pre-study. Thanks...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/-h5mFB  Hi Leonid,    thanks a lot for your evaluation.    It seems to me that the performance of a specific classifier...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/FBcaPP  Yes, right, OWL...  I had not thought of it. Thanks, Scott.    Marina    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/3MSC5B  Leonid:  Multi-class problems are solved using pairwise classification. Have look here:...    
    
    
    I just joined London Text Analytics http://meetu.ps/1H04     
    
    
    Can anyone suggest references about mining query logs for BI and CEM?    
    
    
    Mining query logs for BI and CEM: http://lnkd.in/ZwE2h2     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Y2PvuJ  Leonid: if you wish more technical details, maybe you can contact the WEKA teams for the implementation of their...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ZJereg  Hi Kelly and Magnus,    thanks a lot for your suggestions. It would be handy to start from some pre-built...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/q7HDGa  Hi,    you could compute the POS n-grams (trigrams, 4-grams etc) on a large (standard/national) corpus and then...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/FaAv8n  Thanks, Alfredo.  Marina    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/J4XDcM  Hi Nilanjan,    see also some comments on your question here:...    
    
    
    RE: How to construct a taxonomy of user's interests automatically?: http://lnkd.in/7ARPxN     
    
    
    RE: How to construct a taxonomy of user's interests automatically? http://lnkd.in/EhkgGh     
    
    
    Marina:Santini http://lnkd.in/PWBe4Z     
    
    
    Mining query logs for BI and CEM http://lnkd.in/rYXB_Z     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/kp_Mch  Suggestions are welcome through LinkedIn, Facebook, Wordpress and Twitter.  Link to the blog post:...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/vawUSi  What about using overlap coefficients (Jaccard, Dice, and similar)?  Maybe also semantic cues (e.g. synonym...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/fjvi6v  Now that I think of it, I reckon I had a similar problem in one of my experiments (Cross-testing... : an excerpt is...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/kcGmEN  Yes, why not? it would be a good idea to give it a try.    Thanks, Alla!    Cheers, Marina    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/jRBx_s  Hi Prateek,    I would like to keep the goal undefined for the time being. I would like to have a broad views of...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/42hbjG  Great! Thanks a lot, Ina.    
    
    
    Free Online Course: Social Network Analysis: http://lnkd.in/UgpiHQ     
    
    
    Free Online Course: Social Network Analysis http://lnkd.in/C7Cwnf     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/VKGcsR  Smart!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/7PSyPM  Thanks for the useful Link!  Cheers, Marina    
    
    
    Reblogging: Informer, Spring Issue: http://lnkd.in/dKUv4R     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/RFqB8S  "Research into online learning suggests that it is roughly as effective as classroom learning. It’s easier to...    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/196117758743461093/ … Marina's blog    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/EPX6Z2  What is a "Chief Disrupter", Bruno?    
    
    
    Online Free Course for Agile Developers: starting soon: http://lnkd.in/ZFCmCe     
    
    
    Free Online Course: Agile Development for Software Engineering: starting soon http://lnkd.in/e7HGRV     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/196117758743470900/ … Agile Development    
    
    
    Text Analytics, The Difficult Future You Can’t Avoid http://www.tomhcanderson.com/?p=5741  @tomhcanderson    
    
    
    @bonnier_rd, your Klout Score is 26 (I'm a 51). Check out your @klout profile today! http://klout.com/bonnier_rd?n=tw&v=invite …    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Q8YyNy  Hi Seth,  when did you write this article? In 2011 or earlier? Can you give us a publication date? It can be...    
    
    
    #instawalkfotografiska   @ Järntorget http://instagr.am/p/Kj8vwTDWG8/     
    
    
    #instawalkfotografiska   @ Gamla Stan http://instagr.am/p/Kj9dBPDWHI/     
    
    
    #instawalkfotografiska   @ Gamla Stan http://instagr.am/p/Kj93EJjWHO/     
    
    
    #instawalkfotografiska   @ Gamla Stan http://instagr.am/p/Kj9_-GDWHP/     
    
    
    #instawalkfotografiska http://instagr.am/p/Kj-ZWojWHU/     
    
    
    #instawalkfotografiska http://instagr.am/p/Kj-tbTDWHc/     
    
    
    #instawalkfotografiska http://instagr.am/p/Kj-1ibDWHg/     
    
    
    #instawalkfotografiska http://instagr.am/p/Kj-6ayjWHi/     
    
    
    SearchInFocus: Searching for Actionable Intelligence: http://lnkd.in/QjXfeD     
    
    
    SearchInFocus: Searching for Actionable Intelligence http://lnkd.in/8ZNSrU     
    
    
    A little tutorial on mapreduce: http://lnkd.in/yxWg6b     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/THTm4t  Oleg: for big data. Another useful introduction is: "Data-Intensive Processing with MapReduce" by Jimmy Lin and...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/uh6zvP  c u there!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/przrd9  Oleg:   1) Type of Data: mainly tweets, FB posts, emails, query logs  2) Detection: Users' interests, topics,...    
    
    
    Mining Query Logs: Query Disambiguation & Understanding through a KB: http://lnkd.in/Xz7YWw     
    
    
    Mining Query Logs: Query Disambiguation & Understanding through a KB http://lnkd.in/aZUNnv     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/EmqVeQ  Thanks, Mark!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/eH3P52  I understand your objections.   However, I do not object against the creation of a more comprehensive and flexible...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/wbrE5c  Kelli: culture is always hard to encode because it can be ... everything. If one manages to narrow down the focus,...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/5wgT-v  Hi David,  your concern is justified. But I would go practical ... this means that I would start from real-world...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/-G4_66  Hi Mohammad,    have a look at this : Classification of Web Sites at Super-genre Level   by Christoph Lindemann and...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/R9xwrP  I enjoyed reading Tom's review of the SAS12. I agree with Tom's conclusions but I would use a slight different...    
    
    
    LinkedIn Events: Findability Day 2012 http://linkd.in/KLLBBE     
    
    
    Contextify: Contextualized Information and Content Enrichment: http://lnkd.in/kjrCp4     
    
    
    Contextify: Contextualized Information and Content Enrichment http://lnkd.in/J5kuSW     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/sAAq7V  Hi Alexander,     thanks for your suggestions and insights. Anaphora resolution is certainly an important factor...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/tfmDQN  Hi Vineet,    I really appreciated all pointers. They very useful for my research.     However, I have the...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ywQxza  Hi Alexander,     thanks for your suggestions and insights. Anaphora resolution is certainly an important factor in...    
    
    
    Genres on the Web http://www.springer.com/computer/ai/book/978-90-481-9177-2 … via @twitterapi    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/2ZTWHR  Hi Rajve, thanks for your encouraging feedback!  Cheers, Marina    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/tWMj7T  Elliot: I will keep you informed about context. I will post a summary of tools/suggestions in the next weeks....    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/xpQ8u3  That's a big question, Alexander. Ambiguity is pervasive. Just think of the metaphors used in the internet/computer...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/n8eKP5  Håkan: what is genre? that's another big question :-)    I will give you a short answer. Do not hesitate to let me...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ae6q6h  Alexander: yes, why not?    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ydCU8c  Hi Elliot,    I do not know what happened to Lingomotors. When I was there, the aim was the creation of a...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/mSRVs4  Myungdae: I am not familiar with SKOS yet, but I will explore it in the future.     By the way, in last week's blog...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/dH4jtz  Alexander, I have not decided the taxonomy of subfields because this must be discussed in large panel. However, it...    
    
    
    I just joined Stockholm Big Data http://meetu.ps/crjld     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/SiyAt3  Hi Ian,  thank you for your interest! Can you give us some examples of "unsafe context"? Unsafe context makes me...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TKUPHz  Eliot: if you are interested in more discussion on this topic there has been a paralled thread here:...    
    
    
    Sociolinguistics & Opinion Mining Systems: http://lnkd.in/HSRanE     
    
    
    Sociolinguistics & Opinion Mining Systems http://lnkd.in/uPf_vT     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Yp8X6u  Hi Robert,   sorry for this inconvenience.  I do not know why the link from the blog  post is not working.   The...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/wJtdST  Fixed!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/MHYsb7  Timothy: interesting comment. My personal opinion is that situational context (i.e. the situation that triggers the...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/__tvB6  Thanks, Timothy.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/q7pmFq  Maybe Alexander can give us more details about sociolinguistic features...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/VeCKHE  Diana: I was reading a paper that you co-authored -- Automatic detection of political opinions in Tweets...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/KSxtDq  Let me add another more general but very recent pointer:    Sentiment Analysis and Opinion Mining  New Book, Bing...    
    
    
    A Very Short History of Big Data http://wp.me/p1AMkl-85  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ijvSZ9  Thanks, Diana!    
    
    
    Reblogging: Practical advice for machine learning: http://lnkd.in/GZPjAi     
    
    
    Reblogging: Practical advice for machine learning http://lnkd.in/emgzBk     
    
    
    Historical Tweet Collector via @texifter | @scoopit http://bit.ly/MlVt4O     
    
    
    Reading Suggestions: Meaning & Genre — Affect & Buying Behaviour: http://lnkd.in/tB-EuR     
    
    
    Reading Suggestions: Meaning & Genre — Affect & Buying Behaviour http://lnkd.in/nUsQiD     
    
    
    Prototyping an Emotional Conversational Agent: http://lnkd.in/yhg2kz     
    
    
    Stratified Sampling for Oversampling Small Sub-Populations: http://bit.ly/LUet5R     
    
    
    Test Your Text Analytics Knowledge http://lnkd.in/uKxbB3     
    
    
    Next Gen Research Ad Measurement http://www.tomhcanderson.com/?p=5761  @tomhcanderson    
    
    
    A freely available, open source taxonomy and autoclassification tool: http://lnkd.in/Z99QU9     
    
    
    A freely available, open source taxonomy and autoclassification tool http://lnkd.in/Nww-Xj     
    
    
    @FlaxSearch Hi Charlie, I have just reblogged Clade here: http://www.forum.santini.se/2012/06/reblogging-a-freely-available-open-source-taxonomy-and-autoclassification-tool/ …
Sounds fascinating....    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/K7heJR  Thanks Vijay!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/PCRQUw  Not sure, Myungdae...    
    
    
    Genre 2012 -- Carleton University 26-29 June 2012: http://lnkd.in/VcPwhz     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/xdNJ5Z     
    
    
    Reblogging: Designing Search: Results pages: http://lnkd.in/vR9FFi     
    
    
    Review: The Word-Space Model Revisited http://lnkd.in/3ykkJ4     
    
    
    The WebGenreBlog: The Word-Space Model Revisited http://lnkd.in/Mzuzhm     
    
    
    Communities of emotional avatars http://lnkd.in/mYcgxQ     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/eCq_tA  Hi Eduard,    can you point us to any trial version of the technology you describe? Is any web prototype available...    
    
    
    Reblogging: Gavagai! Gavagai! http://lnkd.in/bR4DX3     
    
    
    Review: Creating Corpora With Active Learning http://lnkd.in/KixgEp     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Zy-W9i     
    
    
    The WebGenreBlog: Creating Corpora With Active Learning http://lnkd.in/RFjEDP     
    
    
    Vacation Time!: http://lnkd.in/gR9htz     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/4QE9ZC  I pass your request to Magnus, David.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/jdRfGT  Thanks, Katharina.    
    
    
    Towards Contextualized Information: How Automatic Genre Identification Can Help http://lnkd.in/CKqUdH     
    
    
    Seminar - Towards Contextualized Information: How Automatic Genre Identification Can Help http://lnkd.in/N5gY9F     
    
    
    Seminar on Automatic Genre Identification: http://lnkd.in/2DwnWx     
    
    
    Check out "Exploratory Query-log Analysis" …http://exploratory-query-log-analysis-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Exploratory Query-log Analysis http://lnkd.in/8FDnAc     
    
    
    LET'S CONTEXTUALIZE!: http://lnkd.in/FYSdDi     
    
    
    "Big Data" event in Stockholm: http://lnkd.in/WuPKY6     
    
    
    "Big Data" event in Stockholm: http://lnkd.in/J3Um-9     
    
    
    Exploratory Query-log Analysis http://lnkd.in/8FDnAc     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/_jii7R  Not a bad idea, Tony !    
    
    
    Meeting Report: Big Data in Stockholm: http://lnkd.in/YGqiRb     
    
    
    Meetup Report: Big Data and Predictive Modeling – What’s happening in Sthlm? http://lnkd.in/yaQ4v5     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/BCC9Ui  Hi Paul,   I consider big data as an interesting research problem for linguistics, and above all for computational...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Ra2WgN  Exactly! I probably I misinterpreted what you meant by big data being an industry or the cloud. Can you explain...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/tN7dD4  Hi Chakir, do you mean that the big data area belong to applied linguistics?    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ec_WwQ  :-)  I think we just need different and innovative approaches. In other words, more research...    
    
    
    Mining Web Query Logs to Analyze Political Issues at Yahoo! Research: http://lnkd.in/8vqgbE     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Y_3keY  Thanks for sharing, Paul!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/3mEJBH  I completely agree with you, Oleg!    
    
    
    The WebGenre R&D Group http://lnkd.in/9qCCZ5     
    
    
    Dissemination: Multi-Labeling Web Pages by Genre http://lnkd.in/kwe_Zm     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/JZqiG9  Try accessing the blog home page first:...    
    
    
    Announcement: Coursera Free Online Course to program in R: http://lnkd.in/Y9q-YW     
    
    
    Text/Content Analytics for Suicide Prevention (I): http://lnkd.in/AQXtbU     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/hezC7T  Great! Thanks a lot, Zsofia    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/VReyn8  Thanks, Amit and Wenbo. Highly appreciated!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/aEAJTB  Thanks, Pawel!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/BmpHzJ  That's great, Carole. Big Thanx!    
    
    
    Automatic Language Analysis for Suicide Prevention http://lnkd.in/YQtzJt     
    
    
    Text/Content Analytics for Suicide Prevention (II) http://lnkd.in/GAKhiw     
    
    
    Dissemination: Review : Mehler, Sharoff and Santini (eds, 2011) Genres on the Web. Corpora , Volume 7 (1): 109, May...: http://lnkd.in/hKcfnV     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/WNJab8  Thanx Alison. I update the blog post with your "reinforcement" of Pennebaker's work.    
    
    
    Graduate Programs in Big Data Analytics and Data Science   http://wp.me/p1AMkl-cl  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/hj8z7t  Hi Oleg and Dario,    I would like to add your useful discussion to the comments to the blog post, so others can...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/RV65gK  Thanks Frank and Marcel! I add your suggestions to the blog post.    
    
    
    Dissemination: Trigrams and Psychology: http://lnkd.in/EXG3Qf     
    
    
    Dissemination: CYBEREMOTIONS -- Collective Emotions in Cyberspace: http://lnkd.in/UX8DHU     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/jzEBNz  Great! Thanks, Kenneth    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/znvym2  Let me think, Alexander...    
    
    
    Check out this Meetup with Quantified Self Stockholm http://meetu.ps/llRd0     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/CyCjeT  Dear all, I keep the blog post...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ABcy8p  Thanx, Isabel. I add your suggestion here:...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/EVQpc2  Very good pointer, Jonathon! Thanx    
    
    
    Request: Looking for Multi-Dimensional Social Network Datasets/Corpora/Collections http://lnkd.in/HaYd3b     
    
    
    TheWebGenreBlog: Looking for rich social network datasets http://lnkd.in/M5dR5Z     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/mR24zY  Many thanks, Lee.    
    
    
    Dissemination: Search Solutions 2012: November 29, London: http://lnkd.in/V_FzVG     
    
    
    The Science Behind Social Media, Natural Language and Big Data (Infographic) http://lnkd.in/gt6R5T     
    
    
    Reading Suggestion: From Sentiment to Intent: http://lnkd.in/8U94Wa     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/FrSp9u  Alexander: I asked Michael Thelwall about findings related to sociology+psychology. Here is the answer:    "We...    
    
    
    Summary: Multi-dimensional Social Network Datasets http://lnkd.in/cqpw_7     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/EeeKvK  Terrible experience! Thanks for sharing.     Language analysis is always important in order to prevent tragic and...    
    
    
    A taxonomy for book genres (I) http://lnkd.in/Kr6zBw     
    
    
    A taxonomy for book genres (II): http://lnkd.in/i54gnP     
    
    
    Book Genres - A List Of Every Writer Should Know To Be Successful http://lnkd.in/Kr6zBw     
    
    
    A taxonomy for book genres (I) http://lnkd.in/8hwb9K     
    
    
    A taxonomy of book genres (III): http://lnkd.in/rEjdm8     
    
    
    A taxonomy of site genres: http://lnkd.in/BVSdcN     
    
    
    Exploratory Query-log Analysis http://lnkd.in/8FDnAc     
    
    
    Query Log Analysis Workshop: Program and Abstracts, 25 Oct 2012, Lund, Sweden http://lnkd.in/ZJQP3J     
    
    
    Dissemination: Ngram Viewer 2.0 by Research  Google: http://lnkd.in/QNazY3     
    
    
    SearchInFocus: Exploratory Study on Query Logs and Actionable Intelligence http://lnkd.in/A5cR7D     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/wDSzvs  Hi Piotr,     it is interesting what you say. Do you have any example, or experience to share on this subject?...    
    
    
    Towards a Computational Theory of Digital Genre (I): Working Definition of Genres for Computational Purposes http://lnkd.in/ZSN7hD     
    
    
    Actionable Corpus and Actionable Intelligence http://lnkd.in/q2HYPC     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/MKby_6  Hi Kelly and Mor,    I listened to an interesting presentation about temporal modeling of search queries using...    
    
    
    Thesis Review: Opinion mining and lexical affect sensing http://lnkd.in/vJExAP     
    
    
    Thesis Review: Opinion mining and lexical affect sensing -  http://www.forum.santini.se/2012/11/thesis-review-opinion-mining-and-lexical-affect-sensing/ …    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/SjqCtY  done!    
    
    
    Help with Student's Survey: http://lnkd.in/eZYUa9     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/n3-AZD  Ok, Diaa. The request is posted here:...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/E77kuA  I complete agree with Carole. Features are fundamental for classification tasks. However corpus composition and...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Wmu2B9  Hi Mustafa, I suggest asking Alexander. He is on LinkedIn, you can easily connect with him, I believe. Otherwise....    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TMB9zC  I have no problems in agreeing with you about the importance of stopwords (a. k. a. most frequent words). However,...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ajdCt7  Hold on a sec... " fashion, politics, art, etc" are NOT "genres", they are topical categories.  Comedy, tragedy,...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/wcztdJ  Mixed categories, or fuzzy categories, are a common problem in all types of classification. If you think of music...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/PTSCfz  That's useful help for improvements, Gary. Diaa, if you improve your survey, you  will get more meaningful results....    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/dx_rJv  Extremely interesting, Przemyslaw. I would really appreciate if you could send me the pdf of your accepted paper...    
    
    
    Dissemination: Informer: Autumn 2012 Issue: http://lnkd.in/fVSGnv     
    
    
    Dissemination: Collecting Twitter Tweets - Free Tools: http://lnkd.in/V6AYTY     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/vrcMwh  Nice e-magazine, Pascual. Very relevant to my interests    
    
    
    Seminar in Stockholm: Language in the Digital Age: http://lnkd.in/EanHen     
    
    
    Thesis Review: Emotion in Information Retrieval http://lnkd.in/e4329S     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/rZD5qB  Thanx, Antonio    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/4-X9Xj  Thanx, Manjunath    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/aKJtAE  Glenn: following the author's reasoning, the latter.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/acTNfN  Thanks, David! It's great to have you in this group discussion. Take care    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/vSZYWv  Hi Diana, unfortunately I am not aware of any emotion analysis in Spanish. I will keep you posted whenever I will...    
    
    
    Thesis Review: Cross-Language Ontology Learning http://lnkd.in/Sp_5Nj     
    
    
    Free online course: How to build a search engine: http://lnkd.in/mph6Sg     
    
    
    Reblogging: Big Data and Healthcare: http://lnkd.in/FTqAey     
    
    
    I'm attending a Meetup with Stockholm R useR group (StockholmR) http://meetu.ps/nkwCR     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/nGkg-p  Absolutely, culture and language play a big role also in the query log genre.   It would be interesting to see what...    
    
    
    Highlight: Collective Intelligence: http://lnkd.in/7vyDTd     
    
    
    Report:  Language in the Digital Age – META-NORD National Workshop http://lnkd.in/PvJ6U4     
    
    
    Reblogging: Report on Search Solutions 2012, 28-29 November 2012, London, UK: http://lnkd.in/t9AhuZ     
    
    
    Reblogging: A view from the inside - SAS perspective: http://lnkd.in/bCHjNH     
    
    
    Free Webinar on R: http://lnkd.in/Rqy8rj     
    
    
    Question: How to Define Criteria for Subgenre Classification? http://lnkd.in/UDNSgV     
    
    
    Dissemination: Classification of TEXT genres http://lnkd.in/jHNvSx     
    
    
    Dissemination: Cross-domain analysis of task and genre http://lnkd.in/2ShAem     
    
    
    Dissemination: Semantic Uncertainty http://lnkd.in/JFSEpi     
    
    
    Interesting study: Social media & Customer care: http://lnkd.in/GfE5_9     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/W7Sq6u  Hi Fahime,    Have you already asked the members of all groups interested in corpora? For example, all the groups...    
    
    
    Reflection: Analysing Emotions of Social Writing http://lnkd.in/s_useR     
    
    
    Dissemination: A free semantically annotated corpus: http://lnkd.in/bwNyKg     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/UyTTqU  Have a look here: [http://nl.ijs.si/ME/|leo://plh/http%3A*3*3nl%2Eijs%2Esi*3ME*3/Zay9?_t=tracking_disc]...    
    
    
    Dissemination: Information Architecture & Search: http://lnkd.in/q_tAf8     
    
    
    Webcast on Bid Data and Statistics: http://lnkd.in/WYAxUu     
    
    
    Request: Corpus-Based Sublanguage Glossary http://lnkd.in/ydCWZj     
    
    
    Thesis Review: Resolving Power of Search Keys http://lnkd.in/6bzepy     
    
    
    Season's Greetings: http://lnkd.in/sKX_xi     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/4hAnei  Hi Valentino,    thanks for your suggestion.   Bootcat is certainly a quick way to create corpora from scratch....    
    
    
    Dissemination: Final Conference of the EU FP7 CyberEmotions Project: http://lnkd.in/-CnK3x     
    
    
    Dissemination: Final Conference of the EU FP7 CyberEmotions Project http://lnkd.in/3zee36     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Y5Hch9  Great, Lance!  Thanks a lot for such a detailed description.  Merry Christmas,  Marina    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/nk-Q9s  Hi Asslam,    I would suggest something like "Evolution of search topics over time"...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/sUKqs6  ....or, to say it in other words, topic trends in search queries...    
    
    
    Invited Talk: How Emotional Are Users' Needs? Emotion in Query Logs: http://lnkd.in/8N6NBr     
    
    
    Invited Talk: How Emotional Are Users' Needs? Emotion in Query Logs http://lnkd.in/HSvPcT     
    
    
    Dissemination: Synthesis Lectures on Information Concepts, Retrieval, and Services: http://lnkd.in/jnZcD5     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/KNEN2b  Big thanx Willy and Jason. Great hints.    
    
    
    Book in Preparation: A Computational Theory of Digital Genre http://lnkd.in/kewfSj     
    
    
    Book in preparation: A Computational Theory of Digital Genre http://lnkd.in/Dg-RxE     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/pQzpcn  Thanks Khaled. I will think about it.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/5fFNpC  Big thanks, John, for your detailed comments.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/WPQ7xF  Hi Khaled, if by DFA you mean deterministic finite automata, the answer is I do not know yet. The initial...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Vtjw_P  Hi Chaker,    may I ask you what you mean by multi-language genre classification? are you referring to documents...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/B4FzTJ  Can you give me an example of such a genre? maybe Facebook posts? or are you referring to something else?    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/iT6P7S  Yes, I will discuss this kind of multi-linguality.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/dfh_Rq  ok, I will get back to you later. Thanx    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/HNzHb6  TOC = Table of Contents    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/hBY_BB  No problem, Khaled.    
    
    
    Dissemination: Facebook Search Power: http://lnkd.in/r3XA_D     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/3vNCMm  Hi Gideon,    I thank you very much for your reflections and thoughts. I will include them in my list of discussion...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/EJ7DQB  Dear Nyasha, I appreciate your feedback. I will think about introducing multimedia genres, or at least I will try...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/5taXh9  With pleasure...    
    
    
    Presentation: How Emotional Are Users’ Needs? Emotion in Query Logs http://lnkd.in/kn2WRC     
    
    
    Dissemination: Informer - Winter 2013 Issue: http://lnkd.in/RwyidR     
    
    
    Query Logs for Download: Italian and Swedish: http://lnkd.in/VqXCaj     
    
    
    Query Logs for Download: Italian and Swedish http://lnkd.in/EHvHTm     
    
    
    R you in Stockholm? Join the next R useR meetup: Text analytics using R: http://lnkd.in/jGbSWN     
    
    
    R you in Stockholm? Join the next R useR meetup: Text analytics using R http://lnkd.in/ZqBZPX     
    
    
    R you in Stockholm? Join the next R useR meetup: Text analytics using R http://lnkd.in/ZqBZPX     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/56dBgF  Big thanks, Vyacheslav! Probably I have inadvertently duplicated the url :-(  I am going to fix it...    Cheers    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/uZaRi7  Great!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/CcimWm  Hi,    You can can by reading wikipedia article on Information Extraction...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/J3njiQ  For those who wonder about the emotional strength of a query such as: "How to stop breastfeeding and make it sleep...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/SE3wkB  Alexander, when you say that "most emotional texts are emotional only implicitly" this means that probably we do...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ttrCDE  Great, Katerina!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/rjNDuF  Download this pdf from the web  Information Extraction: Techniques and Challenges, by Ralph Grishman    Read also...    
    
    
    Emerging discipline: Collective Intelligence: http://lnkd.in/5VquhG     
    
    
    How could language technology help out with youth suicide prevention?: http://lnkd.in/pvKnUJ     
    
    
    Dissemination: Suicide Prevention using Administrative Data: http://lnkd.in/rt2aGG     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/F-7Xa8     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/GrJZU3  Thanks to you, David, for the pointers!    
    
    
    Dissemination: http://lnkd.in/4TMSJ8     
    
    
    Dissemination: Arvid Kappas' view on Emotions and Cyberemotions: http://lnkd.in/Ffvx-5     
    
    
    Dissemination : Parsing Models for Identifying Multiword Expressions: http://lnkd.in/fjP9Dk     
    
    
    Multi-Word Expression and Machine Translation: http://lnkd.in/CZkTXS     
    
    
    Announcement: Advanced Threat Protection summit: http://lnkd.in/Ye_V4t     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/JR8PRy     
    
    
    Bringing Genre into Focus : BULLETIN of the American Society for Information Science and Technology: http://lnkd.in/ad29Sn     
    
    
    Check out this Meetup with Stockholm R useR group (StockholmR)! http://meetu.ps/w4tld     
    
    
    Meetup Announcement: Text Analytics and R (Stockholm): http://lnkd.in/D-hYni     
    
    
    Applying Name Entity Recognition to the identification of topic trends: http://lnkd.in/DWCRN9     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/XddEJB  Hi Taous,    I am afraid can't help here :-)  I am sure you will find good hints on the web    
    
    
    Small data, mid data and big data: http://lnkd.in/e46VYM     
    
    
    Microblog language identification: overcoming the limitations of short, unedited and idiomatic text http://lnkd.in/BUEQZs     
    
    
    Peeping into the future: Sending your smartphone to med school: http://lnkd.in/cMeqsR     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/iirxsu     
    
    
    New Book: Data Mining and Knowledge Discovery http://lnkd.in/vGZYZK     
    
    
    Open Access Article: Microblog language identification: overcoming the limitations of short text http://lnkd.in/jxPQJw     
    
    
    Collective intelligence and language resources http://lnkd.in/CZYfCD     
    
    
    Call for Papers: TIR 2013 - 10th International Workshop on Text-based Information Retrieval: http://lnkd.in/8rzDHw     
    
    
    Call for Papers: TIR 2013 - 10th International Workshop on Text-based Information Retrieval http://lnkd.in/tK5NTM     
    
    
    Customer Analytics: http://lnkd.in/8x8zmg     
    
    
    Call for Papers:  Forty-Sixth Annual Hawai’i International Conference on System Sciences (HICSS-47) - Materiality...: http://lnkd.in/zETEpT     
    
    
    How Big Data Is Changing the Whole Equation for Business http://lnkd.in/8u38rE     
    
    
    Dissimination : HICSS-47 Minitracks: http://lnkd.in/xabPz9     
    
    
    Dissimination : HICSS-47 Minitracks http://lnkd.in/Qi9-Pv     
    
    
    Call for Papers: Digital Forensics: http://lnkd.in/u3ZX4Q     
    
    
    Presentation: Text analytics and R – Open Question: is it a good match? http://lnkd.in/-d_-G9     
    
    
    Presentation: Text analytics and R http://lnkd.in/kDiQq5     
    
    
    Commercial Evolution of Social Networks http://blog.gnip.com/commercial-evolution-of-social-networks/ … via @gnip    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/xzhZaA  Hi Triss, from the discussion came out that R is good, but not for big big data (say >= terabytes). So it depends...    
    
    
    Live casts of the Text analytics using R meetup: http://lnkd.in/pRp5JN     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/7KGEdZ  Thanks, Carole! The whole discussion was lively and inspiring.   Live casts of this meetup are available here:...    
    
    
        
    
    
    SEM 2013: Second Joint Conference on Lexical and Computational Semantics: http://lnkd.in/fGBbjw     
    
    
    Customers Analytics at Sentiment Analysis Symposium: http://lnkd.in/VdWCVn     
    
    
    ONLINE COURSES IN UNSTRUCTURED TEXT ANALYTICS: http://lnkd.in/42chg9     
    
    
    Reblogging Information Interaction: last post by Tony Russell-Rose: http://lnkd.in/YcCUFu     
    
    
    Tutorial: Practical Sentiment Analysis: http://lnkd.in/WpCsHv     
    
    
    Colorful Pipes In The Dalles - Stunning Photos Of Google's Massive Data Centers - Forbes http://lnkd.in/3XGnCd     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/dz5aFg  You can find R code suggestions in this thread:...    
    
    
    A rare look inside Facebook’s Oregon data center [photos, video] http://lnkd.in/7sgx3S     
    
    
    Homo socialis...: http://lnkd.in/G4UBU9     
    
    
    About Representativeness of sample size: http://lnkd.in/Kz5btV     
    
    
    SPSS, SAS, R, Stata, JMP?: http://lnkd.in/u_xMae     
    
    
    Datasets, Corpora and Forensic Linguistic Research http://lnkd.in/hx9-jQ     
    
    
        
    
    
    Top 10 Most Funded Big Data Startups: http://lnkd.in/xXKZuv     
    
    
    The Big Data Paradox: http://lnkd.in/XiT7qx     
    
    
    Text Analytics World | Interviews http://lnkd.in/zy6G_Q     
    
    
    An Interview with Tom Reamy: http://lnkd.in/En8BMN     
    
    
    Screencast from StuartWShulman's Library: Bloomberg Pilot Project: http://lnkd.in/dyqu-K     
    
    
    Open discussion...: http://lnkd.in/mRmvCT     
    
    
    The Zuckerberg Case / Forensic Stylistics from the Bench http://lnkd.in/Mqp2as     
    
    
    Reblogging: Ensemble Learning: http://lnkd.in/dc26-F     
    
    
    Three principles of text analytics heresy by Meta Brown: http://lnkd.in/99b7Yi     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/fiakKZ  I would love to travel to St. Louis :-)     BTW, this article was suggested by Kyle Silvestro, whom might be an...    
    
    
    Tweets, Posts, Tags and Likes: Is Social Media the Future of Outbreak Epidemiology? http://lnkd.in/ie9fgn     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/eGu2s5     
    
    
    Towards a Cross-Lingual Lexical Knowledge Base of Lexical Forms http://lnkd.in/d_XAPz     
    
    
    Towards a Cross-Lingual Lexical Knowledge Base of Lexical Forms -  http://www.forum.santini.se/2013/04/cross-lingual-lexical-knowledge-base/ …    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/PbiMue  Thanks a lot for the suggestions and ideas. I am going to collect all the hints (also from other sources) as...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/rAbqVi  Hi John,  a timely update of lexical resources for single words and multiwords is both a monolingual and...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/a6h2hC  I am updating the blog post's comments with suggestions and hints from different discussion groups and sources......    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/fP4dsD  Big thx, Maria Teresa!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/8_4BWS  Thanx, Suzanne    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/fJA9We  I will do that, Stephen. Thanks for advice and encouragement.    
    
    
    Search that sucks: http://lnkd.in/JZtu8r     
    
    
    Scenarios for the Future of the IT Industry http://lnkd.in/v-j4sD     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/5uheFb  Good suggestion, Paolo. I have now added BabelNet (and some other resources) in the body of the blog post. Thanks.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/K9tsjR  ok, good to know. Thanks!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/sSAznY  Thanks for sharing your experience, Leo. I am sure you were a pioneer in the field. Thank you also for stressing...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/QQMZDc  I see what you mean, Leo.   I tried "ontsteking" --> English, and also "inflammation" --> Italian.   You said "We...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/btiaMZ  Hi Carole,  I am thinking of a cross-lingual lexical resource that can be used for NLP and by humans. Afterall,...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/zYA6pw  The wiki is still not perfectly in shape. The home page is ok, but the repository is still 404. You can start...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/qhUS4N  Thanks!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/47-idP  The WebGenreWiki works fine now.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/k4Ugya  Good to know about EU projects, Luca. Thanx    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Rb96UJ     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/KN-_uU     
    
    
        
    
    
    Requests for proposal (RFP) and IR http://lnkd.in/hvHV2S     
    
    
    Request for Proposal (RFP)  and IR http://lnkd.in/M_KkAb     
    
    
    The psychology of (cyber)emotions: http://lnkd.in/Z9f35p     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/4bRz3j  Thanks a lot, Martin, for your pointers. Hope I can attend the Findability day here in Stockholm!    
    
    
    Dissemination: Enterprise Search Summit in London: http://lnkd.in/-atUMS     
    
    
    Dissemination: Register as a predictor of linguistic variation: http://lnkd.in/TeKAhW     
    
    
    Ph.D. thesis: Domain Adaptation for Parsing: http://lnkd.in/3cnk7w     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/2tMjVi  This is the link to the pdf:...    
    
    
    Research Advances: Automatically Assessing Machine Summary Content Without a Gold Standard: http://lnkd.in/5zxYVS     
    
    
    Research Advances: Automatically Assessing Machine Summary Content Without a Gold Standard http://lnkd.in/PCjQQ7     
    
    
        
    
    
    Text Analytics in 2013 - Overview: http://lnkd.in/ujugJV     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/H4DWYK     
    
    
    Old School BI & the new vision http://lnkd.in/HtNrVc     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/_7nSJ5     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/dyGwqw  Thanks for your feedback and support, William!    
    
    
    Think Mid Data, and Triangulate: Tom H.C. Anderson on Next Generation Research Methods http://lnkd.in/WgTkzZ     
    
    
    Dissemination: Machine Learning Pitfalls: http://lnkd.in/_nzZKE     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/MV-4B5  Good idea Ramin :-)    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/5ZD-KH  no need to apologize, David...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/A_uipc  done!    
    
    
    Video Lectures recorded at Final Conference of EU Project CYBEREMOTIONS: http://lnkd.in/E-Wdfd     
    
    
    Papageno: Predictive Models for Crisis Intelligence http://lnkd.in/j3PGHq     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/P2zGTz     
    
    
    Papageno: Predictive Models for Crisis Intelligence http://nblo.gs/L5AyJ     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/k5cbHa  Hi Ina,    I would be great if you post post them here. Eager to know your suggestions, which are always to the...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/XS56tA  Thanks a lot!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/CcmztK  Thanx Bill!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/CUV7wC  Thanks a lot, Tamarie!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/-56DSG  Katerina, I could not find record of "early bird registration" (which is very common in the academic world when it...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/9qkGaM  big big thanx!    
    
    
    Horizon 2020, Framework Programme for Research and Innovation http://lnkd.in/F49-Aw     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/3F2r2d  Thanks for sharing your experience, Manuel and Martin!    
    
    
    Information sharing: Horizon 2020: http://lnkd.in/iuD6Jm     
    
    
    Annotated dataset for opinion retrieval in Twitter: http://lnkd.in/dhNzPU     
    
    
    Annotated dataset for opinion retrieval in Twitter http://lnkd.in/96YjCf     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/QyPWBP  Hi Charlie,  absolutely! I am interested.... marinasantini.ms@gmail.com    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/_WjNqX  Hi Stefan,   I do not see any inter-rater agreement stated in the paper (see the link in the discussion...    
    
    
    New PhD Thesis: Predicting Linguistic Structure with Incomplete and Cross-Lingual Supervision: http://lnkd.in/RGcxV5     
    
    
    New PhD Thesis: Predicting Linguistic Structure with Incomplete and Cross-Lingual Supervision http://lnkd.in/P5d3Cd     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TJv9hh  Hi Harsh,     I suggest contacting the authors directly. Their emails are in the paper...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/uu8duf  "language" and "linguistic structure" are very vague expressions, if one thinks of it.  are we referring to...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/GVtWf4  Thank you for the pointers, Lucy!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Dissemination: Ninth Suicide Prevention Conference in Stockholm http://lnkd.in/_NjCAm     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/VuWa4H  Thanks, George!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/8jyiSF  Sure, Tanja!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/NdfJa3  Georgios Paltoglou suggests also a paper in last year's ECIR about annotating the TREC microblog 2011 qrels for...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Pya7iF  Timo and Phil, thanks a lot for your references and interest. I hope I will manage to share ideas through a blog...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/dmJUr5  Thanks Debanjan and Vinayak for your comments. I will publish a blog post...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/zAm957  In the next weeks I will point out some challenges. So we can have a more focussed discussion on a number of...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/UWUbnp  Tania, would you like to share with us the link to your dissertation/report? It is very much related to the topic...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/8Yd-sU  Absolutely great!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/quhFFS     
    
    
        
    
    
    IoT Week, Helsinki, 16-19 June 2013 What would you like to know or present regarding Data Analytics? http://lnkd.in/u5NNg7     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/h9bzv5  I am sharing with you this discussion started in the the UBIQUITOUS NETWORKS - Internet of Things, Internet of...    
    
    
    Opinion Retrieval and Ranking: the creeping and  ineluctable force of Genre http://lnkd.in/qwbxqx     
    
    
    Squib: Opinion Retrieval and Genre Conventions http://lnkd.in/5YRtVV     
    
    
    Opinion Retrieval and Ranking: the creeping and  ineluctable force of Genre http://nblo.gs/Lxy8E     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/yFWcbK  Hi Quinn, can you give us some references or the website of the project?  thanks    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/SkTWe3  Big thanx, Quinn!    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/gWgmgt  Thanx, Glenn!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/DXYFv9  Hi David,   thanks for the reference to Intelligence. I will read the full article when I get hold of it. It fits...    
    
    
    Call for Papers: Special issue on Computational Intelligence for Natural Language Processing: http://lnkd.in/A-kjPD     
    
    
    Call for Papers: Special issue on Computational Intelligence for Natural Language Processing http://lnkd.in/Q6ri2s     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/QvpijR  You might be right about the state of our social and resource sharing, David. But we are rapidly improving,......    
    
    
    Dissemination - Workshop announcement: Factor Analysis vs Principal Component Analysis: http://lnkd.in/UyYRmr     
    
    
    Dissemination - Workshop announcement: Factor Analysis vs Principal Component Analysis http://lnkd.in/WDWt3X     
    
    
    Dissemination: Were the Victorians cleverer than us? The decline in general intelligence...: http://lnkd.in/yXcEpH     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/72jaHW  David, thanks for the article!    
    
    
    Enterprise Search has a very bright future! http://lnkd.in/aiHJyk     
    
    
        
    
    
    Request: Sentiment analysis tools for non-coders?: http://lnkd.in/64DPej     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/VgYJ_C  Thanx Evgenia and Ghada!    
    
    
    Culturonomics: Glossary of political terms: http://lnkd.in/NA_T2x     
    
    
    Culturonomics: Glossary of political terms http://lnkd.in/Y7Cpwv     
    
    
    Towards a Safer Web (with Language Technology) http://lnkd.in/43ubkQ     
    
    
    Towards a Safer Web (with Language Technology) http://nblo.gs/MwTET     
    
    
    Threat analysis: corpora available?: http://lnkd.in/h-vsp2     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/-UxXQC  Thanks David!    
    
    
    Threat analysis: corpora available? http://lnkd.in/jVwuhP     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TmnZVe  Great Christopher! Thanks    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/exTdb9  Thanks, Bob. See my email.    Debanjan, start having a look at the CTAD (Communicated Threat Assessment Database),...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Avus9E  That's one of challenges, Debanjan. Maybe u can suggest a smart solution for this problem?    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/jDgcxw  That's one of the research questions we would like to contribute to answer...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Pyiy6W  Stat reading this: Tammy Angela Gales "Ideologies of Violence: A Corpus and Discourse Analytic Approach to Stance...    
    
    
    Dissemination: Search & Text Analytics: http://lnkd.in/VvjJns     
    
    
    Dissemination: Search & Text Analytics http://lnkd.in/d29a5v     
    
    
        
    
    
    Resource available for research: weblog and social media dataset http://lnkd.in/jGhiMs     
    
    
    Dissemination: Digital Health Days 2013 in Stockholm: http://lnkd.in/grnzpA     
    
    
    Dissemination: Digital Health Days 2013 in Stockholm http://lnkd.in/jRcjZy     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/hN-VyK  Which thesis, Pedro, are you interested in?    
    
    
    Reblogging "Follow the Data" latest post:: http://lnkd.in/uATZiN     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/z5mRFb  The resource is downloadable from here:...    
    
    
    Call for Participation: The 7th Linguistic Annotation Workshop (LAW): http://lnkd.in/mdqC-q     
    
    
    Machine Learning as a Service: http://lnkd.in/6AZ4wJ     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/sHegUD  Yes, absolutely, Saeedeh!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ma-Dds  Text Mining, Text Analytics & Machine Learning    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/3TGvGQ     
    
    
    Predicting policing based on Big Data: http://lnkd.in/pWR2Bc     
    
    
    Dissemination: Computational Linguistics, Volume 39, Issue 3 - September 2013: http://lnkd.in/Z4syPy     
    
    
    Vaghe stelle dell'orsa...    
    
    
    Lecture 1: Introduction – Machine Learning for Language Technology http://lnkd.in/R7v36A     
    
    
    Lecture 1: Introduction – Machine Learning for Language Technology http://nblo.gs/OpQxt     
    
    
    Distributional Semantics applied to Flickr® Tags http://lnkd.in/nT8ZNf     
    
    
        
    
    
    Distributional Semantics applied to Flickr® Tags http://nblo.gs/OuGe9     
    
    
    Lecture 02: Decision Trees and Nearest Neighbors http://nblo.gs/OuGe8     
    
    
        
    
    
    Lecture 03: Linear Classifiers http://nblo.gs/OziCN     
    
    
    Why your brain may work like a dictionary - life - 29 August 2013 - New Scientist http://lnkd.in/8r6_JS     
    
    
    Lecture 04: The Weka Package http://lnkd.in/b5Zq2Bb     
    
    
    Lecture 04: The Weka Package http://nblo.gs/P6Vub     
    
    
        
    
    
    Lecture 5: Structured Prediction http://nblo.gs/Pjrek     
    
    
    Cloud and Big Data Day 2013 - Program http://lnkd.in/bbkj96X     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Forensics Analysis of #Westgate Tweets http://lnkd.in/bJx_7Hi     
    
    
    Cloud and Big Data Day http://lnkd.in/b_eyBXK     
    
    
    Cloud & Big Data Day http://nblo.gs/PGoM4     
    
    
    Lecture 7: Learning from Massive Datasets http://lnkd.in/bnvdiAR     
    
    
    Lecture 7: Learning from Massive Datasets http://nblo.gs/PRofF     
    
    
    Semantics Perspective on Physical-Cyber-Social Computing http://lnkd.in/bsgsU4A     
    
    
    Automata | Stanford Online http://lnkd.in/bGDvwQj     
    
    
    Machine Learning | Stanford Online http://lnkd.in/b5YYbAd     
    
    
    Tools and insights for a data scientist http://lnkd.in/btWEtHp     
    
    
    Entropy Calculator in Python http://lnkd.in/bkTRrpU     
    
    
    Random Forest and Naive Bayes for predictive modelling http://lnkd.in/bPkhJYM     
    
    
    Where do Twitter trends start? Try Cincinnati. http://lnkd.in/bpPXfmi     
    
    
    Course: Semantic Analysis in Language Technology http://nblo.gs/QuHGH     
    
    
    Announcement: New Meetup Group in Stockholm on Machine Learning http://lnkd.in/bMmDMRf     
    
    
    Machine Learning on Coursera http://lnkd.in/bxrwiR2     
    
    
    Learn Machine Learning from the class archive on Coursera http://lnkd.in/bxrwiR2     
    
    
    Michael Collins’ Natural Language Processing course review http://lnkd.in/byFk2w7     
    
    
    Lecture 1: Semantic Analysis in Language Technology – Introduction http://nblo.gs/QQASi     
    
    
    Lecture 1: Semantic Analysis in Language Technology – Introduction http://lnkd.in/bdK7GXZ     
    
    
    Dataset sharing services at the International AAAI Conference on Weblogs and Social Media (ICWSM) http://lnkd.in/b_u8kyC     
    
    
    Collocations and Textual Genres: Recent Findings http://lnkd.in/bmymrCe     
    
    
    Lecture 2: From Semantics to Semantic-Oriented Applications http://nblo.gs/RglpV     
    
    
    Affect Detection in tweets - Microsoft Research http://lnkd.in/bgdef4V     
    
    
    How to build your own Twitter Sentiment Analysis Tool | DatumBox http://lnkd.in/bXCVezc     
    
    
    Forensic Linguistic Evidence http://lnkd.in/bRdAj3k     
    
    
    Lecture 3: Structuring the Unstructured via Sentiment Analysis http://nblo.gs/RnQqf     
    
    
    Review: Academic Writing and Genre (2008) http://nblo.gs/eM54l    
    
    
    Review: Multimodality and Genre (2008) http://nblo.gs/eOUXA    
    
    
    Book Review: Discourse on the Move (2007) http://nblo.gs/eRuI5    
    
    
    Book Review: Email Hoaxes (2008) http://nblo.gs/f2w2O    
    
    
    Book Review: Corpus Linguistics and the Web (2007) http://nblo.gs/f8xh2    
    
    
        
    
    
    Chapter Excerpt: Riding the Rough Waves of Genre on the Web http://nblo.gs/fo4Vv    
    
    
    Abstract: Conventions and Mutual Expectations http://nblo.gs/frzIr    
    
    
    Abstract: Identification of Web Genres by User Warrant http://nblo.gs/fxkJ9    
    
    
        
    
    
    Excerpt: Cross-Testing a Genre Classification Model for the Web http://nblo.gs/fUsRK    
    
    
    Abstract: Formulating Representative Features with Respect to Genre Classification http://nblo.gs/g2bnQ    
    
    
    Abstract: In the Garden and in the Jungle: Comparing Genres in the BNC and Internet http://nblo.gs/g9ZHY    
    
    
    Web Genre Analysis: Use Cases, Retrieval Models, and Implementation Issues http://nblo.gs/geBkw    
    
    
    Abstract: Marrying Relevance and Genre Rankings: an Exploratory Study http://nblo.gs/gmMVb    
    
    
    Abstract: Classification of Web Sites at Super-genre Level http://nblo.gs/gzd6T    
    
    
    University of Borås: lecture and seminar slides http://nblo.gs/gC9dh    
    
    
    Abstract: Mining Graph Patterns in Web-based Systems: A Conceptual View http://nblo.gs/gL7Sm    
    
    
    Excerpt: Genre Connectivity and Genre Drift in a Web of Genres http://nblo.gs/gWex0    
    
    
    Looking for genre-specific corpora http://nblo.gs/h7BmZ    
    
    
    Abstract: Genre Emergence in Amateur Flash http://nblo.gs/haBix    
    
    
    Supercrancky mood not allowed!    
    
    
    Abstract: Variation Among Blogs: A Multi-dimensional Analysis http://nblo.gs/hkgRb    
    
    
        
    
    
    Chapter: Any Land in Sight? http://nblo.gs/hGbYC    
    
    
        
    
    
    A trip to Barcelona in May…. What shall I “Discover”? Topic extraction and mood analysis? http://nblo.gs/irEbL    
    
    
    Glimmering stars of the Great Bear... A new year starts, and new adventrues begin... I wonder if I will ever resume my diving course...    
    
    
    The sheer idea of jumping off a 10-meter high platform makes me terrified! Uhm must be feasible... But... Maybe I can just dive from 5m :-)    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @jazzygio I will ring you up later during this sunday .... Smile    
    
    
    What's happening? Don't ask me: ingen aning...    
    
    
    