“@StayPuft: Without them, you'd all be named Zuul. Thank Ghostbusters It's Friday. #TGIF” Definitely.    
    
    
    Firm in outbreak probe has history of run-ins with FDA http://usat.ly/1bkdwSJ  via @usatoday    
    
    
    Superpowers, Please http://wp.me/p2N5DR-QJ     
    
    
    @SFriedScientist @bgrassbluecrab I figured that's how your goat habit came about!    
    
    
    Superpowers, Please http://nblo.gs/QqktO     
    
    
    It's @HammDiabetesCtr Research Symposium. Having fun getting sciencey again.    
    
    
    @bam294 @drugmonkeyblog Yeah, I'm sure that's the first time your kid has heard that term.    
    
    
    @GertyZ @doc_becca @bam294 
SO. MUCH. WRONG. CAN'T. UNSEE.    
    
    
    Hey @Sephora - I pinned and blogged your nailpolish #SephoraSweeps | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/19EuZ9t     
    
    
    @DrRubidium I do not miss winter in Nebraska.    
    
    
    At #HHDCSymp learning about FGF21 and diabetes. Promising new area for treatment    
    
    
    FGF21 makes white fat act like brown fat. #HHDCSymp    
    
    
    @bam294 @drisis @MTomasson EXCUSE ME?????    
    
    
    @drisis @bam294 @MTomasson I've never done diddly squat with stem cells. Of course, I'm no longer funded...    
    
    
    @bam294 @drisis @MTomasson Bourbon with stem cells...isn't that what starts the zombie apocalypse?!    
    
    
    FGF21 effects are NOT CNS-mediated. Yay! No brainer!    
    
    
    Adiponectin required for FHF21 effects. #HHDCSymp    
    
    
    @bam294 He's been educated today.    
    
    
    FGF21 andGLP1 have synergistic effects on body weight via loss of adipose tissue. Lowers intake and raises energy expenditure #HHDCSymp    
    
    
    Almost time for the research award reception. Great keynote by Andrew Adams of Lily.    
    
    
    En route to COMO for #MizzouHomecoming vs South Carolina. Hope the streak continues.    
    
    
    @drisis OK but limit the sprog to white wine.    
    
    
    “@mbeisen: I've got to take Apis #ReplaceWordsWithBugs #ReplaceWordsWithInsects @RELenski @Graham_Coop”
Bonus for urine joke!    
    
    
    Time to start getting my game face on. It's my usual face, just during a game.    
    
    
    Nearing Lot X. Let the tailgate begin! #MizzouHomecoming    
    
    
    Game day. Life is good.    
    
    
    The sun came up this morning, even though my Tigers disappointed. I'm left with Chiefs on the radio right now.    
    
    
    TOUCHDOWN CHIEFS!!!!!    
    
    
    @kidney_boy This test result has national security implications and has been redacted by CIA operatives in your lab.    
    
    
    KC now 8-0. W00T!    
    
    
    “@JaniceSimon: The ad with the family trick or treating as Star Wars characters cracks me up every time. Love the Princess Leia baby.” +1    
    
    
    My teams gave me nailbiters, but my @Sephora manicure survived - http://bit.ly/19EuZ9t     
    
    
    Insect ID #sciox RT @JenLLane: @PHLane can u ask bug guy if this is a #termite ?? Anyone? pic.twitter.com/ECeMo47EPO    
    
    
    For next hour will be live tweeting the Hamm Lecture in Diabetes Research #HammLect given by Peter Bennett.    
    
    
    Inaugural Hamm Prize, like Nobel for diabetes research. #HammLect "American Indian Contribution to Understanding ... Type 2 Diabetes"    
    
    
    Peter Bennett's natural history studies of the Pima Tribe in Arizona have provided much of our understanding of onset of DM2. #HammLect    
    
    
    Remote feed to Chickasaw nation as well. #HammLect    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: Hot right now: letting your newborn keep his placenta for six days http://bit.ly/1gVyCOu ”    
    
    
    Video intro with jurors discussing importance of body of work. Linked obesity and DM2. #HammLect    
    
    
    Ends with discussion of next generation of researchers. I hope they can get funded. #HammLect    
    
    
    1960s: "Adult onst" DM seen as milder form that ran in families. #HammLect    
    
    
    Bennett trained in Rheumatology. Came to US to do arthritis survey among Pimas living in hot dry climate. #HammLect    
    
    
    Found rheumatoid in Pima despite climate, plus lots of DM. #HammLect    
    
    
    1965: Set up center for NIH in trailers on Gila reservation. Began health survey. #HammLect Found DM prevalence 8-fold > rest of world.    
    
    
    1976 demonstrated bad outcomes with diabetic pregnancy. #HammLect    
    
    
    Pima studies gave us international criteria for diagnosis of DM2. #HammLect    
    
    
    Association of DM and obesity documented 1981. #HammLect    
    
    
    Established hyperinsulinemia as risk factor for development of DM2. NOT INSULINOPENIA! #HammLect    
    
    
    Bennett gave Lilly Lecture at ADA in 1977. #zombies    
    
    
    1982: CRC in Indian Health Center allowed sophisticated metabolic studies such as clamps. #HammLect    
    
    
    Separate Pima population in Mexico with higher activity, less obesity and diabetes.  Heard this presented at ADA in 1992 #HammLect    
    
    
    Gestational DM offspring had 70% prevalence of DM by 30 years of age. #HammLect    
    
    
    Same mother, pre-DM offspring 30% risk! post-DM infant 70%. Points to intrauterine environment. #HammLect    
    
    
    Also documented increased DM risk with low and high birth weight. #HammLect    
    
    
    Also demonstrated protective effect of at least 2 months of exclusive breast feeding. #HammLect    
    
    
    Documented DM2 in adolescent, young adult Pimas. Separated DM 1 and 2 by mechanism rather than age of onset. #HammLect    
    
    
    Pathways to early onset DM2. Bennett 2004. Figure to pull. #HammLect    
    
    
    High risk of vascular complications especially CKD with early onset. #HammLect    
    
    
    Epidemiology of complications study with Kelly West, faculty member at OUHSC. #HammLect    
    
    
    Identified bp as risk factor for progression of retinopathy, nephropathy. #HammLect    
    
    
    All excess mortality occurred in patients with proteinuria. Now shown in other populations as well. #HammLect    
    
    
    2005: link of complications with periodontal disease. #HammLect    
    
    
    Albuminuria is clearly a bad outcome marker in DM2. #HammLect    
    
    
    Lifestyle interventions as successful in Pimas and other Native American populations as in general populations. #HammLect    
    
    
    Without Pima studies, we wouldn't know a whole lot of stuff about DM2. #HammLect    
    
    
    What an utterly amazing career. #HammLect    
    
    
    @SciTriGrrl @GertyZ @Doctor_PMS Zombie drop bear would be even more awesome.    
    
    
    “@StayPuft: Accepting mediocrity is the greatest villain the world has ever known.”    
    
    
    “@TheOnion: Enzyme Humbled To Have Played Part In Successful Biochemical Reaction http://onion.com/Hp9oZt ” SNORT    
    
    
    @GertyZ @bam294 Bacon as birth control? How does anyone get pregnant?    
    
    
    Well-Deserved Spoils to the Laureate http://wp.me/p2N5DR-QR     
    
    
    Peter H. Bennett + Pima Indians; what a story! #sciox http://scientopia.org/blogs/whizbang/2013/10/29/well-deserved-spoils-to-the-laureate/ …    
    
    
    Well-Deserved Spoils to the Laureate http://nblo.gs/QyljG     
    
    
    Getting laundry done so I can pack for 10 days of travel.    
    
    
    Peter H. Bennett: First Hamm Prize Laureate | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/19Q8Tk9     
    
    
    An Open Love Letter to Millennial Women http://wp.me/p42dSL-1O  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    Please RT:  RT @TKrattenmaker: Props to @JLCBamberger for bringing this to light. http://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2013/10/29/voter-id-laws-texas-womens-rights-column/3309505/ …    
    
    
    @JLCBamberger Voter repression is serious business.    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: Gawk at the opulence of the fanciest debutante ball ever http://bit.ly/1h0XMLN ” OMG Can't wait to blog about this.    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @DNLee5 Best way to remove glitter nail Polish is to soak in it.    
    
    
    “@StayPuft: What if for one day of the year, people weren't monsters? http://twitter.com/StayPuft/status/395633235222208512/photo/1pic.twitter.com/kISadF9PHc ” not this one    
    
    
    @DNLee5 Cat hair: accessory or condiment? Discuss. (If you live with cats you know it's both)    
    
    
    @DrugPitbull @drugmonkeyblog @bam294 @GertyZ Multiple layers of flavor when you tear them to bits?    
    
    
    Before Jenny McCarthy: Suzanne Somers’s 13 Craziest Quotes: Sex, Adam Lanza, and More  http://thebea.st/1gddfHe  via @thedailybeast    
    
    
    A Most Formal Thing http://wp.me/p2N5DR-QW     
    
    
    WARNING: Cannot be unseen... RT @Jezebel: Here's Matt Lauer dressed as a Baywatch babe http://bit.ly/19eJ7XB     
    
    
    @DNLee5 Like the new profile pic!    
    
    
    Charity silent auction in hospital lobby. I love shopping at work!    
    
    
    PLEASE BURY "REPLY ALL" SOMEWHERE IN A DEEP MENU IN EMAIL PROGRAMS SO IT'S HARD TO USE!!!
/end rant; sorry I yelled    
    
    
    “@StayPuft: Happy Halloween from Miley Cryus and Gozer! http://twitter.com/StayPuft/status/395940934631706624/photo/1pic.twitter.com/aqpm0ctt8b ” Ouch!    
    
    
    Saw girl dressed in Batman body suit with black tutu & cape and gold crown. I wish I had worn that today!    
    
    
    Tree Lobster would've rocked! RT @scicurious: ...happiest thing I've seen today. RT @SirPatStew Happy Halloween. pic.twitter.com/29kAlLVzgP    
    
    
    A Most Formal Thing http://nblo.gs/QCa1R     
    
    
    OMG. RT @daviddespain: Ha. Full of energy (or full of shit) via @ScienceBasedMed http://www.sciencebasedmedicine.org/full-of-energy/     
    
    
    “@bam294: The 7 Habits of Highly Effective Zombies http://fw.to/EElyNSK ”    
    
    
    @TSZuska @DrRubidium Cancer might be cured already!    
    
    
    @DNLee5 But if they don't, you get to eat chocolate. #SnickersIhope    
    
    
    @docfreeride At 11 yo went as Monster Crossing Highway Sign.    
    
    
    Damn it's early to be dressed and ready to roll. I hope @aamcannual appreciates it. Time to fly!    
    
    
    Back in Flight http://wp.me/p2N5DR-R5     
    
    
    #FF @j_storytime just because.    
    
    
    Back in Flight http://nblo.gs/QDD2w     
    
    
    “@moorehn: No matter what profession a woman is in, she's in the service profession. http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2013/nov/01/women-work-harder-favors-never-counted …”
MUST READ    
    
    
    Really #AAMC13 no wifi in ConventionCenter? Makes it difficult to share, especially from lower floors    
    
    
    “@Sci_Phile: Buried alive about 5 hours of air in a coffin...you'd go unconscious before suffocating! http://www.popsci.com/article/science/how-long-could-you-survive-coffin-if-you-were-buried-alive …” Reassuring    
    
    
    “@SarahKSilverman: My religion is science nature & love” +1    
    
    
    “@aamcannual: What are you looking forward to most during #aamc13 annual meeting?” Seeing colleagues while learning.    
    
    
    Awaiting Leadership Plenary at #aamc13 regarding change.    
    
    
    .@OUHSC Valerie Williams, Chair of AAMC Board of Directors addresses the plenary session. Boomer Sooner! #aamc13    
    
    
    Literally dance of change. Past is waltz. Tradition, lockstep. Not flexible. #aamc13    
    
    
    Twist: energy, individual. Line dance: structured. #aamc13    
    
    
    Tango: structured but adaptive. Room for individualism but requires teamwork. #AAMC13    
    
    
    In current healthcare, education and research environment, let's get ready to tango! #AAMC13    
    
    
    Hoping text of this talk will be available somewhere. Love dance metaphor. #AAMC13    
    
    
    And Valerie Williams leaves the stage while Shall We Dance plays. #AAMC13    
    
    
    Now President Kirch takes the stage. #AAMC13    
    
    
    Sheesh. Early am earthquakes in Oklahoma centered on our subdivision.    
    
    
    Plenary ends early. They aren't opening Exhibit hall for reception for 5 minutes. Gridlock! #AAMC13    
    
    
    @artologica Clear box    
    
    
    “@DrRubidium: Exactly. RT @SamuelLJackson: WTF?!!!” Useful in so many situations...    
    
    
    Reception has Makers Mark. Why yes, I will review more for Academic Medicine. #AAMC13    
    
    
    Breaking in new shoes and watching #Mizzou football vs. TN Vols. Go Tigers. pic.twitter.com/5zVhhC3DXG    
    
    
    @TellDrtell To go with wine dress with gold trim. Perfect and inexpensive on sale.    
    
    
    @bam294 Missouri Tigers! You didn’t know I hail from Missouri?    
    
    
    @bam294 Springfield. Dads a Mizzou alum but taught at (Southwest) Missouri State most of his career.    
    
    
    @GertyZ @bam294 Graduated fromBA/MD program in KC. Spent 7 years at SLU in first faculty position. So yes to all 3 cities in the state.    
    
    
    @GertyZ @bam294 SW corner on interstate 44. About 50 miles from Branson.    
    
    
    @GertyZ @bam294 That's the Branson demographic.    
    
    
    Keeping Score: What Really Counts http://wp.me/p2N5DR-R8     
    
    
    Keeping Score: What Really Counts | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/19odfjd     
    
    
    @bam294 @GertyZ Kirkwood. Where'd you go to high school?    
    
    
    @bam294 @GertyZ They were basketballand volleyball powerhouse while we were there. spouse grew up in north county. Went to McClure North.    
    
    
    @PacerProf Yup. That's why I retweeted. Then realized application to personal life.    
    
    
    @bam294  I can see that without ever meeting you IRL that I know of    
    
    
    Keeping Score: What Really Counts http://nblo.gs/QFUMg     
    
    
    @drugmonkeyblog Truman theTiger has won many mascot competitions. And for the most part game crowd is buzzed on Budweiser.    
    
    
    Night Tweeps. Time to rest up for meeting sessions and NFL football.    
    
    
    @bam294 @drugmonkeyblog And Kansas sucks.    
    
    
    @bug_girl As long as the sleek pink bunny isn't there as well.    
    
    
    I think people add and delete me on G+ just to make me think something is happening.    
    
    
    Thinking outside the box about non traditional scholarship is packed! #aamc13    
    
    
    Boyer's types of scholarship.    
    
    
    Standards for quality improvement reporting excellence SQUIRE
Available online. #aamc13    
    
    
    Brainstorming scholarship. #aamc13    
    
    
    Getting ready to hear from the hosts of Morning Joe. #aamc13    
    
    
    KC remains undefeated after victory at Buffalo. 9-0 folks!    
    
    
    @mistersugar Didn’t realize you were here either! See you somewhere tomorrow.    
    
    
    @ProfLikeSubst @doc_becca @LettersOfNote Must create autotext entry for my emails now.    
    
    
    @DoctorZen @biochembelle @doc_becca Rituals of liquor, please.    
    
    
    Goals: 3-5 year time frame. #AAMC13    
    
    
    Strategic initiatives and operation plans support goals that support vision. Strategic planning session #AAMC13    
    
    
    Metrics essential for ongoing planning and adjustments. #AAMC13    
    
    
    Balanced scorecard approach to planning with ongoing assessment and adjustment. #AAMC13    
    
    
    @mrhunsaker @DNLee5 @DrRubidium @David_Dobbs Stickers! If they come off can be easily replaced.    
    
    
    @DNLee5 Cattle prod?    
    
    
    @David_Dobbs @mrhunsaker @DNLee5 @DrRubidium Leading to detailed budgets.    
    
    
    @DNLee5 Well you are an OSU Cowboy. Pistols firing!    
    
    
    GWIMS connect session overflowing! Glad to see so much interest at #AAMC13    
    
    
    Personal branding aka graceful self promotion. #aamc13    
    
    
    Scholarship: Dissemination of learning    
    
    
    @TheLabMix @docfreeride Citizen medicine = homeopathy, herbalists, touch therapy, crystals...    
    
    
    @David_Dobbs @seelix @Sci_Phile @jtotheizzoe You almost need two moderators and a scribe to make “unconference” work well. #sciox    
    
    
    I don’t recall any health/medicine topics on 2014 schedule. #sciox    
    
    
    .@kTraphagen But no specific health/ biomedical conference yet... Plans? #sciox    
    
    
    Call for Academic Problems http://wp.me/p2N5DR-Ra     
    
    
    Call for Academic Problems http://nblo.gs/QK93L     
    
    
    Love this flick for these reasons: Elizabeth Taylor's Feisty, Feminist Turn in Giant http://pulse.me/s/vHq7v     
    
    
    Call for Academic Problems | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/19whGIY     
    
    
    Goodbye Philadelphia. Will miss my #aamc13 friends. Will not miss ads for NJ governor race.    
    
    
    Now it's time for Atlanta and #kidneywk13 Go TeamUrine!    
    
    
    @BrianSMcGowan Great day for the natives.    
    
    
    Every stall in this PHL airport restroom is accessible with changing table and sink. Way to go! pic.twitter.com/ZieTfWAFLG    
    
    
    “@JenLLane: @phlane did you see this? The Making of a GraterHead http://wp.me/pzqrI-yw ” Love them bear fans.    
    
    
    OH. "I have you're phone records. Stop lying. You've been calling her...calls listed loudly in airport. Bit sad I couldn't stay and watch.    
    
    
    @biochembelle @jgold85 @docfreeride Thing with filling as a sandwich. Taco, wrap etc.    
    
    
    @Sci_Phile @NerdyChristie My daughter spears them around Florida.    
    
    
    @rocza @para_sight @docfreeride @jgold85 @biochembelle I consider pasties, pie rogues, etc sandwiches.    
    
    
    Call for Academic Problems | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/19whGIY     
    
    
    I have landed in Atlanta for #kidneywk13   Let the festivities begin!    
    
    
    “@nephondemand: Many thx to AbbiVie & @ASNKidney 4 free wifi @ #kidneywk13   Will make tweeting & blogging easier” AMEN TO THAT    
    
    
    @doc_becca @artologica Frankly any cocktail looks good at the moment.    
    
    
    “@Jazinator: Randy Olson (@thebenshi) just followed me on Twitter. I feel almost important :-D.” Same here. Will that gete discount for cxn?    
    
    
    What should we call a group of nephrologists? I vote for Pee-ple #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Miss Rainicorn is a delicate flower. pic.twitter.com/xIKduQDXUY    
    
    
    @kiwiskiNZ I am the Pee Queen. Urine is golden.    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Also someone wants us to fix hyponatremia to levels I usually don't aim for... #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @thebenshi Have the app and read the book, but I want to do the workshop!    
    
    
    @thebenshi Cool. I'm in Oklahoma City. Not a place you're likely to be....    
    
    
    It's #kidneywk13 Pee-ple. Watch out Atlanta!    
    
    
    #kidneywk13 Awake, dressed and ready for urine. First stop: Presidential plenary.    
    
    
    @kidney_boy @edgarvlermamd @kdjhaveri @nephondemand So is there "evidence" to support aiming for 135, other than selling more drug?    
    
    
    @kidney_boy @edgarvlermamd @kdjhaveri @nephondemand Just wondering. Just because I haven't seen it doesn't exclude it's existence.    
    
    
    @kidney_boy But it's kidneys, ergo fascinating! More should follow for #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Pedi Nephro could be the model. Covers all aspects of kidney dysfunction. #kidneywk13 I hated adult nephro as med student for that reason    
    
    
    "@kidney_boy: why do limit our care to late stage disease #kidneyWk13"
Peds Nephrology doesn't, but still cannot attract trainees.    
    
    
    "@UKidney: Become our 1,000th Twitter follower and receive a free bag of normal saline! #kidneywk13" Wouldn't LR be superior?    
    
    
    IMO part of research funding problem is perception that transplant "cures" kidney disease. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @kidney_boy And all talking heads were white d00ds. Hmmmm #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Nothing will happen until NIH can fund top 20-25% of proposals again IMO. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    #kidneywk13 Wonder why there is 10 min lag between my twitter feed and that in the app?    
    
    
    @UKidney @kidney_boy  I'm betting he already has a stadium buddy taped to his leg... #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Kidney Week app has twitter feed based on hashtag. Lagging about 10 minutes so I'm in Twitter app.    
    
    
    @CSHLaboratory @GertyZ Especially if you're a supermodel type...    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Obviously. AAMCs app flowed better.    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: RT @cmaer #kidneywk13 RT @Jessica46961489: The Lori Hartwell Story http://bit.ly/1atz9hl ” Peds Nephrology: this is what we do    
    
    
    Next up: Anthony Atala on regenerative medicine. #kidneyWk13    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: Here is his wikipedia page: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anthony_Atala … #kidneywk13”    
    
    
    Regenerative medicine has been of interest more than 60 years. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Scaffold and vascularization required in addition to mass in vitro growth of. Organ cells. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: this is not just acting as a stent, it is real human tissue #kidneywk13”
Urethral reconstruction.    
    
    
    Similar approach used for vascular reconstruction #kidneywk13    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: tubular organs are one thing but solid organs are another level of complexity #kidneywk13” 
NSS    
    
    
    @kidney_boy I'm sorry, you still can't have one.    
    
    
    Now regenerative cells plus bladder bots could fix a whole lot of badness. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Here is link to bladder bots article http://phenomena.nationalgeographic.com/2013/11/06/cyborg-bladders-stop-incontinence-in-rats-after-spine-damage/ …
#kidneywk13    
    
    
    Note to #kidneywk13 overlords: this room is HOT. Can we move tomorrow's plenary to Superman's ice cave? Thx.    
    
    
    I've been dropped from wifi and can't sign back on. More bandwidth #kidneywk13 . At least ATT has coverage in this cavern.    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Of course, the commercial potential for the living functional penis-in-a-jar is mind-blowing... Yes, I went there. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: showing renal biopsies from the kidneys he built. Holy Shit! #kidneywk13”
Wow. That's all.    
    
    
    Yeah, a segment of kidney will keep you alive, but until we prevent progression, the more nephrons the better IMO. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Yeah, slide with 350 collaborators pretty useless...    
    
    
    Frankly organ regeneration has progressed waaaay farther  than I thought. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @eperlste @MTomasson Yup. I'm no longer in the pool. Sad to see this happen    
    
    
    @doc_becca @eperlste @Bashir9ist @hormiga @MTomasson    
    
    
    @doc_becca @eperlste @Bashir9ist @hormiga @MTomasson Wow. Ignore twitter for a couple of hours and a shitstorm ensues.    
    
    
    Don't know if she's online, but congrats to @Glfadkt on her new knee!    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: Rand Paul threatens to quit politics in what Maddow calls a "meltdown" http://bit.ly/1c28DhJ ”
Promise?    
    
    
    @drisis Will do my best: "I am Spartacus!"    
    
    
    @Glfadkt So I have heard.    
    
    
    “@dandouglas: what idiot called them creationists instead of primate change deniers”    
    
    
    “@Fascinatingpics: For anyone feeling a bit sad, here's a picture from a woman who makes Teddy Bears for her pet rat pic.twitter.com/AszVS70w99”    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: Women are "nothing but abortion machines," sputters Rush Limbaugh http://bit.ly/1dQ9ELK ” Not the worst thing he's said...    
    
    
    @collazor1 @eAJKD I prefer Pee-ple.    
    
    
    Next up I will be live tweeting about the tubulointerstitium in diabetes. From a really hot crowded room. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @sennoma @EugeneDayDSc @eperlste @MTomasson Parent    
    
    
    @KnittingNephron Tempting We are SRO in here.    
    
    
    Wishing I had a personal fan.    
    
    
    @sennoma @EugeneDayDSc @eperlste @MTomasson And the pay sucks most of the time.    
    
    
    PPAR gamma receptor mediates high glucose or AGE stimulated fibrosis in vitro. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Damn autocorrect wants to substitute vitriol for vitro    
    
    
    @GertyZ Lovely. To bad you aren't in Atlanta to blow cool air on me.    
    
    
    “@StayPuft: Happy No Shave November. http://twitter.com/StayPuft/status/398528831041978369/photo/1pic.twitter.com/6XuIrwObnv ” Attn: @misceLANE_ous    
    
    
    SLGT inhibition may have anti inflammatory effects in diabetic kidney. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    That session needs bigger room. Sitting by wall of fountain till I quit sweating. pic.twitter.com/ZA8vZrdDED    
    
    
    Dear god, how many generations of cephalosporins are we up to now?    
    
    
    @DNLee5 Does dark set up require glow stick collars? #rodentrave    
    
    
    Dear lord. #kidneywk13 wifi is overwhelmed and SLOW right now.    
    
    
    Hello Kiss! pic.twitter.com/PFWUpMsIWM    
    
    
    Optimizing care for homeless CKD patients. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Hells yes! I first reported it!    
    
    
    Homeless present many barriers: mental illness, substance abuse, mistrust of system. Prevalent CKD risk factors hard to treat. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: GFR not albuminuria is best index of diabetic nephropathy #kidneywk13”    
    
    
    Must move homeless into housing before other health issues can be effectively addressed. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @kidney_boy It's like finding gambling in a casino    
    
    
    @palmd What generation is yours? Mine has no issues    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: reduction in mortality good
reduction in morality is bad

Ts are important #kidneywk13”    
    
    
    @palmd mine is 3. First with retina display    
    
    
    In a perfect world I cod have chocolate martinis for breakfast as well as dessert.    
    
    
    “@AcademicsSay: I have a statement followed by two questions.”    
    
    
    Day 2 of official ASN scientific sessions. I could use a nap. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: KDIGO mobile app.

http://ajkdblog.org/2013/11/07/kidney-week-2013-kdigo-app-past-present-and-future/ …
@TDAungst”

Loading now    
    
    
    OMG! ASN napkin rings at the Kidney News luncheon! #kidneywk13 pic.twitter.com/2pkgycDWpx    
    
    
    Saw ads, booth for unfamiliar company. Still have NO CLUE what they sell or do. #badmarketing #kidneywk13    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: ...We suck at teaching palliative care and fellows feel uncomfortable with handling this. #kidneywk13” not big Peds issue    
    
    
    Communications training improves nephrology fellows' confidence in difficult patient discussions. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Q: What are effect duration for communication training? Still under study.  #kidneywk13    
    
    
    So glad to see rigorous educational research #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Wow. Like this IChoose Kidney app. Wonder if it has pediatric risks included? #kidneywk13    
    
    
    IChoose Kidney app is free for iPad in App Store. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @PHLane: Here's comparison for 10 year old girl. #kidneywk13 pic.twitter.com/hPC4fB5S1z    
    
    
    Against my better judgement, I'm hanging around for @kidney_boy to present his #nephmadness abstract. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @drisis I have gold studded d'Orsay pumps for tonight's fancy dinner. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @drisis Will send out photos by tweet in a bit :)    
    
    
    @drisis Nice. Love the green.    
    
    
    @drisis I know, I know...    
    
    
    VICTORY! The Spanx are on. #KidneyProm13    
    
    
    #KidneyProm13 footwear pic.twitter.com/pkXCJvcAga    
    
    
    And now the Omni has a chocolate martini or three for me. #KidneyProm13    
    
    
    View from Omni bar. pic.twitter.com/ZSWCbQ8ukc    
    
    
    It's chocolate and it's liquor. pic.twitter.com/Ok0bPRVMZo    
    
    
    Second round has arrived YUMMMMMM...    
    
    
    @kidney_boy You look a bit different IRL.    
    
    
    “@mutigersdotcom: The coin will flip here in two hours. #MIZZvsUK #Mizzou pic.twitter.com/qTSOFDzvp5” Tiger Time    
    
    
    “@ASNKidney: Study: Fluid Overload Ups CKD Progression Risk More than Diabetes http://asn.kdny.info/qEkz4  #kidneywk13” Cause or marker?    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Why are you accepting EVIDENCE rather than what MUST BE TRUE?    
    
    
    “@carlzimmer: Saxophone Lung. That is all. http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2013-11/acoa-inc103013.php …”    
    
    
    AMEN "@kidney_boy: If you are going to say “sorry for this busy slide” Stop and fix your damn slide!

Respect your audience

#KidneyWk13”    
    
    
    #kidneywk13 appears to be the event of the negative clinical trial...    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Why bother showing something you know damn well is meaningless as a visual?    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Drug class that has been cardio protective in, like, every other study ever??!!!!!!    
    
    
    “@UniteBlueOK: She's nothing if not consistent with her hatred and bigotry...

http://www.ok.gov/triton/modules/newsroom/newsroom_article.php?id=223&article_id=13011 …
#UniteBlue #OK”    
    
    
    2013. The year of the negative study. #KidneyWk13    
    
    
    Next year kidney wk in Philadelphia. Think we need social media sleepover @MutterMuseum    
    
    
    “@GeorgeTakei: Oh myyy. pic.twitter.com/99zuV9Fzgt” nothing to add.    
    
    
    In room 30 minutes ahead of session to make sure I got seat. Kidney Health Initiative (KHI) first year review. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    “@SciencePorn: Bathroom graffiti (if you're a student, do this graffiti at your school for the science) pic.twitter.com/WtJbk32pnz”    
    
    
    First up 
Patrick Archdeacon On the origins and operations of #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    #KHI coalition of society, FDA and industry to address kidneys. Pilot project on end points of lupus for tris. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Now presenting results of pilot project. Lupus nephritis end points. Lupus nephritis trials network + #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Focus on investigator initiated trials and long term follow up.  #LNTN #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Goals: evidence based end points for lupus nephritis and definitions of subtypes (refractory, severe) #KHI #LNTN #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Showing recent lupus trial end points; all over the place... #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Comparisons across trials impossible. #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Including FDA brings in other end points such as lupus flares, CKD etc. #kidneywk13 #KHI    
    
    
    Lit review for end points showed under representation of black, Hispanic patients in lupus trials. #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    "I know you can't read this"...   AACK! My eyes! Why are you showing me stuff like this? May as well be in comic sans...    
    
    
    Creatinine criteria often based on entry level, not pre-flare baseline. #kidneywk13 #KHI    
    
    
    Duration of response may warrant inclusion as response criteria in lupus. #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Partial renal response not good enough; same ESRD progression as non responders. #kidneywk13 #KHI    
    
    
    Process and projects ahead for #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    #KHI criteria: health need, involves multiple members, could improve health, clear deliverable. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    #KHI pic.twitter.com/PGPfArTX2i    
    
    
    After submission comes member comment period; standard online discussion board. #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Subcommittee review and score, followed by vote of full board. #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    After approval call for workgroup members. Including patients! #kidneywk13 #KHI    
    
    
    Currently 9 projects in comment/review process in #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Deliverables include standards, workshops, and white papers. #KHI #kidneykw13    
    
    
    Consensus on clinical trial end points is focus of a number of pending proposals in #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Wow. Much more pressed with #KHI now that I know what it does. #KidneyWk13    
    
    
    #KHI pic.twitter.com/M1Rg0JATc5    
    
    
    Love MU Football app for keeping me up on the game while I'm at #kidneywk13 doing professional stuff #MIZZvsUK    
    
    
    Some tweeple have also provided football updates while I'm hanging with my pee-ple. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Panel of #KHI stakeholders now beginning. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @KnittingNephron Planning evening near a screen, even though Mizzou will be done (and victorious).    
    
    
    #KHI has facilitated cross communication among members about work already in progress, use of existing data sets. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Another goal: transparent infrastructure to facilitate collaboration. #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Room perhaps half filled. Actually a bit chilly. #firstworldproblems #neverhappy    
    
    
    “@PureWow: Behold, your new virtual mailbox @OutboxMail: http://pwow.me/HFs8Un ”.                                WOW!    
    
    
    #KHI integrates multiple patient voices into medical innovation early in research process to help innovation go better. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Stuart Goldstein presenting issues on pediatric studies making them more challenging. #KHI #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Did you know <20% of drugs have had PK studies during continuous renal replacement therapy? #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @sethmnookin Did that in SF once. My husband hit a line drive off Lou Seal's ass that knocked him down. #goodtimes    
    
    
    @kidney_boy @KnittingNephron Tomorrow is day 10 on the road. Heading to the airport before it ends.    
    
    
    Hope I'm in the room for blood pressure control. If not, may just nap. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    The Four Horsemen May Charge Over the Earth—but Coca-Cola Will Remain - Tristan Donovan - The Atlantic http://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2013/11/the-four-horsemen-may-charge-over-the-earth-but-coca-cola-will-remain/281178/ …    
    
    
    @KnittingNephron Yup. Now I'm shivering. And never happy.    
    
    
    Proportion of hypertensive adults controlled with meds doubled over 20 years. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    28% of uncontrolled hypertensive patients on3+ meds. CKD, obesity frequent. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Pseudo resistant Htn: suboptimal adherence, measurement artifact (white coat). #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Resistant Htn has high rate of sleep apnea in part through volume redistribution. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Preferred combinations: ACE or ARB plus diuretic or calcium channel blocker. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Fourth bp drug should be spironolactone if tolerated. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Anti hypertensive therapy a major driver of costs of cardiovascular disease. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    Combination of ACEI and thiazide may be best first line treatment for primary hypertension. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @sethmnookin Uh, urine for bp? Tell me more    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: Low dose dopamine, this zombie will not die. ANZICS Lancet 2000 #kidneywk13” how many times must it fail?    
    
    
    Higher co-pays decrease adherence. SURPRISE! #kidneywk13    
    
    
    I found heaven in Atlanta. It's warm but the beer is cold. pic.twitter.com/gY81FZaBzH    
    
    
    “@palmd: Powerful.  Sad.  Biz as usual.  http://www.emilywillinghamphd.com/2013/11/no-not-back-to-our-regularly-scheduled.html?m=1 …” Shit.    
    
    
    I have a butt-load of steps to make goal today. Yes, I will be the crazy lady pacing in the hotel.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria Did you answer?    
    
    
    10,000 steps done. Packing (as much as possible) done. Football on.    
    
    
    @sethmnookin yeah...bring gloves.    
    
    
    OMG FUMBLE!    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: Any tweeters left standing?”
Nope. Sitting on my bed, getting ready to head home. Day 11 on the road    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Never figured you for bromance, but first Chertow, now this...    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: Pedicures and capillaries #kidneywk13 pic.twitter.com/Ep1oRnCH6h”
If I'd known about pedicures, I'd have gotten up for session!    
    
    
    “@AcademicsSay: The best writers do not wait for inspiration.” This one is for real.    
    
    
    Off to airport. Today ends at home. Goodbye Pee-ple. #kidneywk13    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Not really unless you're hunter-gatherer. Next question please.    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: NY prostitution case dismissed because pea coats http://bit.ly/19RZ5at ”. O. M. G.    
    
    
    On the ground in OKC, trapped in the back row of the plane.    
    
    
    Good to be home, but I miss the theory of nephrology while I'm in the trenches practicing it...    
    
    
    @LOLGOP Wow. It must be really difficult to get parking there...    
    
    
    @drisis St.  Louis isn't the south. Lived there, it's just not southern.    
    
    
    “@leahjosephson: KIDNAPPING --> MT @FundTexasWomen This really alarmed us this morning.  pic.twitter.com/jmxzmGNmyB”    
    
    
    @HopeJahren Autumny orange just arrived from @JulepMaven - yes, I belong to a polish club. pic.twitter.com/9BnYw2mKtO    
    
    
    “@StayPuft: Probably the greatest painting of all time. http://twitter.com/StayPuft/status/399990418009370624/photo/1pic.twitter.com/wf3RGUuPQA ” even Ghostbusters couldn't help Dallas last night :) :)    
    
    
    @palmd @doc_becca Camo for male patern baldness? Masquerading as chemo patient for sympathy?    
    
    
    Now That's What I Call a Sheep Dog! http://cheezburger.com/7892492032     
    
    
    “@anildash: ...many things...divide Gen X and Millennials, but ... Baby Boomers are the worst.” WATCH IT, WHIPPERSNAPPER!    
    
    
    @palmd If you choose a Bieber-assisted birth he may eat your baby?    
    
    
    DNA Test Stuns Man Who Wants All-White Town http://shar.es/8tMkA  via @newser
Not certain what markers they are using.    
    
    
    @docfreeride I learned macrame with Mandy by Barry Manilow.    
    
    
    Hyperkalemia at 0400 sucks. That is all.    
    
    
    @drisis So what's an appropriate quinceanero gift?    
    
    
    @kidney_boy More impressed with the real "8" I had earlier...    
    
    
    Interested in kidney issues? Follow @ASNAdvocacy on twitter for the latest society efforts.    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: 15-year-old girl gets Apple to look into its offensive definition of "gay" http://bit.ly/1e4k7TX ” uh, AWESOME    
    
    
    Watching Twister. Love it's portrayal of scientists and Oklahoma.    
    
    
    Watch out, Raleigh, I'm coming back! #sciox    
    
    
    @drisis I tried to buy those ruby house slippers! Hospital gift shop was out of my size :(    
    
    
    @RueLaLa Jewish or Christian/Common Era calendar?    
    
    
    Shoot for the Moon http://xkcd.com/1291/  pic.twitter.com/hVp1rCDHdP    
    
    
    #manicuremonday gets sparkle topcoat for the weekend. Volatile, Formula X, @Sephora over Brielle, @JulepMaven pumpkin spice color.    
    
    
    Spell checker just changed "complications" to "comic actions." Oh, Apple, I wish it were so...    
    
    
    OH: Nurse on phone, "I want to talk to someone who will be helpful and not call me sweetie." You go!    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @doc_becca @sgtscience7 @Doctor_PMS I'm not a boy, but I prefer a "ragged" right margin rather than justification.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @gertyz You neuroscientists have sessions on etiquette? Nephros just accept that we will piss each other off.    
    
    
    Just had lunch at BluBBQ and my hair smells smoky. Delicious, but smoky. http://okcbbq.com/     
    
    
    Why I Will Be There: #Scio14 http://wp.me/p2N5DR-Rd     
    
    
    #sciox at crossroads: http://wp.me/p2N5DR-Rd     
    
    
    @PatchyClamp @MyTChondria @GertyZ Absolutely intended! I'm a professional!    
    
    
    Just read #SFBatKid story. I WANT TO DO THIS!!!!    
    
    
    Being Batman is everyones' wish, deep-down! 
RT @thinkprogress: What San Francisco’s Bat Kid tells us about America http://thkpr.gs/1jadSi3     
    
    
    Nothing like a box from @RueLaLa with red reptile Stuart Weitzman pumps to make my cold better! pic.twitter.com/ctNoigXGca    
    
    
    “@biochembelle: ... same cell type from different anatomic compartments often behave differently. #lifeinscience” #whyscientistsdrink    
    
    
    “@GeorgeTakei: Rebel. pic.twitter.com/hKLYmbqypJ”    
    
    
    Why I Will Be There: #Scio14 http://nblo.gs/RaXNu     
    
    
    Why I Will Be There: #Scio14 | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/17z9YiM 
#sciox    
    
    
    Troubleshooting of Dad's computer last night, first Windows 8 experience. Should be Windows 666 since it's clearly the work of SATAN.    
    
    
    OK the wind sure is sweeping down the plain today. Please stop.    
    
    
    @bug_girl I hear butterflies are insufferable about their photogenic potential.    
    
    
    OMG! OMG! White fudge covered Oreos are in the stores! #hoarding    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: Nope, these foods need to GTFO out, too http://bit.ly/1f0grpt ”    
    
    
    “@businessgp: RT this if you have 'met'someone on #twitter that you now consider a friend. #research” yup    
    
    
    @HopeJahren @chambanalaura @KateClancy Want me to figure out a diagnostic code for dickhead?    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @drisis Part of the etiquette lesson.    
    
    
    @HopeJahren @chambanalaura @KateClancy DSM Just came out. ICD 10 has been delayed for medical E&M codes.    
    
    
    “@BranVanChemist: Georgia just wants it more.” Oops. Guess not.    
    
    
    @BranVanChemist Best game I've watched today. Other than seeing Texas squished    
    
    
    Just signed up on #Mizzou bowl tix list. W00T!    
    
    
    Do you know where your cephalopod is? @GoComics! #lio #GoComics http://www.gocomics.com/lio/2013/11/17     
    
    
    Misc Nursing Order:
Patient to watch SNF and cheer for undefeated KC.

Perhaps unethical?    
    
    
    @sennoma @jtotheizzoe @docfreeride We could all attend his session dressed as Madame Curie and beat the snot out of him.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @docfreeride @sennoma @jtotheizzoe That would mean developing rap skills. May have to find another outlet. Will explore.    
    
    
    Yeah...
RT @TheOnion: This Week Last Year: Intern Just Happens To Be Beautiful 22-Year-Old Woman http://onion.com/1fLAFAV     
    
    
    @SeeArrOh @docfreeride @jtotheizzoe @PBS not certain how it celebrated thanksgiving or intelligence either. Perhaps it was Opposite Day?    
    
    
    “@ASNKidney: A Scientific Journal For Kids, Edited By Kids http://asn.kdny.info/qSXpx ”cool!    
    
    
    @HopeJahren @AcademicsSay Hope not since most of them are quite...familiar...    
    
    
    GO KC!    
    
    
    Why I Will Be There: #Scio14 | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/17z9YiM 
#sciox    
    
    
    @loveofscience @PsiWavefunction @AndreaKuszewski @sennoma    Curie look-alikes beating him up was meant to be joke. Unlike calls to fire him    
    
    
    @loveofscience @PsiWavefunction @AndreaKuszewski @sennoma I think of how many times a week I tell someone I have to kill them...    
    
    
    The Real Problem with Marie Curie http://wp.me/p2N5DR-Rg     
    
    
    Grad school rec letter mad libs http://scientopia.org/blogs/neuropolarbear/2013/11/17/grad-school-rec-letter-mad-libs/ …    
    
    
    @DNLee5 Rat's nails could use a good soak.    
    
    
    Seeing patients on #ManicureMonday pic.twitter.com/rQPdvlk4Kq    
    
    
    @biochembelle Without Hazelnuts you can't have Nuttella.    
    
    
    @theJAYFK @DrRubidium This  post will get mileage 4EVAH!    
    
    
    @kidney_boy It's another NephroZombie like "renal-dose dopamine." Something that will not die.    
    
    
    @HopeJahren Better than seeing a finger... ;)    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @AmasianV Sharpening the wood chipper blades?    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @drisis Ends with grant me the wisdom to hide the bodies of those I have to kill.    
    
    
    @biochembelle @MyTChondria "She can castrate many mammals."    
    
    
    KD at the line. #WeAreThunder pic.twitter.com/vqQWq4fFAd    
    
    
    #WeAreThunder pic.twitter.com/FcYII3Fmp0    
    
    
    @MyTChondria Has @AmasianV learned to line dance for you yet?    
    
    
    Reggie Jackson sinks 2 from the free throw line with 15 seconds in regulation. #WeAreThunder pic.twitter.com/KYbIodSjce    
    
    
    @AmasianV @MyTChondria Chaps then.    
    
    
    “@KMBTweets: WHAT SHE SAID!!! “@NkechiThinks: PATS LOSE!!! I AM SOOO HAPPY!”” Doesn't quite make up for KC loss, but it does warm my heart.    
    
    
    The Real Problem with Marie Curie | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/17G4vqz     
    
    
    A sexist joke or a joke about sexism? http://wp.me/p2C0bz-6v  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    @drisis Just sing and dance. They'll never forget it. You'll never have to do it again...    
    
    
    .@GeorgeTakei Apparently I'm Vulcan. Would explain a lot. pic.twitter.com/M5Rn9Ao5ba    
    
    
    We must choose FREEDOM!!!
RT @Jezebel: Pediatricians say Flamin' Hot Cheetos are burning your kid's insides http://bit.ly/18l43w7     
    
    
    @KateClancy @ihearttheroad @ShipLives I would favor a "shit-storm." Far messier than a show.    
    
    
    @ihearttheroad @KateClancy @ShipLives Aren't we getting splatterd by it anyway? Also appreciate "utter fuckstorm" from @edyong209    
    
    
    @ihearttheroad @KateClancy @ShipLives @edyong209 I feel like I've been splattered in the course of these events.    
    
    
    The Real Problem with Marie Curie http://nblo.gs/RftNx     
    
    
    Does anyone ever think inside the box anymore? Why do we even have the damn box?    
    
    
    @seelix @KateClancy @ihearttheroad @ShipLives @edyong209 Sounds so organized though. Circus more chaotic. Shit Circus?    
    
    
    @doc_becca Like next year at sfn?    
    
    
    @ShipLives @seelix @KateClancy @ihearttheroad @edyong209 
Let's face it, if this recent activity were a movie, Jackass would be the genre.    
    
    
    Rob Ford looks like Goldfinger. Call James Bond.    
    
    
    Scientist Hijacks Seventeen Magazine’s #ManicureMonday http://www.slate.com/blogs/future_tense/2013/11/20/manicuremonday_seventeen_magazine_s_hashtag_hijacked_by_scientists.html … via @slate    
    
    
    @scicurious @bobbleheads Rosalind Franklin. Not a share of the Nobel, but a bobblehead would be nice!    
    
    
    .@biochembelle Often the background section of a grant gets turned into a review article. Also they get lots of citations.    
    
    
    Word keeps crashing today. Obviously, the digital deities do not want me to work any longer. I should go shopping.    
    
    
    @scicurious @sennoma @bobbleheads Damn you. I now crave my own custom bobble head. As Wonder Woman...    
    
    
    @scicurious @sennoma @bobbleheads I saw that body in the selection as well.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria You've earned a drink. Let happy hour commence!    
    
    
    @artologica @tehpet @wehaveno Damn right. Know a bunch of folks who will want one.    
    
    
    Watching Judgement at Nuremburg. Never realized how hot Maximilian Schell was.    
    
    
    @NerdyChristie @HopeJahren lovely fish and nails!    
    
    
    SCIENCE BLOGGER BOBBLEHEADS!!!!!    
    
    
    Son working university IT support calls. He could be an Apple Genius some day, or even part of Geek Squad! #SoProud    
    
    
    Mass extinction? No; clearly dinosaurs were saved in the First Rap(tor)ture!
Sorry; I had to go there... pic.twitter.com/43WWwwoq8k    
    
    
    Could Companies Really Block the Contraception Mandate by Claiming Personhood? http://www.slate.com/articles/news_and_politics/jurisprudence/2013/11/corporations_are_claiming_personhood_to_block_obamacare_s_contraception.html … via @slate    
    
    
    @doc_becca No, it's the dude who carries your mugs and suggests the appropriate one for the situation/beverage.    
    
    
    Auditory Double Takes http://wp.me/p2N5DR-Rm     
    
    
    Douchebag. RT @aetiology: Awesome. Lactation consultant admittedly LIES about being vax'd http://bit.ly/17P31u2     
    
    
    Auditory Double Takes http://nblo.gs/RkFfM     
    
    
    Busy day complicated by freezing rain. Now we have the fireplace going. Almost worth the weather...    
    
    
    @GertyZ I remember those. Even the alcohol can't numb the memory.    
    
    
    Kick off in 15 minutes. M. I. Z. #MIZZvsMISS    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @HopeJahren I would go with white, but Malbec can never be completely wrong.    
    
    
    “@MyTChondria: Miley Cyrus just turned 21?! But I'm already so fucking sick of her...” Let's get an amen to that!    
    
    
    @GertyZ Just wait till they wake you at 3am for breakfast. #beentheredonethat #justsaidhellno    
    
    
    @GertyZ Good luck with that.    
    
    
    Hey Tigers: pick six would be great now.    
    
    
    Missouri 10-1. FUCK YEAH! Go tigers!    
    
    
    “@GeorgeTakei: Tell me you feel like I do about this. pic.twitter.com/MMYKHUDccn”    
    
    
    @TomLevenson @jaredbkeller "Want a drink". "Where is bathroom?"  "Want to buy it".    
    
    
    @TomLevenson @jaredbkeller in travels I figured out where is bathroom is most important. 1/2    
    
    
    @TomLevenson @jaredbkeller Others solved with object of desire in 1 hand, platinum card in other.    
    
    
    @TomLevenson yeah..I don't go places without aMariott Rewards program...    
    
    
    “@venetianblonde: Being tweeted everywhere by so many folk: Tom Baker's best memory #DoctorWho. Sheer class. pic.twitter.com/xjSb37QyRi”    
    
    
    @TomLevenson That's a sacrifice some of us make.    
    
    
    @GertyZ Might be easier to move than clean.    
    
    
    Someone thinks I should stay home and do this all day: pic.twitter.com/E0vRXjT5zO    
    
    
    The look that says, "You betray me." pic.twitter.com/BMRpcDaWiQ    
    
    
    “@kidney_boy: Maybe GFR and proteinuria for stage and add progression as a Grade. Use stage and grade like the oncologists.”    
    
    
    Seriously, OK, Why would anyone cancel anything because of this weather?    
    
    
    Holiday decor spotted today: Large Nutcracker Soldier and the word "Peace" - was irony intentional, or just a bonus?    
    
    
    They seem pretty white-bread-and-mayo. Even my spouse eats cordial cherries...    
    
    
    @BranVanChemist I believe it's Hammacher Schlemmer that has one for 200K.    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: The Myers-Briggs guide to wine http://bit.ly/1euPvvk ” WTF is Nebbiolo?    
    
    
    “@WhySharksMatter: Please make "Shark bunnies" happen @SyFymovies http://m.9gag.com/gag/aKzmqXQ ” Holy Grail for killer rabbits, please    
    
    
    @BranVanChemist We are capable of spending it, but the only car I would spend that much on is a Tesla Batmobile.    
    
    
    “@DNLee5: Safety first! Chain mail gloves for handling my African Giant Pouched Rats #DNLeeLab pic.twitter.com/qqhx7K2rOA” #ManicureMonday    
    
    
    Just wrapped a Christmas Gift. I'm officially ahead of schedule this year! #1sttimeforeverything    
    
    
    The cactus cannot lie. It must be Christmas. pic.twitter.com/O0nudSv4mt    
    
    
    Cranberry bars done. Turkey thawing. Brine chilling. Liquor purchased. Thanksgiving, I am ready!    
    
    
    The turkey is in the brine. 

Sounds like some sort of secret agent code.    
    
    
    Morning battle with a 48" outdoor wreath. Round 1 went to the wreath; round 2 to me, albeit at the expense of my nailpolish.    
    
    
    @drugmonkeyblog How else do you get to Cat III?    
    
    
    @drugmonkeyblog I hear PEDS can help that happen...    
    
    
    An Open Thank You http://wp.me/p2N5DR-Ru     
    
    
    @MyTChondria Wild Turkey is much easier to prepare...    
    
    
    Well, he must have some useful skill-

Who knew? Speaker Boehner brags about his turkey brine http://usat.ly/1cvP2qG  via @usatoday    
    
    
    Love dude reading replies:

MT @m_m_campbell: Women in STEM, YouTube, & sexism: http://youtu.be/yRNt7ZLY0Kc  #SciComm #STEM #womeninscience    
    
    
    @drisis Recipe please.    
    
    
    Looks like the last clinic patient of the day is the only one planning to show. They called to ask if they could come late.    
    
    
    I'm the only one left in the office area. I've wrapped 8 gifts and completed all my med records. At least I have Twitter to keep me awake.    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @drisis RECIPE DAGNABIT!!!!!    
    
    
    An Open Thank You http://nblo.gs/RvrcQ     
    
    
    3 hours till @misceLANE_ous arrives home for food and football.    
    
    
    The youngin has arrived. Let the festivities begin!    
    
    
    @MyTChondria Axe makes you seem alive?    
    
    
    @drisis So dental dams and flavored condoms?    
    
    
    Happy Black Friday Eve http://wp.me/p2N5DR-Rp     
    
    
    Happy Black Friday Eve http://nblo.gs/RwhdC     
    
    
    @MyTChondria perhaps Axe is the definition of stench.    
    
    
    “@doc_becca: Yes, we have #thanksgivukkah napkins. http://Instagram.com/p/hQ9lhZlyXH/ ”
Shouldn't that bird be wearing a yarmulke?    
    
    
    The bird is in the oven. I repeat, the bird is in the oven.    
    
    
    Offspring seems satisfied with the meal. @misceLANE_ous pic.twitter.com/heRX1EaUVO    
    
    
    Quick nap done. Hot tub getting warm.    
    
    
    We got the hottub working. pic.twitter.com/UyjfWhrOUt    
    
    
    And the bourbon comes out post tubbing. I'm thankful now.    
    
    
    Just made a movie of my twitter: https://www.vizify.com/pascale-lane/twitter-video?s=twitter&u=125062&f=1033&t=share_follow_me_video … Let me know what you think, then make your own. #FollowMe #Vizify    
    
    
    Hey @drisis, @bam294, @GertyZ, you've got a starring role in my video: https://www.vizify.com/pascale-lane/twitter-video?s=twitter&u=125062&f=1033&t=share_follow_me_friends … #FollowMe #Vizify    
    
    
    @GertyZ @drisis @bam294 You are the tweeple I've had the most interactions with, so your avatars are in this twitter highlights video.    
    
    
    “@BranVanChemist: You know what gets me about Black Friday mobs? I've been in mosh pits that had nicer people than that.”    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @GertyZ @drisis  Yeah, @bam294 won't be in the sequel.    
    
    
    @seelix And now in a teeny weeny bikini!    
    
    
    @drisis @DrRubidium sort of like sparkling chain mail.  Fierce!    
    
    
    @drisis @StrangeSource @DrRubidium I hope you're running to the liquor store.    
    
    
    On the road for COMO. #blackout #Mizzou    
    
    
    About 2 hours from tailgate. Got my#blackout manicure on. #Mizzou pic.twitter.com/uvZMOm6eM6    
    
    
    Holy Shit! What a game and #mizzou prevails. Bring on Auburn and SEC Championship!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Writing patient info post whole rocking a soft rose gold #ManicureMonday in honor of #Mizzou the SEC East champions!    
    
    
    @RefrigeratorCat I thought you were the holiday edition.    
    
    
    One more clinic patient then I hit the gym. Yeah, it's been a while.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria So any takers on the Gosling earrings?    
    
    
    10 companies paid Happtique for health app certification http://shar.es/DZZnl  via @MobiHealthNews    
    
    
    Great post: Is The National Cancer Institute Telling Me to Remove My Breasts?: http://daviddobbs.net/smoothpebbles/is-the-national-cancer-institute-telling-me-to-remove-my-breasts/ …    
    
    
    Hit the gym (it hit back) and stayed under my daily calorie count. Feeling pretty damn good but sore right now!    
    
    
    “@DrRubidium: Map of the Lake Monsters of America http://laughingsquid.com/map-of-the-lake-monsters-of-america/ … via @LaughingSquid"
OK has a giant killer octopus???    
    
    
    Words I live by... http://www.gocomics.com/shoe/2013/12/03#.Up3k5pAvsPI.twitter …    
    
    
    I swear I was nowhere near Kentucky...
Reward offered in theft of rare Kentucky bourbon http://usat.ly/1bbdDmj  via @usatoday    
    
    
    Nutcracker Hell http://wp.me/p3tZWd-1m     
    
    
    Nutcracker Hell | Pascale Hammond Lane, MD - http://bit.ly/1cjfW6P     
    
    
    Nutcracker musings http://wp.me/p2N5DR-Ry     
    
    
    @JenLLane Didn't know you would want to be immortalized in a dress that looks like a purple lace curtain. Shall I scan it as well?    
    
    
    Nutcracker musings http://nblo.gs/RG4IZ     
    
    
    @MyTChondria You're disappointed, aren't you? Amazon doesn't sell THAT kind of nutcracker.    
    
    
    Truthy... RT @TheOnion: "somehow made its way through life with no male genitalia" http://onion.com/1gCmdLZ  pic.twitter.com/pFJ38IKRPQ    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @_ColinS_ 
I bet with enough food coloring I could make your urine purple, at least in the jar...    
    
    
    Oklahomans already fretting about winter storm forecast in 2-3 days. Guess there's no time like the present for anxiety.    
    
    
    @kidney_boy @kendonaldson @DrAFDouglas Saw 96 in brain damaged toddler once in ICU.    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @guardian Nor High Society, Funny Face, 7 brides for 7 brothers, Chicago, Mary Poppins...    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @guardian ignores Disney animated flicks: Little Mermaid, Beauty and the Beast, Aladdin, Lion King...I'd take all over Oliver    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @guardian Those cartoons sure have done well on stage.    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Whole thing was incredibly sad. :(    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @guardian Flick didn't translate well. Saw it done live once. Loved it.    
    
    
    @woollymammoth @kidney_boy Well, said toddler "lived" if you want to call it that. Brain damage at birth, reset osmostat in 120s. #cheating    
    
    
    @woollymammoth @kidney_boy Saw high 170s in kid with NDI fluid restricted after closed head trauma. He also "lived."    
    
    
    STOP! Read this NOW: The selfish gene is a great meme. Too bad it’s so wrong http://aeon.co/magazine/nature-and-cosmos/why-its-time-to-lay-the-selfish-gene-to-rest/ … via @aeonmag    
    
    
    “@AcademicsSay: p = .0551”
Usually followed by "Fuuuuuuuuuuckkkkkkkk!"    
    
    
    @drisis Is this his uncle's influence?    
    
    
    @DrRubidium I didn't think Dicaprio was hot enough to leave the lifeboat.    
    
    
    @drisis ALWAYS frisk them for scissors first.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Nutcracker Hell | Pascale Hammond Lane, MD - http://bit.ly/1cjfW6P     
    
    
    @exlarson I hope they're double stuff or white fudge dipped!    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @drugmonkeyblog Cut a dissertation into 140 character tweets then storify it.    
    
    
    Did anyone collect/storify the posts about 23&Me and the FDA? #sciox    
    
    
    It's not babies:

RT @WIAReport: What Drives Women Out of STEM Fields? http://bit.ly/1jlDYBw     
    
    
    Selfie is the word of the year...

RT @BorowitzReport: Shocking photos: http://nyr.kr/1g6EFyM     
    
    
    @kidney_boy Do you know of a formula to incorporate residual renal function into Kt/v for hemodialysis patients?    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Especially if I could just do research without worrying about grants!    
    
    
    MAHVELOUS! Exactly what I needed. Thanks.

RT @mikethemadbiol: .@PHLane @David_Dobbs did http://daviddobbs.net/smoothpebbles/i-got-your-23andme-v-fda-links-right-here/ …    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @drisis They taste good, and my diabetic relatives appreciate every bit of carb lowering I can offer.    
    
    
    I know several tweeple who might want this shirt...
http://mediacdn.snorgcontent.com/media/catalog/product/h/o/homeiswherepantsgrass_fullpic.png …    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @drisis Cherry-flavored frosting is a clear abomination.    
    
    
    Just watched my first "Miss Fisher's Murder Mysteries." Hope Netflix keeps streaming it long enough for me to watch all the episodes!    
    
    
    OKC now in the 4-6" of snow path instead of 2-4". Getting all sorts of closure/caution notices. Right now it's 45 and no precipitation.    
    
    
    @doc_becca @dillonkondor Except there is extra cookie; still prefer creme to cookie ratio of double stufs    
    
    
    @fivethirtyeight Schadeneditor?    
    
    
    @kidney_boy I'm taking on 23&me. What do I do next?    
    
    
    I'm so tired of my nose running. When will this cold go away?    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Cool.    
    
    
    @drugmonkeyblog Couldn't go any worse tha wars on cancer and drugs...    
    
    
    @drugmonkeyblog Verily.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Basics: What is an OS? http://scientopia.org/blogs/goodmath/2013/12/05/basics-what-is-an-os/ …

Great simple explanation!    
    
    
    At least it's now snowing to justify some of the panic in OKC.    
    
    
    @scicurious Murine porn FTW ?    
    
    
    “@AAUW: #progress RT @womensmediacntr: Twitter names female board member with media experience http://buff.ly/1eU0u0E  at @mercnews” W00T    
    
    
    @MyTChondria Oooo. Good recall. I'd almost forgotten that a group of women was a binder!    
    
    
    4" of snow have shut down the entire state of Oklahoma; Minnesotans with 4WD could invade and occupy right now.    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @GertyZ Not an injury that was ever discussed in doctor school. Along with "wandering womb" ...    
    
    
    @kidney_boy It's what we have. Whole concept of maintenance needs revisiting. Lots of assumptions.    
    
    
    @kidney_boy Prettymuch.    
    
    
    @TheFuckingCat I'm pretty certain we celebrate our cat's birth every day.    
    
    
    BEDLAM! Oh, Mizzou BB in half an hour against UCLA. And that #SEC championship game at 3. Yup, it's big screen time...    
    
    
    @David_Dobbs @docfreeride @SFriedScientist Now don't mussel into the conversation.    
    
    
    @SFriedScientist @David_Dobbs @docfreeride I will leave you all to "slug" it out.    
    
    
    “@DrYapyapi: OMG! Eathquake! Plus snow on the ground!” Biggest one yet!    
    
    
    These damn epicenters too close to home.    
    
    
    Since earthquake we can't find the cat. Dottie, what did you do???    
    
    
    THATS A WINNER! #Mizzou tigers hand UCLA their first hoops loss of the year. Now can football team grab victory as well ?    
    
    
    @BranVanChemist Happy Holidays!    
    
    
    Now for the Big Game. Go #Mizzou    
    
    
    Much more comfortable than TAMU game... In MU Slanket in our sorts media room with wall sized screen. pic.twitter.com/qWBEcldzF3    
    
    
    “@Englishscope24: SEC Championship!!!!.. Lets Roll!!. #Missourah”    
    
    
    MIZZOU BALL! #SECATL    
    
    
    Mizzou on the boardwith3. #SECATL    
    
    
    Damn. Ok #Mizzou let's get 7 and go back ahead. #SECATL    
    
    
    MIZZOU TOUCHDOWN! FUCK YES!!! #SECATL #Mizzou    
    
    
    “@Englishscope24: Is there anyway to still hear the crowd but mute the CBS broadcast?" QFT Tired of hearing "but Auburn."    
    
    
    Ok #Mizzou D, shut them down this series! #SECATL    
    
    
    @wilbanks IfI were playing that drinking game, I'd be too smashed to tweet right now. Of course, that might not be all bad.    
    
    
    Come on #Mizzou we have brought out the bourbon!    
    
    
    Beautiful #Mizzou move that damn ball! I <3 football!    
    
    
    @Englishscope24 Can we figure out a way to get rid of these announcers? They just SUCK.    
    
    
    @AstroKatie @DrRubidium Mine was steel gray. First slide was brine shrimp.    
    
    
    @AstroKatie @DrRubidium 3 slides came with scope. Only one I remember is brine shrimp.    
    
    
    @averyholton @MyTChondria @FlyFrontier @FrontierCare Gee @united was more helpful than that on my travels.    
    
    
    @tehpet @AstroKatie @DrRubidium I looked at every bodily fluid I could think of...at 9 years old.    
    
    
    @bam294 YOU LIVE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Peter Higgs Says He Would Never Make It in Science Today http://gizmodo.com/peter-higgs-says-he-would-never-make-it-in-science-toda-1479041093 …    
    
    
    Wearing my blog hoody. Woman in store just recognized it. Reads it. I feel almost famous!    
    
    
    @docfreeride Admire the drive, but I feel your pain.    
    
    
    “@mutigersdotcom: .@mizzoufootball is headed to the @ATTCottonBowl vs. @CowboyFB on Jan. 3, 2014! #Mizzou” I will be there! Go Tigers!    
    
    
    Thursday's lecture is updated and the handout posted online. And now it's clinic time.    
    
    
    Frightening implications.

RT @szvan: Bode Miller Changed His Mind And Hurt Pregnant Women's Rights Along With It: http://www.rolereboot.org/culture-and-politics/details/2013-12-bode-miller-changed-his-mind-and-your-rights-along-w …    
    
    
    [My Best Tweets] 
 (14RT, 7Fav) http://twitter.com/PHLane/status/400728190433230848 …
 (8RT, 6Fav) http://twitter.com/PHLane/status/398156150648340480 …
 (8RT, 4Fav) http://twitter.com/PHLane/status/396629334473338880 …    
    
    
    [My Twt Collage] @kidney_boy @drisis @DrRubidium @docfreeride @DNLee5 @bam294 @GertyZ via http://anatweet.com/collage  pic.twitter.com/aMQjSDr3jT    
    
    
    Not Ready for Prime Time: 23andMe http://wp.me/p2N5DR-RE     
    
    
    Attn: @kidney_boy

RT @PHLane: Not Ready for Prime Time: 23andMe http://wp.me/p2N5DR-RE     
    
    
    Not Ready for Prime Time: 23andMe http://nblo.gs/RQzDR     
    
    
    @DNLee5 Confession: Unless discussing race, I do not think of you as black; you're Danielle, a multifaceted woman.    
    
    
    @DNLee5 @BlackPhysicists Once I know someone, I think of them as an individual, as "Danielle" in your case. 1/n    
    
    
    @DNLee5 @BlackPhysicists If someone asked me to describe you, I would say you were black. But if someone mentions @DNLee5 I don't think 2/n    
    
    
    @DNLee5 @BlackPhysicists "Oh @DNLee5 is that black girl/woman." 3/3    
    
    
    @DNLee5 I still feel last weeks planks.    
    
    
    @drisis You haven't been traveling enough lately.    
    
    
    Not Ready for Prime Time: 23andMe | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/18xCc8H     
    
    
    @ChristosArgyrop @kidney_boy I disliked adult nephro as student because it was general IM on dialysis patients and AKIs who died.    
    
    
    @ChristosArgyrop @kidney_boy Yeah, you can't die without dialysis.    
    
    
    @ProfLikeSubst @drisis @MTomasson Thinking about a superhero suit    
    
    
    Just watched Jurassic Park. Still sad they didn't end it like the book, with pack of compys eating guy alive.    
    
    
    @HopeJahren Penis trumps boob.    
    
    
    “@seelix: YOU GUYS, I GET TO HAVE SURGERY AND NOT BANKRUPT ANYONE. I consider this a win. #thanksobama”
Glory be!,,    
    
    
    I love this design at Snorg tees:
http://mediacdn.snorgcontent.com/media/catalog/product/b/a/batandrobinkids_fullpic.jpg …    
    
    
    At grand rounds on competency based medical education. Will be amazing or a snoozefest- nothing in between with this topic.    
    
    
    Forecast for temps in 50s by weekend. Should take care of remaining snow, ice, and snirt.    
    
    
    @SCWIST @docfreeride Interesting that title focuses on dating, not problems as professional, even though latter is discussed at length.    
    
    
    “@dasheddogma: @sandraholla actually, something I could support would be a petition to bring Trader Joe's to OKC @Lady_Brains” +1    
    
    
    @drisis "Plugging the fuck out of" sounds dirty. Like, 50 shades dirty.  @scicurious @drugmonkeyblog    
    
    
    Need gifts for your girly friends? Consider Boob Glue et al.
http://www.retailmenot.com/blog/weird-products-for-women.html?utm_medium=blogger_network&ch=spons&utm_source=taboola&utm_content=4021066&utm_campaign=syndication …    
    
    
    @HopeJahren @JahrenLab So your lab is staffed by cats???    
    
    
    OH DEAR.
MT @waitwait: ...found the music we'll be playing over every single segment of the show from here on out:
https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/smooth-sax-tribute-to-outkast/id207916184 …    
    
    
    @artologica Can't @tehpet lap up the spill?    
    
    
    Thoughts on Medical Care http://wp.me/p2N5DR-RL     
    
    
    Thoughts on Medical Care http://nblo.gs/RYkJf     
    
    
    @HopeJahren WHERE IS PHOTO???
#TeamButt    
    
    
    @HopeJahren At least I have SOMETHING to look forward to...    
    
    
    @TomLevenson While a school shooting is happening in Colorado.    
    
    
    “@mutigersdotcom: Exactly three weeks from this moment ... we'll kick off the @ATTCottonBowl! #Mizzou” I will be there. Go Tigers!    
    
    
    Heading home from party. Spouse stops at hardware store. I may not fit in right now. pic.twitter.com/rCGELyMCjy    
    
    
    @HopeJahren @MyTChondria No, that's butter ;)    
    
    
    What's up with your Hoosiers @Glfadkt ? Losing to Notre Dame???    
    
    
    FOOTBALL HULK
on @GoComics! #inthebleachers #GoComics http://www.gocomics.com/inthebleachers/2013/12/15 …    
    
    
    @HopeJahren @JahrenLab #teambutt all the way! #TheAmaizingRace    
    
    
    THx to internet, I can wait till Sunday am and watch only the funny parts of SNL. Really, what more can you ask from the web?    
    
    
    RIP Peter O'toole, star of Lawrence of Arabia, one of my faves. That and My Favorite Year.    
    
    
    @drisis Of course. Quit wasting bandwidth and buy it.    
    
    
    THUNDER UP!    
    
    
    “@StayPuft: The Dallas Cowboys are experiencing the biggest meltdown since 20 tons of marshmallow exploded over New York.”
I loved it.    
    
    
    @kidney_boy NSAIDS being used more.    
    
    
    Thoughts on Medical Care | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/18H0XiZ     
    
    
    Happiness is remission in any disease.

RT @kidney_boy: Happiness is remission in membranous nephropathy pic.twitter.com/Sb2EwGWsLR    
    
    
    I seriously doubt that Jane is partying right now.
RT @littlepinkbook: Jane Austen is celebrating her birthday today! http://ow.ly/i/2Iw9i     
    
    
    “@carlzimmer: MT @edyong209: another possible winner for your scientific acronym competition. http://dawgpaws.sourceforge.net/  CZ: Woof!”    
    
    
    @HopeJahren I think mine adds a little something extra... pic.twitter.com/ZBU4Yk5f8v    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: Chorus line of kittens perform Christmas carols http://bit.ly/18S3CcD ”
And that wins the internet today.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria I just hope not in the veterinary sense...    
    
    
    The gym tried to kill me yesterday.    
    
    
    My people know me well! I get to start EVERY day of 2014 with shoe porn...
Preview of Jan 1: pic.twitter.com/X39hqp1eOS    
    
    
    Why didn't I think of this?
RT @Jezebel: Foot numbing spray eliminates the pain of horribly fabulous high heels http://bit.ly/1bQygn6     
    
    
    @SciTriGrrl @ProfLikeSubst @Jezebel Article discusses the mind-numbing option...    
    
    
    A Holiday Tradition http://wp.me/p2N5DR-RO     
    
    
    A Holiday Tradition http://nblo.gs/S8a7b     
    
    
    “@pash22: Could virgin births be real? http://www.today.com/health/just-time-christmas-could-virgin-births-be-real-2D11762820 … via @todayshowhealth” Yeah, saw a bunch of these on OB as med student.    
    
    
    “@Jesus_M_Christ: If one more person prays for a set of Beats by Dre...”    
    
    
    “@davidkroll: today's @AdamsLisa http://lisabadams.com/2013/12/18/end-clinical-trial-gdc-0032-faslodex-ct-results/ … " But don't read with guilt if you study other disorders. Those pts suffer as well.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @AmerZahr I always wondered why people of the Middle East were considered Caucasian. I guess that's so Jesus could be white.    
    
    
    @docfreeride What about hip flask? #liquor    
    
    
    @MyTChondria I want Doritos concession.    
    
    
    “@rockportbasset: For every re-tweet, @MegynKelly Will Receive This Image of Black Santa II pic.twitter.com/Z649wNK7Yl”    
    
    
    @MyTChondria We knew you were "sick". Want me to sing Soft Kitty?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @PsycGrrrl @MyTChondria @Dr24hours I'd like a man in chaps for every convo today about dimes...    
    
    
    QFT"@drgitlin: On days like today, when I found my job rather frustrating, it helps to remember my days in retail to put things in context.”    
    
    
    @kidney_boy you're a 10-year old at heart.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @MGhydro @drugmonkeyblog Reminds me of mom.,,    
    
    
    @DNLee5 @erincandy Spanx. Bike. Shorts.    
    
    
    Study: Routine costs, not law, lead to most new increases in health insurance premiums. http://usat.ly/1bRqdTu  via @usatoday    
    
    
    “@StayPuft: RT if you don't care what color Santa is. 

(White, black, red, green, blue or marshmallow).”    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @GertyZ @FedEx Perhaps hanging up is the service.    
    
    
    @drskyskull @MyTChondria Dentistry.    
    
    
    Go to @Heifer now. For $20 you can give a family a flock of ducklings and start a real duck dynasty.    
    
    
        
    
    
    2 hours till tip-off. #thunderup    
    
    
    Ignore the nonsense. $20 for a real duck dynasty @Heifer http://bit.ly/1cDHHUm     
    
    
    A lot of Bull at this end of the court. pic.twitter.com/qusZuKjPNp    
    
    
    @BranVanChemist Cheapest solution to a big oops.    
    
    
    A Holiday Tradition | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/1cB7AnP     
    
    
    @TheFuckingCat For $20 you can help a family establish a real duck dynasty @Heifer    
    
    
    End of the Year Meme http://wp.me/p2N5DR-RT     
    
    
    End of the Year Meme http://nblo.gs/Sa7cS     
    
    
    Tired of #DuckDynasty? Start a real duck dynasty for only $20 - http://bit.ly/1c552BP     
    
    
    @DukeLemurCenter At least we know what the lemur says. Not like those damn foxes ;)    
    
    
    @docfreeride @DrRubidium @gdnwhiteboard @GuardianUS Pretty certain the 3rd Santa Clause installment wins this one. That's the Jack Frost?    
    
    
    @DrRubidium @docfreeride @gdnwhiteboard @GuardianUS While You Were Sleeping starts around Xmas,  but not Xmas movie.    
    
    
    @biochembelle Those are often the guys that are missing a hand...    
    
    
    MT @drugmonkeyblog: most important thing Schekman is saying...stop using journal status rather than paper content  #GlamourMags #Amen    
    
    
    Last patient of 2013 on deck.    
    
    
    @BranVanChemist  We don't deserve nice things if we can't keep @DNLee5 happy :(    
    
    
    “@artologica: Grooooaaaan, kidney card says "this too shall pass" https://www.etsy.com/listing/122509724/kidney-stones-greeting-card … @PHLane” Could hand these out in clinic!    
    
    
    Bourbon and bridal porn on TLC. Life. Is. Good.    
    
    
    “@UnvirtuousAbbey: Best #nativity scene ever? pic.twitter.com/Y3rJVJM4A1” YES    
    
    
    @BbyHeadedDEater Makers Mark. Yummy smokey caramel flavor.mmmm    
    
    
    “@drisis: My fortune as I hang out with La Maestra & KWoww and prep for travel tomorrow pic.twitter.com/MbiHmO1HiL” Great. Fucking. Advice.    
    
    
    @drisis It does self destruct...(cue Mission Impossible theme).    
    
    
    @BbyHeadedDEater Yes to the Dress and Four Weddings tonight.    
    
    
    @drisis No. Read about it. Didn't seem necessary for my wealth, health, or happiness.    
    
    
    @drisis Or advisable. As far as I know my offspring don't either, but then they're 21 and 26, above average Snap age.    
    
    
    @drisis Will look forward to your assessment.    
    
    
    @BbyHeadedDEater Atlanta version has grown on me. Those southerners are so SASSY!    
    
    
    What I Am Reading: Autism Spectrum Edition http://wp.me/p2N5DR-RV     
    
    
        
    
    
    Yup OK has ice. Anyone dreaming of a clear shiny Christmas? pic.twitter.com/8SYuarQzdn    
    
    
    @MyTChondria Ones where they can't play real defense. I was the mom yelling "god gave you elbows. Use them!" While others stared in horror.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria we all needed drinks by the end. Reasons varied.    
    
    
    “@HHageberg: Christmas tree at the UiT library. pic.twitter.com/LGI8GPEtGm”
How cool!    
    
    
    @mbeisen So. Much. Wrong.    
    
    
    “@TheFuckingCat: Humans invented prejudice, so fuck yeah, cats are better. And that's just one reason out of like a purrzillion.” QFT    
    
    
    Time for the bragging rights game, #MIZZOU vs Illinois. GO TIGERS!    
    
    
    Close losses really sting. Consoling myself with Elf.    
    
    
    @drisis Sounds like something I would have said    
    
    
    @biochembelle Yeah...pursuing your own dreams gets punished.    
    
    
    What I Am Reading: Autism Spectrum Edition | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/1c86wLS     
    
    
        
    
    
    @GertyZ @drisis Or just get a lot drunk!    
    
    
    Hubby home. Having cocktails. Holiday    
    
    
    “@MyTChondria: RT if you like oxygen!” I enjoy breathing chemicals all the time.    
    
    
    What I Am Reading: Autism Spectrum Edition | Whizbang - http://bit.ly/1c86wLS     
    
    
    Oatmeal scotchies with double chips about half done.    
    
    
    How Y’all, Youse and You Guys Talk: See my dialect map and make your own. http://nyti.ms/1crRbYg  
Pretty close to Springfield, MO    
    
    
    Hubby exhibiting perfectionist tendencies about holiday. This cannot end well.    
    
    
    With @misceLane_ous and @JenLLane pic.twitter.com/adErdatqzA    
    
    
    Daughter made 6 minute connection in ATL yesterday. Bag did not. Time for emergency shopping to acquire church clothes. Thx @AirTran    
    
    
    @drisis Sanity.    
    
    
    Celebrate! http://wp.me/p2N5DR-RR     
    
    
    Celebrate! http://nblo.gs/Shpwt     
    
    
    Full contact card game in progress.    
    
    
    Ribbon. Bags. Best holiday ever. pic.twitter.com/IO9pvB1vBV    
    
    
    Daughter opens new ornament, Larry the Lionfish. pic.twitter.com/cqih212aIH    
    
    
    Someone stuffed the stockings! pic.twitter.com/wDGxquUgNS    
    
    
        
    
    
    “@Protohedgehog: Worth using on any festive comment. I love this! pic.twitter.com/CiQ7E84uJx” QFT    
    
    
    @MyTChondria Myspace is now for internet time outs?    
    
    
    @MyTChondria Didn't realize it still existed. Guess everything's forever online.    
    
    
    To @artologica & other artists- @JenLLane wants a piece of shark art. Contact her for details.    
    
    
    Xmas tradition: red sauce with Italian sausage and mostaciolli. pic.twitter.com/5b645lOJwF    
    
    
    Loving the new wine glass! Less mess when the inevitable tip occurs! pic.twitter.com/4uiN4rxZcF    
    
    
    @HopeJahren Yes. Yes, it has.    
    
    
    @MyTChondria @biochembelle My moms would involve a bar.    
    
    
    Newton. Jesus. @MyTChondria What a day to be born.    
    
    
    @drisis @palmd Ketchup on a PASTIE?    
    
    
    Merry Catmas on @GoComics!  http://www.gocomics.com/klibans-cats/2013/12/26 …    
    
    
    @artologica @WhySharksMatter @SFriedScience My sole aches for you. #fishpun    
    
    
    Lionfish shirt. Gift from @JenLLane pic.twitter.com/6QZjbcUzqW    
    
    
    Found art for @MyTChondria pic.twitter.com/RcVAfs1Cco    
    
    
    “@AliceDreger: Necessity is the mother of new cocktail recipes.”
True for damn sure.    
    
    
    @DrRubidium Thought same thing during previews.    
    
    
    @artologica Yes, please. And scarves. Need to accessorize.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Big screen system fixed. Watching sports. Heaven.    
    
    
    Thunder on the big screen. Bourbon poured. Life is good.    
    
    
    @drugmonkeyblog Projector etc coming lose and out of focus, probably due to recent earthquakes. Remounted, reinforced, refocused.    
    
    
    Full contact card game. Me and @MisceLane_ous vs my parents.    
    
    
    After almost a week of sloth and gluttony I made it to the gym. Feeling sore but kind of buzzed.    
    
    
    @docfreeride Great idea, although I usually manage more than one each day.    
    
    
    @docfreeride That could be the definition of sloth.    
    
    
    Hot tubbing after the workout. Yumm. pic.twitter.com/TNvCdSCrEi    
    
    
    @drisis At least you're figuring this out early. Just be sure you get what you deserve if or when you move (google those salaries now)    
    
    
    @StayPuft Why not Slimer???    
    
    
    @zunguzungu @docfreeride Watching Vertigo I will wager.    
    
    
    Attn: @drugmonkeyblog -Pet injures former mayor in Ariz., kills husband http://usat.ly/Keq5YM  via @USATODAY    
    
    
    What a cool image! http://apod.nasa.gov/apod/image/1312/mandelbox077_leys_960.jpg …    
    
    
    The holidays officially end when you realize you have a DEAD TREE in your home. We are there, now, folks.    
    
    
    Cannot believe how thin I was on my wedding day, 30 years ago. pic.twitter.com/yazEPE4Idv    
    
    
    @TomLevenson If you want this one, just come help me de-decorate.    
    
    
    @docfreeride Thanks!    
    
    
    @docfreeride My son wanted to buy gifts with $ he earned, but had to wait till he got paid to shop. We will have "Timmas" tomorrow night.    
    
    
    “@Jezebel: TMZ has moved on to reporting dog rape http://bit.ly/1ciai0I ” Pretty certain the bitch wanted it. #punintended    
    
    
    Re last tweet: Yes, in bad taste, probably offensive, but just couldn't resist.    
    
    
    Awaiting 2014 with Dad's brandy ices (aka Alexanders) and sports on a big screen TV.    
    
    
    THUNDER UPPPPPPPPPPP    
    
    
    Less than an hour left in 2013. Not a great year, but not the worst. Still, good riddance.    
    
    
    “@EmilyKnits: 2014, I have high hopes for you. Please don't suck.” Agreed. +1    
    
    
    On writing a book on @GoComics! #toomuchcoffeeman #GoComics http://www.gocomics.com/toomuchcoffeeman/2013/12/30 …    
    
    
    “@DrJudyStone: RT @io9: knitted #anatomy dissections are amazing -- great science art! http://on.io9.com/7dIXpTy  #knitting”
Attn @DrRubidium    
    
    
    Why is de-decorating the tree so exhausting? I can barely stay upright on the sofa for the Rose Bowl. #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    @joshwitten @docfreeride But I really like it when the bears eat him.    
    
    
    Shoe porn of the day. pic.twitter.com/U3hdU2PMJF    
    
    
    Holidays Done; Football Continues http://wp.me/p2N5DR-RY     
    
    
    Holidays Done; Football Continues http://nblo.gs/Svudp     
    
    
        
    
    
    “@MyTChondria: NIH Application Success Rates Decline in 2013 http://shar.es/9thgN  #Sigh” #Duh    
    
    
    YUCK!!!!! pic.twitter.com/SvXUNK7nAO    
    
    
    @TomLevenson So much wrong.    
    
    
    @drisis What color is that?    
    
    
    Just installed the emoji keyboard. Watch out, twitter verse!
😜    
    
    
    Who are these OU players and where have they been the rest of the season?    
    
    
    @artologica @sciencecomedian @leafwarbler @docfreeride @beatricebiology Really good rate at this hotel in Raleigh with nice lobby bar.    
    
    
    @leafwarbler @artologica @sciencecomedian @docfreeride @beatricebiology Sheraton for sciox    
    
    
    Tickets: check. Map:  check. Mani: check.
Time to head to @ATTCottonBowl @mutigersdotcom🐯🐯🐯🏈🏈🏈pic.twitter.com/8HlqKd9TO3    
    
    
    “@The_Antlers: Bill Self went to OSU, so fuck those guys”    
    
    
    We are inTexas! #Mizzou #ATTCottonBowl    
    
    
    We. Are. Here. #mizzou @ATTCottonbowl pic.twitter.com/ez3voBkbrB    
    
    
    Cotton Bowl pre-game party!!! pic.twitter.com/6TkHgiDHVw    
    
    
    Live band rocking the west end zone crowd. pic.twitter.com/M2P8O2CnRd    
    
    
    Seated for Cotton Bowl. pic.twitter.com/CbrBVQiIUz    
    
    
    #Cottonbowl #Mizzou pic.twitter.com/u3pNNuvwy2    
    
    
    #Cottonbowl #Mizzou pic.twitter.com/1WzTixQIuU    
    
    
    #Cottonbowl pic.twitter.com/5a0cw7qBfy    
    
    
    10 minutes till kick off. #Cottonbowl pic.twitter.com/SPbM2HkLqV    
    
    
    Let's win it for # #Mizzou and #SEC #Cottonbowl pic.twitter.com/TvpTU36vLv    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Missouri Tigers are #CottonBowl champs! pic.twitter.com/16IADLIPG4    
    
    
    “@ElizSimins: "How do you want your hobbit?" pic.twitter.com/uE0a4wrXnE”    
    
    
    @sethmnookin True wild type rats? Or the ones in plastic condos?    
    
    
    Today's goal: get voice rested. Small price to pay for #Mizzou #CottonBowl victory.    
    
    
    @seelix Count me in.    
    
    
    “@SciOfMotherhood: What a deal! Men for only $12. pic.twitter.com/WcO8VdYlVH” Way overpriced given necessary training and maintenance.    
    
    
    “@marynmck: awesome. thank you @SirPatStew 
RT @drflanders: Listen to this old white man. pic.twitter.com/L0zeS8Am0h”
Love    
    
    
    “@MarkCC: Amazing: my flight isn't cancelled. San Francisco here I come!”
Forgot "yet."    
    
    
    Finishing the holiday break by #ThunderUp against the Celtics. Go OKC!    
    
    
    Weekend shoe porn. I would kill for these Manolos. pic.twitter.com/I3Jd0PFABl    
    
    
    @Dr_Bik Something to look forward to every day!    
    
    
    @Dr_Bik this calendar could be a very expensive gift.    
    
    
    @doc_becca Completely in love with these.    
    
    
    